How far is it?
- We're almost there
l'm a greater hurry than you are.
This is social-service, for you
Cholera has spread in the city.
l must see you off...
and take the first train to Jalgaon
Where is Kamla Devi's house?
- Over there
Kamla Devi!
Kamla Devi...
Sit down, children
She must've gone out to fetch water.
She'll be back soon
l can't wait, children.
l must leave now
Here you are...
give it to the lady
l've written everything in it.
And don't start crying
Oh yes... do eat something
Who are you children?
''The children's father
was deported last week''
''Their mother died of cholera.
So l leave them with you''
Your aunt will be back soon
Will you have something to eat?
Well? Whose children are you feeding?
They're now your children, Kamla.
- My children?
Look what a sweet child he is
He'll be of great help to you
when he grows up
Treat them like your own, okay?
- Why not?
They're my brother-in-law's kids.
- Well said, Kamla
How come?
- The children are here. That's why
Oh no. l'm happy because his
father has been deported!
l'm happy because his mother
has died of cholera!
What l regret is that she didn't
take them away with herself
Kamla, what are you saying?
- Right too
When my husband died, their father
threw me out to suffer in penury
And they come to my doorstep today?
This is good indeed
No, Kamla. Don't say that
You must've seen
a nice soul's face today
lt was your face l saw this morning.
- But l'm not a bad man
Oh yes, you're an angel!
A bloody bootlegger!
And you're the goddess
who sells her modesty?
Kamla, don't make me lose my temper.
- Go away!
God has been kind to you, Kamla.
He has given you two little children
Be a good woman and make
good human beings out of them
Not like the folks you and l are.
- They'll see what l make out of them!
Won't you go away?
- l'm going
Listen, Kamla.
Don't you hit them
Get lost, l say!
Don't hit them, he says!
Come on!
Stand here and beg
lf you don't make four annas
by this evening, you've had it
Stretch your palms...
Give me a penny, sir
Give me a penny, sir...
give me a penny
''You'll be robbed,
if you don't give me a penny''
''You'll go to the police station
if a theft takes place...''
''and file a report''
''Why must you do all that?
Just give us a penny''
''Don't give us a penny,
and your grandma will die''
''lf your grandma dies,
you'll do the rites...''
''and feed the Brahmins''
''Why must you do all that?
Just give us a penny''
Brothers and sisters!
We have no support
My brother was born blind.
My father died in the hospital
And my mother, in the war in Burma.
- No
Father died in battle,
mother died in hospital...
Oh yes. Mother died in the hospital
and father died fighting in Burma
My brother is blind.
l was going to blinded too
We have no one. You'll lose
nothing, if you help us
May God bless your children.
- Please give us a penny
Sir... please give me a penny
God will bless you, sir
Give me a penny, sir.
Belu! Come here!
What?
Belu, there's Raj Kapoor
ls that Raj Kapoor?
They're all Raj Kapoors nowadays
l've seen many of their kind
So you can see?
Hello, Chitku.
- Hello indeed
Begging, already?
For pennies?
Shoeshine man.
- Yes, sir
Give me a penny, sir.
God will bless you
l've had nothing to eat, sir.
l'm hungry, sir
Get lost!
Why push a poor boy ?
Give me a penny, and l'll pray for you
2 annas, sir. For my hard work.
And see the first-class polish
''Do not spit''
How much do you have?
- And you?
Berries, 2 for one paisa
Brother, may l buy berries?
- Berries!
l collect money for the polish
and you want to buy berries!
Fresh berries, 2 for one paise
Want to eat berries?
C'mon. Don't cry!
Hey berry-seller!
- Do you have the money?
First let's have a deal.
- You get 2 for a paisa
Let's have 3 for a paise.
- 2, l said. Or go going
Wait... Belu, he won't give us
3 for a paisa
Ask him for four, in that case.
- Don't waste my time
Wait here
Eat one, Bhola.
- You eat. l'm not a kid anymore
Don't put on airs. Eat one.
- You eat it
You'll have to eat one
Ticket-checker! Run!
You still haven't eaten it?
Silly girl! lt won't double
We have seven annas
and two paisas today
Let's hide an anna under the tree
and give the rest to aunt
l don't like to beg, Belu
''Give me a penny, sir...
Give me a penny, my Lord''
And everybody curses us
When we have a rupee and 8 annas...
- What then?
l'll buy two tins of polish,
black and brown, and a brush too
l'll make a rupee every day.
See how much Chitku makes?
What if aunt gets to know?
- She'll give us a thrashing
That she does every day.
But how will she get to know?
Know what? Let's keep the stuff
with John Chacha (uncle)
Check how much we have, Belu
- One paise, two paise, four annas...
We've got to give aunt 4 annas, Belu.
- Oh yes, l know
Four annas, five annas...
- Here's 2 annas more
You've messed up my count!
You count it, l can't
Bhola! Here comes Chitku!
Hide the money
Beggars everywhere
Hello, Chitku.
- Hello
Back from begging...?
''Give me a penny, my lord...?''
Can't you find other work?
- ln a few days, Chitku...
we're going to stop begging.
We're going to buy polish and a brush
You will see then.
- See what?
Young pissers!
You talk about polishing shoes
lt's a big ask, my boy.
lt took me a year to master it
Big deal! Bhola will learn it too.
- Bhola will? As if it were a joke
lt has been our family business...
And he'll learn it in a day?
Where will you get the money
to buy the polish and the brush?
We've collected the money.
- No, we haven't...
Shut up!
What were you doing by the tree?
- Nothing. We were only playing
Playing eh?
Say hello to Kamla on my behalf.
Kamla...! What a beauty
Bhola, l told you not
to talk to him
John Chacha said he's not a nice boy.
- We won't talk to him again
Let's go John Chacha. Come on
Has it sprung something?
- l sure can see a strand or two
Didn't l tell you?
That's the real oil
Get started again
John Chacha!
Run out of polish, John Chacha?
- Polish?
What a shine he has given you!
- Not polish... it's a massage
But your hair, John Chacha...
- l've sprung some, son
Look, Belu. He had two strands
yesterday. They've disappeared today
You use the polish on your head.
And your face sprouts the hair?
Shut up!
- Use bittergourd, uncle
You'll have long hair.
- Get out!
You're bothering me! Go home!
Your aunt will straighten you out!
Watch it... aunt might see us
l'll go in first, Bhola.
- No, l'll go in first
Wait... l'm going in first.
Hold the puppy
So you're here, little witch?
Where's the rascal?
Didn't l tell you to return with
the provisions before noon?
Where are the rations?
Your mother is dead but she
left me with this nuisance!
l accepted you for
the sake of the world,...
or l'd have thrown you in
the gutters. Where are the rations?
The ration card...?
Your father has been deported.
And the two of you have fun here?
Why don't you just die instead?
What do you mean to me anyway?
The ration card!
- What?
What did you say?
- Nothing.
l've just been mumbling
something, aunt
What have you been whispering?
- l'll play a cripple...
and beg henceforth, aunt.
- So?
l said, l'm a cripple,
l'm hungry, l'm blind...
my parents are dead, give me
a penny, my hand is broken...
Did they give you the money?
- No, aunt
You threw away the money?
- No...
that fat man sneezed
and threw all the stuff out
Threw it out? What rubbish!
- No, aunt. He threw me out
No wonder! Worthless children!
You can't even beg properly
Come, l'll teach you
l asked you to play blind
and beat your stomach
''Mister! May you be happy.
Two paisas... give me two paisas''
''Mister, give me two paisa.
l'll buy myself some bread''
''l've been blind all day...
- Blind all day? What rubbish!
No, aunt... l've been blind
for ages... since l was born!
Remember the song l taught you?
Spread your frock
''l spread my frock for alms...
blessings for you, l have''
Remember now? Do that from tomorrow
And wash the utensils
Where do you think you're going?
And what are we waiting for?
Go and stand in the queue.
- Let me take it first
l must go home, or aunt will beat me.
- Get back there
Get back, boy... back!
How much time for
the rations to be given?
Talk softly. Why're you yelling?
- You talk loudly too
You look like a pick-pocket to me
He asks how many pockets are picked!
Hurry up. Can't you see?
lt's beginning to rain
Come, boy. You're my first customer.
Let me see your palm
How much money are you carrying?
- l've got just 2 paise...
So l'll tell you the future
for 2 paisas worth. Out with it
But sir...
- Out with it son
l've been waiting all day
and nobody turned up
Out with it.
- All right. l'll give it to you
Boy, you aren't going
to study anymore
l haven't studied anything
in the past either
Your two paisas worth is over.
- How about my work...?
Get lost! You want to
know everything at 2 paisa?
Please, sir... Tell me
something about my work
You'll wear out shoes all your life!
- ls that true?
l'm going to polish shoes?
l've had my money's worth!
My business is taking off
Belu, l'm going to be a big man!
That's what the soothsayer says!
See what...
Belu, you got a lot of
beating today, didn't you?
You take a beating for my sake.
But l'll take it henceforth
Belu, see what l've got for you.
Eat it up
You're back, you worthless boy!
Bloody rascal!
You're sitting here!
- Let go, aunt
l've been starving and
you went disappearing!
Rascal! Scoundrel!
Where is the money?
Don't hit him, aunt!
- Get lost, girl
You just want to run away from work!
So starve to death
You're Satan.
- You're Satan
You sell hooch! Thug!
Don't you have a heart? You beat
the children so mercilessly?
Why don't you take the children
away with you, if you have a heart?
l'd be rid of them!
- l don't have enough to feed them
And the sort of work l do,
l could go to jail any day
l wish, every innocent child
like them...
l've heard that crap from
paupers already
lf you don't manage to bring
10 annas by tomorrow, just you see
Every child like them...
Bhola, you took a
lot of beating today?
Yes, Chacha.
- Never mind
Belu, get up child. Come to me.
Are you hungry?
Yes, Chacha. l feel hungry
every day
That's the worst disease
our nation suffers from
Come on... get up
Bravo! You must face every
hardship in life with a smile
Here. Eat
Won't you eat some, Chacha?
- l've already eaten, my dear
You eat. Go on
Bhola, just give up begging
God has given you two strong hands
Since you're a small boy,
do something small for now
These very hands will accomplish
something big in the future
There's nothing in the world
that your hands cannot do
Bhola, starve to death,
if you have to...
but never ever beg again.
Don't ever beg, my son
And aunt says we must
beg every day
John Chacha says we must
never ever beg
What are we to do, Bhola?
- Chacha is right, Belu
Chacha, l take an oath.
l won't beg from tomorrow
Well said, my son.
This is just what l expected from you
l've grown old, you see
l'd surely have helped you.
But you know my ways
You don't know, Bhola.
l've spent a lifetime...
in begging, crime and
other terrible things
l'm a bad man.
But you must be a good man, son
You must become a big man
After l'm dead,
my soul will live in you
ln you lies my new life.
My new life
Have you eaten, children?
- Oh yes, Chacha. Lots too
Chacha, it's such a dark night.
- Yes, Chacha. lt's a black night
Yes children. lt sure is
a dark night
See those slums, Bhola?
- Yes, l do
ln them live thousands of poor people,
leading lives like animals...
spending another black night of
their lives on dark nights
But this dark night will end
some day. lt surely will, some day
l have a strong feeling
And it'll be a new dawn
And the rising sun will
spread gold in their lives
You will grow up. Be well read,
dance and be a happy man
God provides for everyone...
He provides for everyone, my children
''After night...''
''comes day''
''This is how a lifetime is spent''
''After night...''
''This long difficult journey
through life...''
''makes one man laugh,
and another man cry''
''With every step he takes...''
''man moves so far ahead''
''With every straw...''
''is the nest built''
''After night...''
''There is darkness,
there is light...''
''every flower that blossoms,
has to wither away''
''From a playful childhood
you step into youth...''
''and old age makes you suffer''
''The wheel of fortune moves on...''
''and that is what
we call destiny''
''After night,
comes the day''
''This is how a lifetime is spent''
''After night...''
''John Chacha...
you're such a nice man''
''Every child loves you''
''Tell us what to do,
so we don't get a bad name''
''What is destiny, Chacha?''
''Why is one man a beggar and
why is another man rich?''
''Why don't we have any work?''
''To beg for a living
is no good''
''March ahead...''
''you're one in a million.
March ahead, my boy''
''March ahead''
''Never look back,
never be afraid...''
''the earth and the skies
belong to you... just march ahead''
''Reach for the stars''
''You're one in a million, my boy.
Just march on''
''After night...''
''will come a new day''
''After the dark night...''
''will come a new dawn''
Chitku! My money!
John Chacha...
Give me back my money, Chitku!
- Let go!
John Chacha! My money!
What money?
John Chacha!
Chitku's taking away my money!
l'm going to thrash you!
Let go!
Return my money, Chitku...
Else, l'll tell John Chacha
Give me back my money
Let go! Let go, l say!
Chitku! Give me back my money!
Belu, Chitku has taken our money!
How will l buy the polish?
Belu! Our money!
l came to take look at our money
this morning, and saw Chitku around
l quickly took out the money.
l did the right thing, didn't l?
Yes, Belu. You're a very sweet girl.
Come, let's go and buy the polish
But we're still 2 annas short
May l say something, Bhola?
Let's beg for the last time today
No...
- One last time?
Okay, Belu. Let's go
Give us a penny, sir...
We're starving
Go away
Get lost
Go away... you're begging?
What's the boy saying?
- He seems to be dumb
Give the poor boy an anna.
- An anna?
Yes, an anna. Give it to him
Bhola! Come here!
What is it, Belu?
- We have only a rupee and 4 annas
But we had one rupee and 8 annas.
Let me see
Two and two is four...
- You can't count. Give that to me
Eight annas and four annas
make twelve annas
And another five make it 15 annas.
- 12 and 5 is not 15!
Can you even count properly?
- As if you can!
Two and two and two makes it six.
We're still two annas short
What are we going to do?
- l have an idea, Bhola
First class!
- What idea?
How about going to John Chacha
and getting 2 annas out of him?
That miser will give you 2 annas?
- Let's go, come on
Who is it?
- What are you up to, Chacha?
You won't understand.
- Go ahead and tell us, Chacha
l said you won't understand.
- Still, Chacha...
Oh yes. Still
l'm making a unique oil
- Unique?
Yes, it has fennel-water,
powdered clove...
special grass and other things.
l've got to remember that
Special grass. No other grass will do.
Also goose berry crush...
l'll mix all that and boil it in fat.
And the moment l massage my head...
Your hair will disappear!
- Disappear?
Absolutely. Your hair will vanish.
- How come?
You've forgotten a very
important ingredient
What?
- The same old thing
What old thing?
- The seed of the berry
The seed of the berry?
- Yes, uncle
That's what old Kamla uses.
And what long hair she has!
Chacha, for just a rupee's seeds,
you get such long hair
So long for 8 annas
and so much for 4 annas worth
And just this much for 2 annas.
How long do you want your hair?
Will my hair grow with berry seed?
- Of course. We'll go and get it
Give us the money
Money? Oh no!
Berry seed will make my hair grow?
- Yes, Chacha
All right. Wait here
Here you are...
- ls that all? Just one paisa?
No, l can't do it
l can't go all the way,
buy the berries, wash them...
it's going to kill me!
Will 3 annas do, Belu?
- Yes, we'll manage
For Chacha's sake...
So give us 3 annas, Chacha
3 annas?
- Yes, Chacha. Out with it.
All right, since you insist.
But l'll grow hair, won't l?
Oh sure, long hair
Not berry-seed, Chacha...
- Use bittergourd instead!
Damn it!
l understand everything
lf berry-seed could grow hair,
there wouldn't be bald men like me
Bhola, why didn't you buy
the polish from that shop?
lt must've dried up
lying on those shelves, Belu
We'd have wasted our money.
- All right
Let's make sure we buy nice polish.
- Yes, come on
This is worth 10 rupees 12 annas
and this is 1 4 rupees and 5 annas
What are you kids up to...?
What do you want?
We need a first class brush
- And polish
Brown.
- And black
But what brush do you want?
- What brush?
A nice shoe-brush.
- l'll get it. Wait here
When we have empty polish tins...
we'll keep them safely.
We won't bury them under the tree
Here's your brush. For 1 rupee,
12 annas, 8 annas and 4 annas
Which one do you want?
l'll get some polish too
This is a nice one, Bhola.
- But that's worth a rupee
No, this is worth 8 annas.
- Here's the polish
6 annas, 8 annas, 10 annas
and 4 annas
Take your pick
He said 3 annas for this.
- And l thought it was worth 4 annas
Have you chosen something?
- One moment, please
You said 7 annas for this, right?
- No, 10 annas for this and 12 for this
No, he said 3 annas for this.
- What a racket you are creating
Your total is 12 annas and 4 annas...
- 1 4 annas in all
No. 1 rupee and 5 annas.
- Hurry up
You owe me 1 rupee and 2 annas.
- Can't you reduce it a bit?
Can't you reduce it a bit?
- Not a penny. Out with the money
Here you are
1 rupee and 2 annas, 12 annas,
8 annas and 4 annas...
the kids have conned me!
Belu, our Hindustan is free today!
We're giving up begging
Long live Mahatma Gandhi.
- Long live Nehru!
Just see how much of money
l make, Belu
You will buy me berries, won't you?
- l'll even buy you a frock
A red frock?
- Yes, very red
Let's go and tell John Chacha.
- Let's go
What is it, children?
John Chacha, we've brought
something new today
What is it? Show me.
- lt's good news
What?
- Close your eyes. Go on
Here l go.
- Let's go in. Come on
Don't watch, Chacha.
- Who's watching
Now open your eyes, Chacha
Well done, children.
- We won't beg from tomorrow
That's very nice.
This is the way to life, my children
Achieve something,
with these hands of yours
No one's getting anything like this.
Stand in a queue... in one single line
Everyone will get something. The lady
will herself give away alms today
Not only will you get money,
you'll get some grams too
What's happening out there today?
- Nothing, Chacha
Some for me, lady...
My children are starving
l've been starving for 2 days.
God will bless you, lady
Relax... everybody will
get something
Patience
You're giving away alms, lady?
You think God will
give you a bountiful...
for the 2 annas you're
handing out today?
What rubbish are you talking?
- She has built four temples
And two sanctuaries for cows.
- She is blessed with a grandson
So she's giving away alms today
- And what rubbish are you talking?
What l'm saying is right, sir
Had it not been for people like you,
these beggars would either have died...
or worked for a living.
Don't give them alms, give them work
ls that my look-out?
- lt isn't my look-out, neither yours
ls it the look-out of outsiders then?
Whose look-out is it?
Shut up! You dare talk back?
- You interfere in a noble cause?
Get lost!
Old fossil, what nonsense is that?
You don't beg, and you won't let us beg?
That lady came every fortnight,
but now you've offended her too
We won't even get the 2 annas
we used to get in alms!
This is our source of livelihood
You're snatching the bread
from our children?
No, don't say such things. The children
are stepping into a new world
Don't teach them ways
of begging, please
Where's the new world? We starved
yesterday and we're starving today
Where is the new world?
Let's go before the lady leaves
You won't be able to see the new world.
You'll see it in the eyes of the kids
They see the new world
A new order won't happen on its own...
the children will establish it
You were born beggars
and you will die beggars!
But why must you make
beggars out of the children?
Who hit you, Chacha?
l'll give him a thrashing!
l'll beat him to pulp!
l'll beat him!
Let me go, Chacha
''My little boy...
what do you hold in your fist?''
''ln my fist is my destiny''
''l have my destiny
under my own control''
''What do your innocent eyes see?''
''Our eyes see hope of joyful times''
''We dream beautiful dreams
of the times to come''
''My little boy....
what do you hold in your fist?''
''Will you accept a diamond
given to you in alms?''
''What will you do
with the tears life gives you?''
''We won't accept even a diamond
given to us in alms''
''Our tears we shall cherish''
''lt's fun to lead a life
overcoming hardships''
''My little boy....
what do you hold in your fist?''
''Do not hide it from me, children.
Do please tell me...''
''what kind of world are we
going to have in the future?''
''ln the future,
everybody will be king''
''Neither will the masses go hungry,
nor will grief prevail''
''The times will change...
that's what the stars foretell''
''My little boy....
what do you hold in your fist?''
''ln my fist is my destiny''
''l have my destiny
under my own control''
Well done, children
Don't ever open the fist to beg
Whatever happens, don't ever beg
Don't
So you're the one who doesn't
let them beg?
Bhola, go on...
go and get the money
Are you going, or aren't you?
So you are instigating them?
l'll see how they won't go
Don't you hit them!
- Shut up, lame duck
The hooch ruined your leg.
But you won't see sense
l'll see how you brainwash them.
Come on
Well, Chacha...?
No booze today?
Enough of bittergourd, eh?
- Don't interfere, Chitku
And stop seeing Kamla,
or you'll go to prison
My foot!
Wastrels! The two of you
are bent on killing me!
What are you waiting for?
Cook some rice
lf l see you with that old fossil ever
again, l'm going to break your legs!
lf you don't bring 10 annas by tomorrow
evening, don't even come here again
Get that? You will bring the money?
Why don't you speak?
- l'll get the money, aunt
l surely will
We've got to make 10 annas today.
- Else, aunt will beat us
Hello, Chitku.
- Hello
So you've stopped begging
and gone into business?
Yes, Chitku.
- Your aunt knows what you're up to?
No, Chitku. Please don't tell aunt...
- Don't tell her, big deal
That'll cost you 4 annas every day.
- Not 4 annas, Chitku
We'll give you an anna.
- Shut up
l want 4 annas every evening, okay?
Else, l'll fix you
Polish, sir?
Polish, memsaab?
Munna! l've found him!
Where's the brown polish?
- Use the black one, but hurry up
Give that to me
Hurry, the train's about to arrive.
- We're almost through, sir
The train has arrived!
- One moment, sir
Hurry up
The train has arrived!
My shoes!
Money, sir...
l'll give you anna each.
Do a good job, okay?
What have you done?
lt's terribly hot in Bombay.
- We're through, sir
Through? Give them both
an anna each
They've ruined my socks
and pajama!
Ask me to have my shoes
polished again
They can't even wash their faces
and they're out to polish shoes!
Where are they...? Get them
We'll have to be careful, Bhola.
Or we'll have to close shop
Absolutely
We'll give your shoes a shine, sir.
- All right, go ahead
Take off your shoes, sir.
- Hurry up
Who's the insolent?
ls this your shoe?
Aren't you ashamed?
What's happening here?
- The rascal
What have you done?
- What am l to do?
l can't polish shoes.
- Whoever asked you to?
You'll know when someone
gives you thrashing
l'll be careful henceforth, Belu.
Let's go, come on
Boy, come here.
- Polish, sir?
Do you have polish for these shoes?
- Yes, sir. Black or brown?
Where's your feet-rest?
- Fee-fee? Right here, sir
We'll run it on your shoes, sir.
A feet-rest!
- Keep your foot on my thigh, sir
Put some
lt's a canvas shoe and we've
applied polish on it!
Quiet
What have you done, boy?
You've ruined my shoe!
Forgive me, sir...
- Forgive me?
Don't you know what it is
to polish a shoe?
Don't you know?
Bhola! You're crying?
l can't polish shoes... l won't!
l can't do it
How can you throw away
your things like this Bhola?
You'll learn it, Bhola.
Everybody learns, so will we gradually
Don't cry, Bhola.
Listen, let's go to John Chacha
He'll show us how to polish shoes
Don't cry, Bhola.
Don't cry
Come on. Come
Come Bhola, Belu...
l'll teach you an
English song today
You'll sing with me, won't you?
What happened, Belu?
What happened...?
He hit him.
- Hit him?
He hit Bhola.
- Which rascal hit him?
We ruined his trousers, Chacha.
- Ruined his trousers?
He was wearing canvas shoes and
we applied brown polish on it
You went and applied brown polish
on canvas shoes...?
Chacha, l don't know
how to polish shoes
l won't polish shoes, Chacha.
l can't do it
No, my son.
You must never lose courage
Everybody finds a new business
to be difficult initially
You'll learn it. You surely will.
Look at me
l couldn't play the instrument.
But l worked hard and now l play it
l'll show you how
to polish shoes
A nice way too...
like they massage my head
Suppose this is a foot-path
with people and cars passing by
And along comes a gentleman.
How will you approach him?
First-class polish...
absolutely super
And who else comes along?
A Hindu priest
Say, ''Namaskar, priest. l'll give
your shoes a great lndian polish''
But remember to spare his socks.
Also keep out the trousers and dhotis
A great polish!
For black shoes...?
- The black polish
For brown shoes?
- The brown polish
And canvas shoes...
- We don't want it!
Well said! Now go ahead and
get on with it, okay?
''Wait a while before you go away...''
''listen gentlemen,
black and white...''
''We've been waiting for a long time.
We, the shoe-shine boys''
''Wait a while before you go away...''
''listen gentlemen,
black and white...''
''We've been waiting for a long time.
We, the shoe-shine boys''
''One anna for the black polish''
''One anna for the brown polish''
''One anna for a massage
of the shoes''
''Pay an anna, and you'll
have everything''
''We have no riches, we wear no
grand turbans nor gold bangles''
''Ours is a small business...
we're the gay shoe-shine children''
''Wait a while before you go away...''
''listen gentlemen,
black and white...''
''We've been waiting for a long time.
We, the shoe-shine boys''
''Sweet is the fruit
of hard work''
''Very true''
''Left-overs and crumbs...''
''we don't want any''
''Bread earned out of hard work...''
''is welcome''
''And goodies that come for free...''
''we don't want''
''Shame on those who
gorge on ill-gotten food''
''We're hardworking
shoe-shine children''
''Wait a while before you go away...''
''listen gentlemen,
black and white...''
''We've been waiting for a long time.
We, the shoe-shine boys''
''The priest does the rituals;
he makes you get the holy bath''
''We work for a living...''
''we give your shoes a shine''
''The priest asks for a lot''
''We ask for just an anna''
''What discrimination then...?
- When everybody loves the money''
''We don't understand the difference...
we're the shoe-shine guys''
''Wait a while before you go away...''
''listen gentlemen,
black and white...''
''We've been waiting for a long time.
We, the shoe-shine boys''
Red and white...?
What a sight!
Black eyes, long hair and a
lovely red flush on the cheeks
What beauty!
Like a newly polished sandal
Get lost!
l say, what are Bhola and Belu up to
behind your back?
What are they up to?
- He's pulling wool over your eyes
You're applying kohl and they've
even stopped begging nowadays
You're back...?
Where were you all this while?
And Chitku says, behind my back...
- Behind your lovely back!
What are you hiding from me?
- lt's nothing, aunt
l've made 10 annas today.
- 10 annas! How come?
Show me.
- Ten annas, l say...
l'm giving you an anna.
- l want 4 annas!
All right!
So what were you saying, Chitku?
- Nothing
l've found a room for you.
- Really?
You must beg like this
every day, Bhola
Bring 10 annas tomorrow also.
- l'll be late tomorrow, okay?
l say come back before sunset, love
Out with the four paise
Coming!
l hid four annas in this, Bhola.
Know what we'll do with it?
What will we do if Chitku tells aunt
about our new business?
We'll deal with it, when it happens.
We'll buy a new shirt for you
This one's in tatters.
- No. Your frock comes first, Belu
No, your shirt comes first.
This frock will last many more days
Let's not argue... let's go to
John Chacha, he'll settle it for us
What is the matter, children?
- Keep this brush and polish, Chacha
Or aunt...
- She wants you to beg forever
But we've stopped begging, Chacha.
- Yes, Chacha
Really? And l didn't even get to know
that you've stopped begging
Here, have some grams
Decide something for us, Uncle.
lsn't he wearing a torn shirt?
lsn't it a torn one?
- Yes
So l asked him to buy a new shirt
He can buy it with the money
we've made out of shining shoes
But he just won't agree!
- Why not?
l told her Chacha, that my shirt
will last many more days
Her frock is torn. So let's
buy a new frock for her
But she won't agree.
- l said you're buying a new shirt!
So how can you interfere?
- Big deal!
We're buying you a new red frock.
- No way!
Once l say something, it's final.
l don't want anymore arguments!
What are you fighting for?
You buy a shirt.
And you buy a frock. That's all
All we have is four annas, Chacha
We can only buy a shirt for Bhola.
lsn't it?
Four annas?
lt can do nothing for anyone
Why? Does a shirt cost
more money, Chacha?
Yes, dear. lt costs a lot.
lt costs 3 or 4 rupees
For you, l would...
Do you have any hooch, Chacha?
- What?
We were coming here Chacha, and there
was this man in the street...
Not man. He looked like a ghost!
- Ghost?
He said...
- Get me a bottle of hooch
He promised us 5 rupees.
- l said l didn't know
What is hooch, Chacha?
- Hooch?
How'd l know what it is?
Which street was this chap in, Bhola?
He was...
- Near the palm tree. He doesn't know
Must've been someone. What have
l to do with a drunkard?
You kids run along now
and go to sleep
Chacha, just mind our
brush and polish
Won't you play the instrument?
- Sure, l will. Go on now. Go
l'll buy the children
a frock and a shirt
For Bhola and Belu.
l won't do it ever again, Lord
Here's it is...
memorable stuff
Belu, wake up...
the police have arrested John Chacha
The police have arrested him?
- Yes. Come on
This was the boy who
told you, isn't he?
No, lnspector. There's no one with me.
Quickly take me to the police station
Let John Chacha go, Constable.
Or l'll complain to my aunt!
Take them away too!
- No, Constable
These poor kids work hard
to earn living
They gave me no information.
Please take me along
All right. Let them go
Why do the police arrest you?
- Because l'm a bad man
l've committed a crime
But you must never do
something like this
Life is full of hardships,
but you ought to be brave
Belu... you're crying?
What for?
l'll be back soon. Very soon.
- What has John Chacha done, constable?
He's into bootlegging.
- He won't do it again
Am l right, Chacha?
- l'll never do it, my child. Never
Take him away.
- One moment
Give me a smile and tell me how
my bald pate will sprout hair
Give me a smile... go on.
- The bittergourd...
Come on, it's late already
Hey! Pedro!
John!
How come you're here?
- The old business
Hooch?
l told you not to do such things.
- This is the last time, Pedro
Never again.
- Never? Come
Meet the brothers...
- Who is he?
He's a very big man.
Sit down there. Go on
Lala Chhoturam. A 4-month term.
He's here for six months
That's Pestonji...
on an eight-month term
Maganbhai, he's here for 1 7 months.
- 1 7 months? Pleased to meet you
And me...!
- Chimanji! 15 days
ls that all?
- A month actually
All right. Go away.
Meet Professor Lobolo.
- What professor?
Of the brains.
- How come he's here?
He developed something
that would grow hair
He conned 300 men.
For the fraud, he was given 3 years
3 years? Wow, Professor!
l'm delighted to meet you
Please sit down
Professor, l'm very fond
of that oil you discovered
Have you hit upon any new formula?
- l have an entirely new concept
What?
lt has a bit of philosophy too.
- What's philosophy?
lt has to do with the brains
lt's a bit complicated.
- Tell us about it, Professor
Maybe we'll understand something
The only conclusion of everything
is the cloud and hair
Cloud and hair?
We don't get it, Professor.
- Clouds are dark, so is hair
lnvoke the clouds...
maybe you'll even grow hair
What a silly philosophy.
- Not at all
l get what you're saying.
l sure do. Come here and sit down
Clouds mean water
and the other thing is hair
The hair will grow when
the clouds pour, right?
Right!
- But how will it pour water?
That's the beauty of the whole thing!
Come and sit down
lt has to do with practice,
with preparation
Have you heard of Tansen?
- Oh yes!
He caused rainfall, did you know?
- Yes
Now listen
''Pounce on it''
''Come hither, O rains...''
''the fields, our bald pates,
are parched''
''So pour on us''
''Bring water...''
''strike lightning''
''lf you have no rains...''
''fetch some from the river-banks''
''The nightingale sings
in the forests...''
''every heart craves''
''Give us a bountiful of hair''
''Come pouring quickly''
''Come pouring''
''Pour...''
Step away!
This is amazing!
- What happened?
l made a mistake, Pedro!
l have invoked a storm. What will
happen to Bhola and Belu?
What happens of the
poor in the slums?
Give it to me, Belu.
Don't fall, Bhola.
l'm terribly scared
Don't be afraid, Belu. l'm all right.
Give that to me
Bhola, l'm feeling very cold
Why must it rain so heavily?
Mind the kid, lady...
He's getting drenched
Why don't we have a mother?
When will she come?
Mother? She'll come...
with the new dawn...
when it's bright outside
Our mother will come then.
She surely will
Mother will come when it's dawn?
Will she...? Mother...
Mother!
Good morning
Have a cup of tea.
lt rained heavily last night.
- So much more happened too
John Chacha's gone to jail.
- A good thing too
The government must never set him
free. He's a very dangerous man
Not as dangerous as you are.
- Here you are
At least pay for the tea.
- Pay for it?
Are you selling tea now?
- You could say that
My business is all over.
- Why?
Those serpents in your house...
- What?
Nothing.
- Tell me
Bhola and Belu are into shoe-shining
nowadays. They don't beg
l see! They must've hidden
money from me
Nobody would give them even 2 annas
in the monsoons. Look at my state
When they begged, they made
at least a rupee or two annas
But now, they won't even
bring 10 annas a day
They think they can live off me!
l'll throw them out, even if
that's the last thing l ever do!
You're too much...
oh, what a beauty
Mother...
Bloody wretch! You swallowed your
mother, the day you were born!
Where's the brush and the polish?
Chitku has told me everything
l earn money for a livelihood
and you act smart with me?
Get the hell out of here!
Don't come back here,
if you don't have the money!
Bhola, l'm feeling a chill
Belu! You have a fever!
Aunt! Open the door...
Belu's running a fever!
Bhola! Where will we sleep?
What will we get to eat?
Belu, don't be afraid
John Chacha asked us to be brave.
Remember?
Come, Belu. l'll get to work
Here you are.
- ls it okay?
Come
Polish, sir?
- Get lost! What polish in the rains?
Please give me a cup of tea.
- Do you have the money?
l don't have any money.
- So get lost
l'll do a great polish, sir...
How can l have my shoes
polished in the rains?
l'll miss my train.
Don't be a pest
Polish, sir?
Who gets his shoes polished
in the rains?
Here's what l'm wearing.
Get going
Bhola, l'm terribly hungry
l feel as if l'll die
out of hunger
Your fever has increased, Belu.
What am l to do...?
What am l to do, God?
- l'm going to die, Bhola
You'll be happy then?
- No, you mustn't say such things
Sit down here. l'll find someone
who'll have his shoes polished. Sit
Polish, sir?
l'll do a nice polish, sir...
a polish in just 2 paise, sir
Sir, l'll do a very nice polish!
Give me just 2 paisas, sir!
Does anyone have his shoes
polished in the rains?
Your polish will get washed away.
What's the use?
Why don't you do something else?
- l'll give you a nice polish, sir
A very nice polish, in just 2 paisa...
- What a mad boy
Why must l have my shoes polished?
You want money, no? Here you are
No, sir... l can't take this money.
l want work!
l'll give you a polish, sir...
- Take it, son
l'm hungry!
- You're begging!
l'm terribly hungry.
l'm very hungry
Hungry? You'd rather die!
Bhola, l'm very hungry!
Look, Bhola...
there are so many shoes out there
Yes, Belu. When it stops pouring,
l'll polish all those shoes
And l'll bring hot tea for you.
Steaming hot
l'll also bring bread...
you will eat it, won't you?
Polish, sir? l'll do a nice job, sir.
- Go away
Who gets his shoes polished
in the rains?
Polish, sir? l'll do a nice job
Come, let's go to Buribunder.
l'll surely find work there
Polish, sir?
- Go away
lt's over, sir. l'm through.
- Who asked you to polish the shoes?
l've done a nice job, sir.
Please give me an anna?
Get lost!
Boy... take this
- Thank you, sir.
Belu, get up. l'll buy something
for you to eat
Money?
- Look
Bhola, what are you doing here?
Out to polish shoes
on a day like this?
lt's so crowded during the rains...
even if you cut a throat,
nobody gets to know
My word!
lf only you had bought a scissor
instead of brush and polish...
it would end your miseries.
See you then
l'm very hungry, Bholu.
- Sit here, Belu
l'll go and get something for you.
l'll be back in a minute
A cup of tea and bread for me.
- Here you are
My wallet! Someone
has picked my pocket!
Run away, Bhola!
Look, the police!
Over there!
Don't let the boy get away!
After him!
Belu! Get up and run!
lt's the police!
Run, Belu!
Constable, Belu's in there.
- There's no Belu here!
Please open the gate...
my sister's in there!
Get lost!
You love children, don't you?
And look at our luck.
After seven years of marriage...
Which l why l ask you...
- To marry again?
Silly woman
You're not hurt, are you?
l'm hungry...
please call Bhola
l'm hungry.
- The poor girl's burning with fever
Who are you?
- She seems to be an orphan
She must be hungry.
- Give the poor girl some money
She'll buy something to eat.
- All right
Take this, dear.
- No
l don't want alms.
Bhola will be angry
Please call Bhola...
- Bhola, who?
Bhola... l'm hungry, Bhola...
The poor girl has fainted
out of fever
The police have left, Belu!
l'll buy berries for you, Belu.
And a red frock too
Where have you gone away, Belu?
Where will l look for you?
How's she now?
- The fever has subsided
But she's still delirious...
and she seems to be very frightened
No, Bhola... no
Mother...
Mother will come...
when a new day dawns
You? Haven't you left?
l've lost my sister...
have you seen her?
What sister?
- Belu. My sister is lost
She must be in there. Let me see...
- Go away, get lost
Baba, have you seen Belu around?
- No son
Why're you yelling?
Don't you care for my health?
Has Belu returned?
- No, damn you
Have you brought the money?
Don't hit me, aunt...
Belu has gone missing
l'm glad l'm rid of her!
Why don't you die too?
Worthless boy! Go away!
lf you don't get the money,
don't ever come back here
Aunt!
Don't let Belu go anywhere,
if she returns
l'll die without her, aunt.
Don't let her go anywhere
''What land are you headed for
in those fineries, my girl?''
''l go to the land of my beloved
in these fineries''
''What land are you headed for
in those fineries, my girl?''
''Tears flow from
your parents eyes''
''Friends from your childhood
cry at the separation''
''Your brother calls out for you...''
''don't leave your house''
''l go to my beloved's land
in these fineries''
''What land are you headed for
in those fineries, my girl?''
''My beloved's land is oh so far away''
''l belong to him
and he's my beloved''
''l was tied in love...''
''after a lot of thought''
''l go to the land of my beloved
in these fineries''
''What land are you headed for
in those fineries, my girl?''
You will live with us, won't you?
We'll give you a lot of love
You're wearing a nice frock
What is your name?
You still haven't told us
Tell us your name... Go on
You will stay with us, won't you?
- l'm going back to Bhola
Bhola? Who's that, dear?
- Bhola... my brother
So you have a brother too?
- Oh yes
How can we keep her with us Lata?
lt's against the law
And we don't even know whether
she has her parents or not
l have a feeling
that she has no one
Where do you live, dear?
- Over there... with Bhola
The car has returned
from the garage, sir
Go and fetch my coat
Let's go and find out
about her today
ls it okay if you went to
the office a bit late today?
You will take us to your house,
won't you?
All right. Get ready
Come, dear.
- Get the car out, Shyamu
We're going to Bhola, aren't we?
- Yes, we're going to Bhola
Come...
Watch it, dear
Run! lt's the ticket-checker!
Come on
Wait there... what have
you gotten me into?
Wait there, dear...
watch your step
Watch your step
Aunt! Open the door!
- So you're back screaming!
l've brought sweets for Bhola, aunt.
For you too
What airs have you put on
in a single night?
ls she your child?
- No! She's an orphan
She used to live with me...
has she committed a theft?
No, we're the ones who committed
a theft ... by keeping her with us
We wish to keep her with us
We wish to adopt her.
- Will you give her away to us?
Why not? But l've brought her up.
l've faced so many hardships...
you know, it really hurts me
to give her away to you
Do you want to adopt another child?
No, we want just her...
let's go, dear
Take Bhola along too!
- All right, we'll take him along too
Where is Bhola?
- That was her brother
He died a few days ago
and she weeps for him
He's dead?
Let's go, dear.
- No, l won't go without Bhola
l want to go to Bhola...
- Bhola will be coming, dear. C'mon
So go away!
- You don't have to yell at her
Let's go...
- l want to go to Bhola!
Lord, my wish has been fulfilled
With Your grace,
l now have a daughter
Thanks a million, Lord
Belu has gone missing, Lord.
lf l find her...
l'll offer You a day's
shoe-shine earning
l won't forget Your favour
all my life, Lord
You take some too, son
May your folks die! Why couldn't
you tell us a day in advance?
A day? We told you six months ago
to clear these slums
Clear the slums and take them where?
Place them on your head?
Move to Marine Drive, lady
Oh yes, your father owns the place.
Doesn't he?
l say, there's a room available
in Sadhuram's tenement
l'm saying it for your own good
There's a room in Sadhuram's tenement.
Do you hear that?
l could show it to you.
- Where?
Out there, Kamla. You can have
a great gathering there
Why would l take a whole room for
myself? Especially without Kamla
So what do you think?
- What's the rent?
Why bother about rent? Sadhuram
won't fleece you, will he?
lt's just 5 rupees.
- But l'm not giving you any space
Aunt... has Belu returned?
Has my Belu returned, aunt?
So you're back?
- No, aunt
l only came to ask if Belu was back
Where do you think you're going?
lt's because of you that
l've got to leave this place
Pick up all that stuff!
Pick it up... you'll find
a lot of shoes to polish there
Die! Don't you get to eat?
You're not hurt, are you?
- No
''About my heart l spoke...''
''all night''
''Separated from you,
l couldn't go to sleep...''
''all night''
''l'm the mischievous Queen
of Spring''
''The world is crazy about me''
''l'm the mischievous Queen
of Spring''
''The world is crazy about me''
''l plunder hearts
with my piercing eye...''
''l kick up a storm
every lane l pass through''
''l'm adept at weaving tales''
''The world is crazy about me''
''l'm the mischievous Queen
of Spring''
''My charm is unique''
''lt sates your love...
and empties your pockets''
''To give away the heart
is to court sorrow''
''The world is crazy about me''
''l'm the mischievous Queen
of Spring''
''Let people die,
for all l care...''
''l'll continue my merry-making''
''l've got to make
my own world...''
''The world is crazy about me''
''l'm the mischievous Queen
of Spring''
She's now your mother and
this is your father, dear
This is your house
Get lost!
- What happened?
What else? He keeps loafing about the
whole day, and gives me just 4 annas...
expecting me to give him two meals
and a roof over his head
l ask him to beg, he'll make more
money. But he wants to shine shoes!
Dog! Get lost!
And don't you come back!
You're dead, for all l care.
Understand?
Belu, where are you going?
Where were you going?
Where, tell me?
To Bhola.
- To Bhola?
Come, l'll take you to Bhola.
- No, l want to go to Bhola
Why hasn't he come?
l want to go back to him
Of course, dear. l'll take you
to Bhola right now. At once
Lata, how long will we hide the truth?
We'll have to tell her some day
My child... don't you
like this place at all?
Don't you like it here at all?
- l'm going back to Bhola...
Don't you love this mother?
Mother!
You won't even let me sleep in peace.
You're always a nuisance, John Chacha
Nuisance? Why don't you say l'm
killing the mosquitoes in the jail?
Killing them, my foot!
l've been in this cell for 5 years
5 years! l've spent 25 years here
in terms of 2 and 4 months. Know that?
You're a 5-year old kid
and l'm young man of 25
Who's that? Come on in
What's happening, John?
- Not much, constable
This has to do with my honour.
This 5-year old kid...
is insulting a young man of 25.
- Go away. You've been let off
Let off?
- Yes
l had a nice time,
but l'm not coming back again
Really? So the jail has
reformed you at last
lt isn't the jail, constable.
lt's the love of those children
But you won't understand.
- Go on
John Chacha? You've eaten enough
bittergourd here, haven't you?
So you're here? l told you
to stop seeing Kamla
Should l have seen you
instead, Chacha?
l'd still have had to come here.
- What's his crime, sir?
lf there was one, l'd tell. Move it!
- One moment
Chitku, how are Bhola and Belu?
- Everything there is ruined, Chacha
The lady sold Bhola and Belu
to a rich man
Sold them?
- Yes. For only a hundred rupees
You know Sadhuram who owns
the tenement?
He's an acquaintance of his.
Ask him, he'll tell you everything
Move it. lt's late already
What are you looking at my face for?
Polish my shoes quickly
l've got to go to the movies.
Are you through?
How much is that?
- 2 annas, sir
2 annas...?
Taxi, wait here
The cab's going away...
here's the two annas
Hey cabbie! Wait for me
To Regal Cinema, driver.
And make it quick
Mister...
- What is it?
Come here, son
You're such a nice boy
Here you are.
- No thank you
Take it. Buy yourself some sweets.
Let's go
Hey mister...
A red frock
What do you want?
- l want that red frock, sir
Do you have the money?
- Yes, sir. Here it is
Not 2 rupees.
That frock is worth 5 rupees
Sweet berries
What is it? Get lost
l want those berries.
- How much?
Give me the whole lot.
- The whole lot? Are you mad?
lt's worth 2 rupees.
- Here you are
All right, here you are...
take away the basket too
How much for the berries?
- 4 for an anna
Here you are
Sweet berries...
How much for the berries?
- 4 for an anna, sir
Give me eight annas worth
Belu, where have you gone away?
Write, my child
''A'' ... as in aam (mango)
And ''B'' as in basta (bag).
- Not bag... berries
So you like berries?
- l love them
l don't like chocolates
Papa brings chocolates every day.
Why doesn't he bring berries?
He'll bring berries too, my child.
He forgets, you see
l'll ask him to bring berries
for my Belu every day
A lot of berries. Okay?
Write now
Write dear... what are you
thinking about?
''A'' as in ''Aam''...
''B'' as in berries
and ''C''...
- Chacha! John Chacha!
Renu! Where are you going?
My Belu is missing; she's said
to be staying somewhere here
Has anyone of you seen her?
- No
l searched everywhere for her,
but l couldn't find her
Please tell me if you get to know.
She's just like you
Where were you, John Chacha?
l looked so much for you!
Bhola wasn't around, nor were you.
Where did you go away, Chacha?
Where had you disappeared, Belu?
And these clothes...
you look like a princess.
- l live right here, Chacha. Come on
You live here?
- Come on
Come on in Chacha.
You'd like to see my house, no?
Certainly. Why not?
- Come on
Look, Chacha...
isn't it beautiful?
Mother... come...
Mother, this is John Chacha.
We used to live with him
He's a wonderful person, Mother
What's that greeting, Chacha?
Say namaste to her
So you are the folks who have...?
- Yes. We have adopted her
You've done a very nice thing...
a very noble gesture indeed
Please come in
Yes, Chacha. Come on in... come!
Come, Chacha...
l'll show you beautiful toys...
l have so many toys!
l have so many lovely frocks...
all of them are red!
Come, Chacha
And look, Chacha.
l've even started studying
''A'' as in ''aam''.
''B'' as in berries...
And ''C'' as in...
- Chacha!
Come Chacha. Sit down
Please sit there...
- No thank you
This is my place, you know.
- l'm sitting with you too
Want me to show you the frocks?
- Oh yes
And the dolls too?
- Oh certainly
Where do you live?
The whole of Bombay
is now my house
l used to be their neighbour.
These children... l loved them
But where is Bhola?
- See, Chacha!
Lovely frocks...
these dolls!
Belu, fetch something for
for your Chacha to eat
At once!
Please don't talk about Bhola
in Belu's presence
She weeps so much whenever
she's reminded of him
Why? What happened to Bhola?
- Look Chacha! Nice bread...
What's that? Bring some sweets,
fruits and tea for him
Tell Shyamu. He'll bring it.
- Would you like sweets, Chacha?
What happened to Bhola?
- Don't you know?
Bhola is dead.
- Bhola is dead? No...
lmpossible! Who told you?
We were told by that woman
from whom we adopted Belu
So Kamla told you...?
The liar! The devil!
lf Kamla says Bhola is dead,
it means he's certainly alive
l'll surely find Bhola.
l'll find him
lf only we could find Bhola...
- Look at the goodies, Chacha
l'm feeding Chacha with my own hands!
Eat, Chacha
l'll come again tomorrow, Belu.
You like berries, don't you?
l'll bring berries for you, okay?
- Okay
Renu, l've brought berries
for you dear. You...?
This is Mr John;
he used to be Renu's neighbour
No! He's John Chacha!
- l'm very happy to have met you
John Chacha is a very nice man, Papa.
- Certainly, dear. Please sit down
Sit down, Chacha. Please sit down.
- l must go now, dear
Where will you go, Chacha?
l'm not letting you go away!
l'll come again tomorrow
But we're leaving tomorrow
You're leaving tomorrow?
Yes. We're going out of town
for a couple of months
lt'll be a nice change for Renu...
and we want her to forget
about her past life
She must grow up to be a decent,
respectable and educated girl
That has been my desire too
That these children study
and grow up to be good citizens
l'm a very happy man today
So l must leave now, Belu dear
Where are you going, Chacha?
l'm not letting you go!
Bhola's not here either...
l'll come again...
This is now your house, my child
She's your Mama.
And he's your Papa
You will find everything here
And l have nothing
to give you, my child
l'll surely come to see you.
l surely will...
Belu's going to study
and grow up...
and l'll surely come to see Belu!
- Chacha, don't go away!
You won't be here...
nor will Bhola!
May you be happy, Belu
But l'll surely bring Bhola
Buy me some berries, Papa.
- How much for the berries?
2 for a paisa, sir.
- Give me an anna's worth
''Bhola sells it,
and Belu eats it...''
''berries, everybody relishes''
Sweet berries...
Wait!
Give those berries! They're Belu's!
- Belu, who?
My sister, sir. What will l tell her
when she comes asking, sir?
Shut up and come on
Hello, John Chacha.
When did you return?
Have you seen Bhola around?
- No, l haven't
What is your name?
- Bhola
Where do you live?
- Nowhere
Don't you have a house?
And parents?
Parents...?
- So you have no one
l had a sister, sir.
But she has gone missing too
Don't cry. We'll send you
to an orphanage
Take him to Mr Sharma's orphanage.
- Come on
Your name...
- Let them go, constable
But listen... don't get into
business without a licence again
This is now your house, my son.
We are your parents
You'll have everything here
Please let me go, sir...
l haven't done anything
So why did the police bring you here?
- l was selling berries, sir
l thought my Belu would come
to buy the berries
She loves berries, sir.
- Belu? Who's that?
My younger sister.
We were into shoe-shining
She went missing one day.
l looked everywhere...
but l don't know where she is
and how she's managing
You haven't packed your bag, Belu?
Hurry up, dear. Or we'll get late
l'm not going, Mother.
l don't feel like it
You'll like it very much, my child
We'll teach you pony-riding,
take you sailing in a boat...
there'll be so many nice children
to play with you
You will come, won't you?
Aren't you ready yet, Lata?
lt's so late
lt's already eleven and Seth Rai singh
must be waiting for us
What's wrong with her?
- Renu says she's not going
Why not? We're going out
only for her
l'm not going. lf l go away,
there will be no one here
What if Bhola comes calling?
l told you that unless we took her away
she'd be reminded of all the old things
How long will we hide it from her?
Why don't you tell her the truth?
Renu, my child...
Bhola won't come anymore
Of course not!
He'll surely come
No... how will l explain to you?
He's not coming anymore
He'll never come again
''We're your own...
from you, we seek mercy''
''We're your own children...
''We pray for your loved ones''
''ln a world of orphans,
perpetually plunged in darkness...''
''not once did we see a dawn''
''On an evening like this,
for that thing which burns...''
''we seek a lamp of hope''
''We pray for your loved ones''
''The ones whose lives we lit up...''
''have left us alone
in this world''
''May no one ever suffer a fate
like ours''
''We seek solace for
every troubled heart''
''We pray for your loved ones''
''Give us the piece of bread
you may not have eaten''
''The clothes you have discarded...
give them to us''
''We're your own children...
we seek mercy from you''
''We pray for your loved ones''
Sir...
- What?
l want a job, sir.
- Get going
l'll wash your utensils, sir...
- Go away, l say
He wants a job, he says,
and he was eyeing the goodies
May l carry it for you, sir?
- Can you?
Why not, sir? l sure will.
- Go ahead then
Eat something before you
carry things. Go away
l told you, you can't carry it!
... pick it up
Manglu, have you packed everything?
You haven't locked this
Take it downstairs. Hurry
Renu, what are you doing my child?
Hurry up, dear
The train leaves at ten
''Yes, we're going away
for a couple of months''
''lt'll be a nice change for Renu...''
''and we want Renu to forget
her past life''
''We want her to grown up to be a
decent, respectable and educated girl''
My daughter's leaving today...?
Belu's leaving?
l will go over to meet her...
l'll surely meet her
Hey brother, why are you crying?
- Who are you?
God snatched my mother from me
and the Government snatched my father
Yet someone snatched Belu from me and
someone else snatched by berries
What else will l do, if not cry?
- What do you do for a living?
l'm doing nothing at the moment.
l used to be a shoe-shine boy
But l don't even have the money
for that now
Can you give me some work?
- Will you go with us?
We beg for a living.
- And we make lots of money
Will you join us?
- Beg...?
No. l will not beg
- Will you starve to death, if not beg?
Beg till you have the money to buy
the polish. Give it up later
No, l will not beg
No, l will not beg!
- Will you starve to death then?
Beg till you have money to buy
the polish. Give it up later
No, l will not beg
l'll starve to death...
but l won't ever beg!
l won't beg! No... never!
l'm extremely hungry
John Chacha, l'm feeling uneasy...
l'm starved
Beg till you have money to buy
the polish. Give it up later
No!
''Give me a penny, sir...''
Sir... l wasn't beg...
Sir... a penny sir!
One penny, sir. Please...
- Get lost!
A penny, sir... l haven't
eaten in two days
Sir... one penny.
l'm very hungry...
Sir, a penny...
- Go away!
Bhola...? You?
You're begging?
Why don't you die instead?
No... no!
John Chacha! Bhola's going away!
Stop him!
Bhola, wait there...! Wait!
Wait, Bhola... wait!
Wait!
My son! Where have you been?
Where?
Where had you gone away, Belu?
John Chacha, l've found Belu!
''There will be a new dawn''
''And the Sun will
fill their lives with gold''
''You will grow up to be educated,
sing and dance and be happy''
''He looks after everyone...
everyone''
''Never look back,
never be afraid...''
''the earth and the skies
belong to you... just march ahead''
''Reach for the stars''
''You're one in millions, my children.
Just march on''
''After night...''
''A new dawn''