Remain Awake!
Who are you?
Where do you stay?
Why don't you speak?
l am new in this place.
l have come from the village.
But what are you doing here?
l was looking for some water
-Have the wells in your vilage
...dried up, that you came here
looking for water. Go away
Don't appear before me again,
else l'll break your limbs.
Life is a dream and where
does truth or lie come in that
l did everything as told
by my heart.
When l get free time,
l will try to judge whether...
...whatever l did was
right or wrong
When a drop of water fell on
the lips of a stone...
...it is said that it's heart
started beating after drinking it.
l gave one full peg
to my grief filled heart
Poison killed the poison and
dead became alive again.
Excuse me, Sir
Your purse fell down on the road
-And you are returning it?
Have one cigarette on this
happy occasion
Sir, l don't know how to smoke.
Well, then take this money
and go for race or gambling
Sir, l don't take part in gambling.
-Then what do you want?
Sir, l am feeling very thirsty.
May l have some water?
lf you drink water in this cold,
you will catch pneumonia
Buy whatever liquor you can buy
with this money and have it?
Sir, l don't drink alcohol
You don't drink! Then you must
come with me to my house.
So that l can tell my wife
showing you that one who...
...doesn't know how to gamble or
drink suffer like you. Come.
My wife keeps scolding me not
to do this and not to drink
You thief!
Who is that?
-A thief!
What happened? -A thief
has entered your house
Thief! Thief!
Catch him
Why are you shouting?
Why are you making the noise?
There is a thief.
-Thief! Catch him.
Why have you stopped?
-l am not going ahead.
How can you trust the
robbers these days?
They may have weapons with
them. You go ahead.
What happened?
Who is there? A thief!
Why have you stopped? -lf l go
out now, l'll be caught.
Go out soon or my father
will get up
l am trapped in a problem.
-What if l get caught, go away
Why don't you understand? lf l
am caught, they will beat me
You were telling me just now
that you can do anything for me
Do you want me to jump
in Ganga now?
lf you don't go l will hang
myself. Just stand & have fun
You need not have to do that.
l will cut my neck.
Sati, what happened?
What are you waiting for?
Go now.
Thief! Catch him
Wake up, a thief has entered
the house -Thief! Save us
You go. -Why? -Go
What happened? Where did
he beat you?
How could he beat me,
as l escaped & ran away
There is no need to fear,
as unity is strength. Let's go
You ran away seeing the
image in the glass,
Had there been a real one, then?
lf there is no one, who broke
this lace? Where is Kailashbabu?
l am here. But where is my
daughter? Sati...
What happened to you,
my daughter?
Nothing to worry. She just lost
her consciousness out of fear
How dare you come here again?
l have already warned you...
...against coming here.
Actually there was a thief
-So why do you need to care!
Let anyone come to my
house. You must go away now.
You are getting angry without
reason. As there was a thief,
Then where has he vanished?
We are also having the
same question.
But l swear by your name, l
saw the thief entering this flat
But as there are so many people
here now, how can you identify...
...if the thief is hiding among
us? l will suggest that we will...
...let everyone pass by the main
door one by one.
And the thief willn't definitely
know the flat no.-You are right
Attention please! You all stand
up in the queue
Where are you going?
Stand in the queue
Silence please!
Do l have to tell the number of
my flat too? -No need
What is your flat number?
-50. -And yours -132
Yours? -72
What is your number?
-l don't know the number
l see! Which floor
-Upstairs, third floor
Don't know the number. You
thief. Tell me the number
Why are you beating the poor
fellow? He is new here
He is Manikbabu's servant.
Silence. Let's continue
What is your number?
-27
Number? Why don't you speak?
-27!
Have you understood? All have
gone out one by one.
Only Mr Kailash is left. He must
be the thief. What should we do
Huh! Came to catch the thief!
Sati, you had seen the thief.
Have a look and identify him
What's this going on?
Nothing, l just got an itching
l know all itchings well.
Put your hands down.
Have you identified him?
-No, he's not there.
How can you catch the thief, as
thief always reach near...
...a sweet thing.
-What have you said?
l mean, let the poor people like
us to go as we've to go for...
...work in the morning and you
rich people continue the game
But l had seen him with my own
eyes. -Then where has he gone
He must be hiding
somewhere here.
l keep the door locked as
l have a young daughter
lt's not so easy to catch a thief.
And this house has many holes
He fled that way -Who?
-The thief
Now what happened?
-The thief is here
Haven't you seen him? -Yes,
he is in my pocket.
So you are having great
fun in searching the people's...
...houses at night, as you are
quite young in age.
lf the thief is here, go and tell
the police. They'll do something
What is the matter?
-l was looking for you only.
The young chaps are having
great fun in looking for a thief
ln reality, a girl is hiding her
lover inside the house
Who is the girl? -Kailashbabu's
daughter Sati -And the boy?
Actually l needed a clue for
tomorrow's race
lf l don't get some money, l'm
ruined. l'll commit suicide.
l'll catch your feet and will not
get up till you say something.
What will happen merely by my
words as the horse won't run as
...per my words.-Your word have
great powers. Last year also,...
...your words made the crippled
horse run well & win.
l haven't paid the rent for last
six months. And my wife also...
...doesn't talk to me properly.
Please do something
But even if l say, will you be
able to put that large amount?
Yes, l'll be able to do that.
l'll do it anyway.
There it has come! Race no. 6,
Horse no. 8,
lf you bet Rs 50/, you will get
Rs. 1 ,000-Let me touch your feet
But next time onwards, l am not
going to do this for just Rs. 20
Thief! -Don't shout. lt's me,
your husband
So you have come to steal
-Why should l steal?
l was just checking the metal.
After losing everything in the
race, you are now after my...
...jewellery given by father?
Go and commit suicide
Don't be too proud of your
father. Anyone can afford to...
...give so much jewellery
with the bribes he got.
Don't dare to acuse my father
-Don't talk about the race, then.
Thief -You wicked women.
-How dare you call me that
How dare you attempt to
beat your husband?
l pray to you, don't kill me.
You will be hanged
Why this play now? Even you
also attempted to kill me
Thief!
Have you seen the thief?
Why won't l see him? He is
wearing dirty clothes
Where is he? -He must have
gone down through the window.
l pray to you, don't leave
me alone.
Come down soon, l am
feeling afraid.
What happened? -A thief
broke into my house
But a while ago you told me
that it was Mr. Kailash's...
...daughter! ls it your
wife this time? Who is the boy?
Tell me who is that bearded man
whom you hide under the bed?
How can l do that, as l
was sleeping?
l'll make you reveal
everything now. Let's go in
Life is a dream. What is the
truth or lie in that?
Go away from my way. l want
to go home, as l didn't go last...
...night also. No? Do you want
me to sleep here.
Who is actually drunk, you or
me? Go away, friend.
That's terrific. That's why
l go for the foreign liquor.
Now, come here
You are so obedient. But you
are completely naked.
Let's go to my house, l'll give
you some nice clothes.
Where are you running away
Come with me.
lt's completely dark here.
l'll put on the lights.
Wait, l'll bring clothes for you
Now wear all these clothes
How did the drum come here?
-This is not a drum...
...it's my friend. lt obeys all
my words. l'll show you now
Come friend, come ahead
Everything changes its colours
here after seeing you
l'll not stay here. -Don't go.
Please listen to me.
Why should l? You don't listen
to me in spite of being my wife.
And you now want me to move
in the direction of your fingers?
When have l disobeyed you?
Then tell me, why didn't you
obey me that night? Answer me
l'll answer you tomorrow. Now
please have the food.
No, l want the answer
now itself.
Don't shout. Please have
the food first.
l will definitely shout if you
don't answer my question
How could l obey that? No
woman will be able to obey that.
Why not? Cant's a wife obey
to her husband?
No, if the husband doesn't care
for the respect of his wife...
...she willn't obey him too.
You wanted me to dress like...
...those whores, wanted me to go
around with other males & drink
How can any wife tolerate this?
Can't a wife even do this much
for the sake of her husband?
See, l am your wife. And my
disrespect will bring bad name...
...to you too. Why don't you
try to understand?
Don't you care a little about the
sacredness of our relationship?
Keep your sacredness to yourself.
Cook food and worship the idols
But this god of yours who
as life ,hwill go away for good
No, l'll not let you go away. l'll
obey whatever you order to me
Will you obey me? -Yes
Will you sing & dance -Yes
Will you drink?
Tell me, will you drink?
You are my husband. lf you give
me poison, l'll have that too.
Now let's have the food.
Now tell me, what do you
want me to do?
Oh! You are beautiful
You have never even looked at
my face. How l pity myself!
Again the same drama. This
habit makes you look ugly.
Don't go, l'll not cry.
-Then sing a song.
The cool breeze of spring
is blowing in, my dear and
...so don't keep your window
open again.
Or else the maddening wind
will affect you
The light of the lamp
is striking the eyes
And taking away the sleep
in our eyes, my dear
Please don't keep the
lamps burning today.
The cuckoo has doused the
flames of my heart
But my love remained thirsty
Stop this. Do you call it a song?
-Don't you like the song -No
You consider yourself to be quite
clever. Whenever l feel like...
...talking to you, you start giving
lectures. And now l ask you to...
...sing a song, you started
singing prayers.
Then tell me what kind of
song should l sing?
Sing such such a hit song which
has a good rhythm & is lively
l don't know how to sing
those kind of songs
But we have a record player & l
bring new records everyday...
...now you are telling me that
you don't know how to sing that
Have you heard that 'Lucy wow
wow' song? -Yes
Then sing that song.
Come with me.
Sit here and sing.
You spoiled my mood.
All the bottles are vanishing.
Now l'll not let you go.
Excuse me for now, l'll sing the
song some other time
No, you have to sing it now
-l am having a headache
Don't make excuses in front of
me. You want to fool me.
lt's okay then -No, l'll sing
l can't really sing -Then dance,
like the one in films
What is her name?
Wear this dress and dance.
What do you get by insulting
me? What pleasure do you get...
...by giving pain to my soul?
As per the scriptures, there is
no soul in woman.
Then why cry over something
which you don't have
What are you doing? Wait, l'll
change the dress and dance
Now you only can tell me.
l have already done enough.
How much will l have to
fall? What should l do?
Why are you taking so much
time. Come soon
l am putting on the record. l'll
count till three and if you don't...
...come, l'll break the record.
Won't you come? Okay!
One, two..., here you've come!
What are you doing by standing
there? Come near me
Let me have a look at you.
Come near me.
l am only one and
lovers are many!
They attack my
heart together
See, what a problem l have
got in my small heart
My cheek is of pink colour
and have blue eyes
People think that l am shining
like a thunderbolt when l smile
Where have you vanished?
Oh! You haven't worn your
clothes till now
How dare you stand naked in
front of me? Get out
Go off and never come back!
See some rascal has kept the
drum in the middle
They are not at all sincere.
-Let's take it away
Why are you making the noise?
Have you caught the thief?
Not the thief, but the drum
-Whose drum is this?
You have kept the drum in the
middle & asking us whose it is!
This drum actually belongs to the
rascal opposite my room
He is not at all sincere. He
keeps even the garbage...
...in front of my door. You are
all strong. Go & complain to him.
What's the matter-Why have
you kept your drum in middle
That's his drum, not mine.
-But he is saying that it's yours
How dare you? -Can't you
identify the owner of this...
...drum with a hole even by
looking at the whole in his vest?
So the drum is not yours -No
Not even yours -No
Lift the drum -Wait, if it doesn't
belong to anybody give it to me
Come my son, let's take it inside
How dare you take it?
Give it to me?
Not you, l'll take it
What are you waiting for?
Drag the drum inside
Wait. Do you want the drum?
-Yes,-Do you want it too?-Yes
Then l'll toss this coin
-Head for him, tail for him
See the drum is running away
Police?
Lalbazar! Please transfer
the call to the police
Have you caught the thief?
lf the thief was caught, was
there any need to call you all?
He has vanished from the place
-Where has he vanished?
Now tell him
Police! Police!
Open the door
Where is he? -l don't know
Then why did you shot the gun
l was afraid to see it jump
-Whose jump, the thief's?
No, the mouse
You killed the mouse with one
shot. What an aim you have!
Actually the shot hit the statue
& it fell down killing the mouse
Let me see the rifle
-Yes, sure
Do you have a licence?
-Yes -Please show it to me
There is nobody in this room,
nothing is there
What do these boxes contain?
See the licence Sir. There is just
water in those bottles, as l...
...am suffering from indigestion.
-So you keep a factory of them
Constable, confiscate all the
boxes, & search the room
ls the thief caught? -Not thief,
but the main thing -What?
As you are also into duplicate
medicine, go & remove them
Don't know who called the
police -My God! lt was me.
Police! Remove the goods quickly
We have come from the Press
Now we will have fun
Hello lnspector. But who is he?
ls he the leader of looters?
No, he makes liquor. Now we
have arrested him
Why are you leaving, lnspector?
What will happen to the thief
What can we do unless you
allow us to search the flats
Yes, go for it. -Are you mad?
We are all gentleman here
We are respectable people.
Do you consider search to be
some child-play? -Seen that?
But there is a thief inside
-So what?
You are young people. Keep
yourselves on guard
Learn how to stand on your feet
Yes, why expect help from
others in every step?
OK, do whatever you feel to be
right. But don't take law...
...into your hands. -We will
do that.
We are businessmen. So we
always keep the law at bay
Let's go -Thank you, lnspector
Worn out clothes, long bearded
How long was the beard
Do you think l measured it?
Go and call the police
immediately.
l'll make them search all
the flats now
What happened? -You acted
clever & send back the police
Now you are asking what
has happened?
The thief had tried to snatch my
daughter's necklace.
Had anything happened to her,
would you have taken the...
...responsibility?
-But where is the thief?
Do you expect a child to tell
you about the thief?
What are you waiting for? Ask
the police to come with warrents
Have patience. The problem is
not only yours. lt is everyone's
Before taking any step, we will
have to consider it well at first
Yes, once the police is here, it
will be a disrespect for us.
Can't we protect ourselves?
We are not wearing bangles
What happened? -Hah, you are
the first to collect donations...
...for any problem of others. Now
when we are having problems...
...at home, -But what is the
matter?
l am asking you to prepare one
voluntary guard squad.
Otherwise what is the use of
your strength & our donations?
Go and prepare the squad
Attention please!
-Look at me
Some of you come and make our
guard squad stronger...
...so that we can catch the thief.
Stand on the queue.
Start playing
As the family members never
rest in peace till they find the..
...snake & search in every corner
of the house, we willn't also...
...take a rest till we find
out the thief.
lf you want to catch the thief,
come with me
Why are you disturbing us?
-lt's my democratic right to...
...disturb you. My wife is missing.
And it's your duty to find her.
Follow me. -Shut up!
Take him to his room.
Where is your sword, Sardarji?
Attention! Please have a picture
of the enemy in your mind
He is long haired & wearing
worn out clothes.
His eyes are large & terrifying.
Grab him whenever you find him
Now shout with me again:
We are ready to give our lives
This is the drum where the thief
was hiding. -Really?
Brother, Rambabu has annouced
2 carat gold medal for the one...
...who catches the thief.
-ls it so?
Go and tell the others that only
standing on guard will not help.
They will have to search in
every corner of each house.
As the thief was hiding inside
the drum last time...
...we should not spare any box
or trunks from checking
lf somebody objects then?
Who will object, as this is
everyone's problem?
This is a matter of respect for
us. We have to win the medal.
Do you all have Kirpans with
you -Yes
Beware, the thief should
not run away.
Do you know, they've announced
a medal for the thief-catcher
l will definitely win the medal
-Not you, l'll win the medal
Let me tickle you and
check your courage
Atulbabu, please open the door.
We have to search the rooms
Wait, l am coming
What do you want?
-Check everything in the room
Beware, l'll call the police
-Who is in the room?
My wife -Get away
Who is there?-Please
arrange your clothes
We have to search your room
-Not searching, but having fun
Are you familiar with
Mr. Rambabu?
Rambabu, the person who
has declared the medal? -Yes
Go to him alongwith some of
them & collect some donations
What happened? ls the thief
caught -No, it's drugs
Drugs? -They found two boxfull
of Drugs is Atulbabu's room
He is now asking them to accept
Rs. 200 bribe & keep mum
Who is Atulbabu?
-That bald one in room no. 108
Go and collect donation of not
less than Rs.100. l'll go upstairs
ls Rambabu awake? We are
voluteers here. We have some...
...urgent work with him.
-Please have a seat.
How do these people earn so
much money, friend?
Why not? They are not
uneducated like us to sit by...
...the footpath. He was
abroad for 7 years.
He learnt to earn money
there itself.
What's the matter?
Why have you come?
We are volunteers & we have to
keep awake the whole night
So we need some money to have
tea-Give Rs. 20-
No, we will have Rs. 100 from
you -So much! OK, l'll give.
l'll give Rs. 30. But what have
done done to catch the thief?
He will be caught, as he
can't run away.
Volunteers are searching every
room in first & second floor
By now they must have reached
the third floor also
Are you searching every room?
Not only the rooms but each
corner. -They found bags of...
...drugs in Atulbabu's room.
Who asked you to search the
rooms? -After you have...
...declared the medal, all have
become like hunting dogs
They will even search your house
also -OK, you may go now
But the donation? -You'll
get that later. Go now.
Don't open the main door
How much have you printed?
-We are just starting the Rs 5
How much is the order?
-5,000 for Assam, 7,000 for...
...Bihar and 10,000 for U.P.
-Stop whatever you have...
...finished till now. And
disconnect the machine.
But Sir, we have to deliver all
the money by tomorrow morning!
Just obey whatever l have said.
He must be drunk. Go &
tell him that the money will...
...have to be taken out anytime
as it is dangerous now, Madan
The world is accusing one
as theif without reason
Ask your heart who is not
the thief?
Have l told you a lie -No
Have l mixed poison -No
The people are becoming richer
by taking money from the poor
l am calling it theft and
people call it your good fortune
Be careful & stay away!
l have seen many scholars
taking God's name & give alms
But in real life they
enjoy the public money
l have seen the honest ones
getting hanged
And the guilty are
enjoying freely
Am l telling a lie -No
The thief should not run away
while we are busy in singing
You go that way,
we'll go this way
Sardarji, come this way
and have a seat
What is your name?
Why don't you tell me
your name?
Answer me
Who are you?
See, he died as he
was laughing too much.
Please bring some water
lt is not going to help this way,
let's take him to the hospital
This entire hue and cry about
the thief is baseless
Actually someone must have
considered one as a thief..
...in his intoxication.
Everything is false
But is there anything true in
life? You are your father's son...
...& you are son's father. Then in
reality are you a son or a father
Seen this picture of Mr Ram? He
trades in fake notes...
...still people call him Rambabu.
l have never gone to the...
...medical college ever, still l am
a doctor. Don't laugh like that.
Have you ever seen your face in
the mirror? Girls will faint...
...seeing you. Still your name is
Madan. So whatever is going on...
...in the world is true. -All your
arguments are scientific.
What is this?
Where are they taking
Kumbhakarna?
What is the matter?
Why don't you tell me?
Tell Rambabu that l'll be back
soon after solving this problem
Silence! What happened to him?
He became senseless while
laughing- Speak in turns.
He again became senseless
after gaining consciuousness
Let me examine him
Not a serious problem
ls he caught? -Don't make
noise in the hospital
But there was a thief. -Go &
catch the thief outside, not here
Why've you taken the trouble to
come here? l was going anyway
His condition is so serious that
he has to be admitted in hospital
Who? -My employee, he got a
cardiac arrest following...
...the noise about the thief.
-l'll just join you
But why are you looking
so worried?
lf you want to work under
me, don't argue
Go and make all the
arrangements and wait for..
...my signal. As soon as you get
it, carry all the money...
...to the safe place without
stopping anywhere in the middle
Open it
We will bring the stretcher soon.
Ask Madan to give all the money
ls there anything left?
-No
Disconnect the machine, l am
coming downstairs
Give me the key of this room
Do it fast. Make him lie down in
the bed and cover him
Let's take him to the
hospital first
Come fast
Don't gather here,
please go away
There he is dying and you are
having fun by gathering here
Go away
Take away the stretcher and
bring in the bed
Spread all the notes on the bed
Doctor, it's all now your
responsibility
Mine? -Of course
As soon as you get my signal,
carry the bed on your shoulders..
...and don't stop anywhere in the
middle till you cross the gate
Baralbabu and Pranbabu is here
-Bring them in
No, not here. They may also
have similiar business.
But why should l show them my
privacy? Go & keep them busy...
...in talking. l'll join you
Both of you go out & stand on
guard on the road -Ok
Rambabu will join us, let's
have a seat there
We have come to meet you, not
him -Me?
Doctor, we need the bed urgently
The bed is highly in demand this
night. -How come?
Rambabu is sending his goods in
the bed tonight. l have already...
...issued a death certificate for
him. How can l do it again?
Whenever we are in need, you
always say Rambabu is...
...sending his goods. -Then how
will we run our business?
We also donate a lot of money
for this hospital
Baralbabu, it was my idea to
open the hospital, and l put...
...my money on it at first. So my
goods will always go first
Then what's the use of
putting our money in it
Stop this rubbish now. l want to
know from the doctor...
...whether we will get the
bed or not
Keep your cool in this trying
time. lt's no use losing temper
What are you saying, Rambabu?
You are our elder & learned too
Excuse us for speaking like this
out of anger. But please help us
Please do something as there is
danger around
Why should you be worried as
your goods are minimum
So what? The danger is not
minimum
OK, if you have faith on me,
bring all your goods to my house
l will take care of them.
Sometimes you really talk
funny
This is not the time to laugh.
Carry the bed out.
So the bed is already loaded
Yes, go and bring your goods
here as fast
Why are you bringing yourself to
all these troubles?
Doctor, you are my employee
not l am yours
Can you tell me the reason?
-Because you are more intelligent
Yes. As l scolded them l had to
bring them back to me...
...otherwise they will tell
everyone after going out
Now come and let's take
Mayeed out
No, first spread the news of his
death outside, then l'll carry him
ls it so? Then take this. Now all
the responsibility is yours.
Where is Chandubabu?
-He has gone that way
Go & tell him that if he wants
to catch the thief...
...he should meet Gopichand
immediately.
Meaning? -l want to bring down
the heat in Rambabu
What happened Rambabu?
How can l say! He was my old
employee from the village.
He got fever suddenly and died
He is our Rambabu. He has
announced a reward of a...
...gold medal to the thief catcher.
-Please make some space
Gold medal... -Listen to another
news. One of his old employees...
...was having a weak heart and
he died few hours back
Can you please show us
the dead body
There is the bed. Let's see it
We have to take a photo.
What's the noise? This is a
hospital. Go away from here
Why are you troubling the
others? -What do you mean?
We have seen the thief in the
hospital. Go there with a force...
...and check all the covered
things well. -Are you sure?
lf you don't find the thief there,
l'll give you a gold medal
Remove the cloth from his face
lt'll not be removed. Lift him
and carry him outside
We want to take a photograph
for Press, why're you objecting?
Objecting? -Actually,
You want to have fun with
the dead body
No, l'll not allow you to take my
brother's photograph
We don't get peace even after
death -See what have you done!
Listen, it'll just take one second,
& it'll be published in newspaper
No, we don't see dead man's
face in our community
Why don't you leave, as he
is objecting
But what is there to object?
-Why not? You have no right...
...to play with people's
sentiments and beliefs
But will you object if we take a
photo of the covered dead body?
OK, take it
l'll count till three and you
uncover the face by that time
Halt your search. Come with me
l had given all the responsibility
to you. Then how could that...
...person get in there? -l don't
know anything about it, Rambabu
Don't try to fool me, you know
that my name is Ram Mullick
Please believe me. l swear, l
don't know anything.
The news is already spread that
Mayeed is dead. And Press also..
...took his photograph. lf
we get a real dead body...
...what's wrong in it?
-You are right Sir
Poison
Come with me soon
Somehow we will have
to finish him soon
He has seen everything
Aren't you the thief? You need
money, don't you?
Come, l'll give you money.
Bring all the money.
Take these money. Madan, hang
a piece of cloth there.
lf we open the door, they will
cut you to pieces. Go this way.
Thief! Thief!
Madan, go to the terrace
immediately
You also go there, & finish him
before anyone reaches there
Take this. But careful, you
shouldn't be seen -OK
Beware! lf anyone comes
forward, l'll break his head
What is my fault that you are
following me? l am the son of...
...a poor village farmer. l came
to the city in search of a job.
Being thirsty, l get inside your
flat to have few drops of water
You consider it to be my fault
and treating me like a dog...
...by calling me a thief.
But am l the real thief?
l have seen different kinds of
thieves & thefts in all the flats...
...l have entered. Right from
looting respect of a wife..
...to stealing wife's jewelleries,
printing fake notes...
...and making liquor, l have seen
all kinds of sinners & thieves
Being educated, you only want to
give me the lesson that...
...one can't be rich without being
a thief! Okay, this poor has...
...learnt today that l should be a
thief or a robber and gather...
...money by ill means and become
richer than you all by crushing...
...your heads. l will do
that for sure.
Who are you?
Are you the thief?
The door should be kept open
in the morning, otherwise...
...how will the light come inside?
What is this? You hurt your
head and it's now bleeding
Let me see it. lt's bleeding a lot
& you haven't put any medicine
Won't your mother beat you?
-l don't have a mother
What have you stolen?
-l stole nothing at all
Will you steal my bangles? l'll
not tell to anybody. Take these
l am not a thief, child.
l have never stolen anything
Wake up
When the light comes and
removes the darkness of mind
Wake up, my Lord Mohan
Wake up as the world
has woken up
Wake up, Lord Mohan. The new
age is touching your eyes
Wake up, as all the roads &
cities have woken up
Afraid? But you haven't
done anything
You will always find the
world shining...
...if you burn the lamp
in your mind.
The sunlight is making
the earth shine
And fills the thirst of
everyone yearning for light
The sunlight is making
the earth shine
And fills the thirst of
everyone yearning for light
And the mind's worries go
away and it blossoms.
Wake up, dear Lord Mohan!
The new age is touching
your eyes.
Wake up, dear Lord Mohan!
All the cities, roads
have woken up
Please wake up, Lord