"Dance Performance Of Roopkala
Student Of Dance Maestro Mangal"
Girdhar... come here.
Coming Baba.
Remove this poster.
What are you doing?
Stop it... we will
hand you over to police.
Hand over her to the
police for vulgar dances.
She claims to be my student
She is demeaning me.
She is not my student.
Please come in madam
Look old man. Don't create
a scene out here
Get away from here.
Shame on you Roopkala.
Demeaning me for money.
Look, the same poster again
Whose house is this?
Very good.
Great performance.
Don't praise this.
It's a cheap act, not dance
There is no classical touch in it.
You seems to be a dancer?
Yes. I am.
Then don't talk too much
Let's have a competition,
Bring the Tabala.
Very good... very good
Come on son let's
show them some more.
Bring the instrument.
Will you also play?
Yes sir... why not.
"It is morning and the student
has come to take Blessings
from his teacher".
This is called dance.
He is a true dancer.
Let's go son.
Was he Master Mangal?
The dance Maestro.
What! He was Master Mangal?
He is respected all
over the country.
He has won the
Bharat Natraj award
You must be aware of it, sir.
That is true, but don't
talk about that award,
My father had also participated
in the competition,
But dishonest judges
favoured Mangal.
But sir after watching
his son dancing,
I feel as if I have not
been taught properly.
Yes... But it was Mr. Mani
who wanted me to teach you.
. In just six months,
so that you could perform all over.
What else can I do in 6 months?
Mangal would not have taught
you even basics in 6 months.
I don't want to listen to
anything against Master Mangal.
You are humiliating me.
I won't come here again.
Bindiya come here
Master Mangal has just left,
go and see where is he staying?
He is living in a guest house.
Came only yesterday from Banaras.
Girdhar, how was Neela's dance?
She is a naive, Baba.
She is not an ordinary dancer son,
I could see that in her dance.
All the girls we have seen till
now,
Neela, certainly is the best.
We have little time
for the competition.
Yes. Only a year for
Nateshwer competition.
I agree, we will have
to work hard on Neela,
But hard work only
Makes future.
I request you sir,
please accept me as your student.
Is it just enthusiasm, or.
You are serious?
I am serious sir,
that is why I have come to you.
You will have to pay a
heavy Gurudakshina (tuition fee)
Why not sir...
Money, land, house, jewelry
I don't want your property.
I want hard work,
Commitment... of a true saint.
I am willing to give any test sir.
I don't have time for tests,
We have to participate
in the Nateshwer competition
There will be one solo
performance by Girdhar,
And one with a female dancer.
If it is acceptable to you.
Then I will accept you
as my student.
Baba, it is easier said than done
What does she knew
about the hardships of art?
Tell me,
what I have to do, sir?
You will have to face
hardships of practice,
There won't be time
for other things,
You won't be able to cry even.
There will be wounds in your feet
I am ready to face,
what may come.
The aspirations of youth,
love and romance...
Will be replaced by
complete devotion for art.
I am willing to live
like a saint sir.
May god give you the strength
. stick to your decision.
Your new life begins tomorrow,
god bless you.
Congratulations.
Congratulations
God bless you daughter.
Thank you,
have some sweets.
Sir, meet my friend Manilal.
A friend... and an artist also.
Let me know if she does anything
wrong
Yes... yes, why not
Girdhar you will teach Neela
her first lesson... come Neela.
Neela is inviting
trouble for herself
Not earning enough, because
she has stopped performing.
On top of that Master
Mangal's demands...
I spend 50 Rs.
For household stuff today.
Shut up. Look there, your Madam
is working hard. For art,
And you... Unnecessarily
making an issue.
Sit here, touch my feet
and take an oath... oh...
Your husband will
take care of you.
It's my turn now.
Take an oath and say.
What?
I Badalu, slave of
queen Bindiya.
You Neela's servant...
you are like a tomato...
...brinjal
...cucumber
What did you say?
Your wife will take
care of you.
Let me see,
what can you do.
I was joking.
Stop... stop please.
Hello sir...
Hello, hello
please be seated.
Manilal you will see
for yourself.
How well Neela is dancing now.
Girdhar, are you ready?
Yes let's start.
Very good. Well done,
you may go now.
Manilal. What do you think?
It was great sir.
As if Lord Krishna
and Radha were dancing.
That is what true art is.
True art or true.?
What do you mean Mani?
I see a possibility of
both of them falling...
...in love with each other.
I don't agree.
Girdhar has worked with
many beautiful girls
But he has never
crossed his limits.
Then it's fine sir...
You know it well,
I am in love with Neela.
Yes Mani... more than you
I am worried about Girdhar,
Believe me no one in our
family can think of marriage
Unless he wins the Natraj award.
They don't care about love etc.
For us carrying forward the
traditions of family is supreme.
I cant understand what you
are saying, but it's fine.
Good bye Manilal.
Very good Neela...
you performed very well
I know involvement of a
dancer is very important,
But not to the extent
of destroying one's life.
What are you talking about?
I want you to rise in
life Neela.
This is what I expect from you.
If you need some money.
Please send
Badalu to collect it.
I can do anything for you,
but don't get involved with Girdhar
Did you hear anything?
What?
Madam has decided not
to get married.
It's a good decision.
Then why did you got married?
My story is different.
It was a gamble for me.
What...?
It's a different matter that
both of us have won this gamble.
You got a nice husband, and I
got a wife, one in millions.
Leave me... you naughty.
Why did you stop?
Where did you learn it from?
I worked as a driver for a
British officer,
I learnt it there.
I have taught Bindiya
a little bit of it,
but it's not a good dance.
Why?
No Madam you won't
be able to do it.
Why, I would like to see
and dance... you start.
This is very easy...
...come join us
Neela...
Mani are you drunk?
Sir that dance is such, that you
feel as if you are drunk,
Certainly you are a
great teacher,
you taught them Western dance too.
Western dance...?
Never. It's a sin.
May be, but it's great.
Girdhar, you have come
down to this stage?
What a cheap dance?
What is wrong with you?
Ooh. My leg...
What are you staring
at... help him.
You are a bad man.
Try to understand, Neela.
Get this ointment ready,
don't make it too hot
OK I will also come with you.
Forgive me Girdhar it's
all because of me.
Don't be silly.
I know Girdhar It's
difficult. Alas!
I could have shared
it with you.
Your words are enough.
Now there is no pain.
I know it's painful son.
My heart is also crying.
Whenever I beat you I
start cursing myself,
I should have not done it
but what do I do,
I want you to win
thenNatraj award.
Why are you crying,
he will be fine.
Bindiya... food is ready? What's
the matter Badalu?
Need some money Madam,
can I ask Mr. Mani?
NO... no. No question of taking
money from him henceforth.
You work so hard Madam,
you must take some rest
This is what gives
me satisfaction.
What are you trying to do?
I was trying to walk... see.
What are you doing... Don't move.
Why not? I can walk.
Take care. Don't get impatient.
Sing a song Neela.
For the Mahashivratari Festival...
I am going to Benaras,
today itself
What about me, Baba?
I will also come along
You should take rest son,
I will be back soon
I will also get the
dance costumes for you.
Neela. Continue your rehearsals.
Put these things in Tonga,
...take this also.
God bless you,
take care of yourself.
Neela.
How did you make out.
It's me?
My heart said so.
It's in the wind,
I can listen to it.
It seems no rehearsal today.
Who said so...?
It's in the wind,
I can listen to it.
It's not like that.
But if you want then.
There won't be any.
But why...?
Where are your eyes?
Here
What is that?
My feet.
And below them?
Earth.
And above the earth...?
Both of us.
I am asking you what is that?
Oh. This... colors,
But who has done this?
Me... It was a new dance map.
You should have told me earlier
Anyway, get away from here now.
Not that side... this way.
I worked so hard on it,
you have spoiled it all
I am sorry.
What sorry.?
Get away from here.
No rehearsal today Madam?
No... I am not feeling well
I am feeling very sad today.
What should I do?
Go to sleep or take
a stroll, simple.
This is not possible I
can't leave her alone.
Oh... I only came to
pluck some mangos.
Mangos are there.
How is she now?
Fine... she is going for a walk.
For a walk? Alone?
She is going with me.
With you...? Badalu we
will also go for a walk.
Towards the river... Sir?
No... yes to the river side.
Badalu, ask them to go
somewhere else.
Don't disturb us.
Go somewhere else.
Tell them we are not
going to leave this place.
We won't leave this place.
We will dance here.
We will also dance.
We are not going,
we will also dance.
Tell them not to tease
us like that.
Don't tease us otherwise
Madam will get angry.
Madam never said so,
it's your own interpretation.
Don't make me angry.
Keep your maid in control,
she is very short- tempered.
You also keep this bear in control.
Tell her, that I am waiting
I am not waiting for you,
I am waiting for Neela.
She is not at home.
Gone for a walk.
For a walk. Alone!
Not alone, with Girdhar
I don't care with whom! But
Whenever I come she is not at home.
Hello sir.
Hello, don't touch it.
How was your journey?
It was fine! I was more
worried about Neela"s rehearsal,
Hope everything was ok.
Yes. Yes, they are
out on a walk.
This is no time for walk...
Time is just fine sir.
What do you mean?
Very simple! Evening time
is best for romance.
Look Mani,
don't try to instigate me
against Neela and Girdhar.
I have full faith in Girdhar.
I too, but don't forget,
they are young.
Anyway. Goodbye.
Hello Baba.
God bless you,
what about rehearsal?
Neela is not well.
So we went out for a walk.
No rehearsal in my absence?
She did it, Baba.
For which dance?
Tandava of Lord Shiva...?
No Baba...
Oh...! Then Mani was right.
Do you know, why I have
been to Benaras?
For the festival and costumes.
Look, here are these costumes.
This is our tradition,
To carry forward it,
should be your objective
This objective will
never be completed,
if you waste your time
with Neela like this.
I am sorry.
I know... she is
responsible for this.
Don't ever repeat it. Otherwise
we will leave this place.
What is the matter Neela?
White dress and looking sad.?
Today we will practice,
the dance of "separation".
It will suit you also.
"Girl is waiting for her beloved
but he did not come".
Tell me Girdhar,
Baba is angry with me?
No
"Then she got hopeless. And started
throwing away her ornaments".
Don't hide from me,
is it true that you are
going to leave this house?
Don't be silly...
you don't know the truth.
Then tell me the truth.
Sir is only saying, we
should not waste our time
otherwise, he will leave this house.
Don't get angry.
Look at me, don't cry.
Do you have some time?
. I want to talk to you.
Having nice time with Girdhar
these days? And why not?
After all both of you
are living together.
Now onwards both of them,
are going to stay with me.
Why. What is your problem...?
I can't tolerate your
love for Girdhar,
He will only come
here for rehearsals.
I won't allow you to do so.
This is what I want.!
I have always taken care of you,
I don't want to hurt my feelings.
But I never accepted your love.
Maybe! But I helped you a lot.
I thought you are a gentleman.
But now, I know what you are.
I am not a coward.
You have proved it,
and listen.
Girdhar and Baba will stay here
if you don't like it. Then.
Then I should not come here
that is all you want to say.
But I can't forget you Neela.
Don't touch me...
Go, your god is waiting for you,
but remember only I can help you.
Your intimate conversation
is over?
Oh... you are jealous.
...but why do you care?
You are going to leave my house
Don't talk rubbish...
it hurts me.
Oh. What a surprise!
You also have a heart.?
If you talk like this.
I will leave this house.
The way Lord Shiva left Parvati?
And then,
Parvati searched for Shiva,
dressed up like a tribal woman.
I too found you.
Neela...
Baba...
Drink the milk...
...and go to sleep.
Baba will there be
rehearsal tomorrow?
Yes! But for a different dance.
"Saint Vishwamitra prayed for
thousands of years
And cast his
indelible imprint on the world.
By
virtue of his prayers power.
Vishwamitra created a
world of his own.
He challenged Lord Indra,
Out of fear Lord Indra sent
the most beautiful and clever
Fairy of the heaven... Menaka".
Neela are you ready?
Neela. You have spoiled 20 years
hard work of Girdhar.
Why would I do that...?
For yourself...
Is it not true
that you have entangled
Girdhar in your love?
Not at all sir.
I swear my love is sacred.
Swearing again!
You don't feel ashamed...?
Don't forget, your promise,
that you will be committed to dance
Only. And will not involved
in absurd things like... Love.
Let's go Girdhar we won't stay
here even for a minute.
No Baba, I love Neela.
What! You are in love
with Neela?
Then what about dance...?
I can't live without Neela.
You fool... get out from here.
He is in love with Neela,
What should not have happened,
has happened.
I have lost the battle.
Don't say like this sir.
First I lost his mother,
now you have snatched
Girdhar from me
Why did you do that.?
If you say. I will
stop meeting him.
That won't help.
I will go away from here.
He will become a wanderer,
and search you
In every corner of the world.
I am ready to give up my life.
So you want to burden
me with a sin...?
Then... what do I do sir?
Now you cant do anything,
I myself have to do something.
What is that?
I will go somewhere.
But sir... what about your dreams?
Your expectations?
Your dancing bells have
destroyed my dreams,
now with the ashes
of my dreams,
I will go and sit on
Girdhar's mothers memorial.
Oh my god... What should I do?
Neela...
Neela where are you going...?
Come... I will drop you.
No... Wait Mani, I am coming.
Going with him again?
Yes! After all he is
a old friend.
Then. Why this... hypocrisy?
You have betrayed me.
You may say so.
Shameless women!
Baba...
I will also come.
You were right,
she has betrayed me.
Forgive your son Baba.
Cool down son.
I will get my luggage,
Don't worry about the competition,
we will find someone else.
Thank god! We got rid of them.
But what will happen to Madam.?
She will marry... Manilal.
You don't know the matters of
heart,
Because you don't have one.
My heart... You will see
that I was right.
Let me call Madam.
Stop it here.
I want to get down.
What is this?
I was only fooling Girdhar.
First you make a fool of him,
now me. What is this nonsense?
You are ditching me.
Yes. I have ditched you all.
I am ditching to my own self.
You go away
...otherwise I will
jump into the river.
Go to hell
You betrayer!
No I am not, my love is sacred,
Spotless... I am not a betrayer.
Let the world say. Whatever
it wants to say
But you cannot say so.
I am not a hypocrite.
You betrayer! Hypocrite!
No I am not.
For god sake, keep quiet.
You are very lucky,
god saved you.
Why did you save me god?
You should have called
me to your abode.
Don't say such things. Good lady.
Don't call me good lady.
I have given pain to people.
I don't deserved mercy,
I am a sinner.
Please come. Have a seat,
let me call her.
Oh. It's you?
Yes sir your old student,
Roopkala.
What are you doing.
Touch his feet.
Forgive me sir.
Cant forgive you...
you had destroyed
my hard work, for money
I have no place for you.
Have mercy on us, give her
one more chance, please sir.
Sir, you hardly have time
to groom someone else,
You have worked a lot upon her.
Ok, as you wish.
Madam...
What are you doing here.?
I was searching for you Madam.
I am tired.
You will be tired, if you
continue wandering like this.
It's not wandering around.
It's sacrifice.
Don't spoil your life...
I may have spoiled my life but,
I have found my heart
in his memory.
Till he wins Nateshwar award,
I shall remain like this.
But for that, you have
to survive.
Don't worry about me.
I have come here to take
another chance,
You still have time.
Don't waste your life.
I am not wasting my life.
My love is sacred.
It cannot be a one sided affair.
I don't care, he must
win the award,
That is all what I want.
(remember only after winning the
award,
he will think about marriage)
Are you sure, that he will win?
I have full faith in his
talent and my prayers.
I am willing to sacrifice
my life for him.
If you do that, what will
happen to me?
I will see to it,
that he should not win.
Where are you...
Have you gone mad?
I don't feel like dancing.
What are you saying...? Get up.
Neela...
Are you talking to me?
Yes.
But I am not Neela,
I am a devotee of Lord Krishna.
I can't forget you. Neela.
You need peace,
this restlessness...
Will not give you anything.
You are my life Neela,
let's go somewhere else,
Far from here...
...to fulfill our dreams.
Come to your senses.
Concentrate on your dance.
These preachings don't suit you,
You are playing another game
to make fool of someone else.
I will kill you.
Stop it Girdhar... you fool,
if you kill her,
You will be hanged.
May what come... I will
finish her right now.
Stop it... cool down.
Today you are saved, but,
if I see you again,
I shall finish you.
Why are you adamant to
destroy him.? Get lost.
I am going away, you will
not see me again,
Even the news of my death
will not reach you.
Madam has disappeared again.
Again... where she
would have gone?
I am looking for her
since last 4 days.
Let's not waste any time...
Let's go and search her.
We are lucky Badalu, perhaps
we can use his car.
But how?
Just see.
What is the matter?
Madam has disappeared again,
I ask him everyday to search,
And I call her every day,
come on.
Is there enough fuel in it?
Yes...
Don't worry you will
find your car somewhere.
Wait... wait... where
are you going?
Stop... please stop.
What is the matter?
There lying a woman,
unconscious,
Please take her to the city.
No thank you sir...
one woman is enough for me.
I say stop! Oh...
Madam. Madam
She is your Madam?
I am Bindiya, let's go home.
You are looking very ill Madam.
Yes...! I know I won't survive
. but before I die.
I want to meet him for once.
They say everybody
dies empty handed
Weather my desires shall
also remain unfulfilled?
Don't let this happen.
Where do you want to go Madam?
Nateshwer temple.
Attention! All and sundry,
The chief is coming.
Ladies and gentleman since
last many days,
Nateshwar competition is in
progress,
Those who have participated,
have been defeated
By Master Mangal's son Girdhar.
There is no one to compete
with him now, therefore...
Stop...
Competition is not yet over,
There is another artist
to compete with Girdhar
Mr. Ramprasad from Agara.
Good... now we will see
the battle between these two.
One who wins, will be the
claimant for the duet dance.
And will have the opportunity
to win Natraj award.
Please start.
Girdhar my son, go ahead...
If you defeat him, I will
give you Rs. 5,000.
Not 5,000, I want 10,000.
You start first.
Very good...
great...
Well done...
Strange!
What happened?
Medicines are not effective, but,
With the sound of dancing bells
she is becoming conscious.
Very good... Great performance.
Friends today is the last
day of the competition,
Now Girdhar will perform
Tandav dance with Roopkala.
After this there will be Pooja
dance, and in the end,
The award will be given.
I cant betray him...
Then betray yourself. I am giving
you Rs. 15,000... think again.
You won't be able to earn
this much of money,
Throughout your life.
"Centuries ago when the world
was dominated by torture and sin.
Then Lord Shiva got angry.
He started Tandava to
destroy the world,
Gods and human being, both went
to Goddess Parvati,
Without caring for her life
Parvati went to Lord Shiva
and pacified him".
This is the story behind
Tandava dance.
Now you will see Girdhar and
Roopkala,
as Shiva and Parvati.
What are you doing Roop.
Come to your senses.
I have not come here...
to listen to your abuses,
I am going.
Forgive us. Because of ill health
Roop is unable to perform
Girdhar will play Shiva and Parvati
. simultaneously.
But this is not possible.
Sir I request to give
Ramprasd one more chance,
He is ready with his partner.
Friends since Girdhar is unable
to perform.
The opportunity is given to
Ramprasad.
Girdhar... Vacate the stage.
He will not go...
I will dance with him
you?
Baba?
You don't worry about me.
Start the dance.
"Tandav dance created
havoc on the earth.
The earth was crumbling".
What are you doing Girdhar?
Go away.
"Then Parvati requested Lord
Shiva"
Whatever I did was for
you only,
I want you to win this award,
Trust me Girdhar.
"Finally Shiva cooled down
and handed over the trident to
Parvati".
We have witnessed a
great performance,
The Nateshwar award is
given to Girdhar.
Where are you going Neela?
My mission is over.
You have helped Girdhar
winning the award,
You have fulfilled your
duty of a true student,
Lord Nateshwar is also happy,
but where is my Dakshina (fee)
I will do whatever you say.
Now onwards you will serve the
cause of art as man and wife.