This film is based on some
incidents in Mirza Ghalib's life...
in which, many imaginary incidents...
and characters have been included.
They should therefore, not
be deemed real or historic.
Year 1833 B.C., the capital of
the Moghul empire, Delhi...
which, since the times
of the Pandavs...
had been captured
and looted many times.
And every time, the hands of man,
that never accept defeat...
rebuilt it even more beautifully.
The Qutub Minar, like the always
rising passion in the heart...
trying to touch the sky,
and speaking poetically.
Jama Masjid, shows the way
to those gone astray.
The Red Fort,
a symbol of Moghul grandeur.
Every building, every street,
every corner, was young.
Every stone was beautiful.
But regretfully,the revolutionary
world didn't like its style...
and the Sun of the Moghul empire,
after ruling for 400 years...
was now setting.
The last ray of this sun, the last
king of the Moghul empire...
was King Bahadur Shah Zafar,
in whose court...
were famous poets like...
Sheikh lbrahim Zauk, Balmukund
Huzur, Momin Khan Momin,
Fazruddin Khan Adrullah,
Mustafa Khan Sheista...
Shahjahan Aish and
Mohammed Ali Tishna.
They all were renowned poets.
There was another flame apart
from these poets...
who wanted to brighten every corner
of the world with his light.
'Even a gesture is enough'
'As the love grows,
so does the silence'
l wonder where he is spreading
his words again.
He's gone both day and night.
He doesn't even care that
he has a wife at home.
Why don't you speak?
Look at me!
Allah! You are composing
poetry. Sorry.
Coming, father.
Yes, father.
Did you find out where
your husband is?
He is at home.
He hasn't left home for four days.
Do support your husband,
but don't lie to your father.
l haven't seen his
face for five days.
Let me see what he's doing.
We'll be late
for the poetry recital.
He's composing for the recital.
l just saw him.
He must be cursing his own destiny.
l haven't come across
a more unfortunate man.
He has let so many good
opportunities go.
lf this continues, he'll
make you beg one day.
He'll even squander away
his ancestral wealth.
What a man l let marry
my beautiful daughter!
He is not at all worthy of her.
- Greetings father.
- Greetings. Where are you going?
To the fort. Won't you come
for the poetry recital?
l'm not sure.
Did you finish composing?
lt died on the composing table.
Oh God...
Attention!
The scion of the Moghul empire...
King Bahadur Shah Zafar...
the King of Hindustan, is coming.
- Greetings.
Begin the poetry recital.
lnvitees, we begin the recital...
with poetry composed by the King.
Hear it with respect.
'ln love, l do not
have this complaint'
'That l am left with no peace of mind'
'Sorrow has become my friend'
'l don't care whether or not
l have anyone
else to call my own'
'When realization had not dawned...'
'l would always notice others'
faults and qualities'
'But when l realized
the faults in me...'
'l saw no more the faults in others'
'Zafar says, he is not a man...'
'however renowned he may be...'
'the one who has forgotten
God in his good days'
'Who is so proud,
that he does not fear God?'
lnvitees, the lamp is now being placed
before Mufti Saddruddin Khan.
Please hear his compositions.
- Do l have your permission?
- Proceed.
l recite...
'When have l not been infamous?'
'When is the sky not the earth,
and the earth not the sky?'
'l want to say one thing,
but say something else...'
'and then call it a slip of the tongue'
Lala Balmukund Huzur.
'No strength in my legs,
no power in my hands...'
'that can help me pull
the hand of my beloved'
'l am sitting in the street'
'You are beside me...'
'when l have no one else'
Hazrat Momin Khan Momin.
'She is not affected'
'You are close to me'
'No one else is there'
Hold your breath. lt's my turn.
The flame is being brought
before lbrahim Zouk.
Hear with rapt attention.
The opening lines are...
Begin.
'Now l fear and say l will die'
'But if l don't find peace even
after l die, where will l go?'
'l am not among those
who claim to have you'
'ln fact, even if God asks
me, l will deny it'
You are simply great.
Mirza Assadullah Khan.
Alias, Mirza Nausha,
whose pen name is Ghalib.
- Now l will recite my poetry.
- Proceed.
Begin.
- l begin.
- Yes.
'Even a gesture is enough'
'As the love grows,
so does the silence'
Wow, that's lovely.
'She has never understood,
nor will she ever understand me'
'Why did l have to give my
heart to someone like that?'
lt's a gathering of thankless men.
'There are many good
poets in the world'
'lt's just that Ghalib's
style is different'
We don't want to hear
this self praise.
Damn such self praise!
Get lost!
- l won't stay here now.
- That will be insulting the gathering.
You don't care about my being insulted.
Even the king doesn't.
l'm leaving.
- Let's go.
- Where?
Anywhere, but take
me away from here.
Away from this gathering
of uncouth, ungrateful men.
- Very far away.
- Lift it... careful... turn right.
My heart is full of woe
l cannot but tell her
Why try somewhere...
when nothing can be done?
My heart is full of woe
A stranger roams with your letters
lf someone asks what this is all about...
l won't be able to hide it
My heart is full of woe
l do call her...
but, oh, my heart's full of emotions
lt should affect her such...
that she cannot stop
herself from coming
My heart is full of woe
No one can control love.
lt is such a fire
lt is slow to ignite...
but once lit,
it can't be doused
My heart is full of woe...
but once lit,
it can't be doused
He has come.
Mother, he has come.
Who are you?
What do you want?
l don't want anything.
l want to meet somebody.
Who is it dear?
He wants to meet someone, mother.
Who does he want to meet?
Who do you want to meet?
The one who was reciting
Mirza's poetry.
He says the one who was
reciting Mirza's poetry.
Who is he?
What kind of a man is he?
Does a decent man come to
anyone's home at this hour?
Mother says which decent man comes
to anyone's home at this hour?
l am a decent man. l'm a poet.
l'm returning from...
the Royal poetry recital.
You are coming from the Royal
poetry recital? You heard Mirza's poetry?
He was going to recite poetry there.
Come. Why are you standing outside?
You are coming from the poetry
recital? You heard Mirza's poetry?
Did you hear him yourself?
How is his voice?
How does he recite?
Does he sing it?
The King must have been
all praise for him.
He must have bowled over everyone.
No one could have competed with him.
Pardon me, l showered you with
questions the moment you came.
Please come.
Please come, sit down.
What kind of a man is Mirza?
l mean, looks wise.
What about his nature?
- You don't say anything.
- When have you let me speak?
Sorry. Please speak.
l am returning from the recital.
l heard Mirza's poetry.
- He writes well.
- Didn't l say so, Mother?
He has a soft face.
He's fair, tall, handsome.
But he has an attitude.
He is quick to anger,
and takes long to calm down.
Lies! Absolute lies!
You speak as if you have seen Mirza.
So what if l've not seen him,
but l have read and heard about him.
He is such a good poet.
lf l could, l'd talk about
him in every street.
Really? Say the word and
l'll call him.
But we are poor people.
Why would he meet us?
He must not even be aware of us.
This is his couplet.
'l agree you won't
betray me, but...'
'l will be dead by
the time you know'
God! What is this girl doing!
lf they hear you,
what will people say?
Come on now, Mother!
Madam, even l am a poet.
Though an inconsequential one.
With your permission,
may l recite something?
What do you say?
Proceed.
l begin...
'Even a gesture is enough'
'As the love grows,
so does the silence'
lt's okay.
'She has never understood,
nor will she ever understand me'
'Why did l have to give my
heart to someone like that?'
- Here, have betel leaf.
- l am like that only.
You don't appreciate my poetry.
l thank you for the betel leaf.
lt's not that. Your poetry is okay.
But you should realize there's
something special about Mirza.
Maybe. l only know...
that his ancestors
were good marksmen.
Mirza must be good at
wielding a stick.
Pardon me, but please don't talk
like that in my presence.
He should do as his ancestors.
Poetry is not his cup of tea.
- Please leave!
- What?
l said leave!
Poetry is not his cup of tea.
As if he understands poetry!
He's blind, and is called doe eyed!
'l had heard of humiliations, but...'
'l left your home badly humiliated'
- Whatever, but he was our guest.
- We don't want such a guest.
Look at his daring!
He was talking ill about
Mirza in my presence.
l could have pushed
him from up here.
Kotwal Saheb!
Give me Mirza's poetry.
- You still need Mirza's poetry?
- What do you mean?
Why wouldn't l need his poetry?
When Mirza has himself
started coming here...
then why do you need his poetry?
Congratulations on his coming here.
Mirza's coming here?
Are you out of your mind?
Mother, did you hear what
Kotwal Saheb is saying?
We don't even know him.
Then how did l see Mirza
leaving your house?
- lt must be Mirza's ghost.
- Don't talk like that.
Why should it be his ghost?
May he live long.
Give me Mirza's poetry.
'Even a gesture is enough...'
Oh my God!
'There are many good
poets in the world'
'lt's just that Ghalib's
style is different'
Mother! Hold me! What have l done!
How much l humiliated Mirza.
And he got annoyed and left.
There won't be a more
unfortunate woman than l.
God himself came to my door,
and l turned him away.
l wasn't hospitable,
nor did l welcome him.
Such people don't come everyday.
They are not the sun or moon
to rise and set everyday.
- Greetings father.
- Bless you.
Wait! Where are you coming from
so early in the morning?
- From the poetry recital.
- The one that ended at 1 AM?
lt is morning now.
Where were you for so long?
l met friends. We sat chatting
and it got late.
Great. Alright, what accolades
did you win at the recital?
None. There were so many others.
Why are you coughing?
When you arrive, just walk in.
l'm coming.
Let me remove my shoes first.
The Koran has been read
here all night.
There are mats somewhere,
and a wash bowl somewhere.
The room seems like a mosque.
How can a sinner like me...
enter the room of a pious wife
wearing my shoes?
Don't make excuses.
Tell me the truth.
Did Allah answer my prayers?
Were you successful
at the poetry recital?
Only you and your Allah know that.
There were only two people
who appreciated it.
Mr. Mufti and Nawab Sheikhda.
God bless them.
Your enemies?
They are not my enemies.
l was only unsuccessful.
Very unsuccessful.
l was already reeling from humiliation,
and then father chided me.
Don't mind his words,
it's his habit.
That's alright, but l won't
stay here any longer.
Tomorrow, Miyan sir is
renting out his house.
What do you say?
What can l say?
l will go wherever you go.
l will be at your feet.
Dear, had you not been there...
l don't know what l would
have done to myself.
Come, Mirza, come.
What are you doing?
Great, great.
l'm fed up with your goat.
Come on. Great, great.
Mr. Khan, my wife too thanks you.
What of thanks, Mirza, the house
was lying empty anyway.
- lt has life again, now that
you've come. - Thanks.
Tell me. Do you need any money?
No, thank you. God has
been kind to me.
l get Rs. 2,000 per annum from
the British government.
We manage to survive
with that money.
And then, l have many
friends in Agra.
Hello Mirza.
Mathuradas! What brings you here?
- Sir, my money...
- Yes... yes, l understand.
Mr. Kale, excuse me.
My money...
Speak softly! l'll repay your
every penny. Have patience.
How patient can l be?
You have only sent me
two installments.
lt's been five months since then
and you haven't sent a single penny.
ln our religion, it is said...
that if someone takes
even a copper coin...
and doesn't repay it, he has to
pay a gold coin in Allah's court.
- Why do you need to worry now?
- Spoken like a poet again!
l will not go to Allah.
l will go to Bhagwan (God).
Go wherever you like,
but spare me now.
- When do l come again?
- Go now, at least, return later.
Alright, but l won't wait
too long for the money.
Mirza Nausha, why did the
money lender come here?
For no reason.
He's an old friend from Agra.
He has some of my deposits.
He wanted me to take them back.
He said the interest
is too much for him.
- Okay. Good day.
- Good day.
What a time you chose to come,
Mahajan (money lender).
Oh, it's you?
How much money have you collected
with the money lender?
Buy me gold bangles.
l will, when you beget a son.
As if l didn't sire any.
But if they died as soon
as they were born...
how am l to be blamed for it?
- You are very quick-witted.
- Yes, l'm the only quick-witted one.
You are very naive.
- Where are you going now?
- To change my taste.
Mr. Mufti has given an invitation
to eat mangoes.
Wow! The country which
grows mangoes...
why won't other countries
eye it with envy?
- They are so sweet.
- Even sugarcane is sweet.
Now come on, Nawab!
'Ask me, what do you know'
'Compared to mangoes,
sugarcane is nothing'
Sugarcane is only sweet.
But there is a slight tanginess
in a mango's sweetness.
Like a woman who is beautiful,
and a little tangy too.
Mangoes may be tasty, but
they are not that good.
Look, even donkeys don't eat them.
Those who are donkeys
don't eat them.
l'll recite a couplet in praise of mangoes.
Go ahead.
'The mango is the king of fruits'
Even the couplet on mangoes
is so complex.
l ask, why don't you
write simple poetry?
One earns praise only if
his poetry is understood.
Or he's not considered
a poet at all.
Which fool wants to
be praised by fools?
'l don't care for praise'
'lf l don't have any admirers,
l don't care'
l am reminded of the words of
the late Mir Faisal about him.
He said that if he
finds a good admirer...
he'll become a great poet.
- Or he'll be a nonentity.
-You are my good admirer, Mr. Mufti.
Even a gesture is enough
As the love grows,
so does the silence
He has never understood,
nor will he ever understand me
Why did l have to give my
heart to someone like that?
When you are in the city,
l won't have any problems
l'll go to the bazaar...
Mir has made this poet famous.
Beggars are singing his poems.
Listen!
From whom did you learn this song?
You can say it's God's gift.
A girl lives in my neighborhood.
She takes mercy on this
poor man and teaches me...
so that l can make a living.
- What is her name?
- Her name is Moti Begum.
But why does she calls herself
Chaudvin Begum these days?
Whenever she sings, she only
sings Mirza's poetry.
What is your opinion of Mirza?
'There are many good
poets in the world'
'lt's just that Ghalib's
style is different'
'There are many good
poets in the world'
'lt's just that Ghalib's
style is different'
- Good day, Mr. Mufti.
- Where are you going, Mirza?
Where my poetry is understood.
Strange man.
Get lost! Why are you shouting?
You don't even let me
rest at all.
Alright then, take rest. Mirza
is waiting at the door.
- Honest?
- l swear by you.
He's the same man
from the other day.
l am wearing such dirty clothes.
Mother, get me a
good set of clothes.
Keep him busy with conversation
for awhile and then bring him up.
Okay.
Fix my hair, mother.
Fix it yourself,
l'm not your servant.
His coming to our house
every day isn't right.
People will talk.
l'll be glad. Maybe something
clicks between us.
Mirza! Please come in.
'He has come to my house.
lt is God's grace'
'l sometimes look at him,
and sometimes at my house'
l wouldn't go uninvited even
to God's home. But...
'But it should affect him such...'
'that he cannot stop
himself from coming'
You can assume that.
l met the beggar who was
singing my composition.
And found your invitation in it.
So l came.
What do l say about your kindness?
l said so many things
about you that day.
No. You said all that to the
one who came that day.
You praised me. ln fact, you
fought with me for me.
lf it were only that it would've
been okay. But l...
Threw me out of the house.
You did very well.
The 'l' that was between the
two of us, has gone.
lt is only us who have remained.
l am hers, what about me...
You are such a great man, Mirza.
l thought l wouldn't be spared
in the two worlds.
- How do l thank you?
- Don't say that, Chaudvin Begum.
You consider yourself inconsequential?
But it's not your fault.
Even you are among those who
don't know their worth.
A stone in the street is
not considered worthy.
lf noticed,
even a stone is a diamond.
lf unnoticed,
even a diamond is a stone.
Ask me what you are.
l was dejected with life...
and complaining to God.
'Serve me a drink, oh bartender'
'lf you hate me so,
don't give me a goblet'
'At least give me liquor'
l heard you reciting
my composition...
when l was feeling so low.
And l felt l had found
my lost destination.
Yes Chaudvin. Even today, the
situation was the same.
l had problems at home,
and was shunned by my friends.
l have come here. l feel lost.
lntroduce me to myself again.
Mirza, l had this desire for ages...
that l sing your composition
in your presence.
l wish l had asked for more
from Allah today.
Yes Moti Begum. Look what
l have bought for you.
Some trinkets for you.
They are better than his couplets.
But there are some couplets...
which even your entire
wealth cannot buy.
This one coin can buy
all your poetry.
Try it!
Kotwal Saheb! You
have come. Welcome!
Yes madam, and l have even brought
a gift for your daughter.
Jewelry! Wow! lt's beautiful.
Not Moti Begum, Chaudvin Begum!
You dare to flirt with Mirza
in my presence...
and make fun of my love?
Don't you know who l am? l have
taught many like you a lesson.
l am the Kotwal (police
chief) of Delhi city.
Kotwal, don't mind her, she's crazy.
- Maybe, but l'm not his slave.
- Damn you, girl!
You compare the Kotwal
with that petty poet?
You should thank your stars...
that such an important man
is interested in you.
Or who cares for us small people?
- lf you marry, it will only be to him.
- No, l won't marry him!
l am a girl,
not a criminal to be flogged.
Have you heard, elder sis?
ls this your decision?
Constable sir,
what do l do with this girl?
She has just learned to fly.
Her craziness over Mirza will
be gone in a few days.
l'll take care of Mirza.
- You fix the marriage date.
- Anything to suit you.
Will Friday be alright?
So soon? lt's already Monday today.
What have you got to do?
l'll spend money, l'll make
all the arrangements.
And remember, On Friday,
l will come as a groom...
and take my bride away.
The bride is going to her groom.
She need not fear anyone now
My husband is a police chief
l am the beloved of my husband
One look, and l pierce his heart
My hands are red with henna
My husband is a police chief
As a bride, l develop an attitude
l don't meet anyone's eyes now
No one can dare to look at me
My husband is a police chief
l will rule in my husband's home
l won't fear my mother-in-law
or sister-in-law
l will throw out my brother-in-law
My husband is a police chief
The bride is going to her groom.
She need not fear anyone now
My husband is a police chief
- Fittan!
- What is it, madam?
Deliver this letter for me.
- Yes.
- You just take the letter and leave?
Did you ask who it's addressed to,
or where you it's to be delivered?
Madam, it is for Mirza, who else?
What do you think of Fittan,
madam, l know everything.
l taste opium, but l keep tabs
even on seventh heaven.
Fittan sir, where are you going?
Won't this betel leaf be eaten today?
No, today l am going for
a very important...
l swear on God! l can't take
my eyes off you today.
These beautiful bangles
on the fair wrists.
Laces on the scarf.
Oh, my heart trembles.
You prepare the betel leaf.
l'll be right back.
Why don't you eat it?
What is so urgent?
- You don't know. The work is such.
- Really?
Yes, today no devil
or fairy can stop me today.
Damn! l've come across
the devil's home again.
Where have you been, Fittan?
Come, let's share a smoke.
Don't mention it! l hate it!
And l even hate to see
others smoke drugs.
What is life without a smoke?
Damn! l'll have to inhale some now.
But only once, don't insist
that l stay long.
Just puff. lf you insist on more,
God will take care of you.
l won't.
l have some important business
to attend to.
Keep going.
Come, Fittan! Tipu,
even you have come?
- Moti, has Fittan returned?
- No.
l sent him on Tuesday and
it's Thursday today.
l wonder where he disappeared
with the letter.
- Hello.
- You dropped your letter.
- Letter? Letter?
l was supposed to deliver this.
Damn me!
l wasted so much time.
But it's not late yet.
Late for what?
Come and have a smoke.
No, l'll be going. lt's Tuesday
today, we'll meet next Tuesday.
'God bless this city'
'lt's now Thursday night'
Thursday night?
'Oh gentleman, hear my plea'
'God will bless you with riches'
'Give some alms to this beggar'
'lt's now Thursday night'
Wait! What nonsense are you saying?
lt's not Thursday night.
-You can't make any day Thursday.
- Today is Thursday.
- Don't try to fool me!
- Any problem, Fittan?
No. He claims today is Thursday.
Thursday, are you crazy?
lt's Tuesday today.
Ask for a copper coin,
today is Tuesday.
- Yes, it's Tuesday today.
- God help them.
Attention!
A fair has been organized in Meerut
tomorrow, that is, Friday.
Traders can sell their
wares at the fair.
lf today is Thursday night, where
did Wednesday disappear?
l'm wondering the same thing.
Now l understand!
That day was Tuesday.
Yes.
- We slept through Wednesday.
- Yes.
And we regained our senses
on Thursday night.
lt's Thursday night.
Please give some alms.
Here, take a coin.
You win, l lose.
- Thank God it's Thursday night.
- God bless you.
Not Friday. l have an
important errand.
Damn!
What's the matter, Kallu?
Why is the door not opening?
Wonder what the matter is.
First, my father-in-law used
to stop me, then my wife.
Now even the doors and walls
have begun to stop me.
Sir, someone is sleeping
at the door.
- Hey get up! Who are you?
- Me? l am Fittan.
- What day is it today?
- Friday.
Friday! Damn!
Thank Allah!
l've brought this letter for you.
l didn't want to be late,
so l came in the early morning.
'Greetings. l don't know why
l am sending you this letter'
'l know l have no right on you'
'No right to tell you my woes'
'For 2000 takkas, my mother
is selling me to the Kotwal'
'l am against this alliance'
'You are a poet. You understand pain'
'Won't you help me?'
'Right now, when everyone, young and old,
is showering me with advice...'
'l seek recourse in your couplets'
'What friendship is this?'
'l have no one with whom
to share my sorrow'
'Yours, Chaudvin'
What reply do l give?
Say l got the letter.
Leave the reply to fate.
Alright.
Welcome Mirza! You are not
to be seen here these days.
You hardly come here.
What do l say?
You need money to come here.
You don't have to worry about money.
Write one more couplet.
There will be money.
lt is not that, l have the money.
Let's see what happens. Whenever
l've played in my name, l've lost.
l'll play in someone
else's name today.
- Six!
- lt's six!
- ln whose name do you play?
- A lover's.
Fittan, what happened?
Where were you?
Did you give him the letter?
Did he throw it away?
Did he tear it up?
- No.
- Did he give a reply?
Oh yes he did.
He said leave the reply to fate.
- He didn't say anything else?
- No madam.
No?
Nausha, you were not like this.
What is this? No one leaves
the game after winning.
You are nuts. ln fact, a loser
doesn't leave the game.
-l won't let you leave like that.
-No Naushad, l have to go.
Alright then, on one condition.
Promise you will play
a game with me again.
- l accept that.
- Good night then.
Madam, the marriage procession
has left the groom's home.
What? And we are not yet ready.
Wonder where all the girls are.
Even l won't help when they
are getting married.
How much can a lone woman do?
The story is over.
l had thought of such a long story...
that listeners will stay awake,
listening with rapt attention.
And l only will fall
asleep narrating it.
Fittan!
Damn! Go some place else with
that lime, you fatso!
You made me sober with it.
- You also lick some.
- Get lost!
Where is my opium box?
- Take.
- Get lost!
What nonsense is this!
Give that to me!
- No.
- Madam, madam! Come quickly!
You have my promise, don't stop me.
Release my hand.
Have you gone crazy?
Yes, l have. l won't marry
that wolf! Leave me.
- What happened?
- Take care of your bride.
She was taking opium.
Oh my God! What were
you going to do?
How was l to know you
loved Mirza so much.
l don't want to live.
l'm sorry, dear. l am
your mother after all.
Consider my age. Damn that Kotwal!
Damn his money and jewelry.
Fittan, go stop the
marriage procession.
- But it has already left.
- So what? Stop it wherever it is.
l don't want any marriage,
l want my daughter.
Move! l'll go myself
and stop that rascal.
- Madam.
- Mirza!
You have come!
How nice you are!
How nice you are, too,
that you're selling your daughter.
Your hapless child. Being a mother,
you are selling her to a rascal.
- That's not true, Mirza.
- Why are you lying?
What plea is this letter making?
What does that marriage
procession prove?
My poverty, my helplessness.
l was in debt, and was forced
to sell my daughter to repay it.
Money is the root cause
of all problems.
Here's the money.
So that no one says that
an innocent woman...
had to sell herself for money.
Or that a mother sold her affection.
There is none like you, Mirza.
l had already made the decision.
You go yourself and give
the good news to Chaudvin.
l don't have the courage.
- l have come.
- Go away! l said go away!
l don't even want to see your face!
Seeing a woman helpless,
you want to buy her with money.
l belong to the one
l was destined for.
Go away from here!
- What happened?
- No one bothered to listen to me.
Oh my God! What do l do now?
What happened, Moti? Why
did you turn Mirza away?
Yes, l sent Mirza to you.
That was Mirza?
My fate be damned!
l thought it was the Kotwal.
Mother, call him back.
Don't let Mirza go.
What nonsense is this!
What do you mean by shouting
Mirza's name in the street like that?
- Come in!
- Leave me!
How dare you shout Mirza's name!
l won't spare you!
l won't spare you today!
Come!
l won't spare you!
Move aside! She belongs to me!
l have bought her!
The writing has not even
dried on the paper yet.
Here's your writing, your
clothes, your jewelry!
- We don't give a damn for it.
-Do you know what you're saying?
You dare to invite me home
and then humiliate me?
Don't act smart with me.
l've set many like you straight!
- l am the Kotwal!
- That doesn't scare me.
The king is bigger than Kotwal,
and Allah bigger than the king.
- Just try something!
- Such daring?
Don't assume l will leave quietly
after such humiliation.
Even your father will leave!
l swear, l will teach you...
your daughter,
and that Mirza a lesson!
The Hazrat Khan is not my name!
Remember that!
Get lost. Do whatever you like.
Mother! Mother! l have got life
again! l have got life again!
l was reminded of our
first meeting again
My heart complained again
l was reminded of our
first meeting again
l had barely escaped one misfortune...
when l was reminded of you again
l was reminded of our
first meeting again
Life would pass by anyway
Why was l reminded of meeting you?
l was reminded of our
first meeting again
My thoughts keep going back to you
My heart didn't want to,
yet it searched out those memories
l was reminded of our
first meeting again
My heart complained again
- Disgusting!
- What's the matter, wife?
Nothing.
How much you have started drinking!
Now l feel, we will be bathed
in liquor after we die.
Okay, l won't drink.
Please fill my hookah.
No man can't be that decent.
No betel leaf or hookah.
That is what l am saying.
There isn't a penny at home.
And you even spent
what little there was on liquor.
There's nothing more
at home to sell.
God forbid! What are you saying!
God only knows, l never complain.
But l have to speak when
things get out of hand.
Your behavior has made me bold.
Mathuradas, the money lender, is here.
- Go, now deal with him too.
- How do l deal with him now?
- What will happen now?
- Whatever Allah wills.
Does your Allah will anything good?
Come in, Mathuradas.
- Hello.
You have come so early
in the morning?
The interest amount will only
increase with the days.
Not adding in today,
the total is now Rs.279O.
- Please clear my account now.
- How do l clear it?
l cannot wait any longer.
Better clear my account, or
l'll go and meet Mr. Kale...
Wait Mathuradas.
'Keep your honor intact, Mir'
'This is Delhi, not some
other small town'
'l am a poor man, how will
l repay your money?'
'The only property l
have is these poems.'
'A few woven words,
a few praises of women...'
'this is all one will get
from my home after l die.'
Take these.
You must be joking.
This poetry is worthless
in the market.
You are right.
Poetry is worthless
in this money-minded world.
Take them to the king's court.
Maybe you will get Rs.3OO-4OO.
His poetry is not for sale, sir.
Take these bangles for now.
When Allah gives us money...
we'll repay your money too.
No wife, please don't
kill my ego like that.
No sister-in-law, l may be a money
lender, but l'm not hard hearted.
l had only come to remind
Mirza of his duty.
Let me know when you can
arrange some money.
lf you need more money,
l can lend you some.
- l have no words to thank you.
- You don't have to thank me.
l'll take your leave. Good day.
Tell your wife not to
worry about the loan.
- Are you Mathuradas, the money lender?
- No.
Wait!
l forgot my name. My name is
Mathuradas, and l am a money lender.
You have been called to
the police station.
Police station? Me? No!
lt must be someone else.
- What for?
- You'll learn that over there.
- At the police station.
- Spare me, l prefer to go home.
l am no thief, nor related to one.
Leave me! l am innocent. l have
committed no theft or heist.
l didn't elope with any woman.
l am a decent family man.
Walk in!
- He's the money lender, sir.
- l'm a money lender.
Don't be afraid, you haven't been
called here as an accused...
but only for questioning.
- Please be seated.
- Move back! l told you l'm innocent.
The Kotwal is a just man.
- Tell me sir, how can l help you?
- Sit down.
You all leave.
- Tell me something.
- Yes?
Have you lent money
to Mirza on interest?
- No.
- No?
Yes, l did. But that's
not a crime, sir.
Not at all. But you even
take interest from Mirza.
Does anyone lend money
without interest?
There's a limit to the
amount of interest.
Show me your account book
A little more is charged here.
But if l can even get
the principal amount...
l'll waive the interest.
lf that's the case, take the
money Mirza owes you from me.
Sell the paper you have
in his name to me.
- But...
- Don't worry, Mirza is my friend.
l don't want anyone to trouble
him for repayment of money.
That's a very kind thought, sir.
lt makes no difference to me
who l get the money from.
This is Mirza's account paper.
- Go and collect the money.
- Thank you. Good day.
l'll take revenge!
l'll ruin him, or l won't consider
myself worthy of my name!
Mirza Ghalib, son of Abdullah
Khan Baig, be present!
Accused, just admit or deny...
that you have to repay
Mathuradas a loan...
the record of which...
the city police chief,
Hasmat Khan, has bought.
Yes sir, l admit.
And despite repeated reminders,
you could not repay the loan?
Yes sir.
And the payment is
six months overdue?
Yes sir.
The court orders the accused
to repay the plaintiff...
Rs.2000 by this evening and
get the paper released.
lf he fails to do so, the accused
will be imprisoned for six months.
You didn't even give
me a day's time, sir.
The court's decision is final.
l can't repay that
under any circumstances.
Even if l sell everything l have...
l won't be able to collect Rs.2OOO.
Then issue an arrest warrant
in his name, sir.
Wait.
l, Mufti Kadruddin, in my
personal capacity...
deposit Rs. 2,000 with the court
from the treasury.
Mufti sir.
The court is adjourned.
That was good Mirza sir.
But at least tell me...
what did you do
with so much money?
What do l say?
'l used to take loans and drink...'
'assuming my poetry would
bring me success one day'
Mr. Mufti, you have
obliged me today.
l can't thank you enough..
Don't say that. l am not so good.
Even l need a favor.
What favor can you expect
from this poor man?
My brother's son is
getting married.
There will be music
and a poetry recital too.
Such a huge bribe for
such a small favor?
My friends have increased my worth.
What do we do?
We fear your annoyance.
Your poetry was not appreciated
in the royal court...
so you stopped going there.
You don't even participate
in poetry recitals.
So l didn't mind doing
you this small favor.
- Do come.
- Thank you for the invitation.
Thanks for accepting.
Friends, the ladies
have requested...
that Mirza Nausha recite his poetry.
'l may not love, l may be rude'
Go ahead!
lt's an old poem, yet,
l'll accept your request.
l recite...
l may not love, l may be rude
'l may not love, l may be rude'
l may be rude, you may be famous
Don't talk to me,
or have anything to do with me
lf you've no other feelings,
l'll even accept your hatred
'lf you've no other feelings,
l'll even accept your hatred'
The third couplet is...
Wait, l forgot.
'My being is so...'
Oh Allah!
Why did you speak out?
Pardon me madam...
but hearing his poetry you said
'wow', and my heart sighed.
Why is my presence defaming?
Even if it's not a convention,
but a creation of the world
This is for a Ghalib supporter.
Even l am not an enemy
Even though a stranger
may love you
Even though l'm a very loyal man...
you may not love me,
but may consider me a nuisance
Mirza sir!
What is this girl up to?
l will go to the heights
Even though being indifferent
may be your habit
Even though inexpressible
Even though unfulfilled,
at least l have the desire
- Mr. Mufti, l'll be going.
- What's wrong, Mirza?
l am not feeling well.
Please excuse me.
Madam, pardon me,
but l want to leave.
Where are you going?
l paid you 50 takkas and you
may leave only if you return the money.
Take this. l'm sorry,
but l'm not feeling well.
Mirza sir! Mirza sir!
Mirza sir!
- Chaudvin madam, you?
- Yes, it's me.
l always call you,
and you always ignore my call.
lt's not that, l myself
wanted to meet you.
l wanted to congratulate
you on your marriage.
Yes Mirza, if you won't,
who else will?
What do you mean?
Didn't you get married?
Yes, l'm married, but not to Kotwal.
Not to Kotwal?
Then who?
You ask me that?
Believe me Mirza,
l was living on your name.
But unfortunately, whenever we drew
close, destiny separated us.
That night when you came,
l thought you were Hashmat.
And was so rude to you.
But when l realized it was
my beloved who had come...
and who was so close to me...
l, the unfortunate one, didn't
even extend my hand towards him.
Then l tried hard, but...
Why did you want to try hard for me?
l am a useless, worthless fellow.
l only compose poetry,
which no one likes.
Don't say that in my presence.
Your poetry, and you mean
everything to me.
Don't say that.
Don't make me a sinner.
My heart and brain have already
created a dilemma for me.
My heart draws me
towards you, and...
l don't want anything else.
l have found what l want.
l have only one wish.
Come to my house once, just once!
Let me also experience
how a bride feels...
when the groom she desires
comes to take her.
How she dies with happiness!
Chaudhvin, l'll come.
l'll come tomorrow.
Tomorrow! Really? Do come.
l will wait for you.
Why is it, dear, you are sending me out
all dressed up today?
l want others to like you
the way l like you.
What others? Do you know
where l'm going?
What do l know? l only know
you're leaving the house.
Yes.
You're crying?
No.
My eyes just welled up.
They don't shed for no reason.
Heat gathers.
Heat rises and collects in the sky.
What pains you?
Not pain, regret...
l couldn't make a place
for myself in your heart.
l couldn't be the inspiration
for your poetry.
Since l married you,
you've been having problems.
A child is the bond with which
a wife binds her husband.
l couldn't even provide that bond.
- lf you heed, may l say something?
- Yes.
- Marry again.
- Wife ... no ... no!
Allah, what do l do? One stood
by me, one stole my heart.
One is an idol of devotion,
the other, full of love.
No!
Oh heart, what has happened to you?
What is the cure to this ailment?
l am desirous, and he is regretful
Oh Allah, what is all this about?
Oh heart, what has happened to you?
Even l can speak
l wish you would ask
what the matter is
Oh heart, what has happened to you?
l expect loyalty from the one
Who doesn't understand loyalty?
Oh heart, what has happened to you?
l love you very much
l don't know who God is
Oh heart, what has happened to you?
What is the cure for this ailment?
Moti. Mo...
Mirza.
- Didn't Mirza come?
- He's not going to come.
You wait for him needlessly.
You love such a heartless man
who doesn't even care for you.
lt's not that, mother.
l know why he didn't come.
Since he has been ridiculed
at the royal court...
he feels dejected. He has lost
interest in everything.
Moti! Moti!
There's going to be
a grand procession tomorrow.
Won't you come with us? Mirza
Shahrukh will come in a palanquin.
He will be dressed in full glory.
Even the King will join
the procession.
The King? Mother, even l
will join the procession.
l will sing and dance there.
l'll tell the King what
a great poet Mirza is.
Nonsense! Are you a nautch girl
that you will sing and dance?
- Have some shame!
- What shame?
My shame is a slave to my husband.
What husband? Which husband?
Don't you feel ashamed?
l won't let you go.
l will go! l surely will!
Now come on, Mother!
News has come that
the procession of Hindus...
is just a mile away from the temple.
And the Muslims are just one and a
half mile away from the mosque.
Hindus and Muslims
are embracing each other.
They are joining
each other's processions.
Aren't you feeling well?
Then what's the matter?
You're not speaking.
Have l made a mistake?
- No, Zeenat.
- Then why are you somber?
Look outside, both the earth
and sky look velvety.
The streams are gushing,
gardens are blooming...
birds are singing.
Shall l call the dancers
to entertain you?
Want to hear the Malhar (song)?
No Zeenat, l don't feel like
doing anything today.
lf the King feels like that,
what will become of his subjects?
l'm thinking the same.
My ancestors ruled here, widened
the boundaries of their kingdom.
Now the kingdom has become
a slave to another country.
l am wondering if this rejoicing
will continue after us.
Or will it become history?
lt is true, only Allah's
name continues.
Please leave now.
l want to be left alone.
As you wish.
What is the matter, Queen?
You are crying?
What do l do?
Today, l've seen the Emperor in
a mood that l've never seen before.
He is totally depressed. l tried
to cheer him in a hundred ways...
but it didn't work.
What happened to these girls?
Let them dance, sing.
Perhaps that will cheer him.
Make a bungalow for me
on the banks of the Ganga
May you be blessed, my beloved
Plant a garden right
outside my window
l'll get to see flowers
May you be blessed, my beloved
Let's lock our eyes
and talk of love
Let my anklets tinkle
with your flute
Just you and me and no one else
May you be blessed, my beloved
lt needs a lifetime
for a sigh to affect
Who will live until
your tresses grey?
Love unlimited, and desires desperate
What do l do with my heart
until my love is noticed?
Until my love is noticed?
Agreed you won't leave me, but...
l will die by the time
you realize l love you
Wonderful! Who is this girl?
She's the daughter of a slave.
Her name is Chaudvin Begum.
Her voice is melodious,
her song beyond compare!
No one has a cure to my sorrow
A flame has to burn until dawn
lt needs a lifetime
for a sigh to affect
l heard your song, Chaudvin Begum.
lt really pleased me.
Here is a reward for you.
King, l am not worthy
of this honor.
The one whose composition
l sang is worthy of it.
l am just the shadow, he is
the body. Mirza Ghalib.
Oh great! Attendant, go in the
evening with my message to Mirza.
Ask him not to be so annoyed...
and to come and attend court.
Mirza, l am pleased that you came.
Since you left, and until
your return today...
l have been admiring your poetry.
Appreciating your poetry
and style...
in addition to a reward,
l'll also confer a title upon you.
From today, you are the
Royal Poet of the court.
l will recite your poetry
in the royal court.
Oh King, how do l thank
you for this honor?
l and my descendents will
forever be grateful to you.
'May you live a 1000 years'
'May every year have 50000 days'
Congratulations!
Serve me sweets today.
Will you say something,
or just ask for sweets?
Tell me, what is it?
The King has conferred
a title upon your Mirza.
Really?
Yes, and rewarded him
with loads of money.
He gifted him silver bowls,
promised him a monthly allowance...
and also declared him
tutor of the Prince.
Thank you Allah!
And do you know how all this
became possible? Because of you.
Don't say that. lt is his compositions
which the world likes.
lt is God's gift.
l pray that he is more successful.
l will celebrate! l will sing!
Now he will surely come to us.
Then you celebrate and sing.
l will decorate the house.
l will feed the poor.
l will do so much!
l knew this would happen one day.
- But first thank that person too.
- Who?
The one who praised you
before the Emperor.
That's where l'm going.
- God be with you. - God be with you.
l will leave too.
- Come on Mukku Miyan.
- Where sir?
- But sir...
- Oh...
Oh, dear.
Oh. You are so happy
that you are crying?
Enough. A woman's name is crying.
Crying in sorrow,
crying in happiness.
Mirza. God has heard my prayers.
l hope you will still let
me stay at your feet.
Why do you talk like that?
You are my wife.
- Then come home.
- Home? Yes of course.
Lift the palanquin.
'Nazm-ud-Daulah', 'Dabir-ul-Mulk',
Nizam-E-Jung'! Naushad Ali!
What have you
thought about Mirza?
l have been wracking my brains,
but can't think of a thing.
Of course you can't. Your efforts
won't blow out this flame now.
lt's not that sir, l
am trying my best.
Best indeed!
- Sir, we have made some arrests.
- Put them all behind bars!
- Present them at court tomorrow!
- Yes, sir. Come on!
Move, move!
- l've got an idea, sir!
- What?
Alright, you throw the bait,
l'll set the trap.
- Listen.
- Yes?
Your nephew, Arif,
is coming home.
Should we adopt him?
You can call someone your son.
No, l am scared.
Whoever l hold dear, l lose him.
l don't want any calamity
to befall Arif.
Don't talk such nonsense.
Then do as you please.
Who could be happier than l?
We'll have a grown up son,
For what more can we ask?
l will become a father and
grandfather without any trouble.
You will become a mother and
grandmother without any pain.
- Naughty!
- l'm leaving.
Yes sir.
Wow! What lovely flowers.
'l won't stop worshiping that idol'
'Even if l'm called an atheist'
- Let's go.
- Where?
Where l've been trying
to go for so long.
lt's time for Arif to come.
Yes Mirza, it's time you
kept your promise.
The game is waiting for you.
Let's finish it today.
Today? Not today, Naushad Ali.
Can't you wait until tomorrow?
Sorry for being rude, but
who has seen tomorrow?
This is a promise, you'll
have to keep it today.
Alright.
- Mirza didn't come.
- He won't come either.
Don't you understand yet?
You did so much for him,
you even invited slurs.
But with what results?
You are where you were.
No mother, you don't understand
the heart of a poet.
He makes dear ones cry, so that
he can make others laugh.
He burns himself to brighten
other people's worlds.
l am sure he will come,
he will surely come once.
He will keep his promise.
- Let's stake Rs.1OO.
- No, Rs.5O.
You think my pockets are empty.
Here, satisfy yourself.
This is my allowance.
But listen, don't cheat.
l'll use all the tricks to win the game.
Should l throw a winning number?
- Why are you looking outside?
- No reason.
l am not sitting here to lose.
Throw the dice.
Hello Mirza. What's going
on here, Naushad Ali?
Nothing sir, we were playing.
And even the Mirza Ghalib was.
But in the eyes of law, both horse
and donkey are the same.
Mind your tongue!
Don't be rude, Mr. Mirza.
Mr. Khan we won't make
such a mistake again.
What mistake? Who is
making the mistake?
You! Pick up everything,
and even bring Mirza along.
- Pardon us, Kotwal.
- l understand everything!
Naushad is your ally. But don't
think you will escape.
Conspiring against someone
is also a crime.
Handcuff him! And bring him along!
Hey, that's Mirza!
- Mirza Nausha?
- Under arrest?
'Nazm-ud-Daulah', 'Dabir-ul-Mulk',
Nizam-E-Jung'!
- Fittan, don't you want a betel leaf?
- No, damn you!
Oh God! Mirza Nausha!
- Madam! Mirza!
- Mirza has come!
Mirza has come?
Mother!
- Oh my God!
- Take him away!
What happened, Mirza?
Let him go!
Let go a gambler? A man who breaks
the law in broad daylight?
- Move aside!
- l plead with you, Kotwal.
l beg at your feet!
You had asked me to come to
your house once. l have come.
l had not asked you
to come like this.
Let him go, Kotwal.
Don't take out your anger on him.
Move aside...
or even you'll be arrested
for obstructing us.
Arrest me. Say whatever you
like to me, but let him go!
Or take me along, too.
l had come as a groom
to this house. And he.
Move!
You have beaten my daughter.
Allah will beat you!
Damn you! l curse you!
'l am neither a joyous
song, nor music'
'l am the voice of my defeat'
Great Mirza! Can't get
over poetry even here?
He'll feel like an
infidel without it.
l hope you're not dejected.
'l am arrested by love'
'The rest lies in the court's hands'
Greetings, uncle.
'How wonderful that l saw you
today. lt's such a joyous day'
- How are you, Arif?
- l'm fine, uncle.
- How are your wife and child?
- They have sent their greetings.
Give them my regards.
l wish l were present there.
But my being present or not
makes no difference.
Even if l was, l would
spread sorrow.
- Don't lose courage, uncle.
- Everything will be fine, Mirza.
All your friends are
trying their best.
The servant bows at
the Emperor's feet.
l have recognized you.
You are Chaudhvin Begum.
One of Mirza's supporters.
What have you come to say?
l have to beg for the
Emperor's grace.
l have come to beg
for justice, Emperor.
Mirza Nausha has been arrested
by the police in a case.
l know, Chaudhvin.
l am as sad about
this as you, probably.
Such atrocity, this injustice.
Please issue an order Emperor...
that Mirza should be
released immediately.
l wish l could do this.
Emperor!
Hearing this from me, you would
perhaps be surprised, Chaudhvin.
But it is all a matter of time.
There was neither a cry,
nor were there any tears.
Hindustan's King's rule is now only
to the banks of the Yamuna.
The area where Mirza was arrested
doesn't fall under me...
but under the British resident.
At least write a recommendation letter.
l am sure, seeing a royal request,
he will not refuse.
lf that's what you think,
l'll write one for you.
Oh Allah, l have no words to speak.
l cannot do anything.
The King has begun to send
me recommendations?
lf the King begins to
interfere with the law...
there won't be any
law and order left.
The King is not interfering.
He has only requested a thorough
investigation in the case.
Mirza is no ordinary
citizen of Delhi.
Whether he's ordinary or not,
the law applies to everyone.
l don't have to learn what is
the law from you, Kotwal.
The law doesn't say you can provoke
someone into committing a crime...
and then go and nab him.
Pardon me...
but nor does it say that the
criminal should be left alone...
if he's committed a crime.
What criminal? Who is the criminal?
The criminal is Naushad Ali.
And wasn't he a man sent by you?
No, he was sir, but...
A crime, provoked or not...
crime is crime.
You may go gentlemen.
- What did he mean?
- That Mirza won't be released.
- You may leave now.
- l will leave, Hashmat.
But remember, you'll die a dog's
death for these lies and cheating.
No one will even offer water
when you're dying.
You will have to pay for every
deed in Allah's court.
The law is your friend.
You are the Messiah of the poor
Whoever comes to your door,
never returns empty handed
lf you desire, a ruined home
can glow with happiness again
A helpless man can be
absolved of sorrows
l bow my head in obeisance.
My eyes look at you with hope
My complaints have reached my lips
Oh Lord of the world, look...
these crazy people have
come to your door
The complaints, too,
have reached the lips
My desires were faltering
in the streets of sorrow...
when suddenly l thought of you
l have brought my prayers
where destinies are made
l have heard in your court,
destinies are made
l have so many woes
At least look at me now.
At least have mercy on me now
Come out from behind
your curtain and look at me
Where these moths have reached...
my complaints have reached my lips
Oh Lord, had you conferred
the title on my husband...
that he be disgraced like this?
ls this why you conferred
such honor on him...
that he languish in jail?
Madam, who is your husband?
What do l say?
Mirza Ghalib.
Why madam, do you know him?
l... l've heard he's a very nice man.
Very God fearing.
He is God fearing.
But God doesn't pity him.
What happened?
We were happy together,
when a girl entered my husband's life.
She ruined him, ruined my home.
Oh God!
lt's also possible, madam...
that poor hapless girl was not
aware of what she was doing.
Love is blind after all.
But when one loves,
one torments one's self.
What love is this that
ruins other's homes...
to make yourself happy?
lf that girl really loved Mirza,
she would destroy herself...
before any calamity befell Mirza.
How can anything that has
come here go wrong?
l don't ask anything
for myself, Lord.
Please shower your kindness
on this good woman.
That which has reached here...
The complaints too have
reached the tongue...
Moti, has the case finished?
Yes, mother. lt has finished.
My life's case.
Moti! Moti! Fittan! Fittan!
Mother, what wrong have l done?
Why is everything going against me?
- lt's nothing like that.
- l won't live here now, Mother.
l feel everything in Delhi
is after my life.
Take me away from here.
l won't live in Mirza's Delhi.
- Where do l take you?
- Take me anywhere, Mother.
Death is beckoning me.
Let's go and live in such a place
now where there is no one
Where there is no friend,
no one to talk to
Let's go and live in such a place
Make a home without doors or walls
And there should be no
relatives or well wishers
Let's go and live in such a place
lf l fall sick, there should
be no one to look after me
And if l die, there should
be no one to bury me
Let's go and live in such a place
now where there is no one
Congratulations on your
release, Mirza.
Thank you. What do
l gift you, Jailer?
l have only this left now.
Some scented snuff.
Even that is enough from you, Mirza.
Like the fragrance
of this snuff...
your glory will one day spread
throughout the whole world.
Take, give it to someone you love.
l'll keep some for myself.
Kallu. Dear.
l do call him, but, oh my
heart full of emotions
lt should affect him such...
that he cannot stop
himself from coming
lt should affect him such...
that he cannot stop
himself from coming
Open the door!
Are you sleeping during the day?
Who are you, brother?
l am Ghalib. Tell Chaudvin,
Ghalib has come.
She has left this place.
Left? Where did she go?
- God knows!
Now who do l ask where she is?
Hafiz! Do you know where Chaudvin is?
Mirza! Wonder where she went.
She left, and also took along
the recourse of us poor people.
Oh Allah, what do l do now?
Where do l look for her?
l've only heard that a voice is
heard from the square of Mehrauli.
But when you go near,
it fades away.
The square in Mehrauli.
Oh Lord, have mercy.
- Have courage mother.
- What courage?
My daughter has been lying
in bed for the last ten days...
fighting for her life.
She keeps staring at the door
like she's expecting someone.
This was not my destiny
that l'd see my love
That l'd live longer if l could wait
l live in the hope you'll
keep your promise
Thereafter, l don't
care even if l die
l'd die with happiness
if l was sure you'd come
This was not my destiny...
that l'd see my love
This was not my destiny
l don't want to be
defamed after l die
Why don't l just disappear?
l'll have no burial,
no grave anywhere
This was not my destiny,
that l'd see my love
Someone ask my heart...
how obsessed it is over love
Why would l have this pain...
if my love was requited?
l have come, Chaudvin.
Daughter!
Chaudhvin! Chaudvin, l have come!
- My King has come!
- Chaudhvin!
Chaudvin, l have come!
Dear!
Chaudhvin.
- Chaudhvin!
- Dear!
lt's agreed you won't leave me, but...
l will die by the time
you realize l love you
Beauty was freed of the
dilemma after my death
Unfaithfulness is at
peace after my death
When the flame blows off,
smoke is...
released
The fire of love died after me
No one dies with such sorrow
Do invigorate loyalty
again after my death
This humble woman of love has come
Where will this storm of
love go after my death?