You take it easy.
I will tell you all the details
when my husband comes.
Brother, why have they come?
People living in the second plot
of land are troubled by cholera.
People get scared and leave here.
They have come to ask the husband for help.
- Another new question!
Mr. Das, after calling the headquarters….
...find a way to
treat those people.
I will go today and meet the
people in the second part...
...because I won't be coming tomorrow.
Tomorrow is my daughter's
birthday, let's hurry!
Listen Charu,
Aunty has not come.
The car that went to pick him up came from the station empty-handed. - What is that?
He had said that he would come
to meet us on his way to Kashi.
There must be some important work.
Today is our daughter's first
birthday, but aunty can't come.
The party will be boring without him.
- Yes.
Although we were not related to
Aunty, more than our relatives...
...He loves us.
Now is the time to feed the baby.
Okay then, I'll get
dressed later to take him.
Look at Rama's latest dress
Sha!  It's very beautiful.
Today is your daughter's
first birthday, isn't it?
No, on your daughter's first birthday.
And whose birthday is next year?
- Rama's other birthday.
And only on Rama's
birthday every year?
Please wait!  I can't take
care of this one child...
I don't want any more.
- Gentleman!
who
what's the problem
- This child, sir
Why what happened to that child?
- What's next?
what are you saying
Whose child are you?
This is the wife of the husband's worker.
Why didn't he come to work today?
He is dead, man.
He and his wife
both died of cholera.
Yes, this epidemic is
spreading everywhere.
So what brought this boy here?
Now this child has no one, sir.
Who will take care of this child?
- If you can sympathize with the husband...
No way, guests will come
to our house in a little while.
Go now and come back later.
welcome  - How are you, uncle?
how are you uncle  -
How are you, sister-in-law?
Sha!  Very beautiful.
Aya, take him away.
I want an ice cream.
- Okay, I'll get you one.
Badal!  Bring an ice cream.
Listen!
It's okay, son, don't cry.
Get in, lady.
bye Bye.
why this  What are you still
doing here keeping the child?
what's the problem
Whose child is this?
These are the children of our worker.
His mother and father
died of cholera this morning.
There is nothing I can
do to take him away.
We only have the help of
the husband, gentlemen.
Here, take these ten rupees...
...and find another home for him.
Where should we take this baby, sir?  This
little one belongs to a very low caste.
There is no one of this
child's caste in this village.
Then take it to another village
I am looking for
someone like that, sir, but
until then, who will
take care of this Kelly?
His mother and father are gone...
Little by little, this child will
become food for vultures and foxes.
I was able to save the girl
because I got there on time.
Oh my god!
Charu, who wants to put this
kind of trouble in the backyard?
As good as they take him.
- Did you mean that?
Is it good for those foxes and vultures to take him away? - No, I mean...
Come on!  - Yes ma'am?
Can you take care of this
child for two or three days?
What's wrong Miss?
Am I in for it?
Take him inside.
Bathe him in hot water...
...put on Rama's old dress.
Keep him in your room.
- Yes, ma'am.
You are very kind lady.
Find someone of his caste as soon as possible. - Yes sir.
It takes two or three days.
I'll come back, sir, I'll come back, lady.
- Good.
Is it Rama or Sujata who is crying?
- Sujata?
Yes, the other child.
Oh, did you just name him?
why?  Is that a bad name?
- No, not like that.
It seems like a meaningless name.
That child belongs to a very low
caste, but you named him Sujata.
It just popped into my head.
Who is coming in that cart?
Charu!  It must be the aunt.
- Aunt?!
how are you aunty  -
Hey, don't jump, kids!
The leg is amputated.
Because these are my
grandchildren, I have no freedom at all.
He is very naughty.
- Both should be blessed.
You didn't even come to
Rama's birthday party...
...not even sent a letter.
I was ready to come, but I
just looked at Litha and knew...
...It was not an auspicious
moment, so I stayed away.
He said that it is not good
to travel at such times.
Get to know him
Bhavani Shankar Sharma.
He is a very knowledgeable priest.
Performing a Chandipat Pooja in the
month in which the girl child was born...
...Good for that kid's future.
That's why I called
him to come with us.
Praise be to the priest.
- Goodbye!
This lady did not introduce me properly.
Actually, I am not a priest,
but a professor of English.
I do Chandipat Pujas
because of my passion...
...And those who spend time righteously...
...to happiness.
I've been sick lately.
So I thought it would be better if I
went somewhere with a different climate...
...And then he himself
invited me to come here.
That's why I came.  - Very good.
Stay here as long as you like.
I pray that your fortunes
will improve as well as mine.
Like a good son, do I
have water to take a bath?
All this dust is on my body.
Go and get him some water to bathe.
- Come on sir.
Go with him.  - Okay.
Come in aunty.
Come on, kids.
- Show me the child, what was your name?
Rama.
- Rama?  Sha!  It is a very beautiful name.
Wait Charu, I will bring
this river water from God.
Come on.
Charu, you know how Aunty is.
He really thinks about that caste.
Tell Aya to keep that child away.
Aunty should not be allowed to see him.
Is this my son's daughter?
Wait, I'll take him over a bit.
But... he...
- Do you think about him more than his mother?
Very beautiful,
just like her mother.
Born!  Your daughter is very lucky.
Give him to Aya.
- Your daughter is very beautiful.
You will not have to
worry about his marriage.
Look how he laughs with me.
Maybe he recognized me.
Who can be heard crying inside
Did you have twins?
You didn't even tell me that.
- We didn't get twins.
That is our daughter, Rama.
- Then who is this?
Both his mother and
father are dead so we...
But he must be from
a high caste, right?
No, he is low caste.
- Low caste?
Eya Upen, I didn't expect
anything like this from you.
You belong to a good and important family.
- But aunty...
I don't want to hear anything.
If I knew, inside this house...
...I won't even step foot here
because you are keeping a low caste girl.
Please listen to this aunty...
Auntie, now you know the whole story.
Now tell me what you would
do if you were in our place?
What I thought was unfair...
...I still see it that way.
But aunty it's...
- Upen!
Don't argue with me for having
read an English book or two!
Man, that man is leaving.
- Going to go?
Priest, why what?
what's the problem
All this is God's will.
I want to go when I want to go.
Aya told me and I saw
with my own eyes...
...that you keep a low
caste child in your house.
That's amazing!
Is that where you're going?
There is nothing surprising about that.
Our religion has...
...It is not to catch a
low caste to keep with us.
You are a very knowledgeable person.
You must know that it is
also said in science - what?
A gas is released from the
bodies of those low castes.
It pollutes the bodies and
souls of important people like us.
Have you seen the said gas?
Did you know that food contains vitamins?
- Yes.
Have you seen that vitamin?
- No.
Does that mean that
food contains vitamins?
OK, I'm going now.
You asked me to stay...
...But it's my misfortune
that I can't stay longer.
Have a good trip.
The priest got angry and left.
Please stop him aunty.
- Now he won't stop when we say so.
I know him very well
and he is very pious.
I can put up with your
rude behavior but he won't.
What do we do now?
Get rid of this problem
as soon as possible.
I say this for your own good.
I have no problem with that,
I will go to Kashi tomorrow.
Why are you so quiet?
- What should I do?
I started to feel scared too
Because that priest said about a gas?
No, no, it's not. I
hope we won't suffer.
We don't want to suffer...
...But those who do injustice in the
name of religion will suffer the same.
Don't laugh at every question.
Aunt also thinks that we will
get rid of this girl's problem soon.
Listen, tell the guard
to take him away.
Ah, is this Sujata? Nice little kelly. Look at her beauty...
- Aya!
Why did you touch him?
Ah, if I touch him, will I lose
my caste?  Then I'll take a shower.
No, this is no joke.
You are getting too close to him.
- So that's the point?
Don't worry Charu I
have prepared everything.
What did you prepare?
- The guard told me...
...that he found someone
from Sujata's caste.
He will come tomorrow and take Sujata.
Charu, do we have a bamboo shoot in our house?
- Yes why?
Aya told me that Kelly had a little fever.
- Bamboo?
A fever is spreading in
this area, take care of him.
Yes, he has a fever.
I saw that you also touched him
and now you have to take a bath too.
So you tested me, didn't you?
Charu, it's not our fault.
People also get closer to the animals they raise.
But he is a human child.
Will I be able to do my job?
Yes, yes they can.
Charu, the guard...
...Sujata has brought
a man to give.
Mr.
Mr
Hello sir.
I brought someone from the
girl's caste to hand over the child.
What should I do?
Tell Aya to bring the child.
Come on!  Come on!  Bring that kid.
here
Take this girl.
What can I do if I
only take this girl?
Don't forget what we decided.
First I need money, next I need
clothes, I need clothes for washing.
Why am I just accepting this girl?
Do you think I'm stupid?
listen...
are you drunk  - Why...
- Why are you afraid?
Tell him I'm drunk, I
drank with my money.
Why do I put myself through
this kind of misery without money?
Get that drunk off this land!
Guards, take him away!
Be a man before
you take a child.
You will spend all the money
given to you on drinking.
Get him out.
Take the girl inside again.
- That's right.
That's fine, we can't
give him to a lowly drunk.
But we better give
him to someone soon.
He is still a child.
But when he grows up?
No, it is better to stay
away from such relationships.
But where do you put him?
We are going to leave here soon.
Let's find a good family for him
Rama!  Sujata!
Come and drink this milk.
why did you fall for
me  - You fell yourself.
Liar, I won't talk again.
- it's OK.
I'm leaving.
Mommy!  Daddy!
It will fall down from
there. Go down quickly.
Mom!  Dad!
Don't be bad kids, go play.
Looks like he's back...
...Sujatha has been taught
to call us mom and dad.
Is it true, or is it...
...As Rama says, mommy and daddy say.
I don't talk to you
don't talk to me
Don't talk to me!
You don't have a mommy.
- You don't have a mother either.
You don't even have a father.
- You don't even have a father.
Listen, you told me...
...As soon as we get here,
let's hand it over to someone.
Now it's been four years since we came here.
But Sujata still...
I tried hard but we have
responsibility for him.
Neither you nor I want to
give him away to anyone
That is true.
Can't we send him to hell?
From now Sujata is trying
to match Rama in everything.
When he grows up, we will
have to face many problems.
OK, I'll find a good orphanage.
And what about Rama's learning?
I spoke to a good teacher.
He will come to teach from tomorrow.
- Daddy!
Dad, do you eat halwa?
- Do you eat some too?
here
what are you eating  - Halva.
- What?
Don't you know what halwa is?
He always fights with Rama.
Aya told me that she used
to beat Rama sometimes.
They are still children.
Dad!  Don't I have halwa?
come come come here
Don't eat with that spoon.
- why?
Without thinking that he is low caste...
...do you eat what he left?
Sujata take this flour,
can we make puri with it?
Yes we can.
Rama!  Here is a new book
and a stone tablet for you.
Come and learn from your teacher
Where is my book, I do not study?
- No, you play.
Why did you buy the book Sujata?
- I am also studying.
Don't touch these books, your
father will be angry with me.
Brother Bahadur!
Give me a book and I will read.
a book?
I don't have any books, children.
Liar!  Why lie?
There is a book.
But that is Ramayana.
- Okay, then I will read the Ramayana.
Sit down!
I will tell you a beautiful story.
Teacher, I will also
learn here is my book.
Are you going to study such a big book?
- Yes.
Come on Sujata, you can't stay here.
- No, I'm studying too.
Listen up kids.
- not!  Let me go!  Let me go!
Come here... - Let go...
- Why what happened?
Look, father, he
won't let me study.
Go and go and learn.
Who did the letter come from?
- Oh!  Charu?
I have received a reply to the
letter I sent to that anathagar.
They like to accept Sujata.
This orphanage is very famous.
There will be no
problem for Sujata.
it is good.
Take two or three
days off and let him go.
No, I'm too busy
to take a vacation.
And then?  Just ask the
teacher, he will like it...
OK, I'll ask him
OK, I'll take care
of that, don't worry!
I will drop him off there.
Please meet the manager
of the orphanage...
...Tell him to take
good care of Sujata.
Money is not a problem, I'll
give whatever I want - OK.
Teacher!  I want to talk to you.
- Say yes.
Sujata has become very friendly to us.
Please, make him go anyway.
He doesn't want to know, we are
doing this to keep him away from us.
Very good
Is it true, teacher?
- Of course children
That beautiful
place is far away...
...where heaven and earth meet.
You will love to see it.
There are silver trees
with golden leaves...
...They are on top and
the Kottori are always short.
Would you like to go to that country?
- Yes, I would like to.
I am taking Rama with me.
- No children, go alone for now.
Then you can come back...
...surprise everyone
with the beauty there.
We can take Rama later.  - Okay.
Listen!  Listen!  Children,
be ready at five this evening.
I will bring a car.  - Okay.
Charu!  The teacher said that
Sujata is ready to go to the orphanage.
He will pick her up
at five o'clock today.
Have everything ready.
Listen!  Today at the office I...
...I have a special
job, it will be late.
Dad!
Here's your hat.
You carry this all the time;
Why did you forget today?
If I didn't remind you, you
will have to work in the sun.
Yes Sujata.
sujata are you ready
Yes, Master.  - Come on
Teacher, father is not coming?
- not
And mother?  - No...
- Then I won't go.
Listen children, your parents, Rama
and all three have already left for there.
They sent me to get you.
- really?
Yes.
- Then I will come with you.
Mother, mother!
There are sweets and dolls in that world.
- I don't want them.
Listen Sujata...
- Mother!
Mom!  Mom!
Mom, the teacher is very bad.
He tried to trick me and
take me somewhere else.
I will not learn from him from today.
are you crying mom?  do not Cry.
I will never leave you anywhere!
Maybe Sujata would know.  - Yes.
I wanted to see him when he was gone.
I made a mistake.
- Why do you call it a mistake?
There is nothing wrong with
that, you are like his mother.
Maybe this is God's will.
We have been several times before...
...Sujatha tried to keep away
from our lives but it didn't work.
If he thinks this is his
home, let him stay like this.
When he grows up...
...God's blessings will
pave a different way for us.
Listen!  You get angry
when you hear this.
I was ordered to another shift.
What forest are we going to this time?
Prepare things for the
long journey to Dehradun.
No one can be seen.
We have not come to see
our aunt for many years.
We came today without even informing him.
I don't know if he will understand us.
Why doesn't he understand us?
Listen!
who are you  - Didn't catch me?
You came to our house once.
- just wait.
I can't hear very well
until I put on my glasses.
Remember once you came to Madhupur?
Yes, yes Jabalpur eh?
- No, Madhupur, Madhupur!
Oh!  Madhupur!
- Hey!  born  Charu?
God bless you!
You have remembered
your aunt for a long time.
Come on, let's go upstairs.
You are still that low caste girl...
...wasn't sent from home, was it?
Did you bring him this far?
I couldn't get rid of that orphan
girl, she got very close to us.
Don't say such things!
Your family is very important.
You belong to an important generation.
- What shall we do, aunt?
I thought it was our helplessness.
- Sha!
It is not a matter of forgiveness.
You lived in forests and mountains...
...There was no one to
gossip about them at that time.
But now you are
back in your society.
You have to follow the rules in this.
If you keep that low
caste girl at home...
...It also affects Rama's marriage.
That problem came to me too, aunty.
But what can we do?  We are helpless.
- No...
Where is Adir?  Can't see
the man, isn't he at home?
What to say about him?
He went to a city library.
He has his own
library in this house...
...but that's not enough for them.
MA  Even after passing the exam,
this boy's learning has not stopped
Learning never ends, aunty.
So we will go now.
- Be careful.  - God bless you.
Son!  Where is Sujata?
- What time is it now?
I don't know how to watch the time.
- It's 4:30.
At this time, he is
collecting clothes upstairs.
Sujata!  - Why Bahadur brother?
Isn't it tea time?
Tell the cook to put the
kettle on;  I will come soon.
The sugar is gone.
Shall I go get it?
No brother, I sent Basant to the shop.
He will come soon.
Nothing can escape
my girl's eyes.
To tell you the truth, my head is very
confused because of my aunt's story.
Rama's wedding...
What will we do if we have to
face problems because of Sujata?
Nothing to worry about?
You won't have any problems.
If our relatives ask about
our relationship with Sujata...
...What is our answer?
Some people already asked.
Listen, Sujata!
Call me sister and I will ask.
Ok ok sister!  - Why what?
These look great.
- Is that what called me?
No, to something else
Why did you do that?
Don't you remember you hit me yesterday?
Is that too?  wait
I will give tea to father and mother
and teach them a good lesson.
We can marry him but who...
...marrying a low caste
girl without education?
If he is uneducated like that...
...we have to be responsible for it.
Is it tea time yet?
Sujata, you are the watch of this house.
Dad, Mom made a great cake today.
Not me, you made it.
If you didn't tell me how to
do it, I wouldn't be able to do it.
Never mind, I'll fix it.
Charu, there are women's
welfare ashrams, right?
If we take their help, won't Sujata
be able to find someone suitable?
It doesn't matter what his caste is...
...If he has studied,
if he has a job...
...or if you have a small business.
Anyone can find God if they try.
What if we pay a large dowry?
If that happens, there
will be no problem.
Anyone would love to
marry a girl like Sujata.
Who is home?
Is this the eighth house?
This is the eighth house.
- I want to meet you.  - I am born.
Oh, are you...
- I can't understand you.
you don't know me
Is Charu at home?
I am his uncle.  - Ah, come in.
Uncle, you?
Come on, come on.
- Charu, are you okay?
sit down
Sha!  You have
prepared tea for me.
Charu where are your children?
Uncle, God gave me only one child
Talk to him.
I want to see him.
Rama!  - I came in a hurry.
I came here but how can
I leave without seeing you?
did you drink tea
is this your daughter
Sha!  He looks like Goddess Lakshmi.
- Mom, why did you call?
This is my daughter Rama.
This is Sujata...
She is like a daughter to us.
Listen, listen to what I say.
You can't sleep here
go to your room - why?
Honey, don't be stubborn.
Let's go.
- No, today I sleep here.
I said no.
come with me  - Open my pillow.
Why only Rama always
sleeps with his mother?
You don't fit Rama's situation.
why is that  - Mother
Rama's daughter.
And me?
Am I not my mother's daughter?
No, you are not his daughter.
You are a big liar.
If you want to be my
mother's daughter, ask her.
Mom!
Is Rama only your daughter?
Tell me, mother!
Am I not your daughter?
not.  - Then?
You are like a daughter to me.
Son of Adir.
You study sitting so high...
...what if you fall?
Grandma, grab these books.
These are very heavy.
Not heavy?  There is no
such and such knowledge
Wait, let me read it to you.
- No, you don't need to.
I can't understand them.
I came to tell you something.
About marriage?
I said, I am not
getting married.
Not getting married?  - No.
So I am the money in the bank...
...some of the company shares...
...is given to the hospital.
I won't let you give them.
I will not marry, but
keep your property
I won't give you anything.
I will give it to my daughter-in-law
Oh my god.
Then I will not marry.
you love me so much
...Why find someone
who will divide your love?
stupid boy
Our story is not over.
I am going to Upendra's house today.
You should come with me.
- Can't.
I have a lot of work.
- You are always working.
You need to hang out with people.
They came here twice.
You should meet them at least once.
I will definitely take you along
Grandma, why are you
trying so hard to take me on?
There are no
marriageable girls there.
Even so, why are you afraid?
You have made a promise
that you will not get married.
OK, I'll come too.  Please... Send
me some biscuits in Ramu's hands.
I am in Hama.
- I'll send him right away.
Where is Rama?
He is in the garden.
Will come soon.
It is very good for us
to be close to Gandhi.
You can go for a walk in the evening.
...You can be happy here.
Yes, I like it here too, Dad.
Sister!
Listen to this.  - Can't.
I don't want to fight with you.
Are you going to
sit here like a statue?
Dad, tough him out.
You don't tell him anything.
why are you laughing
He wasn't the one laughing.
I laughed too.
No dad, I saw.
He covered his face and smiled.
Okay, don't fight.
Let's go home then.
Sister, let's have a match with me.
Let's see who goes home first.
You can't compete with me.
do not!  Wait!
who are you  - I am Adir.
How are you?
My name is Adir
My grandmother lives in Shyam Street...
So you are the aunt who
lives in Shyam Bazaar...
...famous grandson.
Yes.  - Sit down.
Do you both live in the same house...
- No.
We are neighbors
Oh, why are you standing?
Sit down, imagine your home.
what  - Yes.
You go, I'll come.
Son, did you meet Rama?
Yes, but I still couldn't figure
out which of these two is Rama.
This is my daughter Rama.
He is now a B.A.  studying for  He
has won many trophies in debates.
Mom...
- And Araya?
She is Sujata, my daughter.
Rama is also good at learning.
He is good at homework.
mother
He also has many sports achievements.
He has filled this cupboard.
Boy, everyone
praises his singing.
His birthday is near now.
Come to it too.
Yes, he will definitely come to it.
Why only for birthdays, now
you both know each other.
Come whenever you have time off.
Son, now you are like our relative.
You guys keep talking.
I will go and send tea.
why this  Why are
you bringing tea?
I told Madhav to bring tea.
What happens that I brought?
Aunty doesn't drink and
Adir doesn't drink either.
Go and tell Madhav
to make tea again.
back?
why is that  - Don't argue with me, go.
Upen, come on, we've
been waiting for you.
sit down
This is my Adir son, worship.
Don't want to, son, be happy.
sit down
I was very young when I saw it.
Now he is taller than me.
So tell me, what are
you doing right now?
I'm doing some testing.
Advanced degree?  - Yes.
What is the subject of investigation?
Upen, why are you
talking about learning?
Better than that... Son of Rama...
You sing a song.
Aunt, why do you want to sing?
- Why say why?
Everyone likes your songs.
So let me ask.
Yes, say it, son.
Sing the song that got you
a gold medal in that school.
My throat doesn't feel right today.
There is no such color.
This tea is better than my song.
Have tea first, then we'll see.
Son, have you seen
how intelligent Rama is?
Son Adir, come visit us often.
Yes, he will come.  ok
Why did you sit here?
It's going to rain, come inside.
Look, Charu.
I don't want to keep Sujata
away and hurt her heart.
I don't like it either.
But you know how Aunty
feels about the lower castes.
If Sujata had brought the tea...
...Aunty does not drink and
Adir is not allowed to drink.
Mom!
who am i  - Why are you
asking these questions all at once?
I want to know who I am.
- why?  Why is that?
They drank tea made by Mahadev.
But why not drink the tea I made?
Why do I poison the tea I make?
don't bother me  I
don't have time for that.
Mom, you have to say today.
- Don't bother me Sujata.
I won't let you go without telling you.
tell me.
Where did the strength come from?
Listen to something you like.
who am i  - You... You are low caste.
- Low caste?
Yes, the lowest of the low.
People even move
away from your shadow...
...don't eat anything you catch.
But... how can I be low caste?
- You were born in a low caste.
Your parents are low caste.
Where are my low caste parents?
They are dead.
If they were alive, you wouldn't
be a burden to us either...
a burden
Am I just a burden?
"How do we want to die?
By suicide? Not at all."
"Die for life if you must"
who  - Mr. came to get the
money for the newspaper.
Hang in there brother.
I will bring the money
Sujata!
Don't get me wrong about
your mom, she really...
Dad, why are you telling me this?
I don't understand
his situation, right?
Sujata bring my shawl, I want to go out.
- Okay.
It's very sunny outside, take an umbrella.
I saw you!
come inside
Did this book guy come alone today?
No, grandma came with me too...
...but he's talking to your mom.
sit down
Wait!
Listen lady!  If you bother
me like this, I'm leaving.
Listen!  You are the one who bothers me.
- How is that?
I don't like anyone
to call me lady.
really?  - Yes.
Here, look at this
magazine while I make tea.
"Chandramalika".
Written by Rama Devi.
Don't read it, it's so stupid.
Let me read it first and
then I'll tell you what I think.
My heart!  Oh my dear heart!
You are like a spring flower.
How do you get rid of wasps?
All these colors...
- Don't read it, I'm ashamed.
What is there to be ashamed of?
It's really good.
Rama, who was the other
person with you that day?
my sister  - elder sister?
But your mother said...
Don't mind what mom says.
He reads nonsense anyway.
Don't you write poetry, Mr. Adir?
I don't write
poetry, I just read.
Rama!  I can't see your sister.
Has he gone out?
No, he is at home, but it is
not easy to take care of him.
He does not sit
still for a minute.
He works like clockwork throughout the day.
- Like a clock?
Don't you understand?, ask.
At eight in the morning,
he works in the kitchen
When he sat down at ten in the morning...
...making a list of items
to bring from the store.
At ten thirty in the morning he runs here and there...
...Find Mahadev, give him
money and open his shop.
At three in the afternoon...
...She is picking up the things she brought from the shop.
Anyone can see him
upstairs at four thirty...
Take home the clothes left to dry.
At five in the afternoon he makes tea again.
And this time?
- At this time?  What time is it now?
Now it's half past six, come, I'll take you to see him.
- to where?
come on
The only thing is that I did not
bow to Adir to come here that day.
But today, as soon as he
came back from college...
...Grandma asked if we
should go to Mr. Upen's house
Look how happy they are.
That's a good sign.
Let me go, bad girl let go.
So should I open my eyes?
- Yes, open it.
1, 2, 3.
Mr. Adir, all the roses here...
...the result of my sister's hard work.
His hands have magic power.
I can only write about a garden in poetry.
But he himself is really building those estates.
Sujata, don't you write poetry?
No, sister...
- Rama, I didn't ask you.
Sujata, you are a B.A.  What
are the subjects to study?
Are you talking about
learning with this?
This is a very illiterate, B.A.
How do you know what it means?
So there is no problem that
my sister did not go to a college
He can read and write.
Being able to read and write letters
A B C does not make one a scholar.
My co-worker can do them too.
Grandma, you said we
need to go home soon...
...He said you have
important work to do.
Come on, we're late now.  - Yes.
You go to the car
and I will meet Charu.
Mr. Adir, what happened?
-Nirmal?
Who were you thinking about?
- About myself.
I still can't find you.
How can I send you this letter?
No, I was thinking about my own problems.
Oh, I believe you, so
after all these years...
...you've got a problem of your own.
Good, very good.
Mr. Adir!
I didn't think you would come today.
why?  Did I do something wrong?
- Yes, it's a mistake.
It's great if you make mistakes like that every day.
Why are you standing here?
Let's go inside.
let's go
Mr. Adir established a
badminton team in our college.
Now we are divided
into two groups.
Some people say that only
girls should be in that group...
...Men are not good to be its members.
But I don't agree with that.
We must also give a chance to the
needy boys.  What do you say about that?
Why are you looking around?
Rama, it's six o'clock.  Your sister
should be in the garden now, right?
Who is Sujata?
- Yes - Yes, he wants to stay in the garden.
Then you meet him, I'll go.
Where are you going?
- I said I have a match.
Rama might be studying in the room.
No, I just met him.
He went out to play.
Sujata!
You look so beautiful in this garden.
Do you know what your greatest quality is?
- attribute?  - Yes.
Your greatest quality is
that you have no such quality.
how is aunt  - Is that the
answer I get for what I said?
So tell me what I want to say.
You can tell my qualities.
You have many qualities.
I don't have the strength to say it all.
Then tell me my mistakes.
- Wrong?
Yes, my biggest mistake.
- I don't know, I don't understand.
Really?  don't you understand
My biggest mistake was
coming here just to see you.
Mom's in, wanna meet her?
Let's go and meet him.
Mom!  Mr. Adir has come.
- Adir?  Come on son
Rama!  - He went out to play.
He may not know that you have come.
No, he met me and left.
left you and went to play?
Is playing that important?
Please don't think about them, son.
what are you
doing here  go inside
Sit down, I'll make some tea".
- Please don't worry.
I just came here to see you.
No, son, you just came.
- I'll come another day.
Oh, come on, son.
Rama!  - Why what?
Why did it take so long to come today?
Had drama training in college...
- That's okay.
I ask, when will you grow up?
- why?  what happened
Adir came this evening,
but did you leave him?
At that time I had a match.
- Is that game worth it to you?
I don't know what Adir was
thinking about knowing some customs.
Listen mom, I know what Mr. Adir
wants and what he doesn't want.
Your exam is coming up...
...but you sleep soundly
with the book in your hand.
I do what I like.
What are they for you?
why?  Aren't I your sister?
If you fall asleep
while studying again...
...I pour cold water on my head.
I will beat you before that.
Is Mr. Upen at home?
Yes he is, sit
down;  I will call him.
Hello Mr. Upen, how are you?
Hello, I'm sorry I
didn't catch you.
You had placed an ad in a
newspaper about a girl's marriage...
Yes, yes, sit down.
Listen, Mr. Upen, I
came here today...
...not because my boy is unmarried.
My wish is...
...get together with
a good family like you.
I am lucky that you are here.
So, what are you
waiting for?  I ask...
No, no, nothing like that, I
think very freely in this matter.
I do not expect
anything as dowry.
Mr. Upen asking for
a dowry is very low.
But if you give me something
willingly, I will accept it.
You have very valuable ideas.
Such bad things are
ruining our society, sir.
I don't think money
is very important.
The real value is
that man's character...
...His culture, his ability.
Money is not a big thing.
What matters is the person.
If man is not important,
what can I do with money?
eat them
Oh my God!  When
will our society improve?
Only for people with advanced ideas...
...a society can be developed.
So, what does your son do?
My son B.A.  Passed, Mr. Upen.
- is it.
He is good looking.
But a very free man.
I don't want to do a job.
He wants to start
his own business.
You know you need
money to start a business.
There is a big competition...
- Don't worry about it.
I will take care of
everything for his business.
That's what I expected from you.
Now your daughter is mine...
Sorry, but she is
not my own daughter.
She is like a daughter to me.
- There is no difference.
He might be your relative's child.
- No.
then?
- I think I should make everything clear...
...for someone with good ideas like you.
Actually that girl is of low caste.
I didn't expect this from you.
- But someone like you who thinks new way...
Forget it!  I should
have thought again...
...If this girl was a
drunkard or a blind person.
Be careful!  Next time, don't make fools of
people by placing advertisements in the newspaper.
got it  bye Bye.
Did you hear what that man said?
Come on auntie.  Come on Adir.
Where is Rama Charu?
- Come on aunty.
oh god  - Here is Rama.
Rama, talk to aunt.
God bless you!  Good luck!
Put this here.
Adir says this will suit you.
Very nice!
Look at her, isn't she beautiful?
Here, sister, keep this.
That's really nice of you Rama.
shut up
Come, Mrs. Gupta.
Sha!  Your daughter is so beautiful!
like a moon
No, Mrs. Gupta, you are wrong.
Our daughter Rama is holding her hand.
- And this one?
This is Sujata.  But she
is also like our daughter.
Bring on the sweetness.
here  - Thank you sir.
Listen till Charu Sujata
stays in this house...
...We cannot marry
Rama and Adir.
You know how hard we
work to tie him up, aunty.
You always say the same thing.
Sujata is also trying to find a
boy from an important family.
Forget them.  It doesn't matter
what a low caste girl wants.
It is beyond your limits.
I will call our driver
and find someone better.
why aunty
Your college friends say
they want to hear your song.
Today is my birthday,
so why am I singing?
Meena sings.
-Okay, I'll sing the song;  But you play the piano.
agree
Look what I brought you Rama!
Why are you taking Rama in
your lap and feeding him today?
Why is he dressed
so nicely today?
Today is my
birthday, that's what
Come on!  - Yes ma'am?
- Wipe his mouth.
Have a birthday too mom.
I want to dress
like Rama too, mom!
Have a birthday too mom.
I too will sit on your lap
and eat kheer, mother!  Mom!
Take him away again, he is bothering me.
- do not...
I'm not going, let me go!
Come on.  - Let me go!
Bad boy!  I'll put it in
the room now and lock it.
Mom, have a birthday for me too.
Mom, have a birthday for me too
Mom!
Have a birthday too mom.
Mom!  - Sujata!
Why did you come from the party?
- Why did you come from the party?
I don't understand.
- But I understood everything.
There is no one who can
understand everything in this world.
But I can.
That's a very small problem.
Why is Sujata thinking so much about it?
what's the problem  - Your
mother doesn't call you daughter.
Why are you crying Sujata?
You are Mr. Upen's daughter.
Who says no?
do you believe it
- Without a doubt.
say it again
I can say that a thousand times.
The truth is that you are Mr. Upen's daughter.
Sujata, when is your birthday?
It has been erased from memory.
I didn't understand.
If you understand so
much, why not this?
No one knows
when my birthday is.
I think they know.  - Who?
- Stars glittering in the sky.
The stars must have
shone like this that day.
Sujata, if I tell you…
...that you want to give me
a present for your birthday?
Do you accept it?
Tell me Sujata.
I got that gift.  - Got it?
How is that?
At least you thought so...
...that the girl without
a birthday is also human.
You understood his pain.
I do not expect a greater gift.
Sujata!
But I am very scared.
I can't take that much joy.
Sujata!
Madam, they have come.  - Who?
You told the driver to find
someone good for Sujata...
...so he came with someone.
ok come on
Didn't that guy come with you?
- I am the one.
what do you do for
a living  - Tell him.
He has a shop in his village
Have you been married before?
- Yes.
I... I have been alone for two
years... .  I have... two children.
They are so bad...
that's why I... say!
OK, I'll get everything
ready and let you know.
He has a lot of money, but he's a little old...
- That's okay.
Money is more valuable.
Who is this, Aunt Ah?
Has Rama come to you?
Yes, Rama was
here before this...
...Adiru also said he wanted to come there.
But remember this, Charu.
Do not bring Sujathava to the play.
I mean if he gets there...
Ok aunty, everything
will be fine -yes.
Shall I tell you
more good news, sir?
I found someone suitable for Sujata.
I will tell you everything
when we meet this evening.
Listen Sujata, there is a
play in Rama's college today...
Yes mom, I remember I
would wear that pink saree.
Listen Sujata, Aunty is also coming over...
Okay mom, I'm not going.
It took you a long time to come.
where is sister  - He
had some homework.
He can grow up anytime!
Even though I asked so much, he did not come.
The last bell rang.
You go sit down.
First there is a Manipuri
dance and next is my play.
I need to put on my makeup until then.
- Come on.
Grandma, I won't
wait until the end.
I have some work
to do with a professor.
You are always working.
How did you know I was here?
- My heart told me.
You are Chandalika
in Rama's college...
...didn't go to the play?
I went.  - So?
I came from there
for a reason - really?
Are you lying too?
- Yes, I say.
But it doesn't bother anyone...
...only if it's not
something that I gain from.
I have seen the drama
Chandalika several times.
Yes, how is it?
- Don't you know its story?  - No.
Then why didn't you come there?
just
It's a beautiful story.
- Please tell me.
Bishmanand is a good
disciple of Buddha.
One day, while walking in
the sun, he felt very sick.
As he approached a well he saw.
...a girl draws water from it.
Son!  Could you give
me some water, please?
No, sir, I'm sorry.
- Why is that?
I was born in a very low caste.
You have misunderstood
the child, just like us.
This comforts everyone...
...everyone's thirty nivana
water belongs to everyone.
But sir, I belong to the Shudra caste.
- That's a lie.
Oh beautiful children,
the monsoons bring...
...Black clouds are also
called Chandal Megha.
But does the water coming
from those clouds get dirty?
When Janaki stopped in the forest...
...Chandal also brings
water for him to bathe.
If I give you water,
it will be a sin for you.
How can I commit
that heinous sin?
No, children, that would
do me a lot of good.
Don't let yourself down.
Buddha said if someone
insults himself...
...that it is a greater
sin than suicide.
I am very tired children
please give me some water.
That Chandal girl quenched
Bishmanand's thirst.
He blessed him.
Since then, he considered
himself as a human being...
...not as a low caste person.
But that was in the old days
Do such things happen in our time?
Why Sujata?  Such a great
man was born in our time...
...for the lower
castes all their lives...
...someone dedicated to
stopping injustice from happening.
Mr. Gandhi.
haven't you heard...
...the story about the
low caste girl Lakshmi?
Gandhi treated Lakshmi
as his own daughter...
...He allowed him to stay
in his Ashram in Ahmedabad.
Then a big problem arose.
People stopped supporting
the ashram because of that girl.
But Gandhi did not
change his mind.
How can a man
belittle another man...
...that too based on religion?
He could not bear the
humiliation of this religion.
He faced the hatred of
those who supported him...
...but he did not expel
that girl from the ashram.
Finally, the ashram came to the point where it had to be closed.
Next, as if by God's blessing...
...The ashram received a grant of 13,000 rupees.
Gandhi's patience paid off.
why this  why are you crying
I'm not crying.
Who can cry when hearing
such a beautiful story?
Today I feel like everything
here is more beautiful than before.
Don't you feel the same way?
Sujata!
Why do I like you so much?
Tell me Sujata.
- We're getting late, let's go.
Why are you trying to run
away without answering me?
If I know you like
me the same way...
"Oh Brother"
"Listen, friend."
"Ask, my friend."
Why are you silent?
Won't you answer me?
do you know?
I saw a dream Sujata
what a dream
You had a chandramalika flower in your hair.
There was a red sandalwood mark on the forehead.
You were wearing a beautiful saree…
...You stood beside me
like a beautiful statue.
Tell me, what could be
the meaning of that dream?
It means you have
beautiful ideas.
Sujata, don't skip the question.
Tell me, like in that dream,
when will you come to me?
Any day you like.
At that moment I will be yours...
In that moment you will be mine...
Say it out loud.
Now I only know the tune.
I can't find the right words.
Tell me directly that you can't
sing, why do you apologize?
I promise, Sujatha, as soon as I
get the words, I will sing for you.
Sujata!
- Brother Mahadev?  Come on.
The husband and wife
have come - and Rama?
Lady Rama has not come yet.
Aunt Sujata is looking for someone.
Now it is not a good thing
to delay this issue any more.
But he is older than him.
- We don't have time to choose between good and bad.
Where can we find a
good young man for him?
I don't like the way Adir
suddenly got up from the drama.
I don't know what happened.
Maybe he has
important work to do.
No, boys are very different these days.
It is very difficult to
understand their ideas.
Aunt says Adir is
ready to marry Rama...
...There is no need to wait
until Rama finishes the exam.
If Rama can't marry a gem
like Adir, I am very afraid for him.
hello  - Hello Sujata, I only
remembered the tune at that time.
Now I found the words, listen.
are you smiling  Apparently
you don't like my song.
No, no, I'm not laughing.
Everything I told you today
on the river bank was a lie.
Pure lies please
forget all that.
What are you talking about Sujata?
- Yes.
If you want to see me happy,
don't tell aunty any of these things.
Neither he nor my parents want it.
I'm asking you, don't
ask me about it again.
Sujata!  Sujata!
Listen, Sujata...
Monara Ragum Devi;
His eyes are open.
See the sky absorbed in thought.
Today my dreams have come true.
We have joined.
The music of this rain...
How are you sister?
do you eat tamarind  - No.
- Eat them, they are very tasty.
Rama!  Why does Mr. Adir
praise you so much?
who  Mr. Adir, are you praising me?
In any case, you are going to praise
me, why is there something to ask?
But... Why is Mr. Adir
especially praised?
Even the cook who
makes the roti praises me.
No Rama, this is no joke.
Please think.
- What are you trying to say?
Good people like Mr. Adir
are very few in this world.
There is no doubt about it.
I'm afraid he will be sad.
What should I do if he
has inherited sadness?
Sister, I can't speak any more names.
I'm leaving.
I brought tea, father.
- Where is mom?
It's coming too.
why this  why are you sad
There's nothing wrong with you, right?
- Nothing like that, dad, I'm fine.
Aunt just spoke.
He has decided Sujata's marriage.
- Did he do that?
At least we didn't see that kiss.
Don't go creating problems now.
If Sujata doesn't get married soon...
...We will also have to postpone
the marriage of Rama and Adir.
The girls of this time.
You never know when
they will change their mind.
If we lose someone so good, I
will not be able to bear my grief.
I came to talk to you and
make a decision.  If you think...
Don't make the same mistake
again, I can't marry you.
why not
Because it will be a big loss for you.
I am smart enough to think
about my profit and loss.
Then why are you
doing such a stupid thing?
You can find a
better wife than me.
No, I can't find one.
You belong to an important family.
You belong to a high caste.
You know that, right?
- Yes, I know.
Then you know
your lower caste...
...that there are many people in castes.
- Yes.
The thoughts of low people are also very low.
What happened to you Sujata?
Why are you reading
nonsense today?
There is a reason for that.
- what?
I do not belong to your caste.
Are you trying to say that
you are not related to Mr. Upen?
There is a blood relation with it...
...I don't even
belong to his club.
I belong to a very low caste,
I belong to the lowest caste.
So?  why don't you talk
Will you come back to find me?
Do you want to marry me now?
Are you trying to scare me, Sujata?
It can't be!
I don't like that caste discrimination.
Whoever you are, you are my dream.
You taught me love, you taught me...
That's Mr. Adir!
In the name of God, say nothing more.
I can't stand it.
You still can't marry me.
- Why is that?
For what reason do you
say no to my love again?
Is there any secret?
- Yes, there is such a secret.
what?  - Please don't ask that
I'm telling you, don't listen again,
I can't stand listening to them.
Forget about a low
caste girl like me.
Imagine that the girl
of your dreams died.
Chandramalika flower is lost.
Why are you sitting in the dark, son?
- Just.
You said you can't even go out.
So where did you just go?
- To Rama's house.
If so, then you must have received the news.
-what?
That low caste girl in
their house... Sujata...
...his marriage decision.
The boy is poor in his caste but rich.
Sujath is very happy about it.
Okay, so you can
rest a bit, I'll hit God.
hello  - Hello Rama,
I'm talking to Adir.
Sujata wants to talk.
- Hold on.
hello  - Who is Sujata?
best wishes.
I heard that you are going
to marry a very rich man.
In the end, you rejected
my love because of money.
You know who would give
up everything for money?
Today I had to believe...
...that low caste people
only have low thoughts.
You are the best example of that.
What are you talking
about, Mr. Adir?
Who messaged you
about my marriage?
Someone I can trust.
Then come to my wedding.
- Why is that?
This low caste girl
rubs on your feet...
... He will shave his
hair and leave the world.
Sujata!  Listen Sujata!
Sujata!
Grandma!  - Yes, son?
Do you want me
to get married soon?
What a stupid question, boy!
That's what I live for.
When will a beautiful
daughter-in-law come to this house?
So prepare the
necessary things now.
I want to get Dighayu!
I will send a
message to Upen soon
But Rama's exams...
I want to marry Sujata, not Rama.
what  what did you say
I want to marry Sujatha.
Do you know that she is not Upen's daughter?
- Yes.
And you know he is low caste?
- Yes, I know.
God is the witness!
Are you going to marry that
low caste girl in front of my god?
Go out of my sight, go!
Is it not your God
who created Sujatawa?
Like Buddha,
Ramakrishna, Vivekananda...
...the people you hang around here...
...never said about caste
differences among people.
Don't read nonsense!
They are important scholars.
They are great...
...for thinking that
everyone is human.
It is a great sin to hate another
human being, grandmother.
Keep your advice to yourself!
Come to teach me about religion!
Listen well!  You
can't marry that girl.
She is a child of low caste parents.
I don't believe it, now
she is Mr. Upen's daughter.
You mean then she...
Does being born into the
lower castes change them?
Now then the problem is in the genes?
Then if a Brahmin child
was adopted by a Shudra...
...and still you think
he is a brahmin?
No, then his caste will disappear
and then he will be a Shudra.
So I can say...
...Now Sujata is also
the daughter of a Brahmin
Because he was brought up by
an important person like Mr. Upen.
A man becomes high and low
according to the way he is raised.
Shut up!  You can't beat
me with those arguments.
This is my final decision,
you cannot marry that girl.
So my final decision is...
...I will not marry
anyone except Sujatha.
From today you and
I have no relation.
Run away from my house!
You have no right to
my property or money.
my goodness!  Why are you giving
me so much trouble at this old age?
Lady!  The husband is about to leave
Lady!
The husband is really going to leave.
Please hurry lady!
Adir, where are you going, Adir?
Wait, are you really going?
- Yes.
Are you dishonoring your family?
...because of the desire of
a low caste who is nowhere?
I don't believe in that caste system.
Is your faith the only
thing worth to you now?
Is your duty irrelevant now?
You are leaving this
house for a small reason.
Adir, your mother died
when you were a small boy.
Since then I raised you.
I lived because of you.
I forgot about death.
But you...
Don't you think
about me even once?
Don't you think I
have no one but you?
You're Gyothin, I won't
be able to stay a second.
I accept defeat, please
don't go, children.
I open my hands.
Mr. Adir!
This letter has arrived, sir.
- from whom?  - From Sujata.
you can go
"Mr. Adir, I am
writing you this letter..."
"...because I can't say
everything over the phone."
"It was lucky for me that someone
like you loved a low caste like me."
"But to make you happy I
have to hurt mom and dad."
"I wouldn't do that for
anything in the world."
"They want you to bind Rama."
"If you want to see me
happy, please marry him."
"I've been with my mom and
dad all my life and I respect them."
"Of course."
Charu!  Born!
- Aunt?  Why this time?
No problem?
- No, nothing like that.
what's the problem  You look tired.
- Yes, I'm tired.
I am very tired Charu.
I came to tell you that Adir
wants to get married soon.
Really, that's good news.
But Rama's exams are approaching.
It is Sujathawa that Adir wants to marry, not Rama.
- Sujatava?!
Doesn't Adir know that Sujata is from low caste?
- He knows.
He knows everything.
But why did you allow this injustice?
I lost, son.
I had no answer
to Adir's arguments.
He grew up in this
new world, he learned.
Maybe he's right.
Times are changing
Charu, we can't stop it
But I also cannot change
my thoughts at this age.
It would be good if I also go to
Kashi and calm myself down a bit.
Born here.  - What is this aunt?
These are fifty thousand
rupees worth of bank shares.
I thought I would give
these to Adir's wife.
Anyway, I'll leave these
with you to give to Sujata.
Now it's better to give up
completely on being a loser anyway.
After everything, why Adir...
- It's not Adir's fault.
This is the bad girl's fault.
Is this how she treats our love?
Why are you angry Charu?
Someone hears.
She is like a daughter to us.
Not like a daughter,
she is a poisonous snake!
Charu!
I can't see her
dressed like a bride.
I can't marry a witch...
...of someone who took away my daughter's rights.
Shut up Charu!
- Why do I shut up?
We have created a snake.
We petted her, but she bit us.
- Charu!
What happened mom?
- Shut up!  I'm not your mother.
Get out of here!
I don't want to see your face again.
Charu!  - Mom!
mother
Charu!  - What happened to mom?
- Lady!
Come on, let's take him to the room.
Look Mr. Upen, he
has a lot of blood...
...His heart rate is decreasing.
I think he has a concussion
and we have to be careful.
Do not let him feel too
much anger or happiness.
And... come this way.
Nurse!  Check your pulse regularly.
-Okay sir.
Listen, Mr. Upen, I want to tell you
clearly the condition of the patient...
...is a bit serious.
He needs new blood soon.
I'm ready, take my blood.  - No.
First we need to see
what his blood type is.
Next, matching his blood...
...He wants to take blood
from someone who has blood.
Ask the laboratory inspector
to come immediately.
Doctor!  The patient cannot breathe.
- I am coming.
Listen, don't waste a second.
I will do it, stay with him.
No, his blood is not compatible.
Doctor, the patient's
pulse is gone.
Prepare a choramine injection.
What do we do now?
- I don't understand.
We need to find blood soon.
Is there no one else here?
- Please, look at my blood.
Sujata, you...
- Yes, father
Come, sit here.
Sahani, look at the blood...
...I will give the injection
to the patient until then.
So doctor?
His blood matches the
patient's blood exactly.
Same type.  - Thank God!
Come on, let's not waste time.
Come on, Dr. Sahani.
He is fine now, let him rest.
Call me at noon and tell me about his condition.
Nurse!
You've been up all night.  Go and rest.
- Okay.
Hello, hello doctor, I
am talking to Rama.
You said to inform
about mother's condition.
Mom has no problem
now, she is sleeping now.
OK, I'll tell dad then
I'll leave it, doctor.
Last night I was
troubled by this question.
what is that  - How did Sujata's
blood match Charu's blood...
You think even blood...
...like people are
divided into high and low?
What are you guys talking about?
He is fine now.
I will go home for a while.
What was Adir saying?
Charu defeated Sujata.
- Who?  - All of us.
You wanted fresh blood.
Neither mine nor Adir's nor
Rama's blood was compatible.
But Sujata's blood...
- What are you talking about?
Did Sujata save me by giving her blood?
Don't get up... lie down.
But...how did his
blood match mine?
Don't ask me that, sir.
Only God can answer that.
He is the one who made me,
made you and made Sujatawa.
Maybe he treated
everyone the same.
We lost very badly, Charu.
After Sujata saved you
by giving her blood...
...Now he doesn't owe us anything
He paid us back for
everything we did to him.
It's true, now we have no
reason to be angry with it.
where is he  - In that room,
the doctor told him to rest.
Shall I call him?
No, not now.
Sujata!
Was what you wrote in your letter true?
Won't your decision change?
- No.
It's a shame you sent your aunt here.
I can't marry you.  - why?
It was because of me that mother faced this trouble.
didn't you hear
My breath is poison.
Please go to save
yourself from that poison.
Are you saying goodbye to me with those words?
Say nothing else?
- I want to say.
Then tell Sujata.
- Before you go, promise me something.
That you forget me and hate me.
I'm leaving, but I don't
think I can hate you.
There is no room for hate in my love.
Sujata, you made a
mistake by loving me.
Yes, I was stupid
and I made a mistake.
That mistake of yours
now helps me survive.
I have no other way,
I have no other refuge.
Agree to what I
say and marry Rama.
You will be happy.
Don't insult me ​​with
such things, Sujata.
I cannot deceive Rama.
It is not a problem to be
deceived like this and bear it.
I will never see you again.
Here is your letter, what is
the use of this for me now?
Please forgive me, tell me
you forgive me before you go.
I can't spoil mommy
and daddy's happiness.
I can't hurt them.
Charu, Sujata has failed us once again.
He uprooted our mane first.
Here, read this letter.
"But to make you happy I
have to hurt mom and dad."
"I wouldn't do it for
anything in the world."
We are defeated sir.
But I feel happy
about our defeat today.
Tell me really
Charu this is really...
...are the words of Sujata whom
we thought was our daughter?
He is even better...
Today I understand
how much Sujata loves us.
He showed us our mistakes.
Talk to him, please, talk to him.
- Dad!
Dad!
I brought you tea.
Why talk out loud?  Get in.
No, I'm not letting my
bad shadow fall on mom.
Talk... talk to him.
- Come Sujata.
why are you standing
Leave it and sit down.
Not there, Sujata is right
here on the other side of me.
did you hear  Adir
wants to marry you.
No, mom, no.  - why?
I will never marry, I
will always be with you.
Every girl gets married Sujata.
- No, marry Rama.
Rama is married, but you
should be married too, Sujata.
You're like our...
- Mom!  Don't say that!
Don't say that, mom.
- Listen...
Like a daughter to us!
I can't take it mom, I can't.
You are not like our daughter.
You are our daughter, yes our daughter.
what did you say
Please say that again.
Yes, you are our daughter.
Mom!  Mom!  - Son!
Say that again mom!  I
couldn't wait to hear it.
Mom!  Mom!
Hey why is this?  what's the problem
Why are you all crying?
We are not crying,
Sujata is crying.
why are you crying sister
He cries knowing about his marriage
His marriage?
with whom  - With Adir.
what  With Mr. Adir?
You don't understand mom.
He's not crying mom,
he's smiling mom.
Look at this sister sister!
Look at this.
Look mom, sister is smiling.
Look sister, look at this.
You know son...
...we kept trying...
...to send you out of
our house but we couldn't.
In the end, you will really
be separated from us.
Mom!
Come on son, you're getting late.