Are the specs ready?.
Yes. I will just get it.
Take this.
Show me some nice goggles.
- Yes.
Kamala.
- Mr. Prem.
Mr. Prem, what has happened to you?.
Nothing.
You face is so fluffy and swollen.
Yes.
I see.
Remove the specs.
The money.
Yes.
Take this.
Your specs.
- Yes. Give.
Wait. I will also come with you.
Sir, goggles.
- Some other day.
He had not come to buy goggles.
He had come to buy
a girl.And he took her.
""Covertly and by making pretext.""
""Through my eyes, you
have started dwelling in my heart.""
""With gestures and style.""
""Pretty damsels
know how to make pretexts.""
""l lost my slumber
and the peace of my heart.""
""People call this as love.""
""What spell have you cast??'"
""That I can"t control my innocent heart.""
""l can"t explain to it.""
""Pretty damsels
know how to make pretexts.""
""Covertly and by making pretext.""
""Through my eyes, you
have started dwelling in my heart.""
""You can"t weave
the magic of your eyes on me.""
""The firefly
will it self came to the lamp.""
""Where will you
hide??Where will you escape??'"
""The arrows of the eye sare
not ineffectual.""
""Pretty damsels
know how to make pretexts.""
""Covertly..""
Kumar.. son, where were you?.
I had gone to meet Prem.
- Okay.
He was not there..
so I went to meet Satish.
My other friends were also there.
We all together have given the BA exams.
Everybody has decided to do MA, father.
And this is what I too have decided.
First let your results come out.
You don"t worry about that.I
will surely pass.
And I will enrol
for MA in the next month.
I love it, father.- Good. Very good.
I have abundant work to do next month.
You want to enrol for MA.
I have to search a groom for Kamala.
"Dinanath, you have become very aged."
"Your eyesight too has become weak."
"Many times you
have made mistakes in accounts."
"So you have to resign
from the job from the next month."
Sir has left. There he goes.
Sir!.
Sir, please increase it by another year.
Dinanath.. I am helpless.
But I am helpless. I
have to work at any cost.
I have a young daughter.
I have to get her married.
I have to pay for my son"s studies.
Apart from me there
is nobody else to earn.
Dinanath, now you can"t work.
You have become very aged.
You frequently make mistakes.
Now there wont be any
mistake.I assure you.
I will toil. I will
toil,sir. I will toil.
Dinanath! Dinanath..it
is not about toil.
Your eyesight has become weak.
The office needs new people..young
people. I am helpless.
New people.. young people.
Sir, do me one favour. Appoint my
son in my place.
I will be indebted to
you.He has given his BA exams.
He will surely pass.
Fine. If he passes.. then
I will appoint him in your place.
Thanks. Thanks. Thanks a
lot. Thanks a lot.
Kumar! Kumar!
Yes, father.
Son, come.
Have a seat.
Son, I am sorry. But
you won"t be able to do MA.
I have found a job for you.
Father, this is even better.
I will do MA privately.
And now a days it is
so difficult to get a job.
Very good! Very good, son.
If you passed your BA,
then you will get my post.
Father, my exams went
very well.I will surely pass.
Then I too will become
free from the responsibilities.
You and Chota will have to look after it.
I will get Kamala married.And
I will go to Kashi.
I will have to search a groom for her.
Father, we have already done that.
You have searched a groom for her?.
- Yes, father.
You will solve all my problems, son.
How is the guy?.
Very nice. My friend, Prem.
Kamala likes him. And he likes Kamala.
You just have a meeting with his mother.
Fine. Tomorrow I will
meet his mother. The guy is very nice.
""Learn to feel shy,With downcast eyes..
..and a smile on the lips.""
""l have to go to my beloved"s place.""
""Learn to feel shy,With downcast eyes..
..and a smile on the lips.""
""l have to go to my beloved"s place.""
""When beloved calls, my
heart beats fast and I can"t move ahead.""
""He comes forward,
holds my veil and my arms.""
""l feel shy and l
can"t think of an excuse.""
""l have to go to my beloved"s place.""
""Learn to feel shy,With downcast eyes..
..and a smile on the lips.""
""l have to go to my beloved"s place.""
""When the twilights
of union will arrive..
..two hearts will become one.""
""When the twilights
of union will arrive..
..two hearts will become one.""
""We will lock eyes and
get lost in the dreams.""
""My bangles are clanking.""
""Don"t let the sweet dream break.""
""l have to go to my beloved"s place.""
""Learn to feel shy,With downcast eyes..
..and a smile on the lips.""
""l have to go to my beloved"s place.""
""Learn to feel shy,With downcast eyes..
..and a smile on the lips.""
""l have to go to my beloved"s place.""
Ramu.. check who is there.
God knows where
this Ramu has disappeared.
Accountant! Accountant!
Accountant!
- Yes.
Ma"am.. I dozed off.
You dozed off or you are in a stupor!
Since when you have
been asleep.Where is Ramu?.
Ramu.. he has gone
to buy hay for the horse.
Go and check who is at the door.
Elders have said
it right.Bosses only scold.
And servants have
to dance to their tunes.
Why were you ringing
the bell??What do you want?.
I want to meet Mr. Prem"s mother.
First you will have to
meet Mr. Prem"s accountant.
I am the accountant Kashiram.
Come.
Today I have come
to ask something from you.
My daughter Kamala..is very sensible.
She is educated.
If she gets the chance to serve you all..
..then I will consider myself as blessed.
Yes! Why not! She is educated!
You need a servant! Appoint her.
Accountant, you don"t understand.
He doesn"t have
brain.He only uses opium.
Ma"am, I swear on you.
Now a days you don"t get good opium.
Don"t say it to
anybody.I am in my senses.
Dinanath was twisting words.
My daughter has done FA.
She does the household chores very well.
And she is looking
after our house, accountant.
Yes. Prem too always praises Kamala.
Then what is the matter?.
Tell me. What is the affair all about?.
I can only give the
girl.I don"t have anything else.
I wish the marriage
takes place next month.
I am suffering from BP fits.
If the daughter-in-law comes
to the house..
..I will be free of all worries.
I will fix the earliest auspicious date.
Prem.
What"s the matter?.
Why are you looking so sad?.
Your father had come to our place.
Yes. What has been decided?.
Mother has rejected the marriage.
She has rejected.
- Yes.
Kamala, let us elope.
- Elope!
I was just kidding.
Mother has given her
consent for the marriage.
Really?.
- Yes.
""When you have held my hands.""
""Then do maintain the bond, beloved.""
""Look, don"t forsake me.""
""When you have held my hands.""
""Then do maintain the bond, beloved.""
""Look, don"t forsake me.""
""l will never leave you.""
""Even if the world becomes my enemy.""
""Look, don"t forsake me.""
""Look, don"t break my heart.""
""The wedding procession is adorned
with flowers.""
""And the palanquin is adorned with buds.""
""The wedding procession is adorned
with flowers.""
""And the palanquin is adorned with buds.""
""l have become yours for the rest of
my life starting from today.""
""Starting from today.""
""l will keep the honour of
the marriage intact.""
""Give me the vow, beloved.""
""Look, don"t turn back on your words.""
""Look, don"t break my heart.""
""When the blue sky
will shower down on me.""
""l will always
maintain our bond of love.""
""l have always
maintained our bond of love.""
""Don"t tarnish the name
of love in the world, beloved.""
""Look, don"t break my heart.""
""l will never leave you.""
""Even if the world becomes my enemy.""
""Look, don"t forsake me.""
""Look, don"t break my heart.""
Kamala, we will
get married according to the rituals.
But today with the twinkling stars
as the witness..
..beneath the dais of
the sky..in front of the temple..
..on the earth, l
take you my life partner.
And this is the wedding ornament.It
is a nice piece, sir.
I think this is good, Kumar.
Okay, father.
Then make one like this piece.
Only 1 month and 20
days are remaining for the wedding.
Sir, by that time I will make 20 things.
Accountant, this necklace will look
so good on Kamala.
I have lost my opium box.
Accountant!
- I have lost my opium box.
So I was thinking only about that.
What a beautiful necklace!
It will look so good on Kamala!
Wow, jeweller! You
and your necklace, both are great!
The attires are ready.
After 4 days, the
jewellery too will be ready.
We have to order
more catering items for the guests.
I hope tomorrow your results are declared.
- Yes, father.
Then your job too will be confirmed.
There will be somebody
to look after the responsible.
Look, you are there.
So the arrangements
are been done so quickly.
First!
I am sorry.
It"s okay. It"s okay.
Greetings, Biharilal.
My son has passed.He has come first.
When will you give sweets?.
In the evening. I
will bring Kumar along with me.
Kumar! Kumar!
Brother!
What happened?. What happened?.
Kumar, you have passed.
You have come first, Kumar!
You have come first! Kumar!
Brother!
Father! Father!
Dear, what has happened!
I am ruined, dear! I am ruined!
Kumar! Kumar!
Father!
- Kumar!
Father! Father! Father!
Kamala, who has come?.
The doctor.
- Okay.
Will the bandage around my
eyes be removed today?.
I will do it just now.
My eyes!
- Father!
My eyes! My eyes!
Father!
- Kamala!
Kumar died and I lost my eyesight.
Have patience.
Have patience, Kamala.Have patience.
Ma"am, if you get
Premmarried to Kamala..
..then you will get
her blind father as dowry.
And that 1 2-1 3 years old Kishore will
also be dragged along.
Then look after both of them.
I don"t understand what to do.
Get Prem married to
some girl belonging to a nice family.
And get abundant dowry too.
I don"t want dowry, accountant.
God has given us everything.
Yes. Only a blind man is needed.
Ma"am, remember.. once he comes here..
..nobody is going to respect you.
You think that Kashiram is a fool.
But let me tell you,elders have said..
..that relatives ruin the family.
Fine! I will get Prem
married to some other girl.
Mother.. I will marry only Kamala.
But who will look after her blind father?.
- I will do it.
Forgive me, Mr. Prem.
Kashiram always
thinks about your benefit.
And I will do that in future too.
Invite the blind manand feed two people.
Accountant, you keep quiet!- Okay.
Elders have said don"t
open your mouth in front of boss.
Mother, no matter what..I
will marry only Kamala.
Ma"am, shall I tell you something?.
When the children don"t pay heed to you..
..then the family will perish.
Accountant, what rubbish!
May my enemy"s family perish!
I don"t care whom he marries!
Greetings. Come.
- Greetings.
Come.
Are the jewelleries
ready?. - Yes. It"s ready.
Take this.
Look, this is the necklace.These
are the earrings.
And this is the ring.Keep it careful.
And these are the bracelets.Close it.
And these are the bangles.
It would have been better if you..
..had shown it to somebody.
What are you
saying, Ramnath?. Don"t I trust you?.
It is your grace.
And here is the wedding ornament.
I wish I could see it.
Ramnath, I will leave now.
Greetings.
- Greetings.
Father!
Dear, look where is
your wedding ornament.
Here it is. Father,Why did you go alone?.
Nothing, dear. I just went there.
I just went there.
Father, please don"t venture out alone.
Dear, gradually I have to get used to it.
How long will I depend on you?.
Till the time I am
there. Kishore,take care of father.
I will be back soon.
Father, if brother had been here..
..then you wouldn"t
have to wander around like this.
Son, then why would I have become blind?.
You have become
blind.Brother is no more.
Sister too will go after marriage.
What a grave trouble this is!
Father, who will earn
money??Who will cook?.
We both will do it, son.
No! I will do it! I
will give up my studies!
But I won"t let you face any hardship.
I will work and earn whatever I can.
Kishore! Kishore, my son! No!
I will educate you!
I will look after you!
I will do anything for you!
""Sir! Sir, passing by here.""
""Give me a penny.""
""May your pocket never remain empty.""
""May you celebrate everyday.""
""May you always be merry.""
""May you never be sad.""
""Give me a penny, sir.""
""Give me a penny.""
""Sir! Sir, passing by here.""
""This child will bless you.""
""All your delayed work will be finished.""
""He can"t sleep at
night.The hunger troubles him.""
""Give me a penny, sir.""
""Give me a penny.""
""Sir! Sir, passing by here.""
""l got ruined and the
worldis upset with me.""
""l lost all my near ones.""
""We have become
beggarsto feed ourselves.""
""We wander here and there.""
""We have become
beggars to feed ourselves.""
""We wander here and there.""
""My father is blind.""
""He has to face hardships.""
""He can"t walk properly.""
""Give me a penny, sir.""
""Give me a penny.""
Father! Father, I won"t marry!
Has this ever happened?.
Daughters belong to the in-laws.
Dear, you don"t worry about us.
Our happiness lies in your happiness.
And it is my duty to look after you.
It is my duty to
educate Kishore and make him capable.
Father, I won"t marry now.
Dear, don"t do this.
You will have to get married.
No, father. Till
the time Kishore doesn"t..
..become independent,l
won"t get married.
I won"t do it!
No, Prem. Till the
time my brother doesn"t..
..become independent, I can"t marry.
Kamala! Kamala, you
don"t worry about Kishore.
I will take care of his education.
And I will also make him independent.
But I have to look
after father too. He is blind.
My eyes are his eyes, Kamala.
We will keep him with us.
No, Prem. He won"t do
this.I know him very well.
He won"t come to
his daughter"s in-law"s house.
Prem, give me the duration of 7-8 years.
I want to mend my father"sbroken heart.
Till the time Kishore doesn"t grow up..
..I want to serve him as Kumar.
But Kamala..
- Don"t force your Kamala.
I am yours. And I will remain yours.
Get up. My happiness
lies in your happiness.
Ma"am, elders have
said, don"t procrastinate today"s work.
1 2 years ago.. my wife had
got a heart attack in the night.
She died in the morning.
She loved me so much.
No! Now I won"t get married.
Keep quiet! I am
not talk ingabout your marriage!
I am talking about Prem"s marriage.
Ma"am, you too get BP
fits.May I go to hell!
If before Prem"s marriage..
something happened to you..
..then his house will be ruined.
Accountant! I will
get him married on the fixed date!
He is mad!
Kamala, you are
mad! Kishore..come with me.
The marriage will take
place on the fixed date.
Yes! Yes! The marriage
will take place on the fixed date.
I have come to say this.Kamala is mad.
Kamala is not mad. She is making us mad!
She has made my son mad!
She can wait for 7 years!But
I can"t wait! Get lost!
I will get Prem
married to some other girl!
Don"t do this! Don"t do this!
My daughter"s life will
be ruined!I will explain to her.
You don"t worry. I
will marry only Kamala.
Mr. Prem, will ma"am live for 7 years?.
Accountant, you keep quiet!- Okay.
Prem! You will have
to get married on the same date!
Mother, I won"t change my
mind. Father, come.
Prem!
- I will be back soon!
Disrespecting mother!How
times have changed!
I can"t see this! God,
I don"t want to live any more.
I will be grateful.
Oh Ram!Oh Ram! Oh Ram!
You don"t worry. I
will get married to Kamala only.
Dear, I am depending
on you.Take care of my daughter.
Father, you don"t worry.
Kishore, take father home carefully.
Prem!
- Yes.
So you will marry Kamala?.
Yes, mother. I have given her the oath.
What oath! To marry after my death!
Mother, don"t say this.
I would have got married now.
But I am helpless.
Even I am helpless.
For your happiness, l
refused the proposal from good families.
But now I will see to
it that you get married!
Mother!
If you want to see
me alive..then marry..
..any girl on that same date!
Mother, don"t be
stubborn.My life is at stake.
Even my life is at stake.
Let me tell you!
If you didn"t listen to
me,then I will kill myself.
Don"t kill me by making me
so helpless, mother.
Don"t ruin my life.
I am ruining your life!
Is that why I gave birth to you!
I am your enemy! Fine! Fine!
Marry Kamala after my
death!I will move from your path!
Mother, what are you doing!
What you want?.
- Mother! Mother!
Leave me! I will kill
myself by jumping from the roof!
Then you can marry Kamala!
Mother! Listen to me!
You are under your father"s oath,if
you tried to stop me!
Mother, I will die!
That"s why I am killing myself.
What are you saying?.
- I am speaking the truth.
Mother, please think.
- I have decided!
Okay, mother. I will do
whatever you want.
Sister, somebody"s wedding procession
is passing by!
Let"s watch it from the roof. Come.
Sister! Sister! Sister!
God bless you, dear.
""Where have those days gone??'"
""Where have my days gone??'"
""Sweeter than
dreams,love lier than music.""
""Where have those days gone??'"
""Where have my days gone??'"
""Which pallid moment it was.""
""l was eagerly waitingon the window.""
""l was eagerly waiting on the window.""
""l locked eyes with you unknowingly.""
""l have forgotten those eyes.""
""Where have those days gone??'"
""Where have my days gone??'"
""Beneath the sky twinkling with stars.""
""l was standing behind the banyan tree.""
""The one who quietly closed my eyes.""
""Where has he gone??'"
""Where have those days gone??'"
""Where have my days gone??'"
""Oh my heart..""
""Oh my heart, don"t cry now.""
""The stars of your
destiny have gone into hiding.""
""The stars of your destiny.""
""Fool! Why are you calling him??'"
""Why are you calling him??'"
""Where have those days gone??'"
""Where have my days gone??'"
""Sweeter than
dreams,love lier than music.""
""Where have those days gone??'"
""Where have my days gone??'"
Kamala.
Prem!
Kamala.. mother forced me to get married.
Prem, I have no
complains and grievances from you.
I didn"t marry because of my father.
You got married because of your mother.
Yes, Kamala. But I love only you.
- Prem!
Our love was not meant to last for long.
It was like a dream of a pauper who
wants to own the palace.
It broke.
No, Kamala. Our love
was not a dream. It is real.
It is eternal. For my whole life l
will wait for that true love.
True love begins after marriage.
It contains trust and bondage, Prem.
Kamala, this marriage is my helplessness.
Helplessness gives
only sorrow,not happiness.
Kamala, I am sad. I need your love.
I love only you, Kamala.
Not l, but your wife deserves your love.
You should love only her!
Kamala!
- Prem!
Recognize yourself.
You are a married man.
You shouldn"t hold my
hands.You should hold her hands.
You should fulfil the duty of a husband.
I beg you. Go back to her.
And give her this ring..on my behalf.
Prem.
Shyama, look at me. Look at me.
This house.. it"s
wall.. everything is yours, Shyama.
My heart too..
- Why did you stop?.
Shyama, my heart is like the bird
who is forced to fly.
Before settling down,its
wings are broken.
Shyama, my heart is wounded.
I don"t understand.
Ignorance is bliss. Forget it.
Wear this ring.
- You only do it.
Why did you stop?.
Go ahead.
Kamala.
- Kamala! Who is this Kamala?.
Forgive me, Shyama. Give,
I will put the ring on your finger.
No! First tell me who is this Kamala?.
I lost her and came to you.
In her dejection, I became yours.
You ruined my life.You
turned my happiness to ashes.
Tell me! Why didn"t you
tell me that he loves somebody else!
Daughter-in-law,
love doesn"t satiate hunger.
This huge house,
wealth, fame..everything is yours.
You mean to say that
I have married this house!
I have married the wealth!
No! No! When did I say
this??You have married only Prem.
He will not be mine, accountant!
And a woman doesn"t
want wealth and riches.
She desires her husband"s love!
And I will never get that in my life.
Daughter-in-law, l
have drugs. I drink.
But then I become stable.
Similarly Prem"s intoxication will
automatically sober down.
Keep quiet, accountant.
What do you know about love!
Daughter-in-law,
whatever I have done..
..that is good for both of you.
Daughter-in-law,
elders have said that..
..elders always do the right thing.
And what younger people
do,that too is right!
This is the limit!
Ma"am, daughter-in-law is
very hot tempered.
God bless you. How
will you live with her?.
I have ruined my old
age by getting them married.
Father, I am leaving.
Dear, my life
becomes death sentence to you.
Father, what are you saying?.
Dear, I am right. I am right.
You have sacrificed my
life for me. I am unfortunate, dear.
You have to work to feed me.
Father, it is my fortunes.
And then.. not only for
you..I am working for Kishore too.
I have to educate him.
Father, he only will be our support.
I will leave now.
- Okay, dear.
Met Kamala?. She will
be very sad without you.
How many times I have told you not
to talk to me like this!
Why?. What did I say?.
I just asked whether you met Kamala.
You are mad!
If I was not mad then you would..
..have left me and gone to her.
You married one woman
and you love another woman!
Shyama, use your senses!
I don"t have any relation with Kamala!
I don"t have any
ties with her! Believe me!
Yes! I should believe
you!So that you can meet her!
I am not a fool!
Now either she will
live in this city or me!
If this is your obstinacy,then we will..
..Ieave the city tomorrow.
Accountant, sit.
What to do?. Elder shave said it right.
If a woman wants, she can convert..
..the house into
heaven..or convert it into hell.
Since the time ShyamaDevi has arrived..
..the house has become hell.
If Kamala had come,
then it would have been great!
The family is ruined!
Mr. Prem has left the city.
He took his wife along with him too.
His mother is staying alone.Elders
have said it right.
My wishes are different and God"s
wills are different.
What had ma"am thought and
what has happened?.
Dear, give me tea.
Kamala dear, get tea for the accountant.
- Okay.
Greetings. Father. Greetings.
Greetings. In which standard do you study?.
- 8th.
8th. Very good! Very good!
Dinanath, give me
this child. I have a niece.
She is very beautiful. She
is very talented. She is very sensible.
Accountant.. he still
has to achieve many things in life.
With a sister like Kamala,
all the destinations will become easy.
I will get him married..to my niece.
- Fine.
Accountant, take this.
Dear, I have
fixed everything with your father.
I will get Kishore married to my niece.
You look after
his education,get him married..
..then you can live your life peacefully.
Accountant, he is everything for us.
To make his life a success..I can
even give up my life.
Go directly to school.
And come home directly from the school.
- Okay.
Greetings, Kamala.
- Greetings, master.
Is Kishore not well?.
He has not been attending school for
the past 3-4 days.
He is not attending
school??Then where does he go?.
Hit this.
Oh God!
Let"s go. Time to go.
- Okay.
Where are you coming
from?. - From the school.
From the school! From the school!
- Sister! Sister!
You lie to me! You lie to me!
Sister! Sister!
Sister, now I will go to school every
day. Sister, I lied to you.
Hit me! Hit me more! Hit me more!
No, Kishore! No, Kishore!
Kishore! Kishore!
Kamala!
Kishore!
- Yes, father.
Since when I was
calling you.What were you doing?.
Where is Kamala?.
- I am here, father.
Why are both of your voices so heavy?.
Father, my mouth was full of sweets.
Sister gave me sweets to eat.
Okay. Okay. Kamala,
you got the invitation.
Yes, father. Tomorrow is"Bhai Dooj".
- Take this.
Give.
Kishore, take 2
rupees.Today is "Bhai Dooj".
Give it as a gift to Kamala.
No, father. You want me
to give sister"s earning back to her.
I will give her the gift when
I will grow up and I will start earning.
Son! God bless you, son!
This is for the past 6 years.And
this is for this year.
Brother, you have repaid all the debt.
Sister, even after
taking birth for 7 lifetimes..
..I can"t repay your favour.
You sacrificed
your happiness for my sake.
You sacrificed your life for me.
Kishore, this was my duty.
Seeing you independent..
onlyl know how joyful I am feeling.
And only I know how sad I am feeling.
Instead of passing BA and getting a job..
..it would have been better
ifl had to lead a harsh life..
..and visit your houseand
call you as sister.
Feeling pity for me,
you would have shed tears.
Kishore, you are crying!Wipe your tears.
Instead of wiping my
tears, sister think. There is still time.
Find a life partner for yourself..
- Kishore!
Have you changed your
mind?. I have got my niece"s photo.
Kishore has grown up.
He has completed his education.
He has started earning.
That"s why I have come
to talk about his marriage.
When do you want to get him married?.
You will have to talk
to father about his marriage.
I am such a fool! I
am talking to children!
Where is Dinanath?.
Accountant, I am
here.- Greetings, Dinanath.
I have got my niece"s
snap. Her name is Tara. Have a look.
I wish I could see, accountant.
I am such a fool! Dear,
you have a look and tell me.
If she likes her, thenl
too have no qualms.
Father, I like her.
Accountant, then the marriage is fixed.
Do you like her?.
Sister, if you like
her then I too like her.
Bhabhi, may you always remain married!
Brother, God bless you.
God has fulfilled my wish. Come.
Father, shall I make tea?.
Not now,
daughter-in-law.
Let Kamala and Kishore too return
from the office.
Sister has still not returned?. - No.
Kishore, do you know
why Kamala is so late today?.
Sister has returned.
Sister, you are not well?.
Kishore, I am fine.
There was too much workload.
Sister, I have told you
so many times. Resign from the job.
Yes, sister. Now you don"t need to work.
He is there and you
are working.It looks so bad.
What harm is there?. I
will work as long as I can.
No, dear. Now you don"t need to work.
Now you sit at home peacefully.
Father, I tell her everyday.But she
doesn"t listen to me.
Look, sister. I
don"t mind if you feel bad.
But now I won"t let you work.
I will write
the resignation letter today itself.
Accountant.
- Yes.
No need to come from tomorrow onwards.
Why, ma"am?. I am not sick.
No, accountant.
But there is no need for you to come
to work from tomorrow onwards.
But why?. For what will I be paid?.
I will give you the salary today.
But from tomorrow
onwards,you will not come to work.
Sacked from job! Ma"am,don"t do this!
I will be ruined! I
have served your family.
Now at this age where will I wander?.
Ma"am, I swear on you. I
won"t have drugs. I swear. Forgive me.
Accountant, you can have
as much drugs as you want.
I am going to Kashi. I
plan to stay there only.
Tara!
- Uncle!
Uncle!
- Dear!
Uncle, why have you brought the luggage?.
I need a place to keep
it and a she lter for myself.
I have lost my job. I
have come to stay at your place.
Dear, you have become
quiet.I will go away.
Uncle! Uncle, why are
you leaving?. It is your house.
You can live here
and share our meagre meals.
God bless you, dear. God bless you.
You said what my niece should have said.
Elders have said it right.
During difficult times,
our kin become strangers..
..and strangers become kin.
I will reside in this small room.
Oh no! The opium is over!
Accountant, opium is not good.
Why don"t you give it up?.
Dinanath, now I will have to give it up.
Now there is no income.
Father, I am going to the market.
Do you need anything?.
- Dear, I don"t want anything.
Kamala dear, from today onwards l
will go to the market.
Uncle, why do you take the trouble?.
Dear, there is no trouble in this.
Elders have said
that elders and youngsters..
..everybody in the house should work.
And it is my rule. No work, no food.
Give me the bag and the money.
I will bring the grocery.
Tell me, dear.
1 rupee sugar, 2
rupees lentil,50 cents coriander.
1 rupee sugar.. 2 rupees lentil..
50 cents coriander.
1 rupee.. 75 cents
sugar.1.50 rupees lentils.
And 25 cents coriander.
Hello.
- Accountant, come.
Give me opium for 2
rupees.- Buy some more.
If you give it to me on credit,then
I will surely take it.
I am going through bad times.
Somehow I have saved 2 rupees and got it.
- Okay.
Sugar doesn"t seem to be of 1 rupees.
Uncle wouldn"t have got less quantity.
Even the lentils" quantity
is less.I had asked for 2 rupees.
Even the salt"s quantity is less.
And coriander too is less.
I am not deaf!
I have done deals of lakhs of rupees!
Nobody ever pointed his fingers on me!
Today I got the grocery of 5rupees.
And I have become a thief.
No, no. When did I say this?.
It is possible
that the shopkeeper conned you.
Or maybe I am mistaken.
No, no! I am a thief! I will not even
drink water in this house!
I am leaving.
Uncle, I won"t allow you to leave.
I know that you can"t do this. Come.
Today sister insulted uncle.- Sister?.
Yes. First she told him to
go and buy groceries.
And then she accused him.
She said that the
groceriesare less in quantity.
If sister said it, then it must be less.
You mean to say that my uncle is a thief.
I didn"t say this.
- Sister says this.
If sister says it, then it might be true.
If what sister says, that is true..
..then what I say that too is true.
Sister herself is a thief!
Beware if you called sister as thief!
I will not spare you!
Fine! I am a thief!My uncle is a thief!
I have come here only to be humiliated!
Father.. the matter
has become so serious.
I didn"t say
anything.Tara misunderstood me.
Why are you sad for
this trivial matter, dear?.
Father, at times a spark
is all it needs to burn a fire.
I don"t know what
Kishore must be thinking.
You sacrificed your
life on your brother..
..he will never think bad about you.
Firstly daughter-in-law won"tsay
anything like this.
Even if she says, will Kishore listen
to anything against you?.
I have kept the tea.
I think you are still angry with me.
With whom do I get infuriated?.
- Me. Who else?.
You wanted to thrash me.
Now next you will pluck out my eyes.
These eyes?. These
eyes brighten my life, Tara.
Now let it be.
Today I will tell uncle to leave.
- Why?.
Sister doesn"t like his staying here.
She was complaining to father last night.
I don"t understand
why sister is doing this.
I myself can"t understand.- Forget it.
Motaram, give me 1 kg opium.- Okay.
You can sell this glass.
- Okay.
Dear, are you going to the market?.
- Yes.
Go and sell this.
- Okay.
I don"t understand
how these vessels got stolen.
As far as I know,
no stranger comes to the house.
Even the family
member couldn"thave stolen it.
The family member can"t steal it.
And outsiders can"t come inside.
Still things have
been stolen.That is strange!
The house couldn"t have devoured it.
Elders have said it right.
During bad times kin becomes our enemy.
Am I right, Kamala dear?.
Father.. I will go
and get medicine for you.
Okay, dear.
We hardly manage to
make both the ends meet.
On top of that
stealing, aliments.I am fed up!
Son, don"t spend on my ailment.
I will get well on my own.
You are getting the medicines.
No matter how much we do for him..
.still we have to listen to taunts!
Daughter-in-law,
how did I taunt you?.
No, you give us
blessings.I know everything.
Elders have said you can"t hide robbery.
Kamala"s face clearly revealed..
..that she is the one who steals vessels.
Everybody was
talking.Only she was quiet.
Yes, uncle she was so quiet.
Kamala is very cunning.
She is selling the household things
and collecting money.
She knows that if she
wants to leave from here..
..then she needs money for that.
Tara!
At least use your charms on him.
Keep money with you
only. Go.- Okay, uncle.
Today you have come
early from the office.
Today is Saturday.
Take the money. Give it to sister.
I will keep it.
Fine, you keep it. If
sister asks for money, give it to her.
Okay. Listen! I want a ring.
I will get your name engraved on it.
Fine. I will get it for you.- When?.
Whenever you say.
- Today.
Fine. We will go today in the evening.
Show a nice ring for her.
- Okay.
How did you get these vessels?.
A girl came to sell it.
Do you know her?.
I don"t know her. She
must be around 25-26 years old.
It must be sister. She
only has the cupboard keys.
Keep quiet! How much for all these?.
- 50 rupees.
Take this.
Tara.. I will buy a ring for you in the next month.
- Okay.
Kishore!
What have you brought form the market?.
The vessels were stolen.I
have bought some more.
You should
have brought something for Tara.
I am more concerned about the house.
Fine. Give, I will keep it.
Why?. You want to sell it again?.
Tara!
Can"t you keep quiet?. Go away!
Kishore, what was Tara saying?.
You want to sell it again!
Am I being suspected of robbery?.
Sister, I don"t want
totalk anything about this.
And I don"t want to
hear anything.Just end the matter!
But Kishore..
I told you to end it!
Why are you not letting it go?.
Tara.. sister can do
this..I had never thought!
You will ruin your health by thinking
so much about sister.
Let it be. Quickly drink your tea.
The show is about to begin.
Tara, I will not go to the theatre.
Let"s go. There are
so many troubles in the house.
For an hour or two
we will have a nice time.
Let"s go.
You get ready. I
will go and get the coat.
Kishore! Kishore,l need some rupees.
I need to buy father"s medicine.
Take it from Tara.
Tara.. give me 5 rupees.
I need to buy medicine for father.
I don"t have money! Your brother bought
vessels for 50 rupees!
And the whole month is left.
You don"t have some
money for the medicine.
You must be having it.Use your money.
Tara, I don"t have money.
- Even I don"t have it!
Dear, I have heard that
you are going to watch a show.
Yes, uncle. Will you come?.
Who is it?. Kamala?.
Yes, father.
Dear, you got the medicine?.
- Then give it to me.
Give, dear.
Father, take.
""l had to lead such
a life in this world.""
""Though I was sad, I had to smile.""
""l had to lead such
a life in this world.""
Though I was sad, I had to smile.""
""ln this world..""
""The days passed, lendured many wounds.""
""This heart had to face many hardships.""
""Still I had to seal
my lips for my whole life.""
""Though I was sad, I had to smile.""
""ln this world..""
/""l lead a miserable life.""
""l lead a miserable life.""
""At times I smiled,at times I cried.""
""l had to lead a lifeless life.""
""Though I was sad, I had to smile.""
""l had to lead such
alife in this world.""
""Though I was sad, I had to smile.""
""ln this world..""
Kamala! Kamala dear!
Coming, father.
Yes, father.
Dear, what"s the
matter?. Did anybody say anything?.
No, father.
I am sure that you
are hiding something from me.
Tell me, what is the matter?.
Nothing, father. Father,
I was wondering.. to start working again.
Work?. No, dear. Iwon"t let you work!
Already you are facing so many hardships.
Now I won"t let you work, dear.
Sister didn"t eat the
food that I had prepared.
She wants to cook her own meals.
Initially, only the vessels used to
disappear from the house.
Now jewelleries too
have started vanishing.
I can"t find my ring.
My necklace has disappeared! Iam
sure that sister stole it!
Sister! Where is Tara"s necklace?.
Necklace?.
- Yes, necklace! And ring too!
Kishore, what do I know?.
You do know the shop
where you had sold it, don"t you?.
Kishore.. what
is daughter-in-law saying?.
She is right!
You mean to say that Kamala is a thief!
Yes, she is a thief!
- Kishore!
Aren"t you ashamed to accuse her!
The sister who endured
so many hardships for your happiness..
..who ruined her own
life to give you a good life..
..today you are calling her as thief!
Shame on you!
- Father, let it be!
Dear, now what else is left?.
Today he accused you.
In the future, he will accuse me.
Father, I know
everything.Don"t force me to speak.
Whatever you want to say,
sayit today itself, Kishore.
You might not get a chance again.
- Father!
Dear, he is not your
brother!He is not my son!
He is our enemy! Now
I can"t stay in this house!
Then leave! Who is stopping you?.
Tara! Come with me!
Kamala, take me away from here right now!
Where shall I take you, father?.
Dear, there are countless wells!
Push me in any one of them!
But take me away from
here!Now I won"t stay here!
Father!
- Now I won"t stay here, dear!
Father, keep quiet!
Now I can"t keep quiet!Now
I can"t keep quiet!
I will shout and tell to the world.
Parents, for whom
you are starving yourselves..
..for whom you are slogging..they
are not your sons..
..they are serpents..they are brutes!
Strangulate them! Let them starve!
Father, calm down!
- How do I calm down, dear?.
Kishore used to get wounded..and
I would get worried.
The thorn would pierce
him..and I would feel the pain.
Dear, is this how
a father"slove is repaid?.
Father, please sit
down!Am I not your child?.
No, dear. Take me away from here!
I feel choked here.
Yes! I will take you
away.I will take you away.
Quarrels are common.
But nobody leaves the house like this!
Tara.. I think Kamala had already
decided to leave.
That"s why the vessels
in the house were being sold.
Yes! That is fine.
You guys go away from
here!I want to stay alone.
Tara, let"s go. These talks will increase
this poor guy"s troubles.
Come.
Greetings.
- Greetings, Ganga.
Who is it?. Kamala?.
- Yes, father.
Did you find a job?.
- Father, I will get it.
You have to wander around so much.
If the brother
wasn"t useless,then this..
..wouldn"t have been the plight.
It was better if he
had died when he was born.
Father, don"t say this.
Itis not brother"s fault.
It is all about destiny.
If good days are not there..
..then bad days too won"t last for long.
You don"t worry.
Of course I am bound to worry, dear.
You should have
something to feed yourself.
Now I will try to find some work.
What will you do?.
Father, you worry unnecessarily.
Come on. Rest.
""l got ruined and the
worldis upset with me.""
""l lost all my near ones.""
""We have become
beggars to feed ourselves.""
""We wander here and there.""
""We have become
beggars to feed ourselves.""
""We wander here and there.""
Kamala dear.
- Yes, father.
Whatever we have to
do to feed ourselves..
.. it is not bad.
Dear, I can"t see you
sad.I will beg from tomorrow.
I am there and you
thought of this.. it is not good.
You should have thought of
this after my death.
Dear! Dear! I committed a mistake!
Dear, forgive me. Forgive me.
Sister, did you find any job?.
Today too I am going for the same thing.
If you want to look after
a child..then I will get you a job.
Yes! Yes! I will surely do
it! Take me there!
Come.
Sir is there. His natureis very good.
He is going out for 1 5 days. Come.
Kamala!
Ganga, where have you brought me?.
I won"t work here. I won"twork here.
- Kamala!
I wouldn"t have
gone.But it is important.
It is government job.
Yes! Yes! Listen to
the government!And shoot me!
I am nothing for you!You
love somebody else!
What?.
Shyama, again the same thing.
So many times I have told you.
At least now don"t
talk about these things.
You know that this
will adversely affect your health.
Now I will leave.
Leave! I have not tied you up!
Father, I will also come.
Yes! Everybody leave!
Ramu,you too leave!
Dear, you stay with your mother.
I will get loads of toys with you.
Ramu, give Munna that whistle.- Okay.
Son, go. Very good boy!
Ganga, you don"t
understand.I can"t work here.
And I can"t even tellyou the reason.
If not for yourself, then
at least think about your father.
It is not easy to get a job.
Sir too went away.
It would have been so nice if you..
..had spoken about salary with him.
Now he will return after 1 5 days.
After 1 5 days.
""The moon is so far away.""
""lt prepares delicious sweets.""
""You eat in a plate.""
""And you give it to
the child in a goblet.""
""You eat in a plate.""
""And you give it to
the child in a goblet.""
""The moon is so far away.""
""lt prepares delicious sweets.""
""The goblet broke.
And the child got upset.""
""We will get new
goblets by clapping hands.""
""l will mollify the child.""
""We will have milk and cream.""
""The moon is so far away.""
""lt prepares delicious sweets.""
""You eat in a plate.""
""And you give it to
the child in a goblet.""
""The moon is so far away.""
""lt prepares delicious sweets.""
""The child will go to
visit the moon in a flying saucer.""
""He will play blind man buff with
the stars and have fun.""
""After playing when
my child will feel content.""
""My child will return
home with a gay saunter.""
""The moon is so far away.""
""lt prepares delicious sweets.""
""You eat in a plate.""
""And you give it to
the child in a goblet.""
""You eat in a plate.""
""And you give it to
the child in a goblet.""
""The moon is so far away.""
""lt prepares delicious sweets.""
You are taking such good care of me.
Even my own sister
wouldn"t have done that.
You can call me as sister.
As you wish. I will call you sister.
I too will call you sister.
Whenever I take your
name.. I remember that sinner Kamala.
Why?. What has she done?.
She ruined my family
life.She robbed my peace.
She snatched away my husband.
She snatched away
your husband.He doesn"t love you?.
What love?. I find his love as a charade!
His talks seem artificial and heartless.
As if he is always lost in her thoughts.
I am sure that he must be meeting her.
He always goes out
of town for 8-1 0 days.
You should have found
out the truth. Maybe you are wrong.
Maybe after marriage he
did not even see that girl"s face.
I don"t believe it!
I have heard that girl
has still not got married!
There could have been
some other reason of not marrying.
No! She only wants to destroy me!
She is waiting for my death!
My ailment worsens whenever
I think about that shameless woman!
Dear, give me 5
rupees.The opium has got over.
Uncle, I had given it
to you day before yesterday.
From where do I get it?.
Why don"t you give up having opium?.
I will do it gradually.
Give me some money now.
Uncle, I am speaking
the truth.I don"t have money.
I want to sell these
buttons.- It belongs to you?.
Then what!
- Who is your father?.
Motaram, the opium vendor.
Sir! Listen to me!
She is the girl who had sold the vessels.
Today she has brought these buttons.
These are mine.
Where did you get these?.
Where else?. I have bought it from
Kashiram, accountant.
You don"t get the opium for free.
Tara! Tara!
Scoundrel!
You betray the people
who gave you shelter! Get lost!
Tara!
- What happened?.
Your uncle is a thief!He is a scoundrel!
He had stolen the vessels
and he has stolen the buttons!
You too used to accuse my sister!
Because of you and this scoundrel..
..I banished my innocent sister and
father from the house.
Go away from here
otherwise I will kill both of you!
Get lost!
Forgive me. I didn"t know anything.
He had instigated me.
He is not my uncle. He is my enemy!
Get lost! Thief!
Scoundrel!You robbed my house!
Get lost! Get lost!
Take your luggage!
You found only me to make enmity with!
Deceiver! Beware if you ever came here!
At least give my opium box.
It is empty.
Please forgive me. Forgive me.
I can"t. Father might
forgive you.Sister might forgive you.
I was so unjust with them.
Kamala?.
- Greetings, accountant.
Greetings. You came here and cast
your spell on Mr. Prem.
You did the right
thing. Dear,recommend me too.
I too will lie here on the doorstep.
Your brother banished
me.I have no complaints.
Just make arrangements for my stay here.
Accountant, I am working here.
Mr. Prem has gone out for a few days.
I will leave this
place before his return.
And listen. Don"t tell sister Shyama.
That I am the same Kamala..
..whose name too
she doesn"t want to hear.
Dear, if you forbid
me,then I won"t say it.
Is she that same Kamala?.
Yes! That same serpent! Under the
pretext of job..
Sarla, it is the time
for Munna to have his milk.
Under the pretext of job.. Kamala has
come to ruin your life.
She wants to give you a brutal death.
Accountant!
Yes! Daughter-in-law,l
will be back soon.
"She wants to give you a brutal death."
"Let that witch come now."
Father, I am leaving. And
I will take my salary till date.
Why, dear?.
Just like that, father.
Now I don"t like working there.
They live in that
flat.- Thanks. Tara, come.
Father, I am leaving.
Father!
Sister!
Kishore, leave my feet!
Forgive me, father!
Forgiveme! I made a mistake!
I have made a mistake!
It would have been good if I had..
..strangulated you when you were born!
Get lost! Leave me! Get lost!
Father!
- Dear, you don"t say anything.
It was my uncle"s
fault.Father, forgive us!
Daughter-in-law,
don"t touch my feet!
Till the time you don"t forgiveme,
I won"t leave your feet!
Father, forgive her. It isnot their fault.
- Never!
Father, forget what happened.
What had to happen,
it has happened. Forgive them.
Daughter-in-law, get
up.Get up. Kishore! My son!
Father!
- Kishore!
Sister, make preparations to leave.
We will leave right
away.- Okay, Kishore.
Father, I will go
and tell Shyama sister..
..that I won"t be working at her place.
Let it be, sister.
No, Kishore. I should at least inform
her. I will be back soon.
Shyama sister.
Kamala! Come. Have a seat.
Shyama sister.. forgive me.
I am not going to
work from today onwards.
I am returning to my home.
Why?. Even this is your house.
This is your big heartedness.But
I will have to leave.
Forgive me if I have
made any mistake. Bye.
Wait! Today l
have made offerings. Eat this.
Daughter-in-law, l
got the whiff of food.
You have made sweets.
Yes. Today is the festival.
So I have made the offerings for that.
Have this.
God bless you, dear. I
will have to eat the offering.
This festival doesn"t come everyday.
Accountant!
Aren"t you ashamed to
eat the offerings given to others?.
Give it to Kamala.
You
don"t understand,daughter-in-law.
If you refused offerings,then you
will go to hell.
Keep it here! I say keep it here!
And go and take your share!
Sister, eat it.
- Unnecessarily you scolded him.
I did the right thing.
I don"t like bad habits.
You eat it. Come on.
Why?. What happened?.
Nothing. I felt dizzy.
I will leave now. Greetings.
Greetings.
Kamala! You and here!
- Yes, Mr. Prem.
Where are you going?.
Maybe you don"t know how
happy I feel to see you here.
And maybe you don"t
know how much sad I am feeling.
I used to consider you as God.
But you are not God.
You are a selfish person.
Shyama left everything for your love.
And you didn"t giver her that love.
Mr. Prem, you have
only given her unhappiness.
She is still waiting for your love.
She is not waiting for
my love.She is only jealous.
I was detached from you.
I wanted to live happily with Shyama.
I wanted to forget you.
But she always doubted our love.
She is not well. Believe me, Kamala.
I will even give up my life to cure her.
I too pray to God
that you both live happily.
I will leave now.
Kamala!
Shyama!
Shyama! Shyama! Ramu.
- Yes.
Go and get my bag.
Now I won"t live.
Save Kamala sister. I gave her opium.
Opium?.
- Opium?.
Opium! Daughter-in-law, from where
did you get the opium?.
From your box.
From my box! There
was no opium in my box.
For the past three days, I have been
surviving on another drug.
Nothing will happen to her.
Daughter-in-law,
you don"t worry.
Good. I am saved
from committing a grave sin.
Kamala sister.. now l
handover him and Munna to you.
Forgive me, sister.
Shyama!