Elijah.
Elijah. Elijah.
I am sorry, sir.
What is wrong with your arm?
The cruel Romans..
- The Romans..
For how long will our
God remain a mute witness?
Our God must have become old.
Yes. Sometimes,
even I doubt the same.
Doubt?
Emmanuel.
Elijah.
Beware.
Where will you escape?
Let me go.
- I won't.
Yes, I am an ape.
Emmanuel, you are an ape.
- Sure, I am.
Let me go. Let me go.
Let me go.
Yes, father.
That is bad.
You are a big boy now.
Big boys don't play on the streets.
Even you never did?
- Never.
When I was your age,
I never played on the streets.
All right, father.
Then, even I shall not play.
Bravo. My son is such a good boy.
Right, Emmanuel?
- Yes, Master.
Father, don't talk to Emmanuel.
Why?
I will not, son. Never.
Look, I will be going to
meet an Egyptian merchant.
I will be back soon, son.
I won't drink that.
Elijah. Oh God.
What kind of a bad omen is this.
Everybody, beware.
The governor, the great Brutus,
is on his way.
God knows better who is mad.
Who threw the stone?
Where did it come from?
From there. That boy over there.
- Arrest him. Get him.
That boy threw the stone.
Arrest the little one of a snake.
Emmanuel.
Open the door or we
will break open it.
Open the door.
- Open the door.
Open the door. - Open the
door or we will break open it.
We will break open it.
Open the door.
Let go of him.
Emmanuel.
- Let go of him. Let go of my child.
Let go of me. Emmanuel.
- Let go of my child. Look..
Help.
- Where are you taking him?
Where are you taking the child?
Move away.
He is innocent.
Emmanuel.
Father. Father. Father.
The criminal is here, My Lord.
- Let go of me.
Elijah. Elijah.
This child is not guilty.
He is not guilty.
I know who is guilty.
Mercy, My Lord. It was me who
had flung the stone. So punish me.
Punishing one for the crime of
another is against Roman justice.
Take him away.
Throw him to the lions.
No, My Lord. Mercy, My Lord. Mercy.
My Lord. Have mercy on my child.
- Emmanuel.
Father.
- You can't take him. - Emmanuel.
Elijah. Elijah. Elijah.
Elijah. Elijah.
What is the matter, brothers?
What is it? Why are all of you so anxious?
Emmanuel. Emmanuel,
why are you crying?
Tell me. Tell me.
For God's sake, answer me.
My Elijah is not harmed, is he?
The cruel Brutus has ordered
Elijah to be thrown to the lions.
Save him, Master.
No. No. This can never be.
Elijah. Elijah.
Father. Father.
Come to me, my darling.
Father, where were you for so long?
I am very angry with you.
Angry? Don't be, my dear.
You are the light of my eyes,
my peace of mind.
If you get angry with me,
then how am I going to live?
So, my darling is angry with me?
Go on, hit me.
Come on, hit me like this.
Like this. Like this.
Mercy!
Mercy! Mercy!
Have mercy.
Mercy, My Lord.
Move away, you wretch.
Do not be afraid, dear. I have broken
his fangs. He cannot bite now.
Have mercy, My Lord. Have mercy.
Do not let the blood of a
lowly Jew taint your hands.
Your virtues will be tarnished.
Unyielding as time, and firm as
steel, stands the law of Romans.
Go away.
Forget not that there exists a
law taller than that of Romans.
That of God above.
Let not the hands of
nature's justice..
..reach out to your daughter
to avenge your heinous crime.
No. No. No. Have mercy,
My Lord. Have mercy.
May God protect your
daughter until eternity.
May God never make you
grieve for your child.
May the light of your
eyes never be extinguished.
My innocent one, have the
misdeed of a slave's son pardoned.
I implore at your tiny feet.
With your dainty hands,
set free an innocent dove.
And all his life, he
will pray for you.
Father, why is he crying? Pardon him.
No, Lydia. He is a Jew.
So what? Pardon him.
No. Don't ever do that, my dear.
Go away, you shrewd Jew.
I forgive you.
Glory be to you.
Glory be to you, angel of mercy.
Elijah. Elijah. You are free.
You are free.
Elijah. Elijah.
Leave him. Leave my son.
He has been pardoned.
Pardoned?
Yes. The merciful Brutus
has taken back his judgment.
But what is the proof?
- The proof?
Ask him.
Foolish Jew. Roman
justice is irrevocable.
No. No.
- Father.
Elijah.
Elijah. Elijah.
Master. It is all my fault.
My hands are tainted with
innocent Elijah's blood.
Kill me.
Why don't you listen?
Master, why don't you listen?
Revenge.
Revenge against the tyrant.
Father!
Where is Lydia? Governess! Governess!
Where is Lydia?
She was sleeping right here, My Lord.
Where? Her bed is empty.
Lydia!
Lydia! O'Douis! O'Douis!
O'Douis, find Lydia.
Hurry up. Go, find Lydia. Go!
Why do you not speak?
Speak up.
My Lord, we searched every nook..
..and corner of the palace
but couldn't find her.
Silence. "Couldn't find her."
Couldn't find her, indeed.
Search for her, you scoundrels.
Search for her.
I know it in my heart.
This must be an evil Jew's work.
Search the home of every Jew.
Set their homes ablaze.
Do anything but get my Lydia back.
Go. Immediately. Right now!
Master. I have brought here
the apple of the enemy's eye.
Take this dagger and hack the
little one of Brutus into pieces.
Oh. Grief has turned him to stone.
I presume I shall have to avenge
innocent Elijah's odious killing.
Father.
- Who is it?
- Elijah. Elijah, my child.
She is not Elijah but the object of
vengeance for Elijah's death, Master.
The light of the tyrant Brutus' eyes.
Stab this dagger on her and
douse the raging fires of hatred.
No, Emmanuel. What wrong
has this innocent done?
Blood for blood,
Master. Here, take this.
No. No, Emmanuel. No.
You falter. If your hands tremble,
then I shall slay her.
I shall slay her.
Emmanuel.
- Elijah, look. I shall seek vengeance.
Let go. Let go of her, you cruel man.
Look. Just look at that.
Even she calls me
father just like Elijah did.
Fear not, my dear. From this day,
you will take Elijah's place.
Emmanuel, I have found my Elijah.
Open the door.
Master, Roman soldiers.
You must take the child away.
It is the decree of the
Emperor of Rome. Open the door.
No. I cannot keep
her away from me now.
But..
- Open the door.
Open the door.
Master, there is nobody here.
Escape from the back door.
It is the decree of the
Emperor of Rome. Open the door.
But, Emmanuel, you?
- I must stay back.
Or else they will follow you.
- But, Emmanuel..
Master. Go. For God's sake, go. Go.
Open the door.
It is the decree of The
Emperor of Rome. Open the door.
Open the door.
What is the noise for? Can you
not see it is so late at night?
Silence. Where is Ezra, your master?
He left the town this morning.
We want to search this house.
Where is the girl?
The girl?
- Yes.
The one whom you kidnapped
from Governor Brutus' palace.
This Roman man saw you.
But this Roman didn't see..
..how I hacked the tiny
child into small pieces..
Go. Look for her there.
Master, your slave..
has fulfilled his responsibility.
Goodbye.
"This world, alas.
This world of ours."
"Is a place where Satan treads.
Life here is cheap."
"This world, alas.
This world of ours."
"Is a place where Satan treads.
Life here is cheap."
"This world."
"In the shadow of the sword we live."
"On beds of fire we sleep."
"Before blind prophets we bow."
"And to walls we pray."
"This world, alas.
This world of ours."
"Ruled by tyrants.
Oppressed by religion."
"This world."
"Terror is our king,
and death, our queen."
"Injustice reigns
supreme at every step."
"Hunger is what people
harvest all year long."
"Tears are what people drink."
"This world, alas.
This world of ours."
"The skies rain fire
upon parched souls."
"This world."
"The world continues to
change every single day."
"But unchanged the fate
of the poor will remain."
"Destined never to
smile and to weep forever."
"This world, alas.
This world of ours."
"The downtrodden are sneered at.
The helpless are oppressed."
"This world."
Salutations, Ezra.
- Salutations.
Is this where you live these days?
Yes.
You have got a nice house.
Yes, Abraham.
How long it will
remain mine, only God knows.
Don't say that "God knows".
Say, "the Romans knows".
For quite some time now,
our God has left..
..the lives and deaths of Jews
at the mercy of the cruel Romans.
And He has made
Brutus the lord of hell.
Hannah. Hannah.
Thief.
Am I a thief? Then I will throw
these out of the window, father.
Don't do that. It is worth
ten thousand. Ten thousand.
Shall I throw them out?
- Please don't, my dear.
Ruth, stop her. She
may just throw them out.
Don't you dare touch me.
Here, keep your gems
worth ten thousand.
Is my child angry?
Don't be, my dear.
What would happen if the flame
were to be cross with the lamp?
The lamp would get extinguished.
Dear, the best of these
gems are worthless before you.
But these are what you love.
No, dear.
You are the one who lights up
the life of this unfortunate Jew.
Not these diamonds.
I do it for you.
So that I can buy every comfort
of the world for my dear girl.
..then take them and
throw them into the fire.
Happy?
Father.
My child.
There must be an
announcement from the Emperor.
Listen to the Emperor's announcement.
All the citizens of
Rome are informed that..
..today, on the occasion
of the 20th birthday..
.. of Princess Octavia,
the niece of the Emperor of Rome..
..a grand celebration will be
held before the royal palace.
Where gladiators will fight
and sorcerers will weave magic.
And the chariot races, particularly,
will be a sight worth watching.
Every citizen may join
in the celebrations.
It is also decreed that
every citizen of Rome..
..will shut his business
for three days from today.
And pray for the Princess' long life.
By order from the Emperor of Rome.
Signed under the
seal of Governor Brutus.
By Mercury, the
chariot races will be fun.
True.
May you be damned.
Keep our businesses shut for
three days, decrees Brutus.
Disgusting!
Princess Octavia. By the Gods,
the moon pales..
..before her bewitching youth.
She doesn't belong to you or me.
Well, the Gods have erred.
Princess. The garden seems
to be desperate for spring.
I am looking out for Prince Marcus.
He will never change. Not even today.
Why should he?
God has made him handsome.
Yasmine, do you see him the way I do?
No, no, no.
How can I dare do that, Princess?
I only pray that the
Emperor returns soon..
..and you two get married soon.
Brutus.
- No, don't.
Prince Marcus is not to be seen.
Even I await him, My Lord.
I think it is pointless
to wait for him anymore.
As you wish, My Lord.
Prince Marcus is
still not here, Yasmine.
He must be on the way.
Do not touch him.
He is a wretched Roman.
But he is wounded.
Fetch some water quickly.
Go.
- Okay.
Where am I? On earth? Or in heaven?
Please remain quiet, as it is,
your mouth is smeared with muck.
I have brought water.
The Roman soldiers are
on their way. Let's go.
But what about him?
- Wait longer, and we are doomed.
Come on, get up. Let's go.
Are you all right? I'd told you
the horses are no good on a hunt.
Let's go.
Why are you looking over there?
I said, let's go.
Please come in, Physician. Come in.
The patient's
condition is very delicate.
He's wounded in one place
but says he's hurt elsewhere.
You are very naughty, Antonio.
Very naughty.
The wound is minor.
I will give you a balm.
Even the mark will be gone in a day.
Here, take this.
Permit me to leave now.
Give a potion for smiling too.
He has forgotten how to smile.
You possess that potion,
Antonio. Not me.
Bear one thing in mind, Prince.
After applying the balm,
wash your hands properly.
The balm must never touch the eyes.
Or else, you will be
blinded instantly.
Okay. Goodbye.
Antonio.
- Yes?
Well, yes, even I am leaving.
How are you, Marcus?
The wound is better.
Why then did you not
attend the celebrations?
I was not feeling too well.
Marcus, without you,
all colors turn pale.
All songs lose their melody,
all pleasures appear so dismal.
Come, join the
celebrations and sit beside me.
No, Octavia.
I seek to be excused today.
Marcus, do you want me to
yearn for you even on my birthday?
My eyes look out for you.
I am feeling a bit uneasy, Octavia.
I apologize.
Stop laughing. Remember the promise?
The one I catch is mine.
Yes, we do remember.
What if I catch all of you at one go?
Then all of us will be yours.
That's quite a good proposition. Good.
Considering the fact that you may
not find a man as handsome as me.
Do not run. Do not run.
As radiant as the sun I am.
And to all I shall bestow
my rays. Come on. Come on.
Where have the girls disappeared?
Where are they?
I caught you. I caught you.
My darling, I have caught you. - Antonio.
Yes?
You are enjoying yourself.
But have you thought of the Prince?
Marcus is upset. Go
and try to cheer him up.
As you wish.
"Go and try to cheer him up."
My angels, come with me.
Come, come this way.
So how is the lovesick one?
Oh. It appears as if the sickness
has gone, and only love remains.
Antonio.
My mistake. Both are present.
The sickness as well as love.
Antonio, I request you to
leave me in solitude right now.
Solitude? If youth seeks solitude
then it is a malady, my friend.
..with the world's best known
cure, vibrant celestial beings.
Come with me.
Come. Sit.
Antonio, ask them to leave at once.
Antonio.
Do not abandon me like an orphan.
Take me along too.
Halt, you Jew. Or I will kill you.
Master? In Jewish robes?
And a secret, it must remain
at any cost. - So it shall be.
Leo.
- Yes, Master?
Yes, Master.
Listen. Listen. Listen to
what a seasoned man says.
But empty these hands are not.
A treasure of magic they hold.
So, tell me, what would you wish for?
A lover. A lover.
Why not wait for your
moustache to grow, young man?
But do not lose heart. In this
bag are two nymphs just for you.
Nonsense. Nymphs,
and in such a tiny bag?
Do you not believe me? Okay,
Look here.
- Sir, stop fooling people.
Are these girls or playthings?
Every lover is like a plaything.
Look.
Oh nymphs in heaven,
set down to earth.
Create magic and turn
the playthings into lovers.
"In my solitude, at dusk and dawn
thoughts of you come to haunt me."
"The heart is beyond control now,
eyes are all that remain now."
"A thousand unspoken
words the eyes conveyed."
"Many a time in the lonely nights
when on the moon I set my sight."
"Thoughts of you come to haunt me."
"My heart has become restless,
my eyes have a lost look."
"In my solitude, at dusk and dawn
thoughts of you come to haunt me."
"The heart was so crazy,
look what I have done."
"A malady struck me, look
what cure I have found."
"Somebody go and tell him."
"Thoughts of you come to haunt me."
"My heart has become restless,
my eyes have a lost look."
"In my solitude, at dusk and dawn
thoughts of you come to haunt me."
"Under a false notion I
was that the story was over."
"Everybody has gone away
leaving behind a deserted look."
"But sure I am, a
thousand times I will say."
"Thoughts of you come to haunt me."
"My heart has become restless,
my eyes have a lost look."
"In my solitude, at dusk and dawn
thoughts of you come to haunt me."
Madam.
Why are you so late?
- It is been just a while.
Do not lie. You went
to watch the performers.
Go and buy some fruits
while I buy flowers.
Very well.
May I ask, for how long will you
keep staring at that Jewish girl?
I am not staring.
Only drinking in the
Jewish nectar with my eyes.
But for how long?
Until she gives in and
agrees to come with me.
What if she screams?
Well, my arms are powerful. And she..
She is delicate.
Fortunate are these flowers,
for you cast a glance at them.
Cast a glance at me as well.
What do you mean?
When a Roman soldier flings
a flower at a Jewish girl..
..it has only one intent.
- To hell with such intents.
No, no, no. To condemn
love is a crime, my darling.
And crime is what the
Roman law vehemently abhors.
Don't you dare. Let go.
Don't you dare touch me.
Leave me. Leave me.
Not even your God can save you.
- Leave her, you brute.
A human being like
me is enough for you.
Move aside, wretched Jew.
Watch out.
Go, and inform father.
- Okay.
Move back.
Oh, God. For long must
we endure this atrocity?
Dear, you are back. Hannah.
Father, you must embrace him first.
If not for him, wonder what
would have happened to your Hannah.
Son, I do not have
enough words to thank you.
You have bestowed this old
man with a new life today.
How do I repay..
- What are you saying?
I have done no favor. It is the
duty of a Jew to help another Jew.
Come, son. Please come inside.
You have made us Jews proud today.
Hannah, my child, bring
something to eat for our guest.
Why do you take the trouble?
Oh. I forgot to ask
my benefactor's name.
Well, my name is Moshe.
Moshe?
- Yes.
That is a nice name.
But, son, I don't remember
seeing you here or at the synagogue.
Well actually,
I hail from Alexandria.
You must be here on business?
- Exactly.
What do you do, son?
- I.. My business..
I deal in diamonds and gems.
Fantastic. That is fantastic.
Hannah, our guest is
also in the same trade as I.
This is my good fortune.
I hope you will let me
benefit from your experiences.
An apprentice? - Yes.
- Never. Never.
I would rather have you for a son.
Moshe, my son, from now on,
consider old Ezra's house yours.
And as long as he wants..
- Father, let him eat first.
Of course. Eat, my son.
Are you going out somewhere, madam?
No.
Then, will somebody be coming here?
Ruth.
Ruth. Ruth.
Should I tell him you aren't at home?
- Don't.
So what should I do? The
Master is not at home.
So what?
I am not going to permit you to
be alone with a young man, madam.
Hurry, Ruth, or he may go away.
He won't leave until dusk.
Master is not home.
- What?
Okay. And she?
She? She is in. Why?
You have some work with her?
I have work with you.
With me?
- Yes.
Tell me, what is it?
- Let me meet her.
Working at a pretty girl's
house can be such a problem.
Why?
There is no value for me.
This way.
Chat with the cockatoo,
while I go and fetch madam.
All right.
Who?
Did you ask me something?
Don't stretch your neck too
much or it may get twisted.
Shut up.
Why get angry? I just said you
could end up twisting your neck.
Shut up.
- Pali.
Pali is very hot-tempered.
He got angry at me for no reason.
Ruth has spoilt him rotten.
Shut up. Shut up.
Pali, he is a guest.
Oh, my dear.
Is he telling you or me?
He just keeps on chattering.
Can I be friends?
- With whom?
With your wise cockatoo.
Are you very keen?
- Yes, I am.
Then go ahead.
Pali.
I extend a hand of friendship to you.
Pali. You fool.
Never mind. I have no
right to impose myself.
Oh, God. You are bleeding. Come here.
You are bleeding so profusely.
It is your hair that's
smelling so lovely, isn't it?
I am terribly sorry.
Stupid Ruth has spoilt him.
But I think your
Pali is in love with me.
Is this the way to express love?
- Then how does one express love?
Pardon?
It is bad manners to turn
your face away from a guest.
No, I was only thinking.
So was I.
About what?
How nice it would be if I were
to get what my heart seeks now.
A doll as pretty as the moon.
Then buy her.
- Money can't buy her.
Why not?
- Because she seeks my heart.
So give it to her.
I already have.
- Then?
I do not even know
if she has liked it.
Then ask her.
I am indeed asking.
What's this?
Why?
There should be something
left even for tomorrow. Right?
Yes. You must come tomorrow.
Father would be delighted.
And what about you?
Bid Pali adieu before you leave.
- Certainly not.
Why?
- Teach him the ways of love first.
Excuse me.
Goodbye.
Uncivilized bird. You don't
even know the ways of love.
Madam, then you only teach him.
Oh, my dear.
"Oh, my dear."
"I have fallen in love with someone."
"What do I do?"
"Oh, my dear."
"I have fallen in love with someone."
"What do I do?"
"What do you do? What can anyone do?"
"If you have lost your heart,
what can we do?"
"Oh, my dear."
"I was naive, I did not know."
"His look will make me lose my heart."
"Neither would I have met him,
nor would I have lost my heart."
"That's my mistake,
how can I complain?"
"I have fallen in love with someone."
"What do I do?"
"Oh, my dear."
"I have fallen in love with someone."
"What do I do?"
"What do you do? What can anyone do?"
"If you have lost your heart,
what can we do?"
"Oh, my dear."
"The one whose eyes have wounded me.."
"I will take a cure
for my heart from him."
"Neither would I have smiled,
nor would he have come close."
"That's what I have been
punished for, what do I do?"
"Oh, my dear."
"I have fallen in love with someone."
"What do I do?"
"Oh, my dear."
"I have fallen in love with someone."
"What do I do?"
"What do you do? What can anyone do?"
"If you have lost your heart,
what can we do?"
"Oh, my dear."
"What do I do?"
My Lord, the Princess is here.
- Which princess?
Indeed. There are two nowadays.
One is yours, the other is Rome's.
Which Princess, Leo?
- The Roman Princess, Octavia.
At this hour?
- Yes, My Lord.
You are a fool, Leo.
- Certainly not, Master.
Tell her that I am not in the
palace or the gardens. Nowhere.
Go.
Then where are you?
- In hell.
Where is Marcus, Leo?
- You mean my master?
Yes.
- He has gone out.
Where?
- To hell.
What?
- I mean, I do not know.
Why? Did you not tag behind
him today like a faithful dog?
He said he wouldn't go hunting today,
so he wouldn't need a dog.
Hadn't I asked you to remind
him about going out this evening?
I did remind him, but he had
to leave on some secret mission.
Please stop playing, Celia.
Heartless man. Cruel one.
Who, Princess?
Who else but the one to
whom I have given my heart.
Yasmine..
Am I not beautiful?
Does the mirror lie?
Would the mirror dare lie, Princess?
Then why does he not care for me?
Why do my charms not work?
Why does he spurn me?
But..- I had told him that
we would go out this evening.
But he has gone
somewhere and left me desperate.
Princess, he surely must have
been compelled to be secretive..
Secretive? From me?
Yasmine, there are no
secrets between two people in love.
Look, Pali, listen
to me very carefully.
You behaved very
badly with him yesterday.
If he does not turn up today,
then I will not spare you.
Shut up.
- You shut up.
Who is it?
- "Who is it?" Nobody.
What are you talking to Pali about?
You?
I have been waiting for someone.
Oh, I see. Then I have
come at the wrong time.
I will leave.
Please don't.
- Why not?
How is your hand?
The wound has healed but
the scar still remains.
The mark of love does not go
away that easily, does it?
Why is the dressing
not removed? - Well..
I hope it didn't hurt?
- What? My hand?
So that's where it hurts?
- Yes.
For how long will it remain?
Are you happy?
Why would I not be? I have
found something to live for.
What's this?
The necklace which you had lost
at the marketplace the other day.
But this is not mine.
- Everything is yours.
This dawn, its sunlight..
..me, as well as everything I have.
You want to ruin me.
That's because you don't
want a thing. Tell me the truth.
Me?
I have got what I wanted.
The necklace looks so lovely on you.
Indeed. Like fetters
binding a prisoner.
Tell me something.
When will you be going home?
- Me?
When death beckons me.
- Moshe.
Did you ask for me, Princess?
You look disturbed.
Yes, Antonio, I am very disturbed.
I fail to understand anything.
Ever since the chariot mishap,
Marcus seems to be a changed man.
The chariot mishap?
- Yes, Antonio.
Can you find out for me, in
which world he remains lost?
Do not worry,
Princess. I shall find out.
I place complete faith in you, Antonio.
- Thank you.
Yes, I remember.
Why are you staring?
Am I pretty?
- Undoubtedly.
Wash off the muck some day and
look at yourself in the mirror.
Even the mirror will
break with your shine.
You look like a fairy.
A Persian fairy.
No girl has wings. It is we
lover boys who give you wings.
Augustine, look. There is
an admirer of mine here.
Oh, no. Three would be a crowd.
Love blossoms best in solitude.
In solitude.
Get out of the way.
You are getting angry.
It is unbecoming for a man
like you to fight this way.
Big brother. Big brother.
Blind man. You broke my back.
Broke your back?
Is it a back or a big sack?
What would you like?
Apples, pomegranates, grapes?
This seems to be a new shop? - No.
But I give special
treatment for special customers.
And who are you?
- Uncle, why not use a smaller fruit?
He is my uncle. And he is a bit crazy.
Crazy? My foot. Crazy? Am I crazy?
Why should you be? But why do you
not realize that you are my uncle?
Indeed. I am his father.
What? You are my uncle.
- Oh, yes. His uncle.
And these are real fresh.
Plucked from the orchards just now.
Yes. - Take this.
- And this one is from me.
How much is it? - How much?
To hell with the money.
We don't need to. It grows on trees.
Allow me to carry it till your house.
In spite of being a Roman,
you are such a gentleman.
Who told you so?
- What?
Of course, I am a gentleman.
Do you go to reach every
customer in this fashion?
Well, that's a family trade. Let's go.
You must be tired.
- Not at all.
If need be, I could
even carry a customer.
Really?
- Yes.
Give it. This is my house.
Is this your house?
- Yes.
But why do you go to the market?
And who do you think I am?
- Are you the maid?
This..
This house belongs to my Master,
Ezra, the jeweler.
Oh, yes. I have heard
about Ezra, the jeweler..
No. He has a daughter.
Her name is Hannah.
The three of us live here.
Three? Lies. There must be a
fourth person who visits here.
Shut up. No one else comes here.
Will you leave, or
should I call the others?
Sure. Provided they are pretty.
Isaac.
- Louder.
Jacob. - Isaac. Jacob.
These are names of men.
Mozart. - Oh, my God.
Jacob.
Escaped.
"Walking hither and
thither came along someone."
"Oh, heart of me, hide
not from me and answer.."
"From now on, should I call you
by a name your own or my beloved."
"Oh, heart of me, hide
not from me and answer.."
"From now on, should I call you
by a name your own or my beloved."
"Walking hither and
thither came along someone."
"To you I listen and
will continue to."
"The torment I feel I will conceal."
"How much more
should I control myself?"
"Walking hither and thither.."
"Walking hither and
thither came along someone."
"Oh, heart of me, hide
not from me and answer.."
"From now on, should I call you
by a name your own or my beloved."
"Walking hither and
thither came along someone."
"Oh, eyes so intoxicating,
what have you done?"
"For what do you seek vengeance?"
"An effect so
devastating these eyes had on me.."
"That my heart was beyond my control."
"Walking hither and thither.."
"Walking hither and
thither came along someone."
"From now on, should I call you
by a name your own or my beloved."
"Walking hither and
thither came along someone."
"My thoughts are all about you.
I grieve too only for you."
"To even my slumber I say.."
"Let him be present
even in my dreams."
"Walking hither and thither.."
"Walking hither and
thither came along someone."
"Oh, heart of me, hide
not from me and answer.."
"From now on, should I call you
by a name your own or my beloved."
"Walking hither and
thither came along someone."
"Oh, heart of me, hide
not from me and answer.."
"From now on, should I call you
by a name your own or my beloved."
"Walking hither and
thither came along someone."
Welcome, Emperor. Welcome.
By the grace of God,
may you live long.
I do not know either.
Perhaps he has gone hunting
He remains unfettered
by responsibilities.
The zeal of youth is
like a gust of strong wind.
I too have lived
through such years, Octavia.
But, my dear, your marriage
must not be delayed any further.
There is a difference between
coyness and refusal, Octavia.
Are you not happy with this match?
I am happy, My Lord. I am very happy.
Take a look at this diamond,
Moshe. It is so extraordinary.
It is indeed very extraordinary.
Truly exquisite and flawless.
But, father, one needs to be very
lucky to get something as exquisite.
With hard work and sacrifice.
How do you like her reply?
None can defeat my daughter.
Who could it be at this hour?
Ruth. - Yes?
Go and see who is at the door.
Is this the jeweler Ezra's house?
Please come.
Princess Octavia.
Blessed am I.
Thank you for coming here.
What can this slave do for you?
Are you Ezra, the jeweler?
Yes, Princess. Please be seated.
Moshe. What are you doing?
Look at that apple there.
- Forget the apple.
I must get it.
- Forget it.
The axle of my chariot is broken.
Please have it repaired.
I must return early. Or
the Emperor will be anxious.
Do not worry, Princess.
Till the chariot gets repaired,
please rest here.
Hannah, go and get
some fruits and sherbet.
Very well, father.
If you wish, you may
look at these jewels.
Where are you going, Moshe?
- To.. to fix the chariot.
No, no. You must stay here.
Look after the royal guests.
Such a guest could
craft a man's destiny.
I will attend to the chariot.
Don't take..
Yasmine, this is lovely.
Princess, just take
a look at that man.
He bears a striking
resemblance with Prince Marcus.
Ask him his name.
Excuse me.
- Yes? - Who are you?
A creation of God who
crafted this wonderful world.
But why are you hiding your face?
The cruel woman will beat me.
Who will beat you?
The one who is
preparing sherbet for you.
But why would she beat you?
In a moment of weakness in love..
..I promised her never to
show my face to another woman.
But we can be quite adamant.
Are you a man or a rabbit?
A rabbit I am not.
Who is he?
Him?
He has a gift of the gab. But
why doesn't he show his face?
He is shy.
Shy? Or is he sold out?
Princess, your chariot is ready.
Thank you very much
for your hospitality.
I have selected some jewelry.
Please have it sent over.
With pleasure. Blessed are my stars.
Yes. But why were
you hiding from them?
Me? Of course not. When did I hide?
I was only..
Listen..
That woman..
- The Princess?
No. Her slave. She was staring at me.
I will leave now.
Strange are Your ways, God.
Strange are the ways
which destiny leads one to.
The Princess of Rome comes
to the door of a petty Jew.
Moshe. - Excuse me. Permit
to leave. - So soon? No way.
You cannot leave until night, today.
Why? Anything special?
It is an auspicious day today.
Oh, yes. I will be
surely coming tonight.
Do come. Do come.
I am at your service, My Lord.
I was eager to see you, Marcus.
Very well, My Lord.
I wish to bind your wayward feet
with fetters of responsibility.
With the passing of
this phase of the moon..
..I want you to get married.
Do you comply with my wishes?
Why are you silent?
Marcus. I shall
overlook your audaciousness.
Go. You are given time to think.
I would also seek the freedom
to decide for myself, My Lord.
Son..
My fellow-brothers, eating
this holy bread implies..
..affirming our
allegiance to the true God..
..and to the doctrine of
the religion of the Jews.
The one who eats this
bread is a true Jew.
No doubt.
Where are you going, Moshe?
Moshe.
You lied to father. Why did
you throw away the holy bread?
Who said so?
What's this?
I saw you drop the
bread with my own eyes.
No Jew would ever do that.
Hannah.
Do not touch me. I did not know
that you could lie even to me.
Do not cast suspicions
inside a heart filled with love.
Then why do you not
clearly say what the matter is?
I am unable to
express what's on my mind.
I will tell my Hannah everything.
Everything.
Hannah.
You have guests at home.
So go inside now, Hannah.
I shall wait for you
tonight near the ruins.
No. I cannot come there.
Do not be adamant, Hannah.
You have to come.
No. Say what you must, here and now.
Dear, the guests are leaving.
If in my heart, lies love for you..
..and if my love for you is true,
then you will come there.
You surely will.
"Madly in love with you I am."
"Of my love, very proud I am."
"You may believe it or not."
"But people sure will."
"Call it a streak of insanity."
"Or the intoxicating effect of love."
"Then only you are to be blamed."
"Call it a streak of insanity."
"The heart yearns only for you."
"In love I am, only with you."
"You may or may not come here."
"But wait I will for you."
"Call it a streak of insanity."
"Or the intoxicating effect of love."
"If this you fail to fathom
then only you are to be blamed."
"Call it a streak of insanity."
"In such solitude and wilderness.."
"Stifled to death I will be."
"Beckon me a million times then."
"But return I will never."
"Call it a streak of insanity."
"If this you fail to fathom.."
"Then only you are to be blamed."
"Call it a streak of insanity."
Moshe.
I was sure you would come.
Come close to me, Hannah.
Look, how my heart
implores before you.
For peace. For love.
Convince me, Moshe.
Compel me to
understand whatever you say.
Look here, Hannah.
Look into my eyes.
Moshe, your body
burns with high fever.
My soul burns in the fires
of love, Hannah. Douse it.
What.. what am I to do?
Have faith in me.
Doubt not my love, Hannah.
Moshe, words are not
enough to quell away doubts.
Tell me the truth. Are you not a Jew?
Why are you silent?
One word from me, and a
storm of sorrows may break free.
Our love may get poisoned
with hatred.
Hannah, is it possible
that I could lose you forever?
Moshe. Tell me that
you are not a Roman.
I am human. Captivated by
your love, and helpless.
Moshe, tell me that you
are not a Roman. Say it.
Hannah.
If humans are known by such names..
..then yes, I am a Roman.
But there's no
injustice greater than this.
No punishment harsher than this.
Don't touch me. You have cheated me.
What harm had I done to you? tell me.
You have given me life.
With your love, you have
brought light into my dark life.
Lies.
Oh, cruel man, wipe off the
false twinkle of love from your eyes.
Do not look at me that way.
Go away, Moshe.
Hannah.
- I wish to hear no more.
Only because I am a Roman?
Hannah, look not at my religion.
Look at my heart, my love.
I have seen steel, and I've
seen stone. Go away, Moshe. Go.
Hannah, my love, your love has
pervaded every fiber of my being.
In these lonely valleys,
I shall die a slow, agonizing death.
Till my last breath, only your
name will be present on my lips.
But this much, I do promise.
You will never hear my voice again.
Enough. Enough, Moshe. Enough.
Take me away somewhere.
I can live with the
dishonor and seclusion.
But I cannot bear to be away
from you and lead a stifled life.
Then, let us go to a place
where men do not fight over Gods.
Where even the shadow of this
traitorous world won't be cast.
Come, Hannah.
Wait. Where are you running?
This escape will be very difficult.
You will be ruined by my curse
that will come from deep within.
Father.
Ungrateful Roman.
Is this why you
entered my house as a guest?
To lead my daughter into sin?
I will not spare you alive today.
Father. He is innocent.
- Step aside, Hannah.
Coward Roman. Have your
arms no strength anymore?
Do you have a heart, a
soul of a human being..
Sly Roman. I am well aware
of your wicked Roman ways.
You know nothing. Your eyes are
shrouded with misconceptions. - Moshe.
In the name of religion, you
want to strangle true love. - Moshe.
I want to rip the
weed off by its roots.
I shall hang your body
at the crossroads of Rome.
As a lesson to be learnt for
treacherous Romans like you.
I am in love with him. I am
the one who's caused you pain.
Silence, you naive girl. You
do not know what you are saying.
The truth, father.
Give me my dreams, my love,
my desire as alms, father.
Never. Get out of my way.
Or even you will be..
With pleasure, father.
Kill me. Kill me.
I will give up my life at your feet.
Alas.
..has fallen for a Roman's lie.
With great care, I had
nurtured my little girl.
Little did I know that she
would punish me someday.
Father.
Young man, this girl
is the light of my life.
Even a moment's separation
from her would mean death for me.
If you love her,
you will have to marry her.
Undoubtedly.
But before the wedding, all the
rituals will have to be observed.
Fall on your knees.
On your knees. You must
embrace the religion of the Jews.
Hannah will not marry an unholy Roman.
Did you hear that, Hannah?
The infidel whom you were
dying for, refuses the sacrament.
I refuse to abide by
these Sacrilegious practices.
These incorrect tests
of love with religion.
Get out of my sight, Deceitful Roman.
You cannot stop true love,
my ignorant elder.
Love will break through the
shallow barrier of religion.
Moshe.
- Hannah. This is deception.
Come with me.
My child, the venomous snake
is trying to mesmerize its prey.
It is nothing. You may leave.
Do you plan to drown yourself too?
Can wine give you what you have
been pining for since so long?
For the one whom you have
put yourself in this condition?
You are right, Octavia.
I love her,
and I want to win her over too. But..
But someone else.
Then why are you here?
Who is holding you back?
Rome is.
And you are, Octavia.
- Marcus.
You may gain freedom from me.
But Rome..
Rome will never let go of you.
Rome's prestige, power and
future are in your hands.
You are Rome's future Emperor.
And that is what stands
in my way, Octavia. It is.
Yet, you will have
to become the Emperor.
You will have to sacrifice
your desires for your duty.
Marcus, you cannot
betray Rome or the Romans.
Rome needs the future Emperor.
And that's you.
Rome needs a new
Empress too. And that's you.
Undoubtedly.
It is the desire of my nation,
and I cannot shatter Rome's desire.
Rome. Rome. Rome.
How I wish there was a way out.
If not for Rome, there would
not be these grand palaces.
Nor the vicious grasp of the
empire which is stifling me.
Oh, to be away from these confines..
..where I..
- And she.
She, the one who has
snatched you away from me.
Marcus, do not weave a world
of dreams and get shattered.
Like a mountain,
reality towers before you.
You must make me your queen.
Only your queen. Not your love.
I know very well that
you can never be mine.
I have lost you forever.
Yet, we must bring
false smiles to our lips.
We will have to prove
that we love each other.
Marcus, not for ourselves but
for our nation. For our duty.
My lips can be silenced, Octavia.
But my emotions I cannot conceal.
The raging fire may be doused
but its smoke can't stay hidden.
Marcus, you are the Crown Prince.
You can never break the fetters
of duty that bind you.
A prisoner you are. And you will
have to complete your sentence.
Either with a smile,
or with tears in your eyes.
Duty.
Love.
Rome.
'Marcus. Do not forget your duty.'
'Marcus, do not tarnish our legacy.'
'A Jewish girl is not the
price to pay for our honor.'
'Marcus. Cupid's arrow
was shot at me too.'
'But I poisoned that beauty who
wanted me to forget my duties.'
'Marcus. Do not forget your duty.'
'Do not tarnish Rome's
unblemished prestige.'
'Do not malign our lineage.
- Do not disgrace your legacy.'
'Do not put our souls to shame.'
'Marcus.
- Marcus. - Marcus.'
Marcus.
The vast Roman Empire
eagerly awaits your reply.
But, My Lord.. - I am not here
to hear refusals, Marcus.
The wishes of millions of
Romans cannot be sacrificed..
..for your childish folly.
I will announce..
..that the wedding of Prince
Marcus with Princess Octavia..
..will be held at the Senate
tomorrow with great splendor.
"A gush of tears gets
unleashed as I think of you."
"My heart is set
afire as I think of you."
"Grudges I hold
galore as I think of you."
"What kind of a separation is this?"
"The presence of grief
and pain is all pervading."
"The heart now yearns to see you."
"A gush of tears gets
unleashed as I think of you."
"My heart is set
afire as I think of you."
"Grudges I hold
galore as I think of you."
"What kind of a separation is this?"
"The whole world I would
sacrifice just for your love."
"A bond of love, so delicate,
how can I sever it?"
"A gush of tears gets
unleashed as I think of you."
"My heart is set
afire as I think of you."
"Grudges I hold
galore as I think of you."
"What kind of a separation is this?"
Hannah. Hannah, my child.
You are crying?
Do not cry, my child.
This old man still possesses
the courage to challenge injustice.
But I will not be able to
bear seeing you shed tears.
Father.
- My child.
Tears have paled the vibrant
colors of my little darling.
Cry no more, my child.
I tried hard to hold
back my tears, father.
I am the one who deserves to
be punished for this offense.
I have inflicted injustice on you.
A whiff of cool breeze had
turned into a gusty storm.
How could the gardener entrust
a delicate blossom at its mercy?
Even shedding tears of
blood does not melt stones.
Why then do you weep for
that treacherous Roman?
Wipe your tears, dear.
But have you ever thought..
My dear, my days are numbered now.
If you wish to see your aged
father live for some more days..
..then cast away
this shroud of sorrow.
You should face problems
with courage, not tears.
Where from do I seek courage, father?
The tears flow at will.
Even I can weep, my dear.
But with a smile, I say..
Dear God, keep me as You will,
and I shall be happy.
In Your happiness, I rejoice.
Your slave, I am. My Master, You are.
Even we have been invited.
You will also come, won't you?
No, father.
The unfortunate are not
taken for joyous occasions.
It is ominous.
- You must not say that, my dear.
Come on, let's go inside.
"Storm of love rages in the heart.."
"..but a naive man can't fathom so."
"The cruel one only
stares from a distance afar."
"Storm of love rages in the heart.."
"..but a naive man can't fathom so."
"The cruel one only
stares from a distance afar."
"Storm of love rages in the heart.."
"The one for whom
I laid awake all night.."
"..could care no
less about my plight."
"The one for whom
I laid awake all night.."
"..could care no
less about my plight."
"The season of love is in the air,
And my heart is set afire."
"The cruel one only
stares from a distance afar."
"Storm of love rages in the heart.."
"Spurn me not now."
"This is the reward
I have got for loving you."
"Spurn me not now."
"This is the reward
I have got for loving you."
"A promise was so easy to make
but abide by it you could not."
"The cruel one only
stares from a distance afar."
"Storm of love rages in the heart.."
"..but a naive man can't fathom so."
"The cruel one only
stares from a distance afar."
"Storm of love rages in the heart.."
Let the sacred wedding
rituals begin, My Lord.
Come close, children.
Until eternity, may you
live happily ever after.
I have been wronged.
I seek justice, Your Majesty.
No, My Lord. No.
If Roman justice perceives
the rich and poor as equal..
..then my plea will be heard.
The court of Rome has
never denied the aggrieved.
But with what intention..
My Lord, once this
auspicious moment elapses..
..there will be no room then
to seek justice nor a need.
Justice?
Fool. You stand at the doorway
of injustice, and seek justice?
A venomous snake
spews nothing but venom.
Let's go home, dear. We have been
given justice. Enough of Roman law.
Silence, you impertinent Jew.
Do not provoke my anger on
a day as auspicious as this.
If you have come to seek justice
from the Emperor, be courteous.
Jewess, your plea has been
lodged at the wrong time and place.
Yet, I shall hear. You will
get justice. Right here and now.
But, Your Majesty..
- This is my command.
What is your plea?
May I ask, what sentence
the law of Rome gives..
..to a man who traps a woman in
his love and then deceives her?
..who promises to marry
a woman but leaves her to lead..
..a life of infamy and shame.
And then marries another?
In the eyes of Roman law,
such a man is undoubtedly a criminal.
And in the eyes of justice,
deserving of punishment.
Jewess, I wish to know, who is this
cheat who has been so unfair to you?
My Lord, he is the one whom
the world knows as Prince Marcus.
Immoral girl. Would you ever
have anything to do with royalty?
Indeed. And you, oh Holy One,
speak of justice and fairness.
Being a cardinal does
not give you the right..
..to twist royal justice
against the person who lodges a plea.
What a shame! Even the
Emperor's justice today..
..instead of favoring the poor,
favors the oppressor.
Jew. My justice and
reign do not favor any evil.
It will not change to the
tune of the winds of fortune.
Do not be cynical. I know my
responsibilities very well.
Marcus, are the
allegations cast by the Jewess true?
Yes.
Every single word.
Why this sudden silence?
Has the storm of justice calmed down?
Beloved Emperor..
..is your love for your son
being pitted against your duty?
Your Majesty, the
accusations of a mere Jewess..
..cannot be weighed with the
honor of the royal family.
The law is meant for the common man,
not for kings and princes.
Then cursed be your
justice and damned be your law.
A law that threatens the
weak and arms the mighty.
Which is opportune for you
but spells death for us.
Jew!
Were all of the world's
creations made only for you?
Your sorrows are painful?
But that of others, mere tales?
Your blood is blood? And ours, water?
Justice demands that
this wedding be stopped.
That, Prince Marcus
be taken into custody.
But according to Roman law,
cases involving the royalty..
..have been decided
by religious decree.
Therefore, this suit must be presented
in a clerical court, My Lord.
So it shall be.
I do not wish to denounce law.
..that in the eyes of law,
the weak and mighty are equal.
Let him not enjoy any privileges
just because he is Crown Prince.
'How nice it would be if I were
to get what my heart seeks now.'
'And what does the heart seek?'
'A doll as pretty as the moon.'
Oh, my dear.
'Your love has pervaded
every fiber of my being.'
'At your feet, I shall end my life.'
'Till my last breath, only your
name will be present on my lips.'
Hannah.
Princess. You?
Yes.
I am here to implore for mercy.
Why must you mock at my helplessness?
What can a poor Jewess
give to the Princess of Rome?
Everything is in your
hands today, Hannah.
Marcus' future lies
at your discretion.
To make your love a success,
you seek the aid of a helpless girl?
Do not consider me your enemy, Hannah.
Even I am a woman.
I can understand the pain you feel.
But why have you shelved your
honor and come to console me?
The difference being, you are
triumphant, and I have failed.
Sweet words do not
soothe the heart, Princess.
If you had a woman's heart, then..
You have made a mockery of love
and robbed me of my love. Leave.
Hannah. - For God's sake,
go away. And leave me alone.
I will leave. But hear me out.
Because of you, the man you
love will be sentenced to death.
Sentenced to death?
I occupy the seat of justice now.
..will affect not only you,
but the Roman Empire and its future.
In this court of justice,
I give you one more opportunity.
I ask you once more.
Are the charges made by the
Jew and his daughter true or not?
I don't wish to
waste the court's time..
..by repeating my statements.
The allegations levied by the
Jew and his daughter are true.
No, My Lord. I wish to say something.
My Lord, the prince is innocent.
Hannah. - I take back the
charges cast on the Prince.
I made a mistake in
identifying the accused.
The same face, the same clothes.
Everything seemed identical.
But he.. he was not the one.
The Prince has not disgraced me.
My Lord, she is lying.
She wishes to burden
Rome's throne with her kindness.
So, the actual criminal
resembled Prince Marcus?
Yes, My Lord.
Is that why you crossed your limits..
..and accused the
Crown Prince of Rome?
Yes, My Lord.
And the Jew who screamed at
the top of his voice yesterday.
Why are you silent today?
Do not provoke me any further.
Put an end to this story.
If I speak the truth, your heart
will burn. And that's my word.
I swear by my helplessness that
the flames raging in my heart..
..are enough to burn
all of Rome to ashes.
But no. I cannot break her heart.
Today, the one I love has
compelled me to remain silent.
I accept the verdict
which I am destined for.
So much so, that I am ready to
obey your untrue verdict too.
If my verdict is not heeded,
the person will not be spared, Ezra.
Prince Marcus is declared not guilty.
Hannah, you wrongly testified
against Rome's Crown Prince.
And your father, Ezra,
was an accomplice to your crime.
For maligning the royal family,
you are declared its enemies.
And sentenced to death in
containers of boiling oil.
My Lord!
What have you done, My Lord?
She is innocent.
She misled the court
because of her blind love for me.
It is evidence that
matters in court, not emotions.
But it is no justice to
sentence an innocent to death.
I implore you, My Lord.
Kindly retract your verdict.
This is my final decision, Prince.
The Jews ought to be
punished for their crimes.
Is justice blinded by your faith?
Is your justice based
on hatred and prejudice?
Marcus. Your words reek of rebellion.
Perhaps you forget
whom you are talking to.
In your zeal, you have
become devoid of your senses.
To speak against injustice,
is the duty of every human being.
You cannot stifle the
protest of an innocent.
It will rise like gusty storm
from every corner of the world.
And they will vanquish your
empires of injustice and slavery.
Silence, Marcus. Your wayward
tongue challenges my authority.
..which burns in my heart too,
like those of many others.
Beware of the revolution, Brutus.
Or it will consume
you in its own flames.
Soldiers. Arrest the rebel.
You will be given a very
light punishment for rebelling.
You will personally see
your beloved tomorrow..
..being cast in
a container of boiling oil.
So that your
audaciousness is put to an end.
And that a revolution
ensues in your world too.
Forgive him? So that he gets to
challenge the justice of Rome?
Octavia, this isn't an insult of
Governor Brutus but of the Roman Empire.
Whatever Marcus has done is
because of his naivet, My Lord.
And he will have to pay for it,
so that he never repeats it.
Yet, My Lord, Marcus
is Rome's Crown Prince.
Can the law not grant him pardon?
This empire belongs to Rome,
and the Roman law shall prevail.
Governor Brutus is the
judge of Roman justice.
My Lord..
- I am helpless, Octavia.
Leo! Leo!
Be patient, my Prince.
My love and my life are
dying because of Rome.
But as of now, you must bow
before Rome's law and justice.
You term atrocity
and cruelty as justice?
I deem it my duty to rebel
against such law and justice.
I shall have all of Rome
oppose Brutus' cruelty.
I shall unmask his faade.
So that the world can see
his dangerous and true self.
Yes, Marcus. You can surely do that.
But do not forget that you are
surrounded by Roman soldiers.
You are a prisoner, Prince.
Yes, you are right, Antonio.
I am surrounded by the
protectors of Roman justice.
I am rendered helpless.
So that my innocent Hannah gets
destroyed, and I remain helpless.
That her screams die near the
executioners and I stay helpless.
I never knew, Antonio, falling
in love was so grave a crime.
And that its punishment was so harsh.
Antonio, there is still time
for dawn. I need your help.
Antonio can sacrifice
his life for you, Marcus.
But to think of a Roman
Prince pining for a mere Jewess..
Hold your tongue, Antonio.
I will not tolerate
you insulting my love.
You are alien to my feelings of love.
Antonio, you can neither hear nor
fathom the cries of my broken heart.
Prince.
Antonio, I am going out of my mind.
What can I do for you? Command me.
I am not capable of
giving commands, Antonio.
But I have a request to
make to you, my friend.
Fetch me some poison.
Poison?
Yes, Antonio, it is my last wish.
I am your friend, not your enemy.
Ask me my life. But ask not
for something that I cannot give.
Unfaithful friend. Go away.
I do not even need you anymore.
I shall douse this raging
fire without seeking your help.
Remember, Antonio. One bent on
taking his life can do so in many ways.
Marcus. Marcus. Marcus. Open the door.
Marcus. Open the door.
Marcus. Open the door, Prince.
I say, open the door, Marcus.
Marcus. Open the door.
Marcus, in the name of
our friendship, open up.
Prince, open the door.
I say, open the door,
Marcus. Open the door, Marcus.
Open up. Or else
I will break open the door.
Marcus. Marcus. Open the door.
Marcus, my friend. In the name
of our friendship, open the door.
In the name of your love, open up.
For Hannah's sake, Marcus, open up.
Open the door, Marcus,
or I will break open this door.
Marcus, open..
Marcus, your eyes..
I have hidden Hannah forever..
..in the safe custody
of my eyes, Antonio.
Now, nobody can
snatch her away from me.
Marcus.
Antonio.
These stone-hearted
people born as humans..
Now, nobody can coerce me
to witness their atrocities.
These blind people will
call me blind, won't they?
Let them.
Antonio. Antonio,
do not leave me alone.
Marcus.
Just once, take me to Hannah, Antonio.
Just once, I wish to hear her voice.
It would be enough for me to carry
on with this miserable life, Antonio.
Jews. The oils in those
containers eagerly await you.
Beckon your God now to save
you from burning in the oils.
Brutus, I do not fear death.
In any case, my days
are already numbered.
But look at this innocent
girl who has not even seen life.
I can spare both of
you on one condition.
Embrace the Roman creed.
I shall not sell
the garden fearing withering.
My life I will sacrifice but
intact will remain my integrity.
Brutus, our bones can melt
away in those burning oils.
But nothing can
waver our firm integrity.
Soldiers. Stop staring.
Throw them in the furnaces.
My Lord, the fault is mine. Kill me
if you must but spare my father.
I cannot bear to see
my father die with me.
Hannah. Come on.
Wait.
I wish to be kind to the girl.
Burn the girl first. So that
she cannot see him burn to death.
No, Brutus. I cannot bear to
see my daughter dying in agony.
Spare me this horrible sight and
kill me. But have mercy on her.
Take him away.
No. Brutus. Mercy.
For God's sake, have mercy.
Mercy?
Which man will not
melt hearing this word?
Cruel Roman.
Fear at least the justice of God.
Do you not remember
the anguish of losing a child?
Have you forgotten that
even you once had a daughter..
..whom somebody had abducted?
How do you know?
- How do I know?
I also know that Lydia is
not dead. She is still alive.
Lydia. My daughter is alive.
No way. You seek revenge. You lie.
Well, assume it is a lie.
Come on, Hannah.
Wait, Ezra. Do you
know where my daughter is?
Certainly. But I will not say.
You won't?
I will punish you so badly..
..that the skies and
the earth will shudder.
Go ahead. Why delay?
No. No, Ezra.
For God's sake, tell me, Ezra.
I won't.
You won't?
- No. I won't.
Ezra, this head has never bowed
even before the Emperor of Rome.
But I bow before you today.
Have mercy, Ezra. Have mercy.
Mercy?
For the first time,
that word has escaped your lips.
Perhaps you know now that it
is not only the enslaved Jews..
..who need mercy.
Even the tyrannical Romans need it.
But how can a poor Jew show you mercy?
Seek your tyrannical race.
You have never
taught us anything good.
Why should I show mercy to
the one who has never been merciful?
Ezra. Ezra, have pity on me.
Tell me. For God's sake,
tell me where my Lydia is?
I pity your helplessness.
I accept. Anything.
First hear my condition.
After I reveal everything..
..you will instantly cast
Hannah into the furnace.
And wait for Ezra's signal.
Go. Take her away. Tell me now.
Very well. Then, listen.
Fifteen years ago, you had thrown
my innocent son Elijah to the lions.
My servant, Emmanuel, swore revenge.
In order to douse those flames of
vengeance..
..he kidnapped your daughter, Lydia.
But my conscience and
my religion did not permit me..
..to punish an innocent daughter ..
..for the crimes of her father.
I was overwhelmed by mercy,
and chose to forget the past.
I raised your daughter as my own.
Yes. A Jew did. A Jew, who,
in your eyes, is born a criminal.
But where is she?
Where is she? Look there.
Lydia. My child.
- Beware. Where are you going?
Soldiers, kill her.
- Stop. No. This cannot be.
Why can it not be?
Just because she is your
daughter now, and not mine?
Now that you know she is yours,
you are eager to embrace her?
Executioners, kill her.
- Wait, Ezra. Ezra.
Hannah.
Father.
Do not leave me, father.
I have no one else but you.
Don't cry. Do not weep, my child.
My dear, I cannot bear to see you cry.
Come, my dear, embrace
your father just once.
Your voice spews poison.
Your breath reeks of dead bodies.
My child, I am undoubtedly a criminal.
Just once.. just once call me your
father with these innocent lips, Lydia.
Lydia is dead. I am Hannah.
My child. Lydia, return. Please.
Your crimes will return to haunt you,
and you will be punished.
But I am leaving this
world of hatred forever.
My child. Lydia. Lydia.
"Call it a streak of insanity."
"Or the intoxicating effect of love."
"If this you fail to fathom.."
"..then only you are to be blamed."
I have nothing left now.
Have mercy on a lifeless soul,
Prince, and leave me alone.
So that I can find a grave
for myself in some corner.
No, Hannah. No.
Look, I am begging of you
with folded hands. I have lost.
I accept that my
desires have perished.
My dreams have been burnt to ashes.
But don't impose yourself upon
a helpless woman.
Go away, Prince. Go away.
Certain constraints killed my love.
With my own merciless hands, I have
taken out the light of my heart.
Hannah, there's
present a frightful darkness.
And this life seems like one long,
never ending journey.
This path is so..
- Moshe.
Moshe.
Your eyes? What have you done?
I have been punished for my crime.
I have paid for the
innocent tears that you had shed.
I have found immense peace now.
Moshe. Moshe, I seek your forgiveness.
Overwhelm me with your love once
again. Take me in your arms, Moshe.
Hannah.
In the far distance,
I can see the first ray of a new dawn.
Come, Moshe, let us
touch this new light.
Let this new dawn be
witness to our love.
Come.
"Call it a streak of insanity."
"Or the intoxicating effect of love."
"If this you fail to fathom.."
"..then only you are to be blamed."
"Call it a streak of insanity."