guys please comment on the quality of this subtitle...
roliekgeorge@yahoo.com
hello
ya
what?
sir kindly switch off your mobile phone
just one sec one sec please!!!
excuse me!
sir please sit down!!!!
captain ther is a medical emergency
a passenger has just fallen down on the aisle
delhi air india 11 returning to medical emergency
sir excuse  me sir excuse me sir
one minute!!!!!!!
im alright now
thank you!
all go now
i'll go now
gentlemen wait!!
get the vehicle
are you Mr.dullon
why?
should i tatoo my name here?
take out the vehicle fast!!
ok sir!! come sir
should go to hotel right sir??
ya ya we'll go hotel
but through vasant vihar.. take me ther
put some load on accelerator kaake!!!!
ya farhan tell me
you come out fast im reachin ur place in 5 min
what happened dude?
chathur had called
remember him?
who "silencer"?
ya ya
he's tellin rancho is comin
what u're sayin?
hanh he's tellin if wanna meet rancho come to campus at 8, on the tank
oh s*****
hey u come out fast
ya ok ok
sruthi i'll be back in sometime
oooo shoes....
hey i got my friend back
what?
hey i'll come back n speak to u!!!
atleast wear pants n go!!!
now can we go to hotel sir?
we'll go to hotel kaake
but only after goin to  "imperial college of engineering"
ok sir!!!
forgot to take socks dude!!
u talkin about socks??? hey look down even pants u forgot!!!
oooooooo
sir now u can go to hotel!!! but only after goin to airport because my sir is comin there take him to hotel!!!!! same sur name "dullon"
im dullon!! where the hell  had u sent taxi?? is it on runway??
oye rancho
hey chathur where is rancho?
rancho
where is rancho?
welcome idiots
wanna drink madiera(RUM)
this is that rum you all used to drink here?
have a drink
hey where is rancho?
i'll tell u
first u watch this
not my wife... llook at the bunglow  behind idiots 3.5 million
swiming pool heated!!!
living room maple wood flooring
my new lamborghini 6496cc sssss very fast
hey why u showin all these to us?
forgot?
what is this?
5the september..todays date..then wat yaar!!
come bet... after 10 years will come back
over here itself, on this same day
n we'll see who is more successful???
have dareness??.........tell,  will u come??.... will u come?
remember something now???
here only i kept bet with that idiot
i kept my promise
im back he he
stupid
i left my flight n came
he left his pant n came just to meet rancho
from five years we're searchin for him dont know he's dead or alive
or wat do u think? will he come for this stupid bet
he wont come i know he wont come he he eh
what? will u break his teeth or ill only do it.....
one min farhan one min
idiot..  then why did u call us over here?
to meet rancho
come n see where he stayed back n where i reached!!!
means tat u know where is rancho? aah?
yes
where is rancho?
he is in shimla!!!!
#.....he was like a fleeting wind.....#
#.....like a flutterting kite.....#
#.....where did he go? lets find him.....#
#.....he was like a fleeting wind.....#
#.....like a flutterting kite.....#
#.....where did he go? lets find him.....#
#.....while confined channel guided us.....#
#.....he would define his pathways.....#
#.....and loiter along them merrily.....#
#.....while our future haunted us.....#
#.....he would celebrate the present.....#
#.....and live every moment with reckless freedom .....#
#.....where did he come from? .....#
#....touching our hearts .....#
#.....where did he go? lets find him.....#
#.....he was like a shade in sweltering heat .....#
#.....like village in desert .....#
#.....he was like salve for our distress .....#
#.....while we cowered from challenges .....#
#.....he would dive in seas .....#
#.....and swim against the rip currents .....#
#.....he was a wandering cloud .....#
#.....he was our pal .....#
#.....where did he go? lets find him.....#
rancho!
ranchhodas shamaldas chanchad
how different his name was?
that same different thoughts
since childhood we heard that life is like a race....
if u dont run fast others will overtake u...
damn!!! to take birth... had to race among 300 million sp****s he he eh
i born at 5.15am
n at 5.16am my dad told
My son will become engineer!!!
farhan qureshi! b.tech engineer
and my fate was sealed!!!
what i wanted to become?? nobody asked me though?
raju rastogi
ranchhoddas chanchad
tell me ur room number!
D26
follow me
im manmohan
M.M
all these enginneers call me milli meter
milk, egg, bread, wash clothes, iron clothes, filling journals, copying assignment
let it be any work tell me!!! fixed rate no bargain!!
one min one min hold this hold.....
this is kilo byte
this is mega byte n this is his mother  giga byte
take their pictures... this family does'nt byte [bite]
[raju praying]
here comes one more big believer!!!
hi farhan qureshi...im raju rastogi
dont worry
after someday u stay here... ur belief in god will vanish eventually
only naked girls poster sticked by your side.. n u'll say
oh god
get me once!!!
hey get out of here!! out out
give 4 rupees
2 rupees per bag
here 5 rupees... keep change
wow sir u gave me tip
even i'll give u a tip
today night.... wear underwear which doesnt have hole!!!
why?
oh emperor.....
u r great.....
accept our gift
aaahh
this is he-man, he-man take this...
ooohhhoo  white white white
we were humiliated,
hands saluting,
heads down like slaves,
when we saw rancho for the first time!
new gift..gift gift gift gift!
namaste sir!!!
remove your pants n get sealed!!!
whats ur name? tell
ranchhodas shamaldas chanchad!!
huuii hhehehhee
listen brothers learn by-heart!!! by final year u'll learn!!! hmmm
remove ur pants.... remove pant
oooh so u wont listen like this hanh?
dont wear wet pant kid?
come remove now!!
aal iz well aal iz well.............[ranchod baba mantra lol]
what is he tellin?
someone make him understand!!!
hey james bond make him understand!! hmm
take off ur pants of they're gonna piss on u
oye english!!! feeling shy to speak in hindi hanh?
sorry sir i was born in uganda, n studied in pondicherry!!
so little slow in hindi!!!
so slowly make him understand!! who is in a hurry here?
worn again hanh?
[in pure hindi!!!!laughing stock] take off ur pants or they gonna piss on u...
he is tellin piss as muthravisarjan???hahahha
ooo here come pandit learning engineering
hey come out you idiot
come out
come out or else ill piss on ur door!!!
ill count 10
if u dont come out
ill piss on ur door for the whole semester
salt water is a great conductor of electricity
8th standard physics
we all studied it!!
he applied it!!
ICE's director's name was Dr.viru shastrabhuddi
but every one calls him virus
all called him computer virus!!!
oye virus is comin..carryin eggs with him
he has told first years to come down come fast fast
virus was the most competetive man we had  ever seen
if someone overtakes him even one step.........
he could'nt accept it,
to save time he used velcro instead of buttons
and a hook in tie!!
he has trained his mind
that he can write using both his hands at the same time
everday at 2 he used to take a power nap of exactly 7.5 minutes
n used to listen opera
govind had to do all unproductive works like shaving, cuttin nails in this 7.5 mins
what is this?
sir nest!!
whose??
cuckoo bird's nest
cuckoo bird never builds their nest..
they lay their eggs on other birds nest
and when their babies come to the world, what do they do first?
they kick out other eggs from the nest...
competition over
the life begins with murder
thats nature...
compete
or die!
you all so are like the cuckoo birds
and these are those eggs whom u kicked out and reached ICE
dont forget
because every year, 4 lakh applications comes to ICE
among them only 200 will be selected
you
and these
finished
broken eggs!!
my own son applied for 3 years
rejected
everytime
remember life is a race!!
if u dont run fast someone will beat u n move faster than u...
let me tell u very interesting story
this is an astronauts pen
in space, foundain pen, ball pen cannot be used
so after spending millions of dollars
scientists invented this pen..!!
from this u can write in any angle, any temperature, zero gravity
one day when i was a student the director of our institute called me
he said "viru shastrabhuddi." i said "yes sir"
come here!! i got scared
showed me this pen
he said this is a symbol of excellence
i give it to u
and the day when u get a extraordinary student like u
pass this pen to him
from 32 year viru shastrabhuddi is waiting for the next viru shastrabhuddi
any one here in this batch to honour this pen?
good hands down
should i write in the notice board
i said put down your hands
sir i have a question sir...
sir if in space fountain pen ball pen cannot be used why astronaut didn't  tried pencil in space sir?
could've saved millions of dollars
i will get back to you on this
that fellow in night kicks seniors
and in day irritating director, im telling u if we stay with him...
he will put us in trouble
buddy, u though screwed virus completely
oh emperor, u're great..
accept our gift....
get lost, dont u've school?
who'll pay fees? yout father?
u callin my father?
hey stop stop raju wat u doin?
eh listen!
no fees required for schooling!!! uniform is required, uniform...
whichever school u like go, get the uniform of that school..
go sit in the class.....
who'll come to know when there is a huge population???
if i get caught?
if they catch u, then uniform change, school change!!! ehhe
there was really something special about him,
he always used to challenge everything in the world.. each n every move....
he was the only one free bird in VIRUS's nest...
we all were just robots operated by professors remote control...
but he was the only one..
perhaps not a machine!!!!
what is a machine?
why are you smiling??
um.. actually sir
from my childhood i used to dream of studying in an engineering college
today im sitting over here,   feeling excited sir!!!
no need to be so overexcited...
tell.. tell me the definition for machine
um..
sir
machine is anything that reduces human effort sir
will you please elaborate...?
sir um...
all those things which makes the work for humans easier are machines sir
feeling hot!!! pressed button, wind blowing, FAN is a machine sir!!
u can talk to your friend  miles away..TELEPHONE is machine sir!!!
calculate crores in less time... CALCULATOR is a machine sir
sir actually we are dependent in the world for machine sir
from PEN NIB to PANTS ZIB... all machines sir!!
one sec up one sec down, up down up down up
tell me the definition??
sir thats wat im tellin sir..
will you write all these in examz hanh?
"this is machine up down up down up"??
IDIOT!!!
anybody else???
)*&#^*&#*&(%#(*&#
)*&%*&#%&*(#*&%#
$(^($*&%#*&%#
*(&^%%%$^&*&*&^%$%&*
he he eh bla bla bla bla
*(&#*&%(*&#%%#
!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
wow great !!!! perfect !!
great please sit down!
thank you thank you
but sir even i told the same in simple language.....
if you like simple language..
u can go join some other arts n commerce college
but sir.. we should understand it atleast
like this way mugging up from book, what the use sir?
oh you know more than books???
books has the same definition...
and if u wanna pass,, u'll write this itself....
but sir, ther are other books also
get out!!!
ooh why?
in simple language... please go outside...
IDIOT!
so we were discussing about the machines
hey why you came back?
i forgot somethin sir!!
what?
instrument and record, analyse, summarize, organize,
debate and explained information
that are elastative and non-elastative hard bound paper
bag jacketed non-jacketed
with forward introduction, table of cotents index that are
intented for the enlightment understanding
enhancement and education human brains of sense in root of vision
sometimes touch!!
what you wish to say??
books sir books!!
i forgot books sir can i take it?
could'nt you say in simple way?
i tried sometime before, but u dint like it in simple way sir....
professors used to keep rancho outside more often than in classroom
if he get kicked from one class, he'll go sit in another classroom
rancho used to say that knowledge is increasing everywhere.......where ever you get... gain it!!!
he was entirely different from all of us
we used to fight for bathroom
but wherever rancho used to get water, he used to have bath there itself!
he was very much attached to machines
used to carry screwdriver in his pocket where ever he goes
he would open any machine that he finds.... some got closed
some did not!!
there was another guy just like him
joy lobo
sir excuse me sir
mr.joy lobo
sir if u mind lettting me know abt the convocations dates...
why?
actually dad wanted to get a reservation
i'm the first engineer in my village sir..
all the relatives wanted to come on the convocation day
in that case call make a phone call to your dad
son please please  dont waste my time hurry
hello
dad director sir will speak to you
joy
mr.lobo your son wont get graduated this year
what happened sir?
he has violated all the deadlines
with unrealistic mr lobo mr lobo unrealistic project it is i had told already
he making some non-sense helicopter
so i recommend you not to reserve his ticket, im so sorry
sir im just close
is your project ready?
sir atleast take a look at this once sir please
do submit it i'll take into consideration
sir give me some extension sir
why why should i give you an extension?
sir after dads stroke i couldnt concentrate for 2 months sir please
did you leave having food and water for 2 months?
no
did you leave taking bath?no?
then why did you left studies?
sir im very close sir pls take a look at this sir please..
mr.lobo my son died falling from train on sunday afternoon
monday morning virushastrabhuddi gave lecture in this college
so dont tell me that non-sense
i can only give you sympathy not extension
si...r
how cool design he made?? wireless camera over helicopter?
traffic updates security... can be used for all
but VIRUS was tellin this is an impractical design...
wont fly it seems?
how it wont fly? ill make it fly!! hm hm
hey dont tell joy will give him surprise
we'll make this fly out his window and record his reaction
if we do his project, who'll do ours?
test, viva, quizzes included, there are 42 examz in each semester
hey you worry a lot dude
take this hand and keep it in your hand and say,
aal iz well aal iz well
all is well
aal iz well
now he has brought something new our BABA ranchhodas!!
hey in our village there was a watchman...
he used to yell in night saying aal iz well
and we used to sleep tight
one night there was a robbery in our village,
then we came to know that he's blind,
and he yells aal iz well aal iz well
and we used to sleep like fools...
but that day we came to  know about the real fact
see our heart right, is a big coward...
keep our heart as a fool
if you have any big problem in life
tell our heart
no problem baby everythin is ok
aal iz well aal iz well
hm so that will solve problem ? hanh?
no but still it gains the dareness to survive
remember this mantra... this is gonna become more  useful over here
got it got it yeah
take it to  joys window
hey joy, up up
ooye window... see silencer naked naked heheh ehhe
hey joy come out joy
hey joy look outside..
joy....
#... give me some sunshine.. give me some rain...#
#... give me another chance i wanna  grow up once again.....#
you've a good news sir..
neither police got to know
nor joys dad....
everyone will think its a suicide, sir
reason for death in postmortem report
intense pressure in wind pipe resulting in choking
this fool believed tat
died because of the pressure held here...
and from last 4 years of pressure over here? wat about that?
even thats not in the report also sir,
these engineers are so back minded sir
didnt even invent some machine, that could really behold the pressure over here...
if they had does, could've come to know this is not a suicide, its a murder,
are you blaming me for the suicide of joy?
if one student cant tolerate pressure why im i the one responsible?
so many pressure will come in life...
then everytime will you blame other for that?
sir im not blaming you sir
actually im blaming the system
sir i've got some statistics
sir in suicides india is no:1 sir
every 1 half hour one of the other students attempt suicide, sir
student die less in sickness and more in suicide here sir
something is going wrong rightt sir?
i cant tell about other colleges but this is one of the finest college in the country
im running this college from 32 years
i brought this college to no:1 from 28th position
sir wat no:1 sir ???
here we dont've any  talks related to new ideas,no talks on inventions
only great talk on only marks, or else job in USA
we dont gain any knowledge here sir...
here they only teach us how to bring good marks...
now are you going to teach me how to take class?
pls sit down
today we have our great leader behind us
who claims that he can teach better than our highly qualified teachers
so today our professor ranchhodas chanchad will teach us engineering
we donot have all day
you all have 30 secs
should find the meaning of the word written on the board
if u want u can make use of your books too
the one who gets the answer can lift ur hands up
we'll see who'll come first and whos last
your time starts now
time up
time up sir time up
what?
nobody got the answer?
now rewind 1 min of life a bit and think
when i asked this question..
anybody thought that today we will get something to learn new..?
anyone..sir
no
everyone sunk in race
whats the use if u come first studying like this?
will you improve your knowledge? no
only pressure will increase
and this is a college not a PRESSURE COOKER
the lion in the circus also learns to sit on the chair fearing the whip held in his owner's hand
but we call such a lion as well trained,not well educated
hello....
this is not a philosophy class!
tell us the meaning of those 2 words,
sir actually no such words exists sir
these are my friends names
farhan and raju
quiet
non-sense
like this you teach engineering?
no sir im not teaching you engineering, you know better than me
i was teaching you that, how to teach,
and i believe that you learn someday for sure sir
because i never leave my weaker students hand
busted
quiet
quiet i said
i would regret to inform you that your son farhan, raju is goin on wrong routes
if u dont take required action their future will be spoiled
VIRUS's letters fell down in our homes like an atom bomb
there was mourning in hiroshima n nagasaki!
and we were invited to both the home to get kicked
come come inside
see there
we could only afford one airconditioner
and we didnt keep in our bedroom , we kept it in farhans bedroom
for him to study convieniently
i didnt buy car, riding scooter till now
invested all money in farhans studies
we sacrificed our future for farhan's better future.. did you understand or not?
then can u imagine wat i must be going through!
hey you took all these photos farhan?
quiet
he has the ghost of photography in his head
he used to take the images of animals and used to say he wanted to become
wild life photographer
son what was your percentage that year?
91 percent
did you hear that?
from 94 percent straight down to 91 pecent
u feel it funny?
no no uncle no
i was tellin how great pictures he has taken
why you makin him an engineer you could've  made him a wild life photographer
i'm foldin my hands n requesting u
please dont spoil my sons future
kids
come lets eat somethin
when you come next time have food and go....
dad though didnt give us food,
and atlast to fill our hungry stomach, and  to fill the quota of advise
we reached raju's home
raju's home reminds us about the 1950's black and white films
one small bed where his paralysed father rest
one coughing mother
and one sister at her age of marriage
sofa with all springs out
and 24 hours running water from terrace
mother was retired from school and almost tired everytime...
his dad was a postmaster at his age
after paralysis he lost his half body and salary completely....
and sister!!!
kammo(raju's sister) is 28 now...
asking maruthi 800 as dowry...
if dont study n all how she'll get married?
take lady's finger curry.. hand jee thank you
you know wat? lady's finger has now become 12 rupees per kg
and cauliflower 10 rupees
world is looting all over
and upon that your these kind of letters come from college
what will we eat??
want paneer??
someday back u get little of paneer in goldsmith's shop
want paneer?
no no enough
mom just leave it keep quiet, what?
ok ok, i'll keep quiet
earn for kids, work like a servant, and after all these keep mouth shut?
hey these all our news if i dont tell it to my son,
to whom will i say? to his friends?
hey raju
it was a big confusion whether we should control our friend or wipe his mother's tears
then we thought to leave all these matter, and
lets concentrate on mattar paneer now,
even his exhema's cream comes for 55 rupees now
ewwww...
want more roti son???
no no done no stomach filled aunty
lady's finger 12 rupees and caulli flower 10 rupees hehheee
atleast we offered you some food unlike your hungy father
hitler qureshi
hanh hanh your mom is mother teresa right?? she was serving us itchy roti,
dont make fun of my mother
hey leave it, why u all fighting? feelin damn hungry
come lets go have some food outside
this is the end of month who'll give money his mom mother teresa?
to have food doesnt require money dude, uniform is required uniform,
watch there..
come
namaste jee namaste
ooooo uncle
hey listen get us 3 glass of vodka
half soda half water
what are the starters available?
what ever get us two plates each
and leave this here
and change the music yaar..put some ghazal or something
pia what the hell is this?
what have you worn??
bloody eighteenth century watch?
what people will say?
watch suhas's fiance, she is gonna become doctor,
and she's wearing a watch just costing 200 bucks?
please take it off thank you
hi handsome
hey aunty,
you're looking good
dont miss my set darling
rubies?
from mendelaves..
mendelave wow!!!
hey lets go meet david, come i'll show u, ofcourse of course
excuse me
yes
um.. flowers
um.. can i take this glass?
why?
what if u break my head with glass?
why should i throw this on you?
because im gonna give you some free advises,
what?
dont ever marry that fool,
excuse me
he is not a human, he is just a price tag, price tag
he'll embarrass you tellin all prices of different thing all  your life,
your life will be spoiled and your future will be finished,
should i give a demo?
should i find out whats the price for his shoes?
im not gonna ask him, he himself will reveal, just a sec
oh my god
hey hey
what have you done?
its a 300 dollar shoes
u dropped mint chutney on my 300 dollars shoes!
run away, its a free advise, take it or leave it
genuine itallian leather hand stiched,
dad
are these your guests?
these are my students
why they're here?
one sec
this is really good dude, smelling very good,
hey no space for puri dude, adjust it by side, ohh
hi
hey hi,
you helped me opening up my eyes, thank you so much
nothing like that..it was my duty!
can i ask you for little  more help?
ya ya
my dad wont allow me to break the engagement with suhas,
how great you explain!
it would be good if u give a demo for him also,
ya ya why not why not? ill give demo
raju get me chutney,
you're really sweet,
where is he, where is your dad?
totally behind you,
ooh,
aal iz well aal iz well
run away, its a free advise, take it or leave it
what u all doin here?
um sir.. we'll go on the stage, give this envelope n come sir
give it to me
this is my sister's marriage
umm. sis sister?
sir, totally how many daughters do u have, sir?
its empty!
as though we dint invite you,
you all might be from groom's side right?
no sir actually we're from science's side sir
how?
can you explain?
dad, he explains really good,
now itself he'll give demo, give
um... sir in delhi,
power goes out frequently sir
and this really affects the marriage too sir
so i thought to make an inverter
that can generate power from all cars that has come in the marriage,
ohhh
wow
and did you make the inverter?
sir design is ready sir!!!!
um.. where is the design farhan
i've given you the design right?
aah, i had given to raju,
raju design??
sir actually, leave it sir ill make the inverter itself and show you directly,
you can only make us fool, not an inverter!!!
no sir ill surely make the inverter,
i promise
and ill give your name for the inverter
because after all it had been invented in your daughter's marriage
so it'll an honour,
farhan, raju.. i wish to meet both of you in the office tomorrow
sir what was your per plate cost sir,
we'll pay sir
in terms of installment sir
and afterward we wont intrude in any marriage sir
i wont even enter my marriage also sir,
infact i wont marry also sir, even he wont marry also sir
hanh hanh, even i wont sir
even your parents shouldnt've married
2 idiots wouldnt've taken birth in this world
sit!!!!!!!!
be attention...
??????
this is ranchhodas's father's monthly income
2.5 crores rupees,
now from this,
one, or let it be two zero if you remove out...
does'nt make much difference to bother,
but if one more zero is less,
i would worry a little
this is your father's monthly income, mr.farhan!
ye... yes sir,
and now if you make it one more zero less,
now this is your family income mr.raju rastogi,
big reason to worry,
follow viru shastrabhuddi's suggestion, change your rooms
and get shifted with chathur ramalingam
exams are closer, and if you be with that chanchad,
will never pass in exams!
#..... opera started......#
wanna get shaved?
no sir,,
then get lost!
raju you try to understand,
VIRUS is playing games between us, divide and rule
dont get scared,
had to be scared!
for me to get good job, i need good grades, and grades are within his hands,
i dont have rich father like you..using whose money, i can spend the rest of my life
hey raju what non-sense are you tellin?
should we do whatever he says hanh? aal iz well, aal iz well?
you'll  be the only one who gonna catch his tail not me,
now you're crossing the line,
no im making line in between, because i have to support my family!
mom's half salary has been spend on dad's medicines,
sister's marriage is not happening,
as the groom wants maruthi 800,
from past 5 years
mom dint even buy one saree,
yaar..now in this argument..if u r getting mother's saree in between..what can i say?
yaar so like that how many sarees are reserved for one year? heheh
dont make fun of my mother,
hey raju we will study, with complete dedication we'll study,
but not only to pass exams,
some great scholar has told,
"never study to be successful, study for self efficiency"
dont run behind success,
excellence
follow behind excellence
success will come all way behind you,
who the great scholar told this?
BABA ranchhodas???
hey hey dont take tension yaar,
we'll top the exams yaar, nothin is impossible!
nothin is impossible? hanh?
take this,
now put this back, k!!
raju changed his train's bogey,
now he started the journey(saffar) with chathur,
not the "saffar" in hindi,
english's SUFFER
S
SU
SUF
SUFF
SUFFE
SUFFER
SUFFER hehhehe
everyone calls chathur as "silencer"
to make his mind even more sharper,
he used to eat some bengali BABA's PAN,
and he used to leave his HOT AIR!!!!
i din do it!
raaju....
and he always put the blame on others!
SILENCER used to mug up 18 hours a day
and during exam's night, he used to distract others from study
#.... oooo baby.... come on baby ye.....#
he believed in two ways of topping exams
one is to get marks by yourself,  or try reducing other's marks
racho has made the combined plan to teach silencer a lesson,
and to help raju,
our director sir has done much miracle here,
chamatkaar (miracle) means....
i dont want the meaning dubey jee, i'll memorize it....
chathur has been chosen to present introductory speech on teacher's day
he wrote speech in pure hindi from librarian dubey jee to impress VIRUS,
hello,
yes will call,
chathur, you've a call
dubey jee please keep this print out with you, ill come back in sometime,
oohhh even do that work also.... !!!
hey dubey jee!
director sir has remembered you, ya now
ok you give this to chathur , ill come back now
helllo, hello
hello mr.ramalingam,
yes
ya im calling from lajpat nagar police station,
are you from uganda?
h h yes sir,
hmmm your life is under risk,
wat how?
um listen to my instructions carefullly
else when you step out from the college gate
you'll face death in centre of road itself,
why ? what happened?
by the time chathur recovers from this shock,
before that itself racho changed a few words in the speech
like.....
chamathkaar has become balathkaar
[ miracle ]                       [ rape ]
had you called me sir?
who are you?
dubey librarian,
im permenant sir,
CONGRATULATIONS!!
um.. one min one min
commisioner sir's call, hold on,
excuse me sir sir
take phone take it wat to say?
ya ya where was i?
you were tellin, outside gate, my death
hanh! when you go out the gate, you a see a signal in front of you
traffic signal!! hanh ok ok
when that signal becomes red,
all vehicle will stop,
ok ok then
then you cross the road carefully,
you know why son nowadays traffic is huge
so like if any vehicle hits you or somethin, you might die,
what non-sense i know that!
oh u know that, very good son then you are safe,
well done well done.
#......became a fool.......#
hey SILENCER!!! dubey has given you this,
hey you dont call me that CHANCHAD,
CHANCHAD
director told me that he din call me,
he dint call you, i told that he remembered you!!
idiots...
respected teachers,
chief guest minister shri RD tripati ji,
students n my dear friends
today if ICE is touchin sky high limits,
then the credit goes to only  one man
shri viru sahastrabuddhi..
give him a hand,
sir he's sayin it..
but every word is mine
he is a great guy, really you are,
from past 32 years he had continuosly
in this college,
he has done rapes upon rapes,,,
this means.. miracles upon miracles
hope he continues to do so
we feel wondered that,
how a person in his lifetime can do these many rapes ?
with his extreme self discipline..
he's made himself this capable
right usage of time
complete utilization of bell
somebody, learn from him,
learn from him, learn from him........
sit down sit down
today..we all students are here..
tomorrow, we'll spread across so many countries
i promise u all
whichever country we are........... there we'll rape!!!
we'll enlight the name of ICE!!!!!!
we'll show everyone,
the capability 2 perform rape that students have over here
no other students in across the globe has it!!!
no other student, no other student!!
respected minister..
namaskar
you have given that thing for this institution....
that we needed the most....
money money!!!
****
not that.... that means ****
what kinda insulting topic is this boy speakin!
**** is ther with everyone,....
everyone keeps it hidden........
nobody never gives it......
eeaan eaan???
this guy is too vulgar
u have given ur **** in the hands of this rapist
now let us see,
how he makes use of it.........
sahastrabuddhi, dont u have so much of brains
indecent guy
on this golden occasion, i can recollect a shlok,
listen listen..now he'll explain his farting stength in sanskrit
uthamam dadadatu paadham
[ give out excellent fart ]
paadham??? ooo SILENCER.......
[ fart ]                      .
madyam paadam..... tuchuk tuchuk.
[ middle most farting ]                          .
kanishtam thud thudiya paadam
[ smallest thud thudiya farting ]
sur suriiee............ praana kadakam...
[important breath of life]
see, without understanding if u cram things.. this will be the result, see see
By cramming, u can save 4 years of ur college life..
but for the next 40 years of your life, u'll go on getting raped........
aare yaar,we made him understand so much..
but still he hasnt understood,
madyam paadam thuchuk thuchuk...
unbelievable yaar....
u done the right point.. rancho
how fun it was...... hehe
poor fellow dint had any idea......
hey you hey
you swines..
in wat way have i harmed u??
eheh ehe
hey sorry dude dont take it personally,
ill take it personally,
chathur ramalingam is not gonna forget this insult,
ill think of it every minute,
every sec of my life
dude leave it, acttually we were giving demo for raju...
that dont cram things n study.
understand n study..enjoy the beauty of science yaar
im not here to enjoy thing...
then wat?..are you here 2 rape??or have you come here to rape science!!..tuchuk tuchuk!!
laugh.....!!!   laugh on my methods..
one day using this methods...
i'll become successful n show everyone
and then i'll laugh.......... and u'll cry!!
yaar, u're boarding the wrong train again
dont run behind success......
become a great engineer such that success runs behind u.....
these ideals dont work in the real world CHANCHAD
u board ur train........... and i'll board mine
and after 10 years from now..v'll come back on this same station
on this same date,
we'll see whose more successful!!!
you?
or me!
do u dare...
do u dare...???
then lets bet....tel
wil u come..
wil u come..?
wil u come..??
wat are u doing yaar?
wat has happened to him!!
wat is he writing yaar??
dont forget this date.......
i'm not used to such expensive gifts,suhas!
get used to it pia..u're gonna be suhas tandon's wife!!
where's the bill man?
i'll be back hanh!
u had changed the speech right?..dont lie!
oooo...umm..ya
wat problem do u have with my dad, hanh?
i dont have any problem with him ..
i'm making an inverter on his name.....see this
oooh..
broke it!!
why are u behind my dad, hanh?
because he's not running a college, but a factory.!!
where donkeys are manufactured every year....
see..see over there..ur donkey
how dare u call him a donkey!!
then wat else should i call him..???
first he did engineering..then MBA..
n after that he went to America to work for a bank... heeeh
if he had to work in a bank only,  then why did he do engineering?
for such donkeys..life only means profit or loss statement...
he's seeing there's profit being with u, tats why he's with u
you director's daughter whose gonna be a doctor..its good for his image etc etc
he has no attachment with u.....
wat do u think of yourself?
wat do u mean by sayin suhas is not interested in me?
aare..you bought new watch??..one minute..hold this
i have to show u demo everytime......
hey suhas!
where were u?..i've been looking for u!
she lost her watch yaar..she's searchin for it.....
wat!!!!..u lost the watch???
aare leave it yaar..get a new one
aare it cost 4 lakhs.....
4lakhs!!!..mine costs only 150 yaar but shows the same time
oh shut up!!
how could u be so careless pia!!..this careless attitude is disgusting
its disrespectful
tat was a limited edition watch u just lost!
u got it 4 free..so tats it..now u wear your 18th century watch at dinner..
wat?..wat are u staring at?
huh..now u'll start crying..real mature pia
i cant handle this..now stop crying n search!!
seach for some other hand for this watch..donkey!!!
hey..u're solid yaar..u said donkey to him on his face!
get lost!!
yaar its too much noisy here right..??
she's saying thank u to me..but i hear it as get lost
i said get lost only!
aare yaar,why're u getting so angry??
do u know..actually you never had loved him at all!
wat do u mean?
means..whenever he comes infront of u..
have u ever felt like wind is blowing..or dupatta/veil is flying in slow motion??
or the moon looks even bigger in the sky....?
such things only happens in a film, not in real life!
aare no-no..it happens in real life also....if u love a human, it'll happen...
it doesnt happen with donkeys
#.... phone ringing...#
hello!!..ya
wat??..
oh god!!..
ok ok..i'm coming..ya bye bye
hey..u're a medical student right?
i need ur help..its an emergency..please please!
come with me..please
aare yaar..u doctors take an oath tat u'll never say no to a patient!
wat do u call it..hippocratic oath!!
yaar help me yaar..please..its an emergeny..please
u barged into my sister's engagement, u broke my engagement
dad is taking BP pills because of u
and i'm helpin u over here
unbelivable!!
this hippocratics...it has just ruined doctor's lifes!!
aunty, where is raju?
he's gone to get a taxi....we called for an ambulance two hours ago..
our country is so weird..there is a guarantee for pizza to reach in 30 mins..but ambulance!!
he must be hospitalised..urgently!
hey stop man!
move..move..move..move
doctor..doctor..  emergency..emergency..
patient
keep this with u..
hey raju
idiot, u brought dad on a scooter?
then should i have sent him through a speed-post..??
dont get into my dad's profession!!
where?..where is dad?
ask the doctor!!!
this was a close call pia...
if it wud've been late by 2 or 2.5 hours, then we wud have lost him
good that u did not wait for an ambulance n got him on a scooter,
i'll go now..if there is any problem..call me ok..bye
rancho....
thank u yaar!
idiot, are you saying thank u to a friend....?
is tat silencer teaching u manners?hanh?
hasnt he told u.....   friendship is the biggest sthan of a human!
go go..now go..u guys have exam tomorrow,right?
aare there are a lot of exams..... but dad is mostly only one..
now we'll take the post master sir n go only then!!
racho..forgive me yaar..i was frightened!
enough..enough.sshhh..quiet..quiet
forgive me..!!
enough..quiet!
go..meet dad..n dont go with such a gloomy face
go..
thanks yaar
go
#..... he was our pal......#
ur scooty saved a life today..its nice..
how much is it?
put chutney n see..might be,  it'll tel!
aaaaaaeeeee....
hey happy independence day....
but today is not 15th august
but it is so for u..now u can wear ur mom's watch whenever u want!
nobody will say..y have u worn a 18th century watch n all tat!!
bye
hey
how do u know tat it was my mom's watch?
in a sister's wedding..if a girl is nicely dressed head to toe
except for an old watch in the hand, wat does it mean?
on tat day, u were missin ur mom a lot..right?
yes
ur mom must have been very beautiful, right?
yes, how do u know?
have u seen ur dad?..
life is a race..... if u dont run fast....  u'll be like a broken egg of the cuckoo bird
today we'll teach you how to prepare chutney
this chutney is very useful,
this is not only to have,
but its really useful to understand people too..
now the bad time has gone for you...
now u can leave donkeys and start loving humans
time is perfect for startin love....
temperature is constant... and the climate is clear n clean....
and if you felt love for someone....
sure its gonna rain on u............
hello..wake up!!
wat..uncle passed away or wat!! wat?
no stupid!
its already 8:30.. at 9:00,the exam starts..u wanna go or not!!
aare yaar..how can u leave him alone here n go!
i'm there, doctors are there..n its only a matter of 3 hours
comeon..take my scooter n go..now come on go..its getting late
hey!!
why have u worn an old watch!
go!!
sorry sir..we were late..emergency!!
settle down there!
sir they r still writing!!
hello..time up!!
sir..5 minutes sir..we were half-an hour late!
it was an emergency sir..please please
examiner looked at us like we asked for both his kidneys!!
but we still continued to write
while he was busy arranging papers according to roll numbers
its over sir
u're late!.. i cant take ur papers
sir,please sir
sir, do u know, who we are?
even if u are prime minister's son, i wont accept ur paper!
sir do u know our names n roll numbers??
no..who are u guys?
u dont know..then..run run run run
hey..wats ur roll number?
where is it..
where is his paper?
aaaahhh!
today the results were gonna come
scared and innocent!..all were busy striking a deal with god
god..please save me with electronics, i'll break coconuts!
oh snake-god!..save my physics..i shall send one litre milk everyday!
oh cow-god!..just..just get me passing marks
god..i'll treat malati n sangeeta like my sisters..please save my results
god..god..i'll offer 100RS per month..surely god!..promise!
nowadays, traffic constables also dont accept 100RS..as if god wud fall for it!
check..check..check from below..check from below
its your's yaar.. in the last
and your's?
second last!
and rancho?
its not there yaar!
my heart sank,
not because we were last but because our friend had failed!
not posibble!.
its fine chatur
there is a mistake!..its not possible!
this is injustice..injustice..oh god!!
why is this idiot silencer shouting so much?
he has come second....
idiot..whose first then?
rancho!
rancho...idiot..
move..move yaar
we learnt something about human behaviour tat day
if ur friend fails, u feel sad!..
but if ur friend comes first..u feel even more sad!
on tat day..we were sad..
but there were two more people who were sadder than us
ranchhoddas chhanchad..first row..right of the director!
uday sinha..second row..third seat!
alok mittal..second row..fifth seat!
hey!
sir..is it compulsory to sit acccording to our ranks?
why, do u have any problem?
sir, i have problem with entire grading system itself!
its like caste-system sir!..A grade students-kings, C grade students-slaves!
its not nice sir!
do u have a better idea for this?
yes sir, i do have!
results should not be put up on a notice board....
why should we exhibit someone's weakness in front of all?
now sir..if in ur blood test, the haemoglobin count is less.,.
will the doctor give u tonic..or put up ur report on the TV?
u see sir!
so basically wat u're saying is i must go to each one's room one-by-one n say results in their ears!
u've come first..u've come second..i'm so sorry, u failed!
no sir,i dint mean tat way
but the thing is..grade creates divide..divide
now see..i've come first so i'm sitting with u..
whereas my friends have come last..
so they are seated in the last..in a corner
atleat they r sitting in a corner now..if they continue being with u,
next year they'll be out of the photo itself!
neither will they pass nor any company will give them jobs!
sir, they'll find a job some how sir....
there wil be atleast few companies..
which hire people n not machines for work!
its not like tat sir..they'll find a job.. i guarentee
oh..u guarentee it..u guarantee it!
bets..bet??
govind....
if even one among those two get a job in the campus interview..
then shave my moustache!
ok sir!!
happy?
happy sir!
woahhhh!!!!..
by using car's horn..u wanna hide ur horn..idiot!
idiot..   septic tank..u had the churan again...??
i dint do it..
raaaaju!!! hanh.....
we've been very used to this hot air from those days..
this idiot is only responsible for global warming!
i cant take it!
give me..give me ur wallet..i'll go n buy a pant!
leave it yaar..wear this chatur ramaalingam's suit's pant!
hey dont u touch my suit!
leave it yaar..rancho wil recognise u even without the pant!
hey Mr.,where's this address?
brother, if i was so educated....would i be selling groundnuts?
he doesnt know to read
but atleast he knows to speak!
brother..here in shimla..is there any ranchhodas chhanchad??
yes..yes..he stays over there!
#....he was like the fleeting wind.....#
lets go!
#....like a fluttering kite.....#
#..... where did he go? let find him!......#
oye chatur..here's is ur bottle of churan!
oh thanks..where did u find it?
it was in the pocket!
hey..how dare u!..tats my pant..
hey wat mine..wat ur's..its written in gita!
hey shut up... remove pants
hey wat are u doing yaar!..people will misinterpret!
mad..idiot!
hey leave..
hey i want it now!
wat happened?
rancho's dad!
brother, where can i find ranchhodas?
he's sittin over there...
thank you...
rancho
yes
oh sorry..  we wish to meet ranchhodas
i'm only ranchhodas..tel me?
no..ranchhodas shyamaldas chhanchad
i'm only ranchhodas shyamaldas chhanchad..tel me?
rancho....take care of yourself!
ranchhodas chhanchad!!!
raju!!
yaar..i must be the first man in history who travelled from delhi to shimla in underwear that too ..to meet a wrong person!
yaar..the same name..the same degree..n the same photo
but the person is different..wats the matter!..i'm unable to understand!
but from where did silencer get rancho's address?
yes!
oye chatur!..come here
hey..hey..
how dare u open this..i got this from san francisco
its hand-made biscuit..
specially for Mr.phunsuk wangdu!
phunsuk bangdu...now who is this?
wangdu..wangdu..'W'..'W'...phunsuk wangdu..
do u know who that is??
he's a great scientist...400 patents..the world wants him!
i have been chasing him from past one year..n the meeting has been fixed now!
u know..once he signs a deal with my company..i'll be huge!..huge!
now stop praising this wangdu n
tell us from where did u get rancho's address?
u should be thanking phunsuk wangdu..its because of him, tat i found a clue
see this..my secretary tracey was here last month to arrange a meeting with phunsuk wangdu
tracey cudnt get an appointment with phunsuk but i got rancho
i checked shimla's phone directory..in that the name was..chhanchad ranchhodas
then how did his appearance change??
he heard u r coming n got a plastic surgery done or wat?
only one man can answer this!
i'm sorry dad!..
i cudnt fulfil ur last wish!
u kept on telling..take me to haridwar..take me to haridwar
but i was waiting for the highway's tender to be opened
the tender opened over there
and u closed ur eyes over here!
i'm so sorry dad!..
i could not be a good son!
what are u saying yaar?..
u have become such a great engineer,
the degree's been put up on the wall
u r a very good son!
how dare u enter my property without my permission, hanh?
i'll put u behind bars!
u'll go behind bars, idiot!
we have investigated everything..
on the basis of ICE degree, u're taking these highway contracts and hydro projects
this degree belongs to our friend..how did it come to u?
its a 150 hectares property..i'll blow off ur heads and bury u in a corner..nobody will get to know!..
get the point!..now get lost!
i'm taking dad's ashes and going to haridwar..if u say, i'll even take ur bones along with that!
lift the dad!!!!
over there..there there
leave my dad!
aeeeeee..
tell who u are..or else i shall immerse ur dad's ashes over here itself
handover dad to me!
dad's ashes wont go to ganga..they'll go into the gutter!!
aeeee...remove dad from the pot...remove from the pot!
if u press the trigger then i'll press the flush!
see, 'll count till three..tats it!..
hey..whom are u scaring, hanh?..shoot!
raju,put it in!
one..
hey..we'll go to hell but along with that we'll even finish ur dad!..got it
two..
then strain-strain n remove ur dad using a strainer!
wat?
we got the wrong one..this one is empty.
empty???
empty??
empty..v'll empty it!
no no
v'll empty it..v'll empty it..i'm tellin u..v'll empty it
noooooooo...hands up!
come on tel..tel, who you are?
aare, i'm ranchhodas yaa!
aeeeeeeeeeee
no..i swear on dad..i swear on dad..i'm tellin the truth yaar!
i'm ranchhodas..he was chhote!
chhote??????
he was the son of our gardener..
everyone used to call him chhote!
even after his mom-dad passed away...dad let him stay in the house!
he used to do odd house-hold works..u know
changing bulbs..gettin eggs n bread..ironing..like
he was very much interested in studies!
he used to wear my old uniform n get into the school
whichever class he liked..he would go n sit in that one!
i used to take advantage of that..
i used to make him do my homework also
and make him write my exam papers also
i was having a good time!
then one day..
master ji saw that a sixth standard child was solving a tenth standard problem
which class u r in,son?..wats ur name?
we were caught
dad was a big man so master ji thought its better to tell him before telling the principal!
u've beginned this..then u only wil end it!
the whole himachal salutes in front of me..
but as soon as i turn away....behind my back,
they call me an illiterate!
this wont happen with my son!
he wants education...and me..just..degree
let it continue as it is...make this boy an engineer
ranchhodas chhanchad's degree..over there..on that wall i want
i went away to london for four years ..n he kept studyin in ICE using my name
he had a deal with my dad that after gettin a degree from ICE
he wont meet anyone from ICE in his whole lifetime!
he usually said..i wont go meet anyone..but one day two idiots will come searching for me
then wat wil u do?
he misses u both a lot!
i'll give u the address..
go meet him..
but dont tel my secret to anyone yaar..please!
which secret?
aeeeeeeeeee
sir ji..u got d wrong glass..big sir is in this
hey wat d hell is goin on?..
who was that gun man?
aare its a very complicated story n it is without subtitles
u cant understand...
ignore it..ignore it
where are we going?
ladakh
ladakh?..why??
to meet rancho!
is he in ladakh?
what he doing over there?
dont know..but this is a school's address!
school teacher..he he he..master ji!
i'm vice-president of rockledge corporation!
and he..A for apple..B for Ball
D for donkey
next week, i'll be signing a multi-million dollar deal with phunshuk wangdu!
and he..A for apple..B for ball
today, my respect grew even more for that Idiot rancho!
we all went to college only to get a degree....
if we dont have a degree, we wont have a job!
if u dont have a job, no father will give his daughter's hand
bank wont give credit card, n world wont respect us...
but that idiot came to college, not for the degree but to study!
he wasnt afraid to come last or greedy to come first!
who was the first man to step on the moon?
neil armstrong sir!
obviously its neil armstrong, we all know it..but who was the second man?
dont waste ur time, its not important!
nobody remembers the man who ever came second!
after two monthes..26 companies will come to this college to offer jobs to u all!
that means before ur final exams,
u'll have jobs on ur hands!
this is ur last act my friends!
put the medal on the pedal..press the accelerator
go out there n make history
any questions?
yes..
sir, suppose any student gets a job and.....
he fails in the finals by 1-2 marks..
then will the job remain or....?
very good question
is there any other person, in whose mind, the same question is arising?
as expected
please come on stage, everyone give them a big hand..come on the stage..come
come...come..dont waste time!
from past four years, they have been the most consistent students of ICE!
because consistently, they've come last in every exam
come my geniuses..come
if we remove these two people's brains n sell in the market, we'll get a very gud price!
because they r unused brain..never have been used!
n to answer to their question
whether they paas or fail, its not gonna affect their jobs
because they r not gonna get jobs at all!
i guarentee it
their names will be written in gold
FARHANITRATE n PRERAJULISATION!..
give them a big hand please..everybody!
idiot, he raped completely...
collective rape u know..in front of..in front of everyone!
god...i'll stop eating non-veg..i'll light thousands of incense sticks!
do only one thing..
take away VIRUS from this world!
burn him in hell..
make hot pakkodas of him in hot oil....god..
aeee
are u giving god a contract to kill?
idiot u sit quietly, hanh..
idiot every year u sit in the centre with VIRUS n take photo
while we'll be rotting in the side
this year i think we'll be finished out of the photo itself!
aee..
do u know why i come first?
why?
because i'm in love with machines
engineering is my passion..passion
do u know wats ur passion?
hey tats my bag..
keep quiet man!
wat are u doin, rancho?
hey..
this is ur passion..this..this
go n post this letter..
but wat is it?
5 years ago, he had written this letter to his favorite wild life photographer!
andre..isthawa
ya..isthawa
he wanted to go to him..go to hungary n learn work from him!
but fearing his dad, due to hitler qureshi, he never posted the letter at all!
aare..quit engineering..n become a wild life photographer!
do that work which u are talented in!
if lata mangeshkar's dad would have told her to become a fast bowler
or sachin tendulkar's father would have told him to be a singer..
then think..where would they stand today!
are u understanding, what i'm sayin?
idiot..he loves animals but is marrying machines!
ae
baba ranchhodas..
my girlfriend n wife..both are engineering itself
then y do i come last..tel?
because u are a coward..coward
see this..see his hand..the fingers are less..and the rings are more
one for exam..one for sister's marriage n one for job
aare..if u fear so much from the future..u think u can live?
and where wil u focus on today?
i've got weird friends yaar
one fears and lives..and one idiot..dies and lives!
heyy
but u idiot..do both the things..
u fear also and die also...
ae..i dont fear!
hey..listen
he dies on pia and fears to tell
aaaaaaaahehheee
go go..get lost
its easy to give free advise dude but difficult to follow it
if u dare..then go n tell pia..tel
hey from where n all u guys r connecting things..
there's full connection baba
listen to me..listen to me
what i say is..if u go and tell pia about what u feeling
then even i'll go and tel my dad that i wanna be a photographer..
and dont wanna be an engineer
yes
even i'll remove all my rings and go to give interview
now say
say..do u dare..
baba rancchodas rolled his tongue back....what will he say?
come..
come...
where... where.?
mmm hmm.. come...
veeru,
jay has come veeru!!!
see..see if there's any dog!
hey cowards...im not afraid of anythin....come!
hey u guys get in..if there's any danger outside..i'll give VIRUS alert!
idiot..VIRUS..old man!
hey
shall i give background music?
pia?
sshhhhh..dont shout..
i'm ranchhodas chhanchad
listen to me for 2mins then i'll go away
[raju singing...... on background]
[dont say anythin, dont at all say anythin!..]
pia,
the 22minutes tat i spent with u on the scooter
those were the most beautiful 22minutes of my life!
i can spend the rest of my life on the scooter with u
wow!
#.......everythin is still.......#
do u know..u come on scooter everyday wearin a bride's costume in my dreams!
instead of the veil... takes off ur helmet!
and you come near me to kiss me
but that kiss wont happen yaar...
why?
beacuse nose comes in between and then i wake up
nose doesnt come in between, stupid
i'm sorry..i thought u were pia..
i wish i was
sister, why did u interrupt in between?
he took 4 years to say this
pia kiss him n tell him, nose doesnt come in between
you have my permission
kiss him yaar..hez so cute
who is this?
sister
who r u?
do u know..when u were speakin..he kicked..first time!
he..how do u know its a he or she?
dad had asked the astrologer..
he wanted to know,is an engineer coming home or a doctor?
means?
means if its a boy, then its an engineer and if its a gal, then its a doctor
oye champ..u stay inside itself..outside there's a lot of circus!
and the circus's ringmaster, your granfather will spin the hunter and say run!
life is a race..run..be an engineer
but you become watever your heart says
if he scares you too much
keep a hand on ur heart n say AAL IZZ WEll!
he kicked!
say again ..AAL IZZ WELL!
ALL IZZ WEll!
yes..he kicked..he kicked..pia
say ALL IZZ WELL!.
.ALL IZZ WELL!
goooooooo!
you send letter to my dad!....  take this pee-mail freely from us
pigeon..go go go..
pigeon go go go...
pigeon go go go
whoz it?
your coming son-in-law..idiotic VIRUS..and marriage attenders!
rastogi!!
security..that way..that way!!!
so u all have already learnt about the simple pendulum
now lets get down to the advanced study about compound pendulum
its an irregular object oscillating about its own axis
let me demonstrate to u
wats this??
pencil
wats inside it?
lead!
good!  lead is the axis to this pencil
even u can be a compound pendulum if u osscilate about
where is raju rastogi?
present sir!
hi..everybody is here
good morning sir..
where were u last night?
sir, he was studyin sir..he was studyin whole night sir!
really?
he hasnt slept since two nights, thats why he's lookin like this sir!
wat are u sayin!
wat were u studyin?
ummmm..
induction motors sir..induction motor..he studied fully sir..induction motor!
in tat case, mr.raju rastogi..
yes sir........
can u tel me how an induction motor starts?
brrrrm..
brrrrrrrrrrrrrrr..
brrrrrrrrrr.....
stop it!
brrrrrrrrrrmmm brmmmmm brmm brm
sir..rum!!
mr.rastogi, lets have a cup of tea in my office
sir
close the door
do u know how to type?
yes sir
can u type a letter for me?
definitely sir
come sit
sir i'm sorry sir
please type
dear sir,
it is my painful duty to inform u that ur son is restigated..
no no sorry..delete it delete it..go back!
ur son mr.raju rastogi
is restigated from the IMPERIAL COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING!
come on..type type..come on..go on
dad will die sir....
please type
sir,please sir
my decision is final and irrevokable!
he's living only in a hope that he could see me becoming an engineer sir!
you could've thought of this before you pissed in front of my doors...
sir give me one more chance sir, please..just one chance
sir please sir
ok..remove ur name from the letter
and put rancchodas chhanchad's name!
i know he was with you last night!
be my witness and i wont remove u from the college
you have 7.5 minutes with you..to think
#......we wont let you go .......#
#.......we shall not let you leave.......#
#.......even if god might summon you.......#
#.....but we are not the one who fear him.....#
#.....we are standing here in this ground with resolve.....#
#.....take out our eyes from our pal....#
#....no matter how hard you try.....#
#....we're not gonna let you leave lik this.....#
#......we wont let you go .......#
#.......we shall not let you leave.......#
rancho, look at that monitor
raju!
the body is paralyzed due to the shock
but the mind is alert
he can see us and hear us!
please aunty, dont cry in front of him!
talk to him normally.. motivate him.. crack jokes.. keep him happy
oye raju, we have a good news yaar
dad is become proper yaar.... that new medicine worked!
its rastogi family's tradition tat..
if one man gets up..  the other man will lie down!
comeon comeon..getup now
your dad is askin for pia's scooter?
wat do u say?..shall i give it?
wont he bang it?
hey raju, farhan wants to tell u somethin
on the webcam..live from the hostel!
see this..virus has cancelled ur suspension..problem solved
comeon..wake up atleast now!
everythin is solved...
oye..are u listening....hey
rastogi!!
see this..mom bought a new saree..new saree
brand new
it costs 2000 bucks son..see
atleast get up now..idiot
not one..she bought ten sarees..ten!
see
oye raju
raju..tel me,how do i look?
hey..kammo
have u heard about kammo?
aare, kammo's marriage has been fixed
and tat too..without any dowry!
hey..bridegroom..the bridegroom doesnt want maruti 800
doesnt want anything..wants kammo..only kammo..
hanh...
n do u know whoz the bridegroom?
yes
whoz the bridegroom?
guess it
u know him very well
hanh...
he loves animals a lot
hanh..???!!
and ..and he's gonna be a wild life photographer!
hey keep quiet!..keep quiet!
didnt flash??
aare,its our farhan yaar!
as if our farhan will take dowry from u ppl!
aare, our farhan will marry ur sister..farhan!
and that too..free..free..free
hey..hey..
hey..hey raju
raju
if we would have given 1 kilo lady's finger and 1/2 kilo paneer freely to that idiot,
even then he wud get up
what was the need to sacrifice me?
well done yaar..well done well done
everything is fixed..ur sister's marriage is fixed
farhan will marry..ok done!!!
rancho!!..
idiots..how much wil u lie??
u r saved..idiot!!
did u call for a taxi?
i have called for it,... its waiting
thank you,,..
why?
i have to go 4 a job interview
oh..so u gonna go with me?
no..i'll drop u home n i'll go for the job interview!
idiot..why will i go home?
did u forget?..
we had promised something to this idiot!
give..give me ur tie!
why?
give it..i dont think after reading this, u'll be able to go for the interview!
what is this?
its a letter
its come for u..from hungary!
its some photographer..andre isthawan!
idiots..u posted my letter?
he liked ur photos very much..he's become crazy!
he wants to make u his assistant!
he has called you to work  in the brazilian rainforest for one year!
he's sayin..he'll even give u salary!
dad wont oblige!
go to him..n make him understand lovingly..
dont fear today farhan..
otherwise after 50yrs when u'll be old and fallen in the hospital...
and be waiting to die
u'll think then..letter was in the hand..taxi was at the gate..
if i had dared a little bit..life would have been somethin else!
wat do u think, will he like it?
what was the need to get such an expensive one!
today, son is getting a job
now the days to put our head up and roam wid pride are arriving n u r being stingy!..hanh?
aare farhan?
farhan, today was ur interview..right?
i dint go
i dont wanna be an engineer dad!
wat happened..u had an an accident?
sir..umm..
that building in front sir..
i had jumped off its third floor sir!
why?
because i was restigated!
sir i had pissed on director's door when i was in a drunken state...
that devil rancho is still playin with ur brain?
i cant understand engineering..even if i'll be..i'll be a very bad engineer dad!
rancho tells a very simple thing..
whatever u enjoy doing, make that ur profession!
then work wont seem work but a game!
aare..how much will u earn in that jungle?
dad, stipend is'nt too much but i'll get to learn a lot!
after 5yrs, when u'll see ur friends buying a car
then u'll curse urself!
i'll be frustrated being an engineer,
then i'll curse you throughout my life!
dad,its better i curse myself..right?
aare..people will laugh!!
they'll say that you came till final year and had quit!
that kapoor sir told me that u're lucky that ur son is studyin in ICE!
what will he think?
kappor sir din get AC fixed in my room!
makin me sleep comfortably..he himself din sleep in heat!
makin me sit on the shoulders..kapoor sir din take me around the zoo!
u did all that dad!
what u think, makes a difference!
wat kapoor sir thinks, it doesnt make a difference to me!
aare..i dont even know his first name!
have u watched a film n come..are u performing drama?
stop it now..  poor guy is tensed!
god forbid..if he commits something like raju!
then the discussion is only over!
dont say anything to son or else he'll jump from the terrace!
no dad..i wont commit suicide!..
i promise!
that rancho..
whom u call a devil!..
he forcibly made me put ur's and mom's photo in this!
he started sayin that....promise me....that whenever such stupid thoughts come to ur mind!
see this photo and think what will happen to this smile when they see ur dead body!
dad, i wanna convince u!..
but not by hanging this suicide's sword on ur head!
what will happen.... hanh?
if i be a photographer....then i'll earn less right?.. home will be small, car will be small!
but dad, i'll be happy..
i wil be really happy!
whatever i do for u..i'll do it from my heart!
till today..i have listened to whatever u said, today..just once..let me listen to my heart!
please dad!
dad..dont go..please!
return this one..
son, how much will ur professional camera cost?
will we get it against this laptop?
if it costs more money, then ask me son
go..go son..live ur life
yourself marks are consistenly poor..  any particular reason?
due to fear..i was a bright student since childhood
parents thought that it will abolish our poverty!
i started to fear!
when i came here.. i saw that there's a race,.. if u dont come first, no one will recognize u
i started to fear even more!
fear is not good for grade, sir!
i started wearing more rings..praying more
not only praying..i started begging to god
give me this, give me that!
16 bones broke, i got two months to think..then i understood!
sir, today i havent told god..tat get me this job
i just folded my hands..n said thank u 4 this life
if u guys..if u guys even reject me today..then i dont have any regrets
because i believe..i'll somehow do something worthy with my life sir!
see..this very much frank behaviour of ur's is not good for our company!
we need a diplomatic person to handle the clients
and u are way too straightforward!
but..if u assure us that u can control this attitude of ur's..
then..something can happen!!!
sure
after breaking both the limbs, i learnt to stand on my feet sir,
with great difficulty, i got this attitude in me!..it wont cant happen sir!
u keep ur job, i'll keep my attitude
i'm sorry..dont mind sir!
stop
i've been recruiting from the past 25years.. conducted a lot of interviews
to get the job.. people find yes in our yes itself!
from where have u come yaar??..
sir..i??
how much salary will u take brother?..lets discuss
thank u sir..
thank u
oh emperor....
you're great
accept out gift...
govind...............!!!!!!!!!!!
sir you only told if they get job, remove your moustache.....
hanh,.... what have you done?
he eh ehehehheehheeeehhe
im feeling like someone undressed me
humiliated me....
i wont let you conquer, rastogi
you gonna get job only when you pass in final exams,,,,
but this time im gonna set the paper for exam........
dad
thats not fair
everything is fair in love and war....
and this is world war 3
rastogi you're gone this time....
hehe heheheee
what are you doin here?
easy easy....
you're drunk?
ya yaar, had to take two,  four...
two... four??
two or four?
i was in need of dareness...
for what?
to steal this....
what is this?
a duplicate key of VIRUS's office
sshh ssshh sshhhs
questions papers are in the red sealed envelope....
dad has set by himself....
to fail raju in exam..
take it out...
mad or wat??
this is cheating yaar... no..
everything is fair in love and war
eeheh eheheh
ok... just tell me one thing,...
do you really feel...
nose comes in between if wanted to kiss?
hmmm...
ey have this dhokla... hold this,
u gujrati people are too cute yaar.. but why does your food sound so dangerous?
dhokla, phaphda, handhwa, thepla, kakkrah
its seems as though they are some missiles!
come..come on
tonight bush dropped two dhoklas..400 killed, 200 injured!
come on..
aare
i can bear with khakrah, phaphda
but this name of ur's
ranchhodas shyamaldas chhanchad!
yack!!
i wont change my surname after marriage, hanh?
pia, we cant get married
why?..
do u love someone?..
no
are u a gay?
then why dont u propose me?..
are u impotent?
then prove it..prove it
pia..i'm not..
hey stop stop stop stop!
aare, wat happened?
aare, we havent informed pia at all!
oh stop now..my bladders are bursting!!..
oh shutup yaar!
are u in touch with her?
no yaar
but i have her landline no.
then dial it, i'll stop..
ya..stop stop stop
hello!
no place to piss in this country??
hello..ya..is pia there?
she's not there sir
ok..where will she be availiable?..in the hospital?
sir, why will she go to hospital today..  its her marriage today!
she's gone to manali!
pia marriage is over!
its not yet over..see, its a 6 hour's way..if we speed up, then we'll surely reach before the marriage vows!
wat do u say?
now if u have already thought about it partner, then take a u-turn!
ae, no u-turn..straight to ladakh..we'll meet rancho n come back..
friday, i have a meeting with phunsukh wangdu
come..come..sit in the car
if i miss it, u know wat will happen!
the japanese will get in..
they are offering him a first name in the company
phunshuk n fujiashi..profit hearings are....
pia weds suhas!!
and thanks for the suit, hanh!
yaar..virus will suffer a heart attack
hello.., hello
whenever his daughters are getting married..we come off to ruin it!
ok listen..i'll handle pia..u pull out the price-tag!
farhan!
we found rancho, pia!
is it for 107?..
yes sir!
give it here..
how much time do u take yaar?
sorry sir..
come on..go
house-keeping sir!
come in!
more..more..amore
quick quick iron my sherwani!
aare, we found rancho..still, will u marry this donkey?
u're mad, farhan!
dont fool urself pia!
you love rancho even today.. n eating these dhoklas remembering him!
more..more..amore
he's a dog's tail..put it inside a pipe for 12years.. when u remove it..it'll still remain bent!
shutup farhan..suhas is the changed man!
now he never talks about brands n prices!
my 1.5lakh worth sherwani!!!!!!!!!
why do u people eat chutney???
sir'i'll do something sir!
wat..wat will u do?
sir..sir..we get such shirts n sherwanis everyday in our laundry sir!
i'll clean it within 2minutes sir!
sir..one minute sir!
get it soon!
but its too late now, farhan!
pia..pia..come, its getting late!..comeon
pia..i'm raju..dont shout, people will kill me
where is suhas?
aare, he had come from house-keeping..he took away the sherwani!!
go inside..n send suhas
the hymns are going on pia..if i get up n go then all will be furious yaar!
yes farhan, tel me
car is ready at the gate
i'm telling..take pia n run!
aare dont move yaar
sir??
sherwani??
u are here?
yes
whose taking the vows over there?
vows?
if the vows get over..then our marriage will be over..i'm already married pia..lets go!
there are so many people over here..all of the will laugh!!
aare, because people laugh..so will u suicide?
aare..rastogi??
pia.. people will gossip for two days n forget it!
but today if u do this marriage..u never forget that car was at the gate!
we had come to take u to rancho..but only because u feared from people
u got married to this donkey!
house keeping??
yaar pia..there is a small..minor tension..
what?
we dont know if rancho's married or not?
wat!!
aare, i would'nt have happened yaar..it would'nt have happened!
and if it would've happened?
then we'll drop u back!
aare, dont take tension..have this biscuit
hand-made biscuit from san-francisco
idiot,,,.
from where did he come?
ignore it..ignore it..
u eat the biscuits..eat..
its very good
AAL IZZ WELL..AAL IZZ WELL!
till yesterday i was a noble citizen of this country
but in the last 24hours..i had got an emergency landin of a plane
almost immersed shyamalda's soul in the gutter
and kidnapped a bride from her wedding
all for that idiot rancho
but even tat idiot gave out his heart for his friends
he had entered ravan's territory, to steal a question paper for raju
search for a red sealed envelope
ok come...
he was very afraid..that if raju failed, he'll again go n do a high-jump!
but even we were very principled robbers!
we had sweared tat we'll steal the paper oly 4 raju..we wont even c it ourselves!
aare yaar,where has he hidden it?
aare yaar, searching like this, it'll be good morning
rancho, ask pia
where are u, since then i'm callin u?
pia, ur phone
give it to me, one minute pia..pia
jiju..when we say AAL IZZ WELL..it kicks!
it kicked
u heard?
pia, your phone
we got it..rancho..
hello??
aare atleast call me sometimes!!
make its copy..make its xerox copy..quick!
take it
keep it wherever we got it from...
carefully!
oye where had you been???? hanh?
hanh??
take this...
what is it??
enjoy....
question paper....
VIRUS's had set by himself to make you fail in exam....
weird friends i've got....
teaching how to live straight forward first....
then makin me do things that are odd...
no..today..
if i pass, it'll be on my own ability!
otherwise its ok if i fail!
idiot!
idiot won my heart!..my heart said i'll make this idiot my brother-in-law
um.. um... then i controlled my emotion!
go..go..
no sir no sir please..
u had come to change the system!
u'll piss on my door
bloody rascals
sorry sir
you are restigated, if u r'nt gone by morning..i'll call the police
i'll call the police
rascals..rascals all of u!
how did he get my office's key?
i gave him the keys dad
i wish i had given it to my brother
he would have been alive today..
stop it pia
what do u think?..brother, fell off the train and died?
shutup pia
you decided that he'll be an engineer.....
did you ever ask him, what he wanted to be?
how much you pressurised brother, dad..
he thought its easier to die than to give an entrance exam!
what is she saying?
dad, you go into the room!
you get into your room!
pia stop it..wat r u doin pia!..i'm tellin u right..
brother wanted to study literature..he wanted to be a writer
but he could'nt write anything more than this suicide note!
pia, hide that letter..please!
till when will i hide it sister?
once
only once if u would have told him
if u can do engineering then quit it!
do whatever you like!
then today brother would have been alive, dad!
he cannot suicide
u're right dad, it wasnt a suicide...
it was a murder!
in many areas..the roads are immersed in water..their is total traffic jam!
dad..
dad!!..
mona....
aare, i told you to go back right? then why are you coming behind us?
why..is this your mom's road?
please help..we are desperate here! is there only one ambulance in the city?
get an ambulance from some other hospital!
the whole city is immersed in water, sir
we cant do anythin!
no..pia..that..
hey mona..wat happened?
rancho..pia!
rancho, its impossible to reach over here.... so do as i say!
you guys are not understanding!..get water bags..drive fast!!..u're not underst.......
they disconnected!!
monaa!
be careful..be careful
turn on the light..turn on the light!
table..table..table-tennis table
raju,  switch on the webcam!
yaa
ya pia..
hello raju..where is sister....show me!!
ya..hold on hold on
dont worry.. hold on
see this pia
sister ,everything will be alright!  i'm near u..ok?
pia i'm dying..
rancho, when there were no hospitals and doctors in this world even then babies were born...
you guys will carry on sister's delivery
aaaaa
aal izz well..aal izz well..
how dare you...???
wat are you guys doing?
dad, dont come in between..please stay out of this ok!!
farhan, you go get towels and scissors....
millimeter, get cloth drying clip and hot water....
rancho you cover sister...
sister.... push
push..push..come on..
push....
keep quiet..i'm unable to push
rancho, see if crowning is happening?
crowning means?
go get that diagram
rancho, see if the head is coming out
come on rancho..quickly
gooooooo
go go go..go rancho..go..come on
no..no crowning..its not coming..no
sister.. please push
mona..
mona
she's tired pia..
wake her up
if she doesnt push, then it'll be a big problem
vacuum cup has to be put, pia
from where will they get a vacuum cup over there...
wat is a vacuum cup?..how does it look?..wat do they do with it?
i'll show u
if the mother gets tired and is unable to push then this cup is put on the baby's head
suction pump creates vacuum and this cup sticks on the baby's head
then the baby is pulled out
i can make this..i can make it
how?
vacuum cleaner sir..
vacuum cleaner??..
yes sir..vacuum cleaner
but vacuum cleaner's pressure is too much rancho
i'll control the pressure
is there a vacuum cleaner over there?
its there in my office
farhan go soon and get it from sir's office
take the key
mona..push mona..come on push
wat happened?
ya pia
hello raju wat happened?
the light is gone pia
oh god!!..now how wil the vacuum cleaner work
farhan, you get the vacuum cleaner and i shall get the light..
how?
millimeter..get virus out..fast come on
come virus..get out..get out
aare not this virus yaar.. my virus, the inverter that i had made
that?
go get that soon
oh ok..that one..i understood!!!
raju..wake everyone in the hostel
and tell them that we want car battery, wires, tool kit and vaccuum gauge.. come on
come out..there's an emergency in the common room
where is rancho?
sir sir sir..here sir
everyone keep the batteries over here..comeon..quickly!
and the wires
raju.. turn off all switches and connect this inverter to main...
take this
rancho, vacuum cleaner...
farhan.... that camera cleaning thing..what do u call it?
plower..plower..go n get it soon
rancho, take this plower
pull the vaccuum and put it on the pipe..over here!
rancho..its done!
is every swiches off?
now turn on only TT table's n computer's light!
raju, turn on the computer..fast!
help me..connect this..put it in this!
pia..come soon..pia..come soon
love u rancho
farhan..on it
yes
pia, how much must the suction be?
not more than 0.5 rancho
farhan..0.5
cover up
yes
0.5
ok
delivery using vacuum cleaner..i havent seen this in 20 yrs of my career!
farhan..off it..
yeah
raju, get on the table..see me
push the baby down like this..like this
farhan, turn it on..
come on sister....push..u can do it!
come on mona..push..come on
think abt champ..for champ..come on
come on mona..mona push
its coming..its coming
come on sister....you can do it
farhan..turn it off..
ya ya..i turned it off
put two clips..and cut the umbical chord
farhan, get two clips..fast!
put it on the umbical chord and get scissors
careful careful
get the towel..towel
pia..pia,,,why isnt it cryin?
hanh?..
hey
hey champ
rancho rub its back
no..nothin is happening..
blow air into its mouth..
come on..
come on champ
nothin is happening
queit mona..quiet..
say all izz well..  say aal izz well
it kicked
what!!!
say aal izz well..  all izz well
all izz well
yeah!!!!
at that time if VIRUS would have told that his grandson would have been an engineer...
i would have raped that idiot!
but when that idiot opened his mouth, then a miracle happened!
solid you kick.. will u become a footballer or what?
become..become whatever ur heart says
stop....where are u going?..
i'm not finished with you,
on the first day of college, you had asked me a question....remember?
that why dont they use a pencil in the space..
if the tip of the pencil breaks in the space, then it will be revolving under the action of gravity
it can get into someone's eyes, it can get into someone's nose
it can get into the instrument panel..
u were wrong..u were wrong
you cannot be right all the time!
you understand??
yes sir
this was a very important invention.... you understand?
my director had told me....
when any extraordinary student comes...
go go go...go study...
pass in the exams and go away from here......
and now student of the year.. ranchhodas shyamaldas chhanchad
sir..one photo sir!
i wanted to capture all these memories in my camera n take it with me!
on that day, everyone were hugging each other, getting emotional and making promises
that we'll stay in touch, we'll surely meet up once in a year!
who knew that we were seeing rancho for the last time?
yaar, untie him!
i'll sue you all in american court!
raju..
this kinda school..... only can be made by that idiot rancho!
but where is he?
see there..
go in creatures..... go
dont piss over here...
u want a beating, hanh?
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
ha ha ha..
we got him.... that idiot is some where around.. come on
brother, where will we find ranchhodas?
is his name ranchhodas!!!
rancho
chote..chote..chote
aare, whats his name ultimately?
aare, cool down.... cool down
come with me..
where.. where is rancho?
rancho..rancho
farhan, do u know.....he has read every book written by u!!..see this
raju.... he reads ur blogs everyday!
he tells the children about ur research very proudly!
do u remember your helmet pia sister?
it was stolen right?
who are you?.. and how do u remember all our names?
didnt you recognize me?
no
how will u recogzine.. now that millimeter has become centimeter!
oye oye oye..idiot..what centimeter..u have become kilometer!!!
but what are you doing over here?
for the first time, i got a letter on my name.. i found a train ticket from tat
it was written inside that if you wanna study then board the train!
and i boarded it..
idiot rancho..
where is tat idiot?
furjee.. take this n go!!!
you come in my dreams everyday on a scooter wearing a bride's costume !
instead of the veil..  you take off your helmet!
and you come near me to kiss me!
aaaaaaah..ouch!
could nt you tell and go?
ummmm..no..
ummmm...sorry
did u get married?
wat?..wat?..
no..u?
almost, idiot!
then?
then what?
do you love someone?
hmm..
ya
who?
you..!
did you see, the nose does'nt come in between, stupid!
yes, thats right!
idiot rancho!
hi, farhan!
aare keep your hi to yourself!
aare listen to me!
no, you listen to me
aare..u listen to me..listen to me,
no,u listen to me,   i'll explain everything
hey raju
idiot!!
look here...
aeee.idiot
hit him..hit him two-three from my side aswell
because of you, what all i had to become..u know?
this idiot got glasses!
come.. getup idiot.. getup
ha ha eh ehhe hehhhee
hey idiot!
having fun idiots?
hey.. hi chatur
ranchhodas chhanchad.....
namaste masterji
where have u reached?..u have become a teacher in the village, eh?
A for apple..  B for ball
we boarded the bus together right
but your train went away in reverse
straight to primary teacher from engineering
ha ha ha ha
whats the salary chanchhad?..tell me..Rs 5000, hanh?
for me, they are like 100 dollars
my son's pocket money is more than your salary
hey stop this non-sense
he used to do non-sense.. he wanted to change the education system
he wanted to change the world
now he changes children's diaper over here!
will you break his teeth or shall i break it?..idiot
hey let it be!
do you remember...i had told u..
one day you'll cry and i'll laugh
hehehe hahhaa
sign over here.. accept it.. that and lost and i won!
the declaration of defeat.. unbelivable yaar.. chatur.. unbelivable
hey, that is virus's pen
how did you get it.. you stole it?
umm..now what shall i say yaar?
this is for winners..  not losers
no problem..  if u have any difficulty in school and need a donation
to call my assistant, eh!
ha ha ehe he e
A for apple..B for ball
he has'nt changed at all yaar
yaar..ignore it,..ignore it!
leave him yaar..he'll keep sayin anythin
leave it..the good news is ur name is not ranchhodas chhanchad
imagine.... after marriage i would be pia chhanchad!
yack
by the way, whats your real name?
phunshuk wangdu
wangdu?
pia wangdu?
no.. means u r a scientist?
tat means u have 400 patents in ur name?
i wont change my surname after marriage
means you are chatur's wangdu?
are the japanese looking for you?
i dont like wangdu! i think so...
yaar tell me one thing.. are you a scientist or a teacher?
i'm a scientist but i also teach children
means you are the phunshuk wangdu??
yes man..yes
oye silencer.. hey chathur comeback!
stop stop stop
take van, hanh? ehhehe hehe
he wont stop that way!..   i'll stop him!
Mr.wangdu.. i cant believe u called!
i'm sorry mr.chatur but i cant sign a deal with your company!
what sir, what happened sir?
aare how shall i sign yaar.. you took away my pen!
he heh ehehe
what pen sir?.. i did'nt get you
the one thats in your hand.. virus's pen!!
virus's pen??
mr.wangdu?
ya tell me chatur!
A for Apple..B for Ball.... L for lucky!
ehhe ehhee
yaar, he has been raped!!
eh ehhehee
u got me..
u got me rancho
i mean mr.wangdu..  totally flowd me..   good one
i hope our personal problems are not gonna affect our deal....
hey chatur..over here..here
i was just joking yaar.. i knew it from within that you'll do something in life!
no.. u're lying?
no no no no.. i'm tellin you.. i swear
rancho 100..chatur zero
you win, i lose.. you dont believe me
aare yaar
oh emperor, you are great.. accept the gift
i'll give you a free advice mr.wangdu..run!!
run run..
hey rancho.. i'll lose my job yaar... i have small-small kids
baba ranchhodas used to say rightly
kids.... be self-efficeient.. self-efficient
then success will come behind u