Brothers and sisters today your radio
anchor Amin Sayani is very happy
Because l also love today's
requested song
Manoj Sharma from Delhi alias Manu
and Tanuja Trivedi from Lucknow alias Tanu
And raja Avasti from Lucknow
They all have requested for this song
For all you people a song
from 1972
Sister in law you took bath already,
did brother take bath or not?
Let me check.
Cut it fast
You come and have a look
Dont worry everything will be fine
Look at time.
lts very late
What time l call Pandit?
Sister come downstairs
She took my clip
Where is your uncle?
Turn off this
ln laws are about to come here
Have bath.
We still have so much time
Even groom have not reached Delhi
What happen to your coat?
An old lady was sitting beside me,
she dropped tea over me
You got glasses? Since when?
2 months ago
How are you?
l'm fine
These glasses suits you
You are not changed.
How is your leg?
He got glasses
lts a sun glasses
We are getting late for train
Aunty need atleast half hour
to fight with loaders
Look at her.
She is very beautiful
And there is no problem too
Trivedi has lots of property
ls it very urgent?
Just now l have come
Your mother has find out so many girls.
Final girl must be from Kanpur
Bring sister in law fast.
l'm tired of eating mother's hand food
Do fast. l dont have time.
Bring all together
You can never be good
Have a look at picture carefully.
l will not show it to you again
He is coming to see your
sister in law
You have to beat him
l will get marry later.
First l have to beat him
l'm telling you all the luggage
is outside car now
Move it on side
What happen?
Who did this?
Were they thief?
Leave it
l like only refine Samosas (snacks)
You are very lucky l must say
He is living in London for so many
years but he still obey his parents
He want to marry and lndian girl
What are you doing?
Have some sweet
My daughter won a gold medal
Manu was not ready for marriage
l told him so many times than he agreed.
He said yes this is also a work, lets do it
He has a great sense of humour
Foreign girls dont know our culture
My Tanu is very smart
She knows all the work of home.
She made all these food
She got studied in Delhi but her
culture and thoughts are of U.P.
You made a fantastic food
Can l show you my dance?
l have learned it from Nach Baliye
He has learned Snake dance
l was saying lets see girl
Let Manu have some food then
you can meet her
lf god wants and they both like each other
then lets go to Vishnu Devi in evening
l have extra tickets. One of my office wanted
to go with his family but he could not go
May be they did not get invitation from goddess.
We can visit goddess temple
l mean its a good idea
Then we will go back to Delhi
from there
Tanu is not feeling well.
Thats why she cannot come downstairs.lf Manu can
come upstairs then they will meet each other
Lets go. What we will do there?
They both are smart. Let them spent time together
They will not say anything
infront of us
Come upstairs.
Tanu's room is upstairs
Brother in law are you scared?
You want us to come with you?
You sit here.
l call her
Careful
She is having viral since
last 3 days
Doctor give her sleeping pills
Thats why she look very sleepy.
ln Kanpur we got suffered from viral easily
Why are you standing?
Please sit down
You talk with each other.
We are outside
You should not take sleeping
pills in viral
l dont know why here doctors
recommend this
You no need to be shy.
l'm also very confused
But what we can do?
We have to talk
Honestly l was not ready for this
kind of marriage
Your father must told me l'm
a doctor
l work in Pharmaceutical company
and l did graduation in Delhi
And l also got same photo in my room
lf you dont want to talk then
l go downstairs
Are you fine?
What happen?
Did you like girl?
l like girl
Congratulations.
Now you have buy gold jewellery
Everything is done
You liked a sleeping girl
l hate you and every guy
who come to see me
Because of you l took
5 sleeping pills with 1/4 Vodka
What did my parents told you?
Now when you have done everything,
then l tell you one thing.. Goto hell
l have a boyfriend and he is a contractor.
Your black eyes are because of him
Look l have a tattoo of his name.
Now you have to say no
Tomorrow you will dis-agree
for this marriage
Listen to me.
There is a problem
She was smoking at door
She was saying everything is wrong.
She does not want to marry me
She love someone else and she
wants to say no
She also made a tattoo
of his name
But yesterday she said
yes for marriage
You are fooling me in day time
l teach lesson to her uncle.
What are you doing?
For what?
You used toilet
l did not shit.
So what?
Look a man become ghost
after death
but a woman always remain witch
Her father bring everyone to vishnu devi
and she does not want to marry
They will beat me
Go and tell your daughter
dont wants to marry me
l dont want to do this
Why?
What do you mean?
Dont become so kind or
you will be beaten by mother
You tell me what l do?
How to say no?
He is not listening to me.
You tell me how to say no to them?
l think you dont undertand
what l told you yesterday
Ok l'm coming
Shall we say?
Why?
Dont become so kind
lf you cannot say than may
l say?
Father please come here
Come.
What happen? Anything special?
eat it now
He dont wants to marry
Careful
she is my daughter Ayushi
and she is Sapna.
my becoming daughter in law
she lives very near.
She is doing fashion designing from Punjab
Last month she got engaged
with my son
There is alot of problem
How you get hurt?
He is my son raja
You are teasing me alot
Atleast respect guests
He was born in Confue.
Thats why he fights everytime
Have tea
Can l do a round from terrace
You got hurt
Put this on wound before
sleeping
Dont think that we wanted to deceire you
Nobody come when they know
about her name
My sister is very good.
She do all the work of home
Doctors are saying if she got good
treatment then she will be fine
dont think like this.
your sister is very good
lf my brain would be good then
l would marry her
l have a problem.
then why you come here?
l also have to think about them
You are a responsible person
What we can do?
Have food before going
Whatever you say?
You are a very nice man
London guys never give respect
to Lucknow guys
Come downstairs easily
There is a shortage of good girls
What is a use a girl who
does not have 1 hand?
Her second hand was use less
Trivedi's daughter was very good
She was a good girl.
She is very open minded girl
3 times she ran away from home
These days she is having affair
with a contractor
l dont want to see anymore girls.
Next week l'm going back
You do something.
What can l do?
lf he will marry then l will
wear a suit and come
lf not then l will stay in my house
You are listening to Sunil Dutt's song
and living so many years in London
l was thinking you only
listen to English Songs
After drinking this you will see
Tanu more clearly in moon
Tell me one thing
Do you really love Tanu?
Can l tell you one thing?
Marriage are made in destiny.
lf she is in your destiny
then you will marry her
and if not you cannot get her
by any source
Thats why l'm saying you drink
this and lets go to Punjab
Jassi is getting married.
really?
What are you saying?
What are you doing?
You want to come Punjab or
you have to take permission from Tanu?
We need to go just there.
Every guest must ride horse to go there
Why are you playing drums?
How you got attracted with
Bihari family?
With in 3 hours l felt in love
Jassi made agree everyone
He is my chilhood friend Puppi
SHe is my college friend
Problem is that he is in love
He love her alot
Make a promise
lf she will come everytime infront
of me than he will become mad
He become calm after so many requests
lts a matter of marriage
Come with me.
You meet with Tanu and l will with Payal
l dont want to meet anyone
She already has a boyfriend.
Boyfriend will run away
Now you have grown up
Be a man
l love the way l'm
What is your name?
Komal
Very nice name
and yours?
What can l do?
My name is like that
What are you doing?
Are you mad?
Meet her
What you are going to take?
All man are bastard
They are not man. They are horses.
They are telling about horses
Man is a man and horse is a horse.
Man has a brain and horse dont have brain
is your Jassi a horse?
You went inside medical store
What l have done?
l have bought a chocolate
Yes l should buy that too
l have understand. There is one more
medical store ahead, we will buy from there
Like you had so many boyfriends
What is wrong in it?
Every week you make a new boy friend
How can a person have a new love
every week?
l did not study in city that l
will do marry with my parent's choice
l also have values and principles.
What is love?
Who is giving horn?
Your horse has come
l also come.
what you will do?
your brother will sleep well.
who is listening to radio
what are you doing?
let it play
how much is it?
please come with me to there
l have a work with you.
what?
try to understand.
l cannot tell here
Tanu l'm going with him there
you can go in farm,
you both are getting married
what is your speciality?
what is pace maker?
a machine who increase heart beat
l can also do this
l dont have this misunderstanding
how is your boyfriend?
the person who beat me in train
l dont think much about boyfriend because
l usually change them
l like any boy
What about that tattoo?
lts my surname tattoo
How dare you to say that?
l tell you sorry.
Cannot you wait until wedding?
l was mad. lf l tell to my
brothers than they will kill you
you are showing me finger
dont talk to me ever
die here
What did doctor say?
what he will say?
he is watching dreams?
Doctor is very interesting
sometimes poor man's dreams
beat him
lt was a great meeting
lf we do fight then we can
save government
Nobody can do anything with us
Sing with O
what are you doing?
you are with us or with them?
go and sit with them
she is doing hanging out with doctor
why dont you do anything?
until when you will tolerate this?
yes speaking
how are you?
l want to give you a good news.
Manu sharma loves your daughter
They both are in love
l'm your supporter
l'm your supporter.
We have to do wedding fast
we have to go to Punjab
who was on the phone?
do the preparation to go Punjab
you again want to fail
everyone is drinking upstairs
have it
you will not do vomitting,
ask from Bhambhu
l will beat you
please listen to me
do you have anything?
means wine?
give me.
lets have it
you will drink it? yes.
if you are not giving then l will buy by myself
you want it is with soda or with
cold drinks?
you drink it
you are very darling type
l was thinking there must be lighting
and fireworks here
but its very quiet here.
show us your dance
l dont know how to dance
You know how to watch?
Let me show you Kanpuriya dance
what are you doing here?
Manu called you here?
l sit here
you are mad.
we have a 10 mins work with payal's brother
so what tanu is inside
Manu you are my friend. you come in my wedding.
you can go anywhere
what are you doing?
did you call me?
bring us to beauty parlor
come with us
sit here.
your father called me
go with him
he has lots of time
and he is a fool too
l will get ready here.
come with us or l will beat you
you are totally changed,
but you are not changed
everybody is disturbed here because of me
Jassi is not happy.
Payal is hurted
Lets go from here
lt will be good.
why you will go?
its not your mistake
Tanu is angry because of her parents
Dont worry.
We know what we have to do
its already done alot.
Now l dont want to do anything else
Stay happy
there is a boy who loves you alot
he is a doctor and settled in London.
but you love an ordinary doctor
what is wrong in it?
uncle is telling me your stories
dont talk to me.
l dont need anyone's advice in my life
who can give you advice?
you are a princess
why are you shouting?
go and wash your face
l dont know anything about
your new boyfriend
may be he is good and make you happy.
whatever l felt l'm telling you
nothing will be good by hurting parents
as you wish.
everybody is thinking from their mind
nobody called anyone
they got a random call.
you are not so beautiful
he loves you but he is
not fool like you
its useless.
he is going back
where are you going?
he has already left
please drop me to station
you are still disturbed
you will find some other girl
l left my girl because of you.
she was about to fell in love
if you wanted to stay disturbed than
we should stay there
Tanu is coming.
Dont make a joke
you made me run alot
are you angry with me?
l'm wearing your earings
l was disturbed because of my parents
l have not tell this to anyone
Tomorrow my boyfriend is coming and day
after tomorrow we are getting married
you are still very kind heart
you wanted to do Kanyadan?
l have an ordinary ticket
for what purpose you
have put chain?
doctor you??
l told you we have an old relation.
otherwise why you meet me here?
You are going or coming?
my friend had a wedding in kapoor tala
l was also going kapoor tala
but l took wrong train
l think you did not find any
space to sit
i was talking to him about seat.
who is calling you?
what can l tell you?
its a long story
there is a girl.
Manu loves him alot
he got cheated in love
girl is good. she has a boyfriend and
they want to marry each other
l will beat her boyfriend.
l'm from U.P.
its not like that
talk to her.
its your friend's marriage, go there
l'm also going to kapoor tala.
we both we will be there to find some outcome
l have told this to parents that until
manu will not come back, l will not marry
its your marriage.
why you are not getting ready?
He is my friend raja
have you seen Tanu anywhere?
no why?
l'm looking for her
you are great
l found my marriage here. her parents were
there thats why l could not tell you there
we are getting married at 5 PM.
quietly come at registrars office
dont be late. let me get married.
then l will arrange yours
please bring some flowers
one murder is written in my destiny
l will kill raja
dont talk rubbish.
you are talking rubbish
is it a smart thing to bring flowers
in your bride's wedding?
go and fight otherwise go back Delhi
take flowers and let go to
registrar's office
why dont you understand?
why are you messing with me?
tell me his name
let me talk to mother.
tell me your father's name
let me talk to mother
Mother you tell her,
she is teasing me
tell me her father's name
l'm telling you.
rajinder Trivedi
Tell me.
l cant reach at 6 PM
give me pen.
do you have a pen?
try to understand mother
then l cant do anything. you are late.
office time closed
come tomorrow morning
congratulations on your wedding
everything is spoiled
send me his photo.
l will kill him
lf you have any work then tell me.
Take care of yourself
lts a problem
What we will do?
Where we will stay at night?
l have some friends in Jaypur.
they will help us
problem is that nobody will request
for us with Tanu's parents
otherwise we would do with
everyone's happiness
yes l went there.
l went to do wedding
go from here.
l ready her
where you were?
l was searching for you
can you please call Tridevi?
Who made a plan to do wedding
night in Marriott?
he is my husband now
lt was doctor's wedding gift
l dont understand anything
look your boyfriend is calling you
say me best of luck
its me
l have talked to your father
he is agreed for your and raja's wedding
we all are fool
only you are smart
first she wanted to love
you are disturbed why this is happening
so easily?
you are a ghost
then do marriage but you want to do
marriage in different style
l dont understand your problem
a good person has arranged your marriage
and you are also angry with him
you even cant see love in his eyes
l'm not mad that l left my honeymoon
and come here for you
there is someone.
princess is ready. bring her
did you call me?
l was in court that time
arrange next week's london
ticket for me
take care of yourself
l want to say something to you
whatever you are doing,
you need a power
l always wanted to do a work for
l can say yes l did this work
but it never happened
but the work you are doing,
its very good
not everyone is brave like you
who gave this gift?
why you are hiding?
everyone gave me gift,
you did not give me any gift?
my gift is in your room
go and have a look,
lets go payal
lets check what he has given to me
take out paper
its still not too late to think again
strange only you know me
in this whole world
flowers decoration still not complete?
l have an urgent work in Allahabad.
tomorrow morning l will come back
you have to do my work.
we give wedding dress to bride
take this rs 10000 and buy
a dress for him
please do it. if would be here then
i will buy for her
buy a dress from Lucknow
can l ask you one thing?
on that day in registrar's office you
had a pen
then why did you lie?
do you know l live in London
by the age of 12
daily l make breakfast and l eat alone
and l alone go to office
l dont have any good friend
l lived very unromantic life
then parentes forced me to do marriage
l come here and l fell in love with you
is it my mistake?
you told me that l dont want to marry then
l go back. now you come back again
l did not had power in court
l was thinking if you will not get a pen
than you will not get married
can you see any difference between
me and you?
l also cannot see any difference between
me and her
after meeting you l made a tattoo
you know l made a mistake
after meeting Manu l felt he
is perfect for me
he never customize me.
he allows me the way l'm
he loves with my all habits
you will always made a mistake.
remain with me
sometimes you made mistake and
sometimes l made
everything is opposite for you
marry me. you will be change after 4 days
or l will change on 5th day
and if l say l'm already changed then?
there is a big difference between you
and this monkey
l was saying l could not stop
l made a bad deed
tell me do you love me or not?
then how will l know?
you cried alot in car.
did you touch my hand?
still you are thinking.
touch my hand and say
l like the boy
she likes boy
you come here to tell me that
this marriage will not happen
girl is not agree
if tomorrow girl will run away then?
its a matter of their lives.
may be they will divorce in future
look tridevi.
l'm telling you for last time
All the preparations has been done
l'm coming for wedding
go and concentrate in wedding preparation
go from here you all
l have 2000 and you give 5000
give it yo Darudha and send him to jail
are you mad?
let me clean
you area is very smart
can l tell you one thing?
call police or l will die
tell him aunty
where are you inspector?
why are you crying?
what will happen now?
but why are you crying?
l know how to ride a bike
time has gone to sit at back
do whatever you think good
on that day you took Tanu and
l was quiet
because l thought it was good.
today l'm taking her
today you do whatever you think good
is it a joke?
what do you think you can make
fun of me infront of half city?
and l will stand like a cow
if you dare then bring her.
l will shoot you
because l'm feeling l'm doing correct
today l'm taking Tanu with me
because if l'll scare then l will
get shoot
and l'll not scare then l will
also get shoot
you also think that l will not shoot?
l was scared because of Manu otherwise
l'm not scared of anyone
you are right
you become hero, she become heroine
and me...
today when l came out from my house,
my mother did not give me any blessings
nobody wanted that this marriage
will happen
l have made a promise
that l'm coming for wedding
then l remember my one more promise
l promised you that l will arrange your
marriage
Tanu l'm monkey but l'm
not a theif
if he is not a good man and you are not
loyal to him
and if l'm not little bit bad
then god promise l would
shoot him
l was saying that there is an old
relation with you
Happy marriage