What was so urgent?
We have the rest of our
lives. We can meet anytime
Let's go
Veera, I think you should
go back. No one saw us
Vinay, I want to breathe.
Wedding traditions
Welcome! The costumes,
the jewelry, etc...
Please let's get away for awhile
Just for an hour
An hour?
Start the car
- 15 minutes
- Let's go
15 minutes!
5 minutes to go
Time hasn't started
Let's escape these bright
lights. Out in the open
- To the highway?
- Without bodyguards?
Just a glimpse of the highway. Ok?
All the knots in
my brain are untying
Good. Let's head back
Some untying left
A little longer has
become a lot longer
SQ?
Veera, it isn't safe here
You're here
Vinay...
Let's not go back. Let's run away
Yes! Let's make a run for it
And make a beautiful
home on some mountain top
You can be a shepherd. I can cook
It'll be great fun
I'm turning back
Enough!
Should've turned back
ls it closed?
See!
The air is so
different here. So fresh
Breathing the city
air makes you restless
Why can't it be like this?
If you've had your fun, come back
Come out!
Veera, hurry
He's coming from behind
Hey, you scum
Run!
You there, stop!
Stay there, all of you
Swine!
She gets it next
I won't say it again
- What's wrong with the jeep?
- Wasn't it checked?
Take this car
I warned you
I'm watching you
Follow me and I'll shoot you
Call Tonk
Tonk, got a car? Where are you?
- Where to?
- Know Mangar back road?
Drive on. I'll tell you
The road behind the
hills. In the fields
Let her go
Open the back door
Tie her hands
O beloved, I will carry you
far away from this market place
Far away from all your sorrows
Your name?
What's your name?
I want to go home
Name?
Stop!
Speak up!
Veera
Veera, what?
Tripathi
Manek Tripathi's daughter?
I told you a thousand times.
Stay away from the rich
No messing with them
They're linked to big shots
They'll skin you alive
if you mess with them
Now deal with it
He didn't know who she was
Who travels in a
flashy Audi? Tell me
Tripathi's daughter
Yes
The police, the Home
Guard. BSF, the army
They're crawl up your
backside and exit your mouth
Now save your ass
A man should know his place
Why climb a mountain if
you don't have the balls?
What are you staring at?
What will you do? Eat me?
You're scared shitless.
Pair of eunuchs!
Bhaati!
You shouldn't have said that
I won't forget this
No, I won't, Bhaati
Or should I fix you right now?
Put that away
- Easy
- Bullshit
Stay away from the rich
Fear them!
Not a word more
Why should we fear the rich?
Salute them
Open doors for them? Why?
Because they can take
your ass whenever they want
They've got it all. What's left?
We're used to licking ass.
Enjoy getting screwed now
You mother
Let's go
Sit!
You're talking about Manek Tripathi
He owns industries around the world
Ministers and politicians are
his mates. Must we take them on?
What will you do?
What now?
Call him
Hello, Tripathi-ji
You know what? Your
daughter is in our custody
I am texting you an address
Get there with the ransom, please
Yes
That's just what I'll say
And when the girl
gets shot in the leg...
...Tripathi will come
panting with the cash
Or I'll sell her off to a
brothel. In some shady street
Vanished. India is too big
A bad omen is shadowing him
He'll land us in trouble too
You'll die a dog's death, Bhaati
A dog always dies a dog's death
What'll they do to me?
Hang me four times?
I've murdered three men already
I'll die as I lived
But this will happen
This I will do
Listen
Wake up!
Gaurav
Don't be scared
They call me Goru
I'll take care of you
No
I'll talk to you later
We have to go now. Too risky here
Get up. Now!
I don't trust any of you anyway
So do what you have to do
Let's go
Switch off your phones
Their woman is in our hands
Today is our day
Hail Baba Kisan Das!
Hail Lakkad Maharaj!
Hail to our villages. Our land!
Long live!
Any new qawali out in the market?
Listen, brother
People don't like
listening to new qawalis
A special recitation
In honor of Khwaja Gharib Nawaz
- Is it old?
- Very old
Then it's fine
You've outdone yourself
Your name will spread far
Couldn't talk on the phone
- I heard today. Tried calling you
- Where will you hide us?
Things have changed
You're famous now
Wherever you go with the girl,
all Ajmer Sharif will know
And we'll all become
famous. You can't stay here
ls it on the news?
Not yet
Everyone knows because
of the damn police
My God
You have M.K. Tripathi's
daughter. Imagine!
It's me
You unwell?
Your lips must be numb
I'm on your side
Make sure you never
talk to anyone about me
They're dangerous people
Who knows what they'll do to you?
You couldn't even imagine it
I am here
I'll take care of you
You want to return home, don't you?
You want to go home?
Back to your parents?
To your family?
You want to go home?
I'll take you back
You're back?
I gave her some water
We'll feed her later
There's Aadoo
- We're over there
- Sit down
Hey, Aadoo
Hurry UP!
Check the corner
All clear
What is it?
- She wants to run
- So?
Run!
Well?
Run
Where are You? Where am I?
O Lord, show compassion on me
Countless sorrows surround me
I believe that You
will restore my world
Heed the one who has no one
Where are You? Where am I?
How fearsome is the path before me
Why have You turned away from me?
Where am I?
Darkness descends around me
No light to be seen
Body broken, soul defeated
The stars of good fortune have faded
Show a ray of hope
There's nothingness everywhere
Get back!
She ran away on her own accord.
She'll return in the same way
Move!
No tea for me?
I'm making paneer. Will you eat it?
We need SIM cards
Take Tonk with you
Send the stuff back with him
- We need other stuff too
- Don't worry
Can you hear me?
What is it?
Can I come out just
for a little while?
Why?
Closed spaces...
...make my head spin
I'm feeling ill
- Let her out
- I won't try and run
Just for awhile
This is such an odd place
Never seen a place like this
We spend all our time
in hotels on our holidays
No point traveling
May as well just check
into a Delhi hotel
Hotels are the same everywhere
Why am I talking so much?
It feels so unreal
Like I'm watching a movie
I've no control. Words
pour out without my knowing
Actually, I haven't said
a word for almost two days
Feels good sitting
out here. So thank you
I felt like throwing up inside
That's why I said...
Feels better out here.
It's the fresh air
I'm still talking!
I should be tense right now
I am tense
No more talking
- Is the tea ok?
- It's different
It's good. Sugar in
it? Or something else?
Hey! You made the tea
I added sugar, but
maybe some salt fell in
There's salt everywhere
On my face, too
I thought it was only me
Everyone's got salt on them
Look at my arm Salt here too
Why did you have to
run away like that?
I told you I'd make some arrangement
Now listen carefully
Has the salt gone?
No
You better trust me. How
will it work otherwise?
Here's my plan
Panicking won't help
I know what you must be
thinking, brother Mahabir
Maybe you misunderstand
the whole thing
That's possible, no?
I'll tell you what's going on
You've it got wrong. Listen
She's a consignment. Not a girl
lam not arguing...
End of story
And you! Can't you dress decently?
See you
Let's go
We're going now?
- Where to?
- No idea
Will Goru tell everyone?
Shut her mouth!
Tie her hands. In the truck!
What about the truck papers?
And the state border police?
We need the license
plate registration
Show these papers. They belong
to a junked old truck. Here
Well done, brother!
Now what's the plan?
- We talk to Tonk in Ajmer
- Shall I switch the phone on?
Throw that SIM card away
We'll call from a landline
Stop!
Look away!
Where the hell were you?
Where were you?
Have you lost your mind?
How dare you ask?
You can go and relieve yourself,
don't I have to go, too?
Think about it
Come
- What happened?
- Got through?
Tonk will call her
parents from her phone
He'll meet us in two days
I'll sit in front
I'll break your bones
if you talk nonsense
Ok
Break my bones. Satisfy yourself
But I will sit in front
No problem
I'll sit next to her
She'll be sandwiched between us. OK?
I was very rude
I'm never so rude to anyone
I'm usually so well behaved
I have good manners
And with you...
- I felt like throwing up
- Shut up!
Am I saying sorry?
Are we here to show
off our good manners?
Show them off in your father's house
Hurry UP!
Hi, Veera
How are you?
How am I?
I'll think about it and let you know
Let me tell you an old tale
Bless my words as I tell it
My love for Heer dethroned me
Destiny turned me into a fakir
The Lord can destroy
kings and princes
And create wise men and saints
Up!
What happened, sir?
What's inside?
Nothing, sir
Nothing?
Driving an empty truck?
Just some household goods
Or stolen goods from Rajasthan?
I swear on my mother, sir
Get out!
Open the back
- May I talk, sir?
- What is it?
- We're in a hurry
- So?
Can we work this out?
Bribing the police?
You little scumbag
Do you have the means?
Open up! Move
Open it!
Open up. Right now!
Want a caning?
Quick!
The other one
Step aside!
You have a dishonest face
So you confused us. Get going!
You offended?
Should I confiscate it?
No, sir
Let them go
What happened?
Were you hiding?
Did you hide?
Yeah
Why?
This was your chance
Why did you hide?
Don't know
Don't know means?
Don't know means don't know
Maybe I've lost my mind
I could've escaped so easily
What's wrong with me?
Eat quickly if you want to eat
We're not stopping for long
I was nine years old
At home...
He used to bring
imported chocolates for me
My uncle
He made me sit on his lap
And loved me
And then alone...
In the bathroom
He would make me
sit on his lap again
And love me
I used to scream
But he'd cover my mouth
Like this
Cover my mouth
So my screams could not come out
It hurt so much
"It's all over...
"We're done...
"My doll...
"You are the best girl
in the whole world...
"The most beautiful"
He came home again
Again and again he came
Inside I was screaming my lungs out
"Don't tell anyone. Ok?"
One day I told Mummy
Explained to her
Mummy said...
"Don't tell anyone
"Ok?"
I didn't tell anyone
Then one day it all stopped
But he still visited
With chocolates for me
He comes to the house even now
I sit on his lap
He loves me
I laugh
"My doll...
"The most beautiful of all"
The beasts
Manners. Culture
Greet them
Touch their feet in respect
They're all around you
You have to survive among them
Laugh with them
Befriend them
Love them
The place you've got me from...
I don't want to go back there
The place we're going,
don't want to get there
But this road...
It's very good
I want this road never to end
The case was filed at
Dera Mandi police station
All the details are here
This cannot go public
The special cell
is handling the case
Information will be
shared with caution
His name is Mahabir
Bhaati. He's on the run
They're not professional
kidnappers, just petty criminals
Land grabbing, armed robbery, etc
Call from the girl's phone.
Then remove the battery
A call from Veera's phone
First let's find out if
it's worth trusting you
I'll call later
The call's from Noida. Near Delhi
I came of my own accord to tell you
Why would I lie now?
I've no clue where
the swine has taken her
I've come from so far
to tell you everything
Hiding is out of question
Just ask!
They left this place a week ago
They could be anywhere
I'll tell you when to
hand over the ransom money
Just relax. And wait
He called from Calcutta
God knows where she is
What they're doing to her
A bite of sweet paan
A cotton Lahori suit
In high spirits, the firefly soars
The Lord is your
gardener, 0 green forest
Never mind the cuss words,
He watches your every step
Ignore what the world thinks
Take the name of God.
Take the name of Ali
She has taken the path to Him
Firefly, free spirit, firecracker
Flying about intoxicated
Throwing caution to the
wind, I am in Your hands
God's chosen one
God will take away the
suffering He inflicts
Take His name and dance
Growing wild like the peepal tree
No one plants her.
No one can cage her
On this endless journey,
like rainwater falling
Soiled if she touches the ground
Ali is Your name
Throwing caution to the
wind, I am in Your hands
Wow!
Unique places in this country
Tell me
Why are the rich fascinated
by dirty run-down old ruins?
Step to the side
Hold this
Hold it straight. We
need to see the date
- What language is it?
- Bengali
So they think we're
in Bengal. Smart!
You've been abducted. Look upset
Who'd pay ransom for you?
Stop laughing
Be serious
How can I be serious,
looking at you, Aadoo?
I'll turn around
Higher
This place is good
The market is nearby
Better buy her clothes
She'll stand out like this
Everything will be ok
But I'd like to know...
If anything goes wrong,
the ransom, the calls
By the way, are we still...
Sticking to our plan?
Why?
Just asking
We're selling the girl to a brothel
Don't get fond of her
Nothing like that
ls she the only respectable one?
What about the poor?
Women are taken away at night
For some big shot
A woman is required tonight
And who takes her to him?
Her own husband
Her man
He sits outside while his wife
is inside with the big shot
Then the door opens
He brings his wife back home
And takes out all his
frustrations on the woman
Because the rich can have
us when they feel like
To hell with them
Drop it
He's not in the mood
I'll fix his mood
Are you mad?
Never do that
Got it
What is it?
You bought me clothes
Aadoo told me
Stop acting. I look very nice
What is this song?
What is it?
I want to hear the song
That's it
Go now
Mahabir Bhaati
- Where did you hear it?
- What's it to you?
Now I have to know
What song was that?
It's not a song
Then?
So where did you hear it?
My mother sang it
She sang for you?
Tell me
Yes, she sang it for me
When she went to
work, I went with her
I'd cry so she'd sing. Ok?
You would cry?
Does your mother live with you?
Enough. Go inside!
Stand up!
You see, I don't feel like going
Too smart!
Right!
I'm not scared anymore
Don't get offended, but...
I find you really cute now
So what made you cry?
Who troubled the little one?
I won't ask again
Sleep now
Do not cry
Look down!
Where's your mind?
You burnt the food
My adored son, sleep now
Your dreams will carry you
to a field of sweet delights
The parrot on the
tree tells you to smile
The swan wants to befriend you
My adored son
The night is dark as coal
Your eyes fill with sleep
With a blanket of stars covering you
Sleep a sweet sleep
If you toss and turn
The mynah bird will steal you away
A star, a little star
A falling star
Asks after you
Why don't you sleep? Why do you cry?
Why did you get so lost?
What upset you? Who upset you?
What did you leave behind
in the land you came from?
Your mother...
What do you call her?
Amma
So...
ls she well?
I mean
ls she all right?
You have to promise me, Mahabir
Once we're done with all this
You'll see her
Where is she?
In the village
So you'll go to the
village and see her
Tell me what is in your heart
Share your thoughts with me
Sleep now, my adored son
- It's full English, right?
- Total English, sir
This one
Come
Take your stuff
Chandigarh bus station?
I'm proud of you
You leaving?
Take care of yourself
We'll meet again
Look there
A police station. Go inside
and talk to the man in charge
Tell him your name and your father's
name. Say you're the kidnapped girl
You know I won't go
Take your phone.
Call your home first
Can't you hear me? I won't go
You won't go? So what
will you do with me?
Marry me?
Raise my kids?
What will you do?
What's come over you?
Why make a scene?
What will you do with me?
Well?
You know who I am
That's just it
I know who you really are
I killed three people
I have
With these very hands
My life is over.
It'll never get fixed
Never
I will only die. You should go back
I Pray for you
How did it all happen?
I'm telling you to go
It'll be a disaster. Go away!
What's your story?
- How did this happen?
- Shut up!
Go to the police station
I won't go. What will you do?
Let go!
Are you that strong? I won't go
Don't drive me crazy
Kill me too
Stop, Mahabir
Don't be childish
What's wrong?
One minute. I have to make a call
Where do I catch the
bus to Chandigarh?
- Reckong Peo bus stand?
- Get in
Get this straight
Whatever happens, you
don't decide alone. Got it?
Move away. Stand there
I was bound to come this way
My path is somewhere here
I stand at the crossroad
The journey opens its arms to me
Where am I?
Fearsome paths, open roads
Shaky plans, strong bonds
Where am I?
A 20-minute stop. Be quick!
There's no plan about raising kids
Or marrying
There's no plan
All I want is a little more
A little longer with you
Never felt like this before
The way I feel with you
I can do anything
Anything I feel like
And you'll take care of it
I don't even have to think
I've never felt like this
But I'm being very selfish
You'll be in trouble
They thought we were in Calcutta
Now they'll know we're here
Nothing can save us now?
All ruined
What now?
We sit on top
On the roof
Coming?
- Let's decide the next move
- You talk too much
Wrapped in clouds of white wool
I am like the winter breeze
Not caring what's left behind
Not seeing what lies ahead
I ask myself
Where am I?
Finding myself amidst lost desires
Firm desires, shaky pursuits
In all of this...
...where am I?
What are you staring at?
You like the mountains or the sea?
I've never seen the sea
I like the mountains more, too
Like that one
It is calling out to me
Wish we could go there
Then come
We'll go there?
Got other plans?
Let's go
For one second
Are you done? Give it back
Enough. Pass it here
It has power, boss
I'll give you a tight slap
It's not a toy. Give it to me
Tell me something
One bullet and one man is finished?
Two are finished
The one who gets shot
And the one who shoots
It's a bad thing
So why don't you throw it away?
Why keep it?
What the hell do you know?
I can see
We won't fight
No fighting
Don't talk about such things
Again?
Let's go
Let's race
I wanted a home on
a mountain like this
Always wanted one
My home
My dream
Pick any mountain you like
They're all ours
Really?
Yes, they belong to us
They'll be here
whenever you come back
- I'm choosing one
- Sure, go ahead
Keep this
This is my dream home
Exactly how I want it
We're saved so much work
It's ok?
Be comfortable. The
owners won't be back soon
Hungry?
Ten minutes. I'll make something
Go freshen up and just relax
Leave it. I'll do it
This is my home Now out!
Who's denying it?
Let me clean up
Come!
- What is it?
- One minute
This can never be mine
I've come so far away
20 years
Everything will be all right
Amma
Everything is over
I was once a mother's adored son
Mahabir, where's your gun?
- I threw it away
- Veera Tripathi?
Stay away!
Back off!
Get back!
It's all ok
What the hell did you
shoot? Bastard! Why shoot?
What was he doing?
Move back
I'll kill everyone
Veera, there's no time
He'll die. He needs a hospital
Nothing will happen to him
We have to take him immediately
Let's go
Listen to me. I'll
take you to your village
To Amma
I said everything
will be ok. Didn't I?
Nothing has changed
lam telling you.
See for yourself
I know what you're thinking
But you know nothing
The important thing
is we save Mahabir
Save Mahabir
He kidnapped me
But it's not what it
seems. Quite the opposite
What's happened, child?
Nothing's happened
I am fine
Who is this man?
- Let go
- Easy!
What's that for? An injection?
Papa, listen to me. Please
You don't understand
Wait. One second
There's something I must tell you
Stop
Why don't you understand?
What have you done? You don't get it
He died on the spot. Around 9.30
Before we could get
him on the stretcher
Can we take Veera back to Delhi?
- Where's the body?
- In the mortuary
- The post-mortem?
- Done, sir
Mahabir Bhaati?
I'll prepare the injection
Vinay's mom wants to see you
Be nice
Be pleasant
Like everything was normal
What do you think, Veera?
In which city should
we have the wedding?
Convenient for everyone
Every winter they
say: "It's so cold"
Every summer: "Oh
my God. It's too hot"
Why is it such a surprise?
Oh! What is it?
Why are you coming down?
Do join us
And you?
We're fine
Just worried about you.
Hope you'll get better soon
She looks much better
I found my home on a mountain
I cooked food
I cleaned my house
Then the bullet was fired
Vinay loves the mountains, right?
That Austrian resort?
You know Veera's favorite
I always said that...
I would run away
I don't want to live in the city
Doesn't everyone say that?
But who runs away?
I wouldn't have either
If Mahabir hadn't kidnapped
me and taken me away
But now...
I'm gone
I cannot come back
I think you should rest
It's so strange
I was kidnapped
But I was free there
I'm in prison here
Come, Veera
ls this my home?
No chocolates today, Uncle Shukla?
I'll order some now
Where?
Where will you give them to me?
Here? Or in the bathroom?
Enough of this
Yes, Mummy? Something
you want to say?
I don't know what
she's talking about
Can't remember?
Let me remind you
"My princess...
"You're most beautiful
girl in the world. My doll"
Now remember?
With your hands...
...how you'd cover my mouth
So my screams could not be heard
All my screams
My cries of pain
To keep my screams silent
You forced my mouth shut. Hush
In the bathroom...
Again and again
The running tap
Where were you, nurse?
She's really gone crazy
They are right
I was screaming. I was 9
That hand was over my mouth
My cries were silenced. No one heard
It happens
These things happen all the time
So you know what?
I'm not ok with it
This world...
...where this happens
Where you can't tell
a lie from the truth
Everything is mixed up
There's so much confusion
Be careful when you go out
Strangers are bad
A girl should always be careful
Why didn't you ever say...
...l should be careful
inside the house too?
That I should also
protect myself from you
Why didn't you ever tell me?
I was so exposed here
Inside my own home
So I don't want to be sensible
I am foolish. I'm bad
But I am not one of you
I will not come back
Admire the diamond...
...that endures the
blows of a hammer
The deceitful cannot
hide their flaws
Do not display your diamonds
at a vegetable market
Keep them close to your
heart and go your way
If the sun shines on a rainy day
Shadows fall and rise
I make a wish and
you appear before me
Play with me
Distances vanish
You are with me. Day and night
The shadows tell me
0 my companion
You are with me at every step
We are one
O companion of mine