How many stars
spa_le in the sky?
Ever tried countinQ them?
lt would take 6,OOO years to
count those in our Qalaxy alone
How many such galaxies exist?
Scientists reckon
mo billion more
lsn't it possible that amongst
these billions oF celestial bodies
a planet with people
like us exists?
As we explore space
IookinQ For them,
couldn't they be cominQ here,
IookinQ For us?
Hindi pop sonQ
What the thief stole was the
gadget to r_all his spaceship
Without this remote
he could not return home
He neither knew our language,
nor had a friend here
Alone, anguished,
his only thought was...
.. how will l return home?
On the pathway of Time
LiFe is but a brieF name
In its Iuminous mist
We wish, we dream, we exist
But on a beautiFul bend
A stranger may we rmet
LiFe aner liFe
Whose memoy may persist
Extra ticket.
Anyone extra ticket?
- Yes sir...
- l'll take it!
Sory, l raised my hand first
But l called out first
l'm a big fan of
Mr Bachchan, the poet
l'm a bigger fan of his son,
the actor
From age ten, l know all his poems.
Fully memorized
From age five, l know his son's
dialogues - without memorizing
Hello, who wants it?
Give me.
Poety's not his cup of tea
EUR10O
EUR100 for a EUR40 ticket?
Black market of poety!
Queued up
six long hours for this
Time is money
- Go for the dialogues.
- All yours. Ladies first
Just a sec!
Why not split the ticket?
1st half you enjoy the poety.
2nd half l'll savor the acting
That's a damn good idea!
10, 20, 30, 4O
50 more
- 96
EUR96. How about a discount?
We're from the same county
Hail India, bro!
Long live motherland!
EUR1 OO
Extra ticket.
Anyone extra ticket?
Sir!
Can l borrow EUR4?
Please!
Keep my watch till l repay
Please, Sir,
it's the last ticket
Show is sold out, child.
No tickets left
There is one left
with that black marketer
Scoundrel!
Giving India a bad name
So true!
Wait here.
l'll get you that ticket
OK, Sir
Thank you
Yes!
- Sir!
- Do l know you?
Where's my ticket?
Ticket?
Yours for EUR 1 OO
You bloody cheat!
Decaying dacoit!
Senile snake! Capitalist!
Mind your language!
Mind your coat first!
- Now enjoy the show!
- Security!
- Wrinkled wreck!
Let's get outta here
l'll get you for this!
Don't chase me...
catch him!
Oldies these days!
It's a spoilt generation!
Forget it
How can l?
That bandit basks in poety
and here l am
Drop it
Why pine For the pa_y
that shuns us?
Follow the moment
that beckons us
l too dabble in poety
lt's nice. Go on
No. If l go on,
you'll propose to me
- You crazy?
- l mean it!
Your favorite poet,
senior Mr Bachchan
met a lady one morning,
wooed her with verse
By dusk they were married.
So l've read
Really?
And boy!
Look what they produced -
Amitabh Bachchan -
the great actor
Jaggu
Jaggu?
My name
Papa named me Jagat Janani:
world's mother
l got mocked at school
so l shortened it - Jaggu
- From Mumbai?
- No. Delhi
l'm studying N production
And you?
Sa_araz. l study architecture
and work part time
at the Pakistan Embassy
Pakistan Embassy? Why?
Well, l'm from Pakistan
Unlikely the Indian Embassy
will employ me!
What's wrong?
Nothing
My being from Pakistan
perturbs you?
Alright then
Goodbye
Ask not my name,
nor my county
From bondaQe oF
borders break Free
A few steps
on this brieFjourney
Come,
just walk with me
Ask not my name,
nor my county
From bondaQe oF
borders break Free
A few steps
on this brieFjourney
Come,
just walk with me
Past the realms of
word and speech
Hand in hand,
nowhere to reach
A few steps
on this brieFjourney
Come,
just walk with me
Past the realms of
word and speech
Hand in hand,
nowhere to reach
A few steps
on this brieFjourney
Come,
just walk with me
lf the sun scorches
the pathway
A carpet oF shade
will l lay
lF da_ness
fills you with dismay
l'll conjure up
a moon in the sky
lf dejection fills up
your day
With laughter
l'll shoo it away
Laughing, frolicking,
humming a song
Together we shall
walk along
With you,
my fellow traveler
Nothing in this world l fear
Why a few steps,
a whole lifelong
With you l'll walk along
Past the realms of
word and speech
Hand in hand,
nowhere to reach
A few steps
on this brieFjourney
Come,
just walk with me
- Thank you
Mom!
Papa!
She's fallen in love!
Fallen in love?
He's so cute!
More photos please!
What's his job?
What's his family like?
Calm down Mom.
l'll tell you
First, the name
Sa_araz
Muslim?
Yes. Studies architecture.
Family is in Pakistan
Pakistan!
Which Pakistan?
There's just
one Pakistan, Mom
You'll wear burkhas?
Read the Quran?
Have you gone mad?
Don't you disconnect.
Stay put
Start the car
All's doomed, Your Holiness.
Help!
l knew exactly
where Papa was headed
Since childhood one Face had
surrounded us: His Holiness
Bye Mom
from bags to bathr_m walls,
he was omnipresent
Even For a root canal
he would set the auspicious time
He had Qined Papa a God box
with a deity for evey task
Goddess of Wealth
For the stock ma_et
God oF Health For wo_outs
Web-based worship and
sacred sweets by courier
were his innovations
Hail, Your Holiness
Touch his feet Jaggu
Why this fatal infatuation?
Pick up a pen and write
God
Enlighten me
Yes...
Your wish is our command
Write down the prophecy
This Pakistani boy,
Sa_araz,
will betray you
l know he won't
Histoy stands witness:
these people scheme and betray
He will pursue
carnal pleasures
But will never mary you.
He'll vanish
Come home now! One more
night there, and you're dead to us
Mr Sahni
l'll talk to h'er
Child, hit the delete button
Banish him
from your system
Hello!
What happened?
Do you love me?
Of course l do. Why?
- Will you mary me?
- What's the matter?
Yes or no, Sa_araz?
- Yes, but...
- Tomorrow
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow we get married
His prophecy is wrong.
l'll prove it
Mr James Herrick and
Miss Oprah Brown, you're next
- James isn't here, yet.
- Oh, talk to the registrar
Could you just
hold this please?
- Yes of course.
- Thank you
Hello...
This is for you
- For me?
- Yeah
Thank you
lt was from Samaraz
He said: marriage isn't just
bemeen individuals, but Families
Our Faiths, countries,
cultures are diFferent
We can never be happy
iF our Families are unhappy
Don't ty to contact me
l'm sory
Where to go young lady?
New Delhi
l came back to my city, but
my parents refused to see me
l joined a news channel
as a repo_er
Today's stoy:
a depressed dog
That's our breaking news!
Some days we had news,
some days we fabricated it
Missing: God
lf found, contact Tipsy
There's a stoy in this man.
l'll see you at office
Don't be late!
Excuse me?
Why are you
handing these out?
l have a case
pending with Him
He neither solves it,
nor meets me
My life is kaput
He's gone into hiding
Have you seen Him around?
No
Hail Goddess,
Hail Holy Mother
By the way,
what's with the helmet?
Got the idea from taxi-tops
Yellow yells out from miles
Taxis are spotted
easily in traffic
- So?
- So God can spot me easy!
How else will he spot me
in this crowd?
A bit to your left - pe_ect!
Ok, background?
Cue Jaggu
They say
animals are not suicidal
Here's Nikku.
Mr Sweetie Singh's dog
Nikku has attempted
suicide thrice
Jumping off a roof, licking sleeping
pills, hopping onto a gas burner
What's wrong with Nikku?
ls Nikku prey to a
mental problem?
ls Nikku...
What's wrong Jaggu?
What is this shit, Mitu?
Our chat with famed industrialist
Mr Ratan continues
right after this break
Going well, Ratan?
Some coffee?
Get him some coffee
- Chery...
- Oh no!
What's your guess? This dog has
depression, anxiety disorder,
schizophrenia, or ADHD?
Whatever,
why would l care?
Exactly
Why would anyone care?
Then why do we air such bull?
What would you rather air?
Hold him please
See this?
l met a guy distributing
these pamphlets
- He is searching for God.
- Found Him?
No... but
Searching for God - that's religion.
Finding God - that's news
lf he finds God, get him.
l'll put him on air
You know the Company policy
No news on religion,
no news on God. Finished
Man, you've changed!
Where's the fighter,
Chery Bajwa?
You wanna see the fighter?
Take a good look
There are three marks here
These aren't birthmarks
l ran a show against His Holiness,
your Dad's Guru
His devotees shoved a trident
right here in my bum
Anchor cominQ to you
in 10 seconds
That day l swore -
if you want to live in this county
don't mess with religion.
That's it
- l've got a show to run now.
- 5... 4...
3...
2...
1 ...
Welcome back from the break
We were chatting with
famed industrialist Mr Ratan...
The boss killed my stoy
But it came back to liFe
mo weeks later
[ DONmlON BOX ]
Stop! Thief!
He's stealing
from the donation box!
Don't let him go!
Lifting from the
donation box, you fool?
Yes
He's no thief!
While donating
my wallet fell in the box
He was getting it out for me
Trust me
Check for yourself.
It has Rs 5,OOO in it
- That's mine!
- It was
Once in the box,
it's donated
Now, it's God's.
Let them go
Dude, what the hell
were you up to?
Claiming my refund
God took His fee
but didn't deliver
Hang on...
l saw you fish out some money,
then put some back in
l took back what l'd paid
at this branch. Returned the rest
You used to wear
beads and amulets?
Rejected. Gone for good
Why the stickers then?
Self-defense!
God pics on walls - prevent peeing
on face - prevent punches
Mitu, where are you?
Pick me up.
l've no money to get home
l'll fill you in later
l'm at Mudrika,
outside the temple
Hury.
Thanks, bye
Here you go
- For what?
- For the ride home
When someone can't
get home, l feel sad
- Wait.
- That's all l had
l can't accept this
- Why?
- Won't you need it to get home?
Money can't get me home
Why? Where do you live?
ln the step-well ruins
But in this rainy season,
l check into a lock-up
Lock-up!
As in police lock-up?
There are 122 in the city.
l yo-yo between them
And they let you check in,
like a hotel?
Come.
l'll give you a demo
[ Sign: DO NOT URINATE HERE ]
Just watch!
Hey, copper -
Iook here proper!
l'll show you proper!
Jaggu!
We have to
follow that van
- Who are we chasing?
- A stoy
Gimme your wallet.
l need cash
Hury!
Thanks. Bye
Excuse me?
Yes?
l want to go
inside the lock-up
Why?
To meet that guy
You think this is the
Iocal coffee joint, huh?
Saunter in and chillax
with your buddies?
This is a lock-up, get it?
Only offenders get in
Bribing is an offence!
That's why l'm committing it!
l can lock you in
Please do... ASAP!
- Thank you, Mr Pandey.
- One hour, that's it
Hi
l want your stoy.
Will you share it?
Why?
l'm a N reporter.
It's my job
- Go on, ask.
- Awesome!
Your name?
Don't have a name
They call me Tipsy here.
Beats me why
And what do you do?
l'm an astronaut
Astronaut!
Those who shoot off
to the moon?
Been there once.
It's kaput
Sure!
So what's your
favorite planet?
- My own.
- l meant besides Earth?
Earth is mega-kaput
l meant my own planet
lt'll show up there at night
We went bananas,
when we found another planet
with people like us
l was sent here
on a research mission
Boy, what a welcome l got!
My remote got robbed
Without it,
l can't signal my people
and without a signal
they won't come for me
They'll think
it's a perilous planet
That l'm dead as a dodo
Hello!
- Listen...
- What?
Let me out.
l want to go home
Your Highness, convicts
don't decide that. Cops do
l'm not a thief
So say all the thieves
Where's officer Pandey?
Out on his rounds
Officer Pandey!
Shut up, or you get
a knuckle sandwich
You think
l'm talking baloney?
Obviously!
ls Hindi the official language
of your planet?
On our planet...
.. there's no language!
We read minds.
There's no confusion
Here, you utter something
and mean something else
A two-letter word can have
four different meanings
When you nod and say ''oh'',
it means ''Oh, that's cool''
When your eyes pop out,
''oh!'' means bad news
''Your mother-in-law
is moving in.'' ''Oh!''
When angy, you thunder
''Oh! You'll pay
for that blunder!''
And when your thought is deep,
your ''oh'' is long!
''Ohhhhhhh! l see!''
As you hear the words,
you gotta watch the expression
to get the real meaning
lt's torture!
Took full 6 hours to learn Hindi
A whole language in 6 hours?
No one let me hold hands
Finally, a nice lady
Ient her hand
l held it and transferred
her language into my system
Man, there's no limit
to your whoppers!
ls your hand a USB cable,
that transfers files
between computers?
And your clothes? Are faded jeans
the rage on your planet too?
Noooo!
On our planet...
.. no one wears clothes.
There we go bare
Here, at first l thought
your skins were
different from ours
Some had spa_ly hides,
some jet black
Some hides were colo_ul,
some white
Some hides sticky-tight,
some baggy
Then one day
l Found a car
A dancinQ car
That day l reali_ed
our skins were the same
but yours are covered
with a thing called fashion
Radio Commercial
Now l could minQle
Yet l was mocked
Look here -
half man, half woman!
Slowly l got it
There's man - fashion
and woman - Fashion
There was day fashion...
.. and night fashion
Spo_inQ Fashion...
.. and serving fashion
With the clothes,
l Found some photos
lt hit me - these photos
meant su_ival
You could
swap them for food
So l built a po Molio
of this old man's photos
What's this?
What are these for?
Why are you giving me
this junk?
Right! Now we're talking!
Here you go
l got it: this photo had value
on just one kind oF paper
On any other paper,
it was wo_hless
For cash and clothes,
dancing cars were widely available
They were my bank,
they were my tailor!
Once, l got
such magnetic attire
that no photos
were n_ed
Food was pulled to me
For you, Sir
Now, to find my remote, l had to
Iearn this planet's language
Without it,
evey task was a trial
Like telling this gentleman
there was a defect
in his Fashion
l felt l had spoilt his fashion
So l put it back
where it was
[Radio Announcement]
Found him on the road
Some scumbag
hit him and bolted
Seems pretty okay,
but isn't responding
Has his eardrum
called it a day?
Are you deaf?
Can hear alright,
but isn't talking
Seems in a state of shock
Memoy loss, l'm afraid
Remember the scumbag
who hit you?
Remember the license plate?
Remember anything at all?
Come my friend.
Come with me
Be my guest till you
get your memoy back
Keep slamming your head
One knock took your memoy away,
another might bring it back
Seen it in the movies
To figure what he was
yappinQ about,
l had to hold his hand
and transfer his language
Hey!
With memoy loss your gender
sense went for a toss?
Wait a moment...
See this - my license
Sex: MALE
Man...
rogue, rascal, scumbag
To return home
l had to hold someone's hand
Here comes my _any guest
Can't tell guy from gal
Happily hits on all
Here comes my _any guest
Can't tell guy from gal
Happily hits on all
Your Frantic antics iF not stilled,
will surely get me killed!
Don't be a scourQe
Do cueb your urQe
Here comes the lusty lad
My guest with this cra_y fad
Tourist in tacky Qear
are you From near or Far
From Mumbai, Madrid
or MadaQascar
Tourist in tacky Qear
are you From near or Far
From Mumbai, Madrid
or MadaQascar
What was your name at school
Was it nerdy or was it cool?
What's the _ip code
OF your abode
Did you aliQht From a cloud
Or sprout From underQround
Your Frantic antics iF not stilled,
will surely get me killed!
Don't be a scourQe
Do cueb your urQe
Here comes the lusty lad
My guest with this cra_y fad
This memoy loss is a blessing
feuds forgotten
Ienders left guessing
Lovable lad
lnnocent cad
Don't be a scourQe
Do cueb your urQe
Here comes the lusty lad
My guest with this cra_y fad
Here comes the lusty lad!
Here comes the lusty lad
My guest with this cra_y fad
l feel your pain, bro
But don't go grabbing hands
You may end up in bed,
but most likely a hospital bed
Don't give up,
l know place for you
Hand, foot -
hold whatever
No one will bash you here
Come
What a neiQhbomood!
Virtuous, welcoming women
All reachinQ For my hand,
inviting me home
Here l met a serene and
Qentle woman, Pepper
Pepper, take him
to the honeymoon suite
Pepper sat patiently all night
For Full 6 hours,
l transferr_ her language files
ABC - XYZ,
l drew in eveything
First time?... Kaput before you kicked off?
Y...y... yes!
Where are you from?
Far, far away
From an unheard of village
But you speak my lingo!
Because l learnt it from you,
Sister
Sister! You think
this is a convent? Out!
Bro!
Bro, wake up!
You're talking!
Bro, l need your help
Pepper cleared up your throat!
Bro, come with me quick
Memoy and making out
have a direct connection!
Update the docs:
get laid, get well!
lt's urgent, bro!
Okay, let's go
Stop... stop!
Stop, bro!
The jerk robbed me
right here
l need my chain, bro.
l must get it back
- Precious?
- It's priceless!
The thief must be a local
But he'll sell
the loot in Delhi
lf he sold pricey stuff here,
he'd get caught
Then l must go
Where?
Delhi
- Officer!
- Yeah?
- My remote control is stolen.
- Are you tipsy?
Expect the police force
to track your N remote?
- It's not a N remote!
- Then?
Can't tell you.
But it's like a chain
Really precious
- Where was it stolen?
- In Mandawa
And you're searching
in Delhi, you idiot?
The thief came to Delhi
- So?
- So where's the thief?
Blockhead!
It's a city of 15 million
Police are human,
not God
Only God can help you
Surrender to God,
you'll succeed
Only God knows
Ask God, not me!
Trust in God, my child
Who was this God chap?
All said only He could help
What l saw blew my mind
Earthlings had figur_ out
who had manuFactured them!
Their creator lived with them.
He had millions oF houses
Ea_hlinQs took their problems to Him,
which He solved For a small Fee
My planet had no such Facility
l could not believe it!
So decided to test it
One take-away God
Which one?
Rs 20, 100, 500?
Any difference?
In the Rs 20 and Rs 500 ones?
Just the size.
Othemise ditto
Rs 20 God is
equally efficient?
OK, gimme Rs15!
Nothing less
God, l am famished.
Get me some food please
l went bananas
God actually wo_ed!
Now l could Qo home
God, my remote is stolen
Please find it.
l want to go home
God's battey died.
Worked once, then kaput
What do you mean?
Stick a new battey in.
Where does it go?
- It needs no battey.
- Then why is it off?
- Manufacturing defect?
- l make no defective stuff
- You made this God?
- Of course! With my own hands
You made God,
or God made you?
He made us all -
l only make His statues
Why the statues?
To worship Him.
To voice our problems
ls there a transmitter inside?
How can He hear us?
God needs no transmitter.
He hears directly
Directly?
Then why the statue?
What's with him?
Want to bust my business?
What's your problem?
My remote is stolen, Sir
l'm requesting God.
But He doesn't reply
- Are you tipsy?
- Meaning?
You're overloading
this pint-sized God
His itty-bitty feet
can't chase the thief
Bother the big God
inside the temple
He'll run fast
Offer Him coconut and money -
He'll deliver
That'll be Rs 20O
Earthlings waited with fees
to Qet their wo_ done
Full 2 hours later
l got the appointment
God,
please get my remote back
- Where is it?
- Move!
Wait,
He didn't deliver my stuff
He didn't deliver!
See, l paid His fee
- Your work will be done.
- But when?
Can't say when,
but it will be done
- Move on.
- But when will l get it?
Don't block the line, scram!
lf l scram,
someone else may get it
Are you tipsy?
Lady, please!
Where will l get my stuff?
At the mental hospital!
What? Cash here,
delivey at mental hospital!
- Throw him out!
- OK, give me a receipt
Out!
Without a receipt
how do l claim my delivey?
Get out!
But my remote?
Leave!
l can't find my shoes
Someone's taken them.
Now you take your pick
Rotation is routine
at temples
He took the payment,
didn't deliver
What's his name?
- They call Him God
- Real name?
No idea
Where does he live?
ln that temple
- You handed him the cash?
- No. Put it in His box
- Said he'd do the job?
- He says nothing
ls he mute?
Perhaps... maybe
Oh...
Describe him
Ditto
But a bigger chap
Come near...
Are you tipsy?
Yes.
How do you all know?
Think l'm a jackass?
20 years a cop!
Who's tipsy who's not
l can tell in a snap
Frisk him
Let me have a look
Dr D'Mello...
Doc, why get so buzzed
you forget your faith?
Mistook temple for a church!
Wanna rouse a riot?
Go to church.
To your own God
Church?
Get out of here
My stuff!
My remote!
God was crucified for your sins.
Ungrateful man!
Crucified! When?
2,OOO years ago.
For your sins!
What did l do?
l just got here
- Are you tipsy?
- Yes!
God is watching you.
Behave
Where?
Where is God?
What's in the mug?
Wine
Wine!
Now l got it!
God was bored of
coconut water
Now He preferr_ wine.
But wine was expensive
So l had to muster money
l got some from the dancing car,
some from a gentleman
who held out a bowl
oF dole eveyday
You could withdraw
as per need
[Radio Announcement]
Sir, any God house
around here?
Right there
Preacher, let me drink
in God's abode
Or show me a place
where there is no God
Stop!
What's that?
Wine, for God
Where is He?
This lady looked vey sad
To know why,
l Qrabbed her hand
Hitting on a widow,
you lech!
Widow?
How do you know?
Don't you see
she's clad in white?
ls eveything fine?
Eveything is fine.
Just relax. Smile.
So sory
your husband's dead
- What?
- When?
How do l know?
You are clad in white
Brides wear white!
No, widows wear white
Widows wear black,
stupid!
Now don't
stress her out. Go!
All three lost your husbands?
l'm alive you moron!
Want a whack?
A_er many whacks,
l learnt
there wasn't one God.
There were many Gods
Each with His own
set of rules
Each God had noated
His own Company
They called it religion
Each Company had
its own agents
All Earthlings belonged to
some rgligion
and Followed the God
of that religion alone
What was my rgligion,
who was my God?
To find the remote
l had to know my God
What are you doing?
Where is the label?
What label?
The Religion label
How do you know which
Company he belongs to?
Where does God
Iabel them?
Security!
finding my rgligion
was tough
So l decided to
worship all Gods
One oF them would be
my God, who'd help me
lt's You who governs
The world l hear
Do listen to my plea
My home beckons me
God where are You
Tell me where are You
You Quide back to sanity
Those who've lost their way
l too am completely lost
Guide me too, l pray
God where are You
Tell me where are You
Shall l worship You
in temples
ln mosques
do my faith l show
Or to a Qurudwara
would You like me to Qo
Temples and churches,
l looked eveywhere
My hope now,
has turned to despair
Not a single ritual
Did l ever nout
Like millions around
l submit without a doubt
God where are You
Tell me where are You
You have many names
And many Faces too
l've walked each of the myriad
paths which lead to You
ln no shrine did l Find You
What else should l do
To find you give a clue
l blindly Follow and
With reverence treasure
Your evey whim and Fancy
In more than ample measure
God where are you
Tell me where are you
God - l'm all confused
What's my fault?
Why can't my voice reach you?
Understand my plight
Give me some guidance
Please
Shall l talk to you
with hands clasped,
or on bent knees,
head to the ground?
Do l wake you
with temple bells?
Or call out on a loudspeaker?
The Geeta, the Quran,
the Bible - what do l read?
Your different managers
say different things
Some insist fast on Monday,
others urge on Tuesday
Some forbid food after sunset,
some after sunrise
Some say, worship the cow.
Others say slaughter her
Some send me barefoot to the temple,
some wearing shoes to the church
What is right,
what is wrong
l am clueless
l'm at breaking point
l want to go home
l'll do whatever you ask.
Just get me home
Please
Say something
At least one of you...
. . give me some answer
Please
Missing: God
Why the lock man?
l gotcha today
Open!
It's my enty!
Lord Shiva, slayer of sins
who fears none
Security!
Who are you?
Don't you recognize me?
l'm Tipsy!
Where the hell is security?
Do l pe_orm
for boozards in the toilet?
Unlock that door now!
My remote first!
- What remote?
- Of my spaceship
Space... ship?
Memoy loss?
For the zillionth time,
l'm not from here.
l'm from a far off planet
Scooch!
Gimme my remote,
and l go home. Got it?
Brother let me go.
l've little kids at home
l know!
You fathered two Gods
Both are centuries old.
They can be home alone
First my remote,
then your family reunion
Oh God, save me please...
There's a God
above you too?
Lord Shiva, help
Where?
Now presenting the dance of Shiva,
the fearless
Help!
Hail Lord Shiva
l was meditating on the
snom peaks of the Himalayas
when, suddenly - light!
Dazzling light!
lt came from a bead
Iying in the snow
l shut my eyes
and invoked God
Next moment,
l was connected
l said,
''God, enlighten me,''
What is this
miraculous object,
that is warm
even in this biting cold?
God said,
it's a divine bead
from Lord Shiva's necklace
Take it and enshrine it
in a grand temple
Sighting this bead
will heal all suffering
Hail Lord Shiva
Are you ready
for the sighting?
The divine bead from
Lord Shiva's necklace!
Hail Lord Shiva
Stop.
Let him through.
He's awed by the sight
Come.
- Hail Lord Shiva
Not there child.
Come here
Express your ecstasy
Hail Lord Shiva
God, where are you?
Please step out,
l want to thank you
He's right here
l met Him in the toilet
l asked for my property
and He bolted
l thought He vamoosed
But no!
He led me to my property
Hail Lord Shiva
This isn't Lord Shiva's bead
lt's my property,
misdelivered to you
Your bead must be
misdelivered too
Ask God, He is right here.
God, do step fomard, clarify
Anyway,
l'll take my property
That's mine!
Why're you stopping me?
Hail Lord Shiva
Since when have you felt
you're from another planet?
Listen. You need to see
a psychiatrist
Time up! Rs 500 can buy
only this much jail time
Here's my card
My number's on it. l'll get you
an appointment if you wish
Feel free to call. Okay?
Take care
Thank you officer Pandey
You don't believe my stoy?
Then go back to
the suicidal dog, Nikku
That's the stoy for you
l need to go back in
for 2 minutes
Quit these enty - exits
Another Rs 500,
he's all yours
When did l mention Nikku,
the suicidal dog?
You didn't
So how do you know?
When you held my hands,
l read your thoughts
You thought:
this stoy is dead
l got to live with the
Nikku stoy
Don't lie!
l must have mentioned it
l cannot lie.
Lies need language
On our planet
we hold hands, read minds
- Gimme your hand.
- No way
- Ty it...
- Help me, son
My wife's ill. Hospital wants
a deposit of Rs 10,OOO
l'm Rs 500 short.
If you can help...
l'll give you
Here
Give your address.
l'll courier a check
Courier can't reach my home.
Please keep it
Thank you
Sir...
Here's another Rs 100.
For the tip
Bless you
Confirmed.
You are no mind reader
You got conned.
There is no hospital around here
l know!
He's gifting his wife
a five star dinner
lt's her 75th birthday
She'd never been
to a fancy place
He's been saving from
his pension for months
She ordered ice-cream
and his budget went kaput
With a restroom excuse,
he ran out for some bucks
Another yarn!
On our planet, we don't lie
Anyway, it's up to you
- Here.
- Thank you Sir
One moment. Tip him
Why hold back -
it's your birthday!
Thank you
Address: Stepwell ruins
l told you.
On my planet, we don't lie
Hope you haven't told anyone...
.. that you're an alien?
No way!
They'd lock me in a lab,
and rip me up for research!
How come you told me?
Ever since
l set foot on this planet
eveyone has taken
money from me
You were the first to give it up
for me - dumping Rs 5,OOO in a box
l thought you are a good egg.
l could trust you
l'll get your remote back, Tipsy
How?
l haven't figured it out yet,
but you'll go back home
That's my promise
What are you goggling at?
You
Aliens don't drop by eveyday
Eveyone on your planet
has stick-out ears?
Yup, ditto
And they roam around naked?
Isn't it weird?
That crow is naked -
does he look weird?
lf he dons a tie,
he'd look weird
Tipsy, l was awake all night...
.. thinking how to get
your remote back
Hello
Connect to Balbir Singh.
Room No. 4
Wrong number
lsn't this Fortis Hospital?
Since yesterday you've been
dialing this wrong number
lmpossible!
l can't be wrong evey time!
So how do we get
the remote?
Connect to Balbir Singh.
Room No. 4
Sory, Sir.
You've called too late
Balbir died this morning
Huh! How can a
piles surgey be fatal?
Embarrassing,
but don't wory
Death Certificate
will say heart attack
so the family saves face
- Come for the body.
- On my way
Ok, bye
Why did you say that?
Doling out joy
When he finds his friend alive,
imagine his joy!
What!
l was sick of his calls.
So l played a prank
- A prank?
- Tipsy, l was just kidding!
l got it!
Someone is playing pranks
When His Holiness dials God,
cocking his head,
'God, enlighten me',
his calls are going
to a Wrong Number
Someone out there
plays pranks
The real God won't call
my remote a bead
Looks like the phone lines
to God have gone kaput
All calls to God are going
to a Wrong Number!
As in?
Think - would the real God
give such weird solutions?
Like - come rolling to me,
then l'll help you!
Aren't we God's children?
Would a father make his kids
roll for help?
Your Dad ever said - kiddo,
want a new dress? Start rolling!
Another prank - bathe me
with cow's milk! What bull!
And if these calls went to
the real God, what would He say?
He'd say - millions of my children
are starving on streets
Give them milk.
Don't give me a lactose shower
l'm sure someone's playing
pranks, like you just did
Tipsy thought His Holiness
was a victim of pranks
l didn't clear his conFusion
For a crazy idea was
forming in my head
An idea that would
get back Tipsy's remote
Who's this Tipsy?
That's a mystey
But the way he sees
this world is unique
- As in?
- If he saw you smoking,
he'd call the cops to say
you're attempting suicide
Why?
The pack says 'Smoking Kills'
yet you puff away
So what's the big idea?
Face-off
Between
Tipsy and His Holiness.
We'll take
the face-off to N
Ratings will go
through the roof!
l have three trident marks
on my right bum
You want three more on my
Ieft for balance?
Don't wory
Tipsy won't fight His Holiness
but gently explain, that...
.. his calls to God are going to
a Wrong Number
His Holiness will be stumped
Chery!
Tipsy's here.
Just meet him once
l bet his queries
will baffle you
Trust me. Please!
Excuse me,
you dropped this
Oh, thank you
That's not mine
Kamasutra condoms,
strawbery flavor
l hate strawberries, man.
Ask these guys
lt's not mine.
Buzzed bozo!
- Ma'am, yours?
- How dare you!
- Check your purse if it's missing.
- Shameless cad!
- Has to be yours.
- No, not mine
Tipsy, it's his
Ask him all you want
to know about it. Come on in
What's this?
lt's a condom
- What does it do?
- Controls the world's population
How?
lt has to be worn
while having sex
How does your wearing it
control the world's population?
Not just me...
millions wear it
They all borrow it from you?
No. Eveyone has it
- l've a question
- Go on Tipsy, shoot
lf money is dropped,
all run for it
lf a condom is dropped,
all run away from it. Why?
Sex is a vey private matter
Why?
You don't tell the whole town -
l'm having sex today
But, then at weddings,
with fireworks and music bands
why do they tell the whole town -
l'm having sex today?
What's the matter?
l have no answer for you
but l have a job for you
Thank you!
Let's beat it before
he changes his mind
Shield your holy bum,
Your Holiness
My trident is on its way
At this place His Holiness
connects his devotees to God
for solutions to their woes
Listen carefully to his calls
lf you think the calls are going
to a Wrong Number, alert him
- Will that get me my remote?
- Once he realises...
.. the bead stoy is a prank
he'll return your remote
Good plan. Let's go
To build a home for someone
is a holy deed
To build a home for God
is the holiest deed
So donate for the temple
And see
your woes flee
Son, voice your woe
Your Holiness,
my wife's been paralyzed
for six months
The doctors have given up.
What shall l...
God
Enlighten me
Yes...
What place?
What transport?
Your wish is our command
Have you heard of
the Rathong glacier?
No
lt's in the Himalayas.
Take a train to Silliguri
then a bus to Gangtok
then an eight day trek
You'll reach a grand temple
Pray there,
your problem will be solved
Wrong Number!
This is a Wrong Number!
- What?
- Wrong Number
Your Holiness, your phone line
to God has gone kaput
Your calls are going to
a Wrong Number
and a fake God is
playing pranks
What are you tying to say?
l'll explain.
Aren't we God's children?
Yes, so?
Say your kid's in a jam
and comes to you
Will you help promptly,
or will you say
kiddo, l've another house
2,OOO miles away
Come there, tell me
the same problem again
Then l'll solve it.
What bull!
lf the call went to real God, He'd
say: Son, tend to your ailing wife,
don't run after me
after death
you'll come to me anyway
give her your time now. Right?
l can prove it's a prank
Call this fake God
again and ask
What's the guarantee
she will get well
Sir, till you get it in writing,
don't leave her side
Just call
and clear all _oubt
lt's time for His Holiness'
holy silence
Praise be to God
Gloy be to God
This fake God is passing off
my property as a holy bead
He's playing a prank
He is no God.
He is a fraud
He is a FRAUD
God doesn't talk
to us mortals
He communicates
through His managers
- Tipsy has raised a big question.
- What?
ls God really talking
to the managers?
No
So where do the commands
for us come from?
- From a Wrong Number!
- So what should the public do?
Till phone lines are fixed,
don't depend on God's managers
Help each other
in difficult times
A great tip from Tipsy:
Don't rely on God's managers
Rely on each other
Hail Lord Shiva
Tipsy says don't make the temple,
the bead belongs to him
What's in your pocket?
- Do you smoke?
- Yes
- You consume alcohol?
- Occasionally
You smoke cigarettes,
consume alcohol
despite knowing
their fatal effects
Governments
permit these poisons,
factories manufacture them,
stores sell them
Nobody questions this
But in this sacred land of
Lord Ram and Krishna
if l wish to build a temple
why these questions?
Why not question the man
who is tying to stall this temple?
Who's this Tipsy?
What's his real name?
Why's he hiding it?
Is he a Muslim?
lf question you must,
go ask Tipsy
what is his religion?
Find out his religion,
Find out his faith
Centuries ago,
Mohammad of Ghazni
came and destroyed
our temples
Today another invader
wants to repeat histoy
But we won't allow...
Your God asks my religion.
Let's ask Him...
.. the religions of these people
- What nonsense?
- Call up your God!
Why bother God?
l'll tell you
This one is a Hindu.
He's a Christian...
.. Sikh, Jain and...
.. that one is of your religion
Enlighten him
Hello. l'm Sikh
Gr_tings.
l'm Muslim
l'm Jain
Hi
l'm Christian
Hello! l'm Hindu
Bamboozled!
l swapped their robes.
Get it?
Faith is connected
to fashion
Want a demo?
Check the math
Beard + moustache + turban = Sikh
Minus turban = Hindu
Minus moustache = Muslim!
This difference is
made by the fake God
lf real God wanted it,
He'd put a label on us
- Is there a label on your body?
- Mine?
Don't gape, strip and check!
Why be coy?
Strip eveyone, show His Holiness.
Is there any label?
Cut the coyness.
OK, l'll go first
See the bare facts
ls there a label?
Nothing! You see!
Check some more...
Remove this ruffian
Hey!
l'm proving a point
Start the chants!
Praise be to God
Gloy be to God
That's no divine bead
Jaggu!
Stop this farce!
Papa!
You were all of 40 days, when
His Holiness christened you
Remember, he who gives you
a name, can ruin it too
He named me
Jagat Janani
How can he ruin it further?
You!
Name your price
Papa!
Tying to scare His Holiness
to extort money
No, no
You'll burn in Hell!
Fear the wrath of God!
Thank you Papa!
Thank you
l'd solved only half the puzzle.
You pieced it together
Fear is the key
The prankster is
cashing in on fear. Get it?
Not exactly,
but can you explain to Papa?
You bet! l can prove it.
Follow me
l don't have time
for this nonsense
lf it turns out to be nonsense,
l'll call off the show
Exams are on at this college.
The students are scared stiff
Now, we'll establish our business -
The Fear Factoy
Machine installed
A little seed capital
Now the inauguration
Just watch!
Capital doubles in 15 minutes
Look there
The first customer!
Tea... piping hot tea
Check the investment
of the tea vendor
Kettle, tea, sugar, bike,
thermos
And here -
a rock and a red mark
Hot and piping tea...
There, you gotta
woo the clients
Here you shoo them away
Hey, scram.
Give others a chance
There you bow
before the customer
Here the customer
bows before you
lf he's in deep trouble,
he goes horizontal
The Wrong Number guy
trades in fear
He knows - those in dread
to the temple head
You too seem afraid!
Off with these...
Do not question religion
lt's a matter of faith!
lf God didn't want us
to raise questions
He wouldn't give us
the power to reason
Guardians of religion use violence
when they can't answer us
They scare us into silence.
But now we won't be silent
So far one Tipsy raised questions.
Now there'll be a thousand
Friends, pick up your phones
When you spot a Wrong Number,
shoot it and send it to us
We'll put it on N
Dump your fear,
ask questions
Holy Sir!
One question
lf you can conjure gold
from thin air
why don't you end
the nation's poverty?
Answer please
Holy Sir!
Since you're a walking gold mine,
why ask us for donations?
God is great!
This is a Wrong Number
- Jaggu... come with me
- Chery give me a moment
Come with me
The Wrong Number idea
is a national rage
- What!
- It's spread like wild fire
Guru says - to land a job,
feed a cow
ls this cow
an employment agent?
Or posts CVs on Monster.com?
Wrong Number
Watch this one!
He says, convert to
Christianity, or be damned
lf God wanted,
l'd be Christian by birth
Why convert now?
Wrong Number
These girls want to
go to school
A new dictat says:
kill them if they do
ls God so small
He'll deny children kno_ledge?
Wrong Number
What God has destined for you
will happen
He has a master plan
for the Universe
Accept it
Your disciples say:
to get a male child,
buy this book,
and chant the mantras
So buy a Rs 10 book
and bust
God's master plan!
Tipsy! Your show's a hit!
Messages are pouring in
Here's one more
What happened?
lt's Papa. He's ashamed
l'm his daughter
l was in tenth grade
when l wrote my first poem
For Papa
They say my Mom l resemble.
l say possible,
but l'm my Daddy's girl
l recited it
on the Annual Day
All parents clapped
but one whistled with joy
The applause ended,
the whistling continued
lt was Papa
He was so proud of me
And now this message.
Ashamed of you
There's a Wrong Number
in your Papa's head
The day he gets rid of it,
he'll whistle for you again
lt won't happen
Don't be sad. Come with me
On my planet when people are sad,
know what they do?
What?
Recharge the battey!
- What!
- Just copy me
What are we doing?
Shut your eyes!
How do l copy then?
Right.
Keep them open
To steal glances at you all day
To strain For evey word you say
To put evey chore aside
And Follow your evey stride
That's nothing but a
waste of time
Love is a waste oF time
Amorg is nothing morg
But my mind and heart insist
Once in this liFe at least
l must waste my time
Without reason or myme
l want to waste my time
l love this waste oF time
A zillion peeps into the mirror
A million times
l've styled my hair
Countless sets of
clothes l've tried
Emptied pe_ume
bottles with nair
Dressing up is all l did
Did nothing else worthwhile
Now l understand
That love is waste oF time
But my mind and heart insist
Once in this liFe at least
l must waste my time
Without reason or myme
l want to waste my time
l love this waste oF time
My world has
topsy-turvy turned
l know not how to tell you
l smile without rhyme
Or reaSOn
What's happening
l have no clue
The mind just wants to soar
And From roonops yell
Now l understand
Love is a waste oF time
But my mind and heart insist
Once in this liFe at least
l must waste my time
Without reason or myme
l want to waste my time
l love this waste oF time
The donation box is getting
more questions than cash
Your relics don't sell anymore
Millions of abuses on
Facebook and Twitter
- Just five?
- Those are in support
The abuses are in here
lt's time for action, Sir.
Avoiding the issue can be disastrous
Missing: God
Call Chery Bajwa
Tipsy has asked many questions.
l'll ask him just one
- Hey Jaggu
- What happened?
His Holiness wants to come
on the show. To debate with Tipsy
- Tipsy'll rip him!
- It'll be a mother of a show!
Get Tipsy ready.
Put the promos out
'The final Question'
Sunday 6:OO pm
Don't miss, 'The final Question'
My pal's become a star!
Hey look, he's a rock star
Rock star was
roaming butt naked
l made him a star.
The bloke's on N
and me - in this shanty town,
this crappy shack
guzzling booze with
a jackass like you
Star my foot!
Tipsy, some
Bhairon Singh for you
Bhairon!
Take that line
- Bro!
- You lusty lad
You're a rock star!
Bro, where are you?
ln Mandawa.
Coming to Delhi tomorrow
With a gift for you
l've nabbed the thief
who stole your stuff
He sold it for 40 grand
- Guess to whom.
- Whom?
His Holiness!
God said: it's a divine bead
From Lord Shiva's necklace. Take it...
.. and enshrine it in a grand temple.
Sighting this bead...
Hey,
what happened?
The thief who stole
my remote is caught
What! Really?
Bro said, the thief sold it to
His Holiness
Then His Holiness is finished!
We'll tell him -
return the remote,
or the thief tells all on N
So he didn't find my remote
in the Himalayas! He's lying
Wrong Numbers are not
floated by some fake God...
.. but by His Holiness
You knew this Jaggu?
Remember the day
you mentioned Wrong Number
All his calls are going
to a WronQ Number
l knew then you were on the
wrong track. But l kept mum
lf you'd called him a fraud,
people would have killed you
People crave for the unique
WronQ Number!
Your Wrong Number
concept was unique
Today the world supports you
Tipsy, my plan worked!
You're going home!
You'll fly away tomorrow,
my friend
Whoosh... gone
We'll never meet again
There will be such a void
l'll really miss you
Shall l stay back?
How can you?
Simple,
l have a job
l'll get some ID made
and settle here
l'll find someone to
'waste time' with me
l'll mary her
- Who'll mary you!
- Why not?
Your wife will go nuts
introducing you -
Meet my husband.
He's Tipsy!
That's not my name!
- Tipsyyy!
- l'll get a real name
Why don't you suggest one?
A name you love
A man's name must
match his personality
Right!
So how is my personality?
l'll explain
A poet once wrote...
lrony of mismatched names...
No poety, please!
l've something to say
Who says
'What's in a name?'
lf you don't get the right one,
what a pain
Mr Burns is in fact so cool
With violence alone
Mr Peace does rule
His name is Mr Fox
But has no bushy tail
''l love you Jaggu''
One whole ton is the
weight of Mr flower
At his mere sight,
the poor chair does cower
Vey nice... vey nice
Here's a bunch of cards
with different names
Pick the one you like
Danduram Thatte?
- Disaster!
- Next!
Tutari Singh?
Phooey!
Sa_araz
- Sa_araz...
- What happened?
Keep going,
find a good name
What's the matter?
Nothing
''l love you Jaggu''
Brother!
God is in His Heaven
We mo_als on Qround
Nowadays He doesn't have
Time to look around
God is in His Heaven
We mo_als on Qround
Whatever may happen here
He does not reprimand
Thousand evils, million wrongs
He does not take a stand
Plundering is all around
Bombs come to hound
A terrorist ou_it has claimed
responsibility for the blast
They say this was
a mock drill
Persecute our people,
and real war will Follow
We shall protect our God
Where are you
going, Tipsy?
On the show
You don't have to
l must.
More than ever
'The final Question'
Welcome to our special show
in which we meet Tipsy...
Wait a minute
Bring it
What is this?
God says: it's a divine bead
from His necklace
This man claims,
it's his property
God says: build a temple
And this man opposes it
Who do l listen to?
God, or this gentleman
who used to hand out these
blasphemous pamphlets?
First he claimed,
God is missing
Then said, God is a fraud
Next he'll say,
God is dead
What do you want, son?
A world without God?
Do you have any clue
how people suffer?
No food to eat
No place to live
No friend to talk to
People kill themselves.
Slit their wrists, jump off buildings
Why?
Because they have no hope
lf bowing before God,
smearing holy ash,
wearing amulets,
gives them hope to live,
then who are you
to snatch away that hope?
And if you snatch away their God,
how will you fill that void?
This man rants about
Wrong Numbers
Today he must tell us:
what is the Right Number?
You are right, Your Holiness
There was a time
l too had no food to eat
No place to live
l cried a lot
because l had no friend
l had only one hope then -
God
Each day l hoped:
tomorrow will be better
God will find a solution
l agree
belief in God gives hope,
the strength to face ordeals
But l have one question
Which God shall l believe in?
You say there is ONE God
l say no
There are mO Gods
One who created us
And the other
whom you created
We know nothing about
the God who made us
But the God YOU made up,
is just like you
Petty.
Takes bribes, makes false promises
Readily meets the rich,
keeps the poor waiting
Thrives on flattey.
Makes you live in fear
My Right Number is simple
J
The God who created us all
believe in Him
The God YOU created -
abolish him
Yes!
You'll abolish my God
and l'll keep quiet?
l know how to
protect my God
You will protect God?
You!
This is a puny planet
Billions of bigger planets
float in space
And you, sitting in a tiny corner of this
puny planet, have the nerve to say
you will protect Him,
who created the Universe?
He doesn't need your protection.
He can protect Himself
Today someone tried to
protect God and my friend died
This is all that's left -
his shoe
Stop protecting God
Or this planet will have
no humans, only shoes
A Muslim terrorist
blows up a train
and a Hindu guru endures
your sermon. That's nice
What's this Hindu, Muslim?
Show me the label
You created these differences.
Not God
This is the deadliest
Wrong Number of this planet
lt kills people,
separates them
Like your Wrong Number
separated Jaggu from Sa_araz
- What Wrong Number?
- That Sa_araz will betray
He did betray her
- What's going on?
- Hold it
You say my prediction
about Sa_araz was wrong?
Exactly!
Then prove it -
prove my prophecy wrong!
Failing that,
fall at my feet and admit
that you are a liar.
You tried to defame me
What if l prove it?
Tipsy... don't!
Then this is yours
l accept
Turn the cameras towards
Jagat Janani
l hope you will answer
my questions truthfully
ln Belgium you fell in love
with a Pakistani boy
True or false?
Please spare my personal life
On Friday, at 3:21 pm
l predicted this boy will betray you
The next day you went to the
Marriage Registrar's office
but he didn't show up
True or false?
Yes, he didn't come.
Please stop this
Now will you come to my feet
or do l walk my feet to you?
- Sa_araz did not betray.
- Please let it go!
No. Tell us
what happened that day
Please!
Just once,
for my sake
l was at the Marriage
Registrar's office and
a letter was brought to me
Did Sa_araz bring it?
No.
He sent it through a kid
- Was it signed?
- No
How do you know
Sa_araz sent it?
lt could have been
for some other girl
There was another girl.
With a cat, right?
She gave you the cat
to hold for a while
The kid who gave you the letter-
did he know you?
- No!
- Did you know him?
No
Then how would he know
the letter was for you?
Maybe he was told to give
the letter to the girl with the cat
You read the letter,
but didn't call Sa_araz
Did you?
Because this man planted
a Wrong Number - that Muslims betray
Sa_araz didn't betray you
What's going on?
You expect us to believe
these cat and bull stories?
One minute
We'll get to the truth right now.
Call Sa_araz
Hury up!
This number does not exist
Any other number?
Friend, college, something?
- C'mon Jaggu!
- Belgium University
- Hello.
- Hello!
l actually need to get in touch with
one of your grad students
Sa_araz Yousuf
Oh yeah.
He left for Pakistan last year
Has he left a number?
Sory, we are not authorized
to give out information
This is really important
E-mail us your request and
l can fomard it to Student Affairs
Have a nice day dear
His Pakistan number?
- Don't know.
- Think, Jaggu darling
l work at the
Pakistan Embassy
His job -
Pakistan Embassy, Belgium
Mitu, call the Pakistan Embassy,
Belgium
- Copy sir.
- Put it on the speakers
Gr_tings.
Pakistan Embassy
Hello
A student from Lahore
worked with you
- Sa_araz Yousuf.
- Is your name Jaggu?
Hello... is your name Jaggu?
How do you know?
She's called!
The girl from Delhi has called
Farah, it's Jaggu calling
Mr Sayyed, hury,
it's Jaggu's call from India
On the double eveyone!
Sa_araz Yousuf calls us
from Lahore, evey day at 9 am
And with impeccable politeness
asks just one question:
Was there a call for me
from India - from Jaggu?
We say ''No'',
and he disconnects
He's driven us crazy
Wait.
l'll connect you to him
Hello...
- Mr Sa_araz Yousuf?
- Yes, speaking
- Where are you?
- In Lahore. Why?
- Where are you right now?
- At home. Why?
ls there a chair or
a bench nearby?
Please sit down.
You're about to get a jolt
Pardon me?
You have a call from Delhi
Please speak here
Hello...
Sa_araz...
Jaggu...
Hello...
.. hello Jaggu,
what's the matter?
Had you come to the
Marriage Registrar's office?
l had,
but you had left
Why didn't you call?
l got your letter.
You'd said, 'Don't contact me'
l knew you were
under family pressure
But deep down l knew,
one day you would contact me
What took you so long?
l am sory.
l had your Wrong Number
Just got the right number
from a friend
Thank you son
Here, hold this
Tipsy! You're taking
batteries home?
- Don't get them there.
- So many! For what?
Back home, l'll listen
to the sounds l've recorded
What sounds?
Earth sounds -
crows, traffic honking
Up there, you'll listen
to cars honking?
Now and then -
when l miss this planet
Hey, wait!
There's one more bag
Forget it, Tipsy!
You kidding?
It's stuffed with batteries
Wait!
Driver... please stop!
Eveyone on your planet
has stick-out ears?
And they roam around naked?
Why are you staring?
SomethinQ on my Face?
l was in tenth grade,
when l wrote my first poem,
For Papa
They say my Mom l resemble.
l say possible...
Poety means
sparse words, soaring thoughts
Pal, you're really cute
Here's to the
teetotalercalled Tipsy
Who says
''What's in a name?''
No tape had sounds of
crows or traFfic honkinQ
Evey tape had
just my voice
''l love you Jaggu''
Got it!
He sure made me run!
Tipsy, what's in these tapes?
Told you -
crows, traffic honking
Evey night, when your planet
rises, l'll play these tapes
And wave at you.
Like this
Will you wave back...
now and then?
Haven't you recorded my voice?
Your voice?
l think l have...
that one poem you recited
One poem? That's it?
l'm not exactly
in love with you...
.. to waste all my time
over you!
He didn't look back.
Not once
He was hiding his tears
One thing he learnt from us.
One thing he taught us
He learnt From us
how to lie...
.. and taught us
how to love
He loved me enough
to let me go
He came here naked.
As children do
Asked a lot of questions.
And then one day...
.. he went away
Four billion miles away
He left me two parting gifts
Sa_araz
and Papa
Till l live... evey night l'll look
at his planet and wave
l'm sure,
he'll do the same
l miss him
Fellow astronauts,
prepare to land on Ea_h
Remember the Four
Ea_h Su_ival Commandments
One:
Do not roam around naked
Cuddling, making love etc.
must be done in closed rooms
But fighting, making war etc.
is allowed in the open
Two: Beware of language,
it's confusing
lf Earthlings say,
'l love chicken and fish,'
it doesn't mean
they love animals,
but that animals are
on the lunch menu
The gap bemeen thought and
speech is our topic oF research
Thr_: On landing,
Find dancinQ cars For clothes
Hide your remotes deep in your
underwear, safe from thieves
four: the mother commandment
lf anyone says:
l'll connect you to God,
dump the research, take a U-turn
and run For your liFe
Come, don't be afraid
What are you goggling at?
- l have a question.
- What?
On your last visit,
how often were you whacked?
- What's this?
- Self-defense!
Safety gadgets?
- Let's go.
- Not there! This way
Kaput!