'The producer, the director, the artist,
'or any other person associated
with the film do not intend'
'to hurt or disrespect any person,
place, region, country, religion,'
'community or religious sentiments.'
'The filmmaker respects the perspectives
and viewpoints of others.'
"O, Sweetheart... "
"This time when I come home, "
"I'll buy you a motorcycle."
"I'll make you wear the helmet
and hop on the back seat"
"and race my motorcycle ahead."
"O, Sweetheart...
"My dear sweetheart."
"O darling,
don't hold on too hard."
"Imagine what the
platoon will say."
"This time if I get promoted,"
"I'll buy a car for you instead."
Get back.
Let's go... Let's go.
Sartaj.
Sir.
Kailang.
Kailang accompanied by Ebohal.
Along with 70-80 terrorists of KYKL...
Double of what we had expected.
Sir, shall we radio-in the B-team?
Negative.
They won't get here before dawn.
We'll lose the element of surprise.
We might not get
this opportunity again...
when all the terrorists of Nagaland
and Manipur have assembled in one place.
Karan.
Form an outer perimeter
with 10 commandos.
Mainly snipers.
Sartaj, the other commandos and I, will
move in from the left and right flank...
for a direct assault.
You will handle any terrorist
who gets out of our circle.
No terrorist gets out alive.
Copy.
- Copy.
- Good. Best of luck.
Best of luck.
Sartaj.
Anyone spot Kailang?
Negative Sir.
Commandos!
- Yes, sir!
How is the spirit?
- High, sir!
I said how is the spirit?
Jai Hind!
- Jai Hind!
What is Major Vihaan's background?
He's an NDA Topper.
Para-Commando Gold Medallist.
His father; Col. Meher Singh Shergill.
Was martyred in the Kargil war,
in Tololing.
Posthumous, he was
honoured with the Mahavir Chakra.
After being trained
for the Special Forces...
Vihaan was posted in Kashmir,
Jaisalmer, and Manipur.
He was also responsible for the on-ground
planning of the North-Eastern mission.
Boys!
Major Vihaan Shergill.
- Fantastic.
He headed this operation, sir.
- It's a pleasure to meet you.
Donor to meet you too, sir.
Major Karan.
- Very proud of you, officer.
Thank you, sir.
- Well done.
Capt. Sartaj.
- Sartaj.
Thank you, sir.
Your team's bravery and skill...
has put a stop on the movements
of the North Eastern Terrorism.
We're very proud of you.
Thank you, sir.
- Thank you, sir.
We just received a word from RAW...
that the remaining terrorist groups
want to compromise with us.
After the Special Forces mission,
they have no choice
but to compromise with us.
Vihaan.
General. Arjun mentioned that
you've put in a request for...
pre-mature retirement
on compassionate grounds.
Why? What's wrong?
Sir...
my mother has Alzheimer's.
Stage 6.
Her memory is fading by the day.
And, she hasn't been
keeping well either.
I've been posted
in the Eastern Command,
and she lives here
in Delhi with my sister.
I would like to spend some time
with her before she forgets me too.
Bravo.
You're a good son who wants
to take care of his mother.
But it's also important to
take care of your country.
After all, this country
is also our mother.
Isn't there a
way other than retirement?
There is.
What if we transfer you
to the Army Headquarters in Delhi?
You'll stay close to your mother,
and us too.
What say?
Right, sir.
Great.
Mr. Govind.
- Sir.
Arrange a nurse for his mother
who will stay with her 24 hours.
Sure.
Well...
Why don't you all
start with dinner..
Everyone must be hungry.
Doesn't matter how many times you
read that report,
nothing will change.
I have just one request.
When I get very sick,
don't dump me in some hospital.
Mom, no one's taking
you to any hospital.
I feel very afraid when I am alone.
Take your pills.
Here you go.
Take it.
- Neha's promised me...
Mom...
I am trying my best.
I swear.
- I know.
I know you're trying your best.
Mom, take your pills.
May I?
Hi, uncle.
What took you so long to open the door?
- Sorry.
These are all of mom's clothes.
The only thing left
now are the books.
I will bring them over later. Okay.
Oh yes, her medicine.
Did you give her the medicines?
- Just did.
Where is she?
- Inside.
Okay.
Uncle?
At what age did
you get a black belt?
16.
See this?
It's a Green belt.
I'll get my black belt
in a couple of years.
Then you better
be careful around me.
And don't make me lose my temper.
So what are your plans after
getting the black belt, Ms. Karate?
Firstly,
I'll join the army like uncle.
And then become India's
First Female Army General.
Bravo.
Uncle's sycophant!
Because your father's a clown,
isn't he?
You don't think he's
an officer, do you?
Suhana, go get the scissors.
Scissors.
Vihaan, please go help Karan.
- Why?
He's made a real mess
planning your party.
Oh, God.
Our home looks like a
couple of grenades went off.
Seriously.
Scissors.
- Thank you.
Let's go meet your papa.
- Come on.
Mom's nurse will be arriving soon.
The guest room is ready for her...
Vihaan.
- Yes, mom.
When did you arrive?
He just arrived today, mom.
He wanted to surprise you.
How long are you planning to stay?
10 days.
He's planning to take
you to aunt Rajni's house.
In Dehradun.
You better leave.
Karan's waiting for you, okay.
Mom, did you watch
your favourite show?
Suhana, go finish your homework.
Did you eat?
I am really famished. Let's eat.
Uncle. Let's go.
Uncle, Papa taught me
your battalion's war cry.
Really? Tell me.
Courage and competence in war,
sacrifice is the ultimate Dharma.
Come on... You call that a war cry?
When you shout out a war cry...
it should make the
soldier's blood boil.
And your enemies should
shiver in their boots.
That's a war cry.
And start eating
eggs for breakfast.
No more salads like your mom!
Get changed,
And then we can do your homework.
Go.
- Okay.
Sartaj?
Didn't you have a date today?
Why didn't you go?
You didn't hear?
What happened?
He got all dressed up,
wore Armani perfume...
and was about to leave when he suddenly
gets a message from his girlfriend.
Saying "I am tired of
this relationship, its over."
I am really sorry, I didn't know.
I am not finished yet.
A little later she
messaged him again.
Saying "Sorry sweetheart, this
message got sent to you by mistake."
These uptown girls I tell you...
uptown...
But anyway...
How are you going to
manage staff work in Delhi?
A man like you will go
crazy pushing pen in South Block.
Your planning has never failed
in any of the missions.
Sir, you're needed at the border,
not in Delhi.
Look, every soldier
has to this job as well.
And, you both know
that I have to do this.
Now stop making these sad faces
and pass me the cottage cheese.
Did mom's reports come in?
- They did.
It's spreading aggressively now.
Hope you are having a good time.
Please help yourself, guys.
- Karan.
Here's your drink.
- Thank you.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
This is nothing, Capt. Zeeshan.
Vihaan's dad in fact brewed
the best brandy in the world.
And often after returning from school
we would help ourselves to it..
Soon he found
out and suspected us.
So, in order to save
ourselves from the beating...
we transferred half of the
brandy to our school water bottle.
And, we passed urine in the half empty
brandy bottle to make it look full.
Not us, just him.
And unfortunately, the very same night,
his Titu uncle flew in from abroad.
To try the latest batch of brandy.
He took one sip and, Listen. Listen.
He took one sip and said...
"Exquisite!"
Hello, sir.
When did she fall asleep?
- A little while ago.
Did she take her pills?
- Yes, sir.
She has a habit of waking
up in the middle of the night.
If you need anything,
feel free to tell me.
I'll be right here.
- Yes, sir.
Don't worry, sir. It's my job.
And, in case you want to rest,
there's the guest room.
No problem, sir. I am fine.
Thank you.
What is your name?
- Jasmine.
Jasmine?
- Jasmine Almeida.
Jasmine Almeida. Sit.
Sit.
Stop spreading these
lies immediately!
You've turned this into a joke.
Everyone knows that
we're a peace-loving nation.
You blame us for every
trivial attack in your country.
I want evidence!
Evidence!?
What more proof do you need, sir?
What you're saying is baseless.
Absolutely baseless.
Three terrorists infiltrated
our border through the Ravi river.
They opened fire on
a Punjab Roadways bus.
Some were injured...
But the driver kept his head
straight and didn't stop the bus...
and drove straight
to the Government Hospital.
Where are the terrorists now?
Right now they are hiding in
an under-construction building...
near Dina Nagar Police Station.
But the Swat Team have
already started their operation.
Keep NSG on standby.
- Okay, sir.
Which terrorist group
do they belong to?
According to our sources,
these men are from Lashkar.
Do we know how many
people have died?
Four civilians are dead.
And 11 are still serious.
Sir. IEDs were discovered
at the Pathankot Railway tracks.
There's a probability
of finding more.
Sir...
Please excuse me.
Sir.
The Punjab Swat Team
has arrived on the spot.
IEDs were recovered from railway
tracks between Pathankot and Amritsar.
Sorry, sir.
We're doing our best.
Yes, sir.
"O Life..."
"Why was there was
always a rift between us?"
"O Life..."
"Together we took care
of all the complaints we had."
"O Life..."
"Why was there
always a rift between us?"
"O Life..."
"Together we took care
of all the complaints we had."
"I always walked down the path
you showed me..."
"now you must try following me."
"I always walked down the path
you showed me..."
"now you must try following me."
"And away I go... Away I go..."
"In which direction do you go,
o traveller?"
"And away I go... Away I go..."
"In which direction do you go,
o traveller?"
"A part of me is still here..."
"and other part
is somewhere else."
"We've met countless times before."
"Yet every time we meet
you feel like a stranger."
"My destination is right here..."
"yet my path seems complicated."
"No matter how many times
I try to walk towards you..."
"but the distance
never seems closer."
"I always walked down the path
you showed me..."
"now you must try following me."
"I always walked down the path
you showed me..."
"now you must try following me."
"And away I go... Away I go..."
"In which direction do you go,
o traveller?"
"And away I go... Away I go..."
"In which direction do you go,
o traveller?"
"A part of me is still here..."
"and other part
is somewhere else."
"A part of me is still here..."
"and other part
is somewhere else."
"O Life..."
It's been more than 16 hours now
and yet there seems
no respite from this encounter.
The ADI building is being targeted
by rocket launchers and grenades.
And Fire has broken out
in one part of the building.
We've learned from our sources that
two soldiers have been injured...
although we have
no confirmed information.
And the sound of the explosions...
Jai Hind, sir.
Why are you here?
Sir, my case is
under investigation.
My first posting was
in Srinagar in July 2014.
I was just getting
to know my work when...
there was a huge deluge
in the first week of September...
and the dam on Jhelum broke.
Water started to
rise at an alarming rate...
in the low lying
areas of Srinagar.
All the MI-17 and Dhruv
pilots immediately...
engaged in a sortie mission.
Without any rest or food, we started
rescuing people from low lying areas.
On the 7th night at 3 am, we
received a distress call from Rajbagh.
A 7-year-old child
was badly injured...
and stuck on the roof
of her house along with her mother.
There was almost no visibility
due to the rain.
As a result, the Commander cancelled
all rescue missions till dawn.
But somehow I couldn't
get that child out of my head.
I had to do something.
Sabiya and Zooni.
Is anyone from your family
in the Defence forces?
Dad? Mom? Brother?
No, sir.
My husband was.
Capt. Jaskirat Singh Rangi.
Seasoned Punjab Regiment.
He died in an ambush
at the Naushera Sector.
Jaskirat was a big patriot.
The only thing I
am afraid of now is...
whether I'll ever get to prove
my patriotism to Jaskirat or not...
Mom.
Jasmine.
Yes. Yes.
How's your acidity now?
Are you taking your pills on time?
Okay, I am going to call you back.
Where's mom?
- Inside. Sleeping.
Stay here.
Peaceful-Peacefuller.
More peaceful.
Most Peaceful...
- Neha, did mom come here?
No.
Oh, God.
- Mom.
I am extremely sorry.
I am sorry.
It was very urgent.
I wouldn't have if
it wasn't an emergency,
You know me.
I would have never taken that call.
I am extremely...
- I know...
What is your real name?
Jasmine Almeida...
- What is your real name, Jasmine?
Sir, I just told you.
Where's my mom?
- Vihaan...
Relax.
- One second, Neha. One second.
I don't...
- Now you listen to me.
Neither my family, nor
I need protection of any kind.
I am quite capable of
protecting them &amp; myself!
And I definitely don't need an
incompetent and fake nurse like you.
So tell your Intelligence
Department...
to find my mom
by hook or by crook,
and bring her home.
Do it!
Can I take it?
- Yes, you can.
Hello.
Where?
Okay.
Our agents found Mrs. Suhasini
under the Dwarka bridge.
The day I came here I put
GPS tags on all her clothes...
so that we can track
her every movement.
She should be home soon.
I might be an incompetent nurse,
But I am a damn good agent, sir.
I am sorry.
She should be home soon.
Jai Hind, sir.
Jai Hind.
- There's still time for breakfast.
Can we get tea?
Shaqeel.
Let's go there.
That side. Run.
Go on. Go.
They are heavily armed.
Around 4-5 terrorists.
Sir.
- What position?
Two are behind the West Wing.
Major Awasthi's team
has opened counter-fire.
One of them is
on the Admin block...
and the other near the T6 wall.
Sartaj.
- Sir.
Fetch me my Draganov
from the Transit room.
I'll blow their bloody
brains out from right here.
Hurry.
Rohit. Thapa.
Yes sir.
- Sir.
Cover me.
Sartaj, Go through the West Wing
and reach at the fuel depot.
And you two rendezvous
near the T6 bunker.
Sir.
- Best of luck, guys.
Go. Go. Go.
- Yes, sir.
Stop! Stop!
Stop firing!
- Stop firing!
Courage and competence in war.
Sacrifice is the ultimate Dharma.
This is no time to think
about the UN or USA's opinion.
It's time we send a message to Pakistan
in the language they understand.
If we don't give a fitting
reply for this cowardly attack...
then it will shatter the morale
of our army and our civilians.
People will lose
faith in our government.
Sir, we can prepare
for war in three days.
I can send our tanks and heavy
artillery under 8 hours to the LC.
I think we should
dishonour the Indus Treaty.
If ISI gets pressurized
by Pakistani citizens
then maybe they will
lessen their terrorist attacks.
Pakistan is under the ISI.
The ISI is not under Pakistan.
They might let their
people starve to death...
But never stop funding terrorism.
We must think of a better option.
Govind.
A surgical strike, sir.
Surgical strike.
Infiltrate POK and annihilate
their terrorist launchpads...
their hidden terrorists,
their handlers, and guides.
And looking at Pakistan's
nature they will never admit...
that terrorists
are breeding on their land.
So, if there are no terrorists, then
there's no question of a strike, right?
And, since there's no strike, there's no
point of war or international pressure.
Most important...
this is our biggest opportunity
to strike back for Uri.
Doesn't a surgical strike
sound a bit dangerous?
We can use our jet fighters to bomb
some of their bunkers near the LC.
During the Munich Olympics, PLO
terrorists killed Israeli athletes.
But Israel didn't strike back by
just firing a couple of missiles.
They engaged Operation
'Wrath of God'.
They hunted down every single terrorist,
dragged them from their home
and killed them.
In the history of India, we have
never attacked any country first.
And Pakistan has been taking advantage
of our nature from the beginning.
1947, '65, '71... '99...
In fact, sir. Our tolerance
is being mistaken as our weakness.
This is our chance to
instil fear in their hearts.
Make them believe that India
will not take things lying down.
This is a New India.
We will infiltrate them
and hit them where it hurts.
Ravinder...
We have no enmity with
the Pakistani population.
Our war is against terrorism.
I think Govind is right.
Arjun.
I think it's a good idea, sir.
Fine...
In 10 days we'll carry out the most
lethal surgical strike in Pakistan.
Ravinder, you prepare
a team along with Arjun.
And you will lead this mission.
You will do all the planning.
And you will update
me about their progress every day.
Everyone else keeps the
Pakistani authorities busy.
Give them evidence
of the Uri attack.
Ask them for an explanation.
But at no cost should
anyone get a whiff of our plan.
Remember...
these meetings
shouldn't be logged.
Did you eat?
No, sir. Don't feel like it.
Wait, I'll get something.
- No, sir.
I am in a hurry.
I... have received my orders.
They are planning
an operation in Kashmir.
I don't know the details, but...
I guess...
they are planning
to strike back to avenge Uri.
Karan sir always said...
not a single man can die
when Vihaan's around.
He'll even fight
with Death to save us.
I really wish you were
there to lead us, sir.
I found two dirty shirts
amongst Karan's stuff.
And I don't know what to do.
I don't want to wash them
or hand them over to someone else.
I can still feel his
essence in them, Vihaan.
Sir, you once mentioned
in your lecture...
there exists a thin line between
responsible and irresponsible.
I don't want to be on
the other side of that line.
If I don't fight for my men,
my country now...
then I'll be irresponsible
in my own opinion.
And I won't be able
to live with that.
I promise you, sir, you can send me
to any corner of this world to fight.
I will bring all my soldiers
back safe and sound.
Sir, let me be a part
of this mission in Kashmir.
I request you, sir. Please.
Vihaan,
in 8 days you're going to
conduct a surgical strike in POK.
Tomorrow morning Lt. Gn. Grewal
will brief you about this operation.
You will do the entire
on ground planning with him.
Prepare the best team you can.
And revert back to me by the 23rd night
with each and every detail.
Understood, sir.
I wish you all the best.
Thank you very much, sir.
I've scoured these
hills for 40 years.
When I close my eyes,
I don't see my children's faces.
I see Kashmir's
territorial map instead.
And that's why Vihaan,
it will be easy to enter POK.
But what will be difficult
is getting out after the attack.
I understand, sir.
We will plan for everything.
Did you finalize the team?
Out of the soldiers
that died in the Uri attack...
most of them belonged
to the Dogra and Bihar Regiment.
My advice is that
we should include this regiment's
special team in this mission as well.
To win a war,
very often a soldier's emotions,
are more important than his training.
I want to put their anger
and passion to the right use.
At ease.
Commandos.
My name is Major Vihaan Shergill.
And that's Capt. Sartaj.
Please take your phones out.
Now send a text to your family.
Saying that you'll be in Udhampur till
the morning of the 29th of September...
for a special tactical training.
And you won't be allowed to communicate
with anyone during this training.
As a result,
you'll keep your phones
switched off for the next 7 days.
Send it.
Is it sent?
- Yes, sir.
Good. Sartaj.
Now you will all put
your phones in this bag.
And your phones will be returned to you
only on the morning of 29th September.
What I am going to tell you next...
shall never be mentioned
again until your last breath.
On the night of 28th September...
I will give you a chance to avenge our
brothers who died in the Uri attack.
Just like those coward
terrorists brutally killed...
our unarmed brothers
in their sleep...
we will give them a fitting reply...
A chance to behead them.
Are you ready for this mission?
- Yes, sir.
Is your blood boiling for revenge?
Commandos.
Who are we?
- Indian army, sir!
The Indian Army did not start this war
but we will bloody hell finish it.
Yes, sir!
How is the spirit?
- High, sir!
I said how is the spirit?
Good!
Yes, sir.
It's completely our fault.
We'll definitely find out.
We'll have to.
Don't worry.
Goodbye.
You guys are bunch of stupid
lowlife nincompoops.
You don't have kids, right?
Don't even try.
For the past one month
I've been saying...
that there's a mole in our office who
has been syphoning information to India.
And you guys can't find him.
I swear.
I am starting to feel that...
that could it be one of you?
Can you even imagine
the pressure on me?
One week...
If you don't find
that guy in a week,
I'll have one of
you for dinner, and...
I won't even burp.
Don't just stand there
staring at my face.
Get lost.
And Karim, give that file to me.
Stupid idiots.
Mother, it's me.
Hello. How are you?
You wanted Bilqis
aunt's number, right?
Take a pen and note it down.
34...
49...
58...
8... 74...
2201...
Yes..
No, I'm feeling a little acidic.
The indigestion
is causing me to burp.
My stomach is not doing so well.
Also note down
Munnu uncle's number.
Sir, we got the coordinates.
There's a total of seven locations,
all close to LC.
We'll have to physically find the location
of their launchpads in these areas.
Call Srinivas at ISRO.
- Yes, sir.
The pictures from Tripura, Assam
are not clear due to heavy rains.
Hello.
- Govind speaking.
Bharadwaj.
Hi, Govind. Tell me.
Listen, I'm sending
you some coordinates.
I want you to position the
RISAT 1 or the RISAT 2 satellite
over these coordinates
for the next six days.
And don't move them, come what may.
- Okay.
Secondly, relay all the
images directly to Raisina Hills.
We have only two hours.
- Okay.
You will personally scan every
location with the Army Intelligence.
only when we have every
detail about the all the locations.
Correct?
- Yes, sir.
Done, sir.
Send this feed directly
to Raisina Hills.
Sir. We have the feed.
Pallavi.
Pallavi Sharma.
You asked me my real name that day.
I am really sorry about that day.
It's okay.
In fact, even I might have reacted
the same way if I was in your place.
How is your mom?
She is...
She is fine.
Neha is staying with her.
We've also appointed a
full-time nurse, so let's see.
I hope she's better than me.
I think its time. We should get going.
I'll look into this.
Sir.
- Vihaan. Come, sit.
Have you selected your team?
- Yes, sir.
And what about their advanced
tactical commando training?
It's begun, sir.
- Good.
Pallavi. You can begin.
- Sir.
Sir, we've confirmed 5 launchpads
of Hizbul, Lashkar, and Jaish.
Two in Lipa Valley.
Two in Kel.
And one in Bhimber.
These launchpads were easy to find
because they were in isolated areas.
And the remaining two are...
possibly located in the populated
areas of the Muzaffarabad district.
Identifying the exact
location through satellites
in a crowded area
is a little difficult.
I will check at DRDO tomorrow,
whether they can help us
in finding the launchpads.
And Pallavi, keep giving Vihaan all
the details about these launchpads. - Sir.
Vihaan, any suggestion or question?
Which of these launchpads
were used for the Uri attack?
We believe that the attackers came from
one of the launchpads in Muzaffarabad.
And who was the
handler of that attack?
We still don't have any
information on that. Sorry.
These Sigma 5 drones
are our latest invention.
Developed along with...
Israeli intelligence.
Sir,
their range is
close to 50 kilometres.
And they can fly as low
as 2 kilometres above ground.
That's fine, Brian,
but how close can it come to the ground,
without getting detected.
Meaning?
Meaning I want a drone that can
fly outside our enemy's window...
without getting detected.
Sir, that technology
hasn't been invented yet.
I thought as much.
Sir, he's our intern.
What's your name, son?
- Ishaan.
Ishaan Wattal, sir.
What is this?
Sir, it's an unmanned aerial vehicle.
Shaped like an eagle.
What is it called?
- Garuda.
Garuda. Based on Vishnu Puran.
- Ahh... Vishnu Puran.
Sorry, since there are already
so many projects underway...
I use the spare parts
to pass some time. That's it.
Ishaan, make it fly. Come.
Sorry, sir.
Sir.
Sir, when I say so
you must run fast
and throw the Garuda
in the air with full force.
Just a minute, sir.
Raise your hand.
Higher, sir.
A little more.
Sorry, sir.
Sir, 3...
2...
1...
What's the range?
Sir, it can fly up to
a distance of 12 kilometres...
and its got four hours of
battery backup on a single charge.
Infrared and night vision enabled.
It has a 16-megapixel camera
and 7.2x digital zoom.
And it can also hover at one
place for take-off and landing...
Like...
this.
If it can hover at one
place for taking off and landing,
then why did you make Brian run.
Brian.
- Yes, sir.
I need four such
Garudas by tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Sir, this is just a prototype which
this kid has made just to pass time.
It hasn't been commissioned
yet and the R&amp;D for it...
Can four such Garudas
be made by tomorrow?
We can if the entire team chips in.
Good. Brian, stop everything else
and start a separate assembly line, and
put all your technicians to work on this.
Tomorrow afternoon I want Ishaan on a
flight to Kashmir along with four Garudas.
Okay.
You might have just
won us the war, son.
Good job.
Thank... Sorry, sir.
Sir.
Time to prove your
patriotism to Jaskirat.
You're going to be my pilot, Seerat.
Sir...
Excuse me.
- Yes.
Hello. - The army has arrested
two guides in Baramulla.
Chances are they have
information about the Uri attack.
Govind sir wants both of
us involved in the interrogation.
When are you leaving?
- 2 hours.
Palam Air Force Base.
Who was the handler for the
Uri attack?
Where was it planned?
I don't know anything, madam.
I sell nuts in Batmaylu...
Make another excuse
and I will burst your nuts.
Believe me, madam...
Oh Mother...
Who was involved in the Uri attack?
I want names.
Who was involved?
Who was the handler
for the Uri attack?
Oh Mother...
- Farooq, I need names.
Who were they?
- Oh Mother...
Oh Mother...
Who he is?
He's my brother?
What's his name?
Faizal.
Look Faizal,
we're running out of time.
Your brother has two options.
First,
he politely gives us the
name of the handler of the Uri attack.
Second,
I can spill your guts out.
Some tea?
No. Stop him, ma'am.
Please stop him, madam.
He's just a kid.
He will die, madam.
Madam.
Madam...
I'll tell you. I'll tell you.
Idris.
Idris Qayoom Al Baghdadi.
He made the plan.
And Jabbar Firozi was the handler.
This is Idris and that's Jabbar.
They were the planners
and handlers for the attack...
on Uri and on
Pampore before that.
Idris is from Sialkot
and Jabbar is from Gilgit.
Seven years ago they met in one of the
training camps of Jaish-e-Mohammad...
and a few years later,
under the supervision of Jaish...
they started their own
highly specialized terrorist group.
Sirat-UL-Jannat.
Their B-2 training center and
Launchpad is in the Chakothi village...
which is near the Aman Setu ridge
and Muzaffarabad district.
Their guides use the natural caves
situated in the jungles around them to...
infiltrate the terrorists into India.
We've given the army
the locations of these caves.
They are keeping
a watch on these caves.
Four UAVs will be sent to
Kashmir tomorrow from the DRDO...
for additional surveillance.
You must increase shelling
at the LC from tomorrow.
And keep increasing the intensity
gradually so that on the night of 28th...
we reach the
peak of our shelling.
Especially in the areas
from where our soldiers
will infiltrate into POK.
"I will fight."
"The fire in my blood
makes me want to fight."
"I will go to any lengths.
That's my heart's desire."
"A passionate soul is ready to die
for his country. He is fearless."
"The enemies are afraid of him."
"A soldier fights till his last breath."
"He faces death fearlessly
and leaves the enemies trembling."
"I will fight."
There are some boulders
here where you can hide...
but a Pakistani forward post is
at a distance of 60 meters from here.
Take the flight recorders
out of all the choppers.
And color it the same
way as the Pakistani Air Force.
"Our hearts are lit up
with our passion."
"We are not afraid of holding
the flames in our hand."
"We will do something admirable."
"And set a good example
for the world."
"I will fight..."
"It's the burning desire
of my heart to go to any lengths."
"A soldier never gives up
even till his last breath."
"He embraces danger
and brings down his enemies."
"A brave heart is ready to die
for his country. He is heroic."
"He embraces death
and doesn't spare his enemies."
As of 0900 hours,
India has intensified the shelling.
I guess India is still looking
for a befitting reply to our
Prime Minister's speech at the UN.
Sir, I doubt whether this
shelling is for distracting us.
In case if they were
planning another attack...
then our intelligence agency
must have got some kind of news.
India is in no position
to think about another attack.
They are already in a difficult
position with the issue of Kashmir.
This drama will continue
a little longer at the LOC.
Our actors and singers
will be banned.
Trade will get affected.
But soon everything will cool down.
But, we should not make the mistake
of underestimating our enemy.
Zubair.
- Yes.
Afzal.
- Sir.
I should be getting
updates every minute.
Send all the ammunition
you can at the LOC.
We must give a
fitting reply as well.
Is that understood?
Yes, sir.
- Good.
What happened at the meeting today?
You're playing awkward shots today.
There was a strong debate over LOC.
The Indians have made our lives
difficult with their constant shelling.
Some important decisions
were taken today in the meeting.
Forget that.
Watch this shot.
Watch this.
No Zameer,
your head's not in the game today.
You know what, come home.
I'll tell Aasma to make your favourite
dish and your favourite dessert.
No. Not today.
I'll have to stay awake
all night with the Minister sir.
And tomorrow we might have
to go on a rendezvous of the LOC.
Maybe some other day.
What are you plans for 28th?
28... Yes, 28th is great.
Sure.
- Yeah, yeah. Sure.
Come let's look for the ball now.
Can you get me a closer shot?
- Yeah, sure.
Slightly to the right.
Good job, Ishaan. Good job.
Hey...
sit down.
Get it out now, Ishaan.
- I am trying.
Ishaan, come on. Come on, Ishaan.
Come on.
A toy.
Yes... yes...
Try.. come on, Ishaan.
Sir this is the B-2 launchpad
where the terrorist responsible
for the Uri attack came from.
A double storied building with 38 highly
trained terrorist and 5 exit points.
Has our intelligence
confirmed these details?
Yes, sir.
I've personally checked
every launchpad.
What is the plan to attack?
Sir, our 80 commandos
are fully prepared.
On the night of 28th, when
our shelling will be at its peak...
we'll enter POK in four
low flying MI-17 helicopters.
And we'll start our
attack at exactly 2 am.
These 80 commandos will be
divided into four teams of 20 each.
Every team will have
to destroy two targets.
Team Alpha, Along with
Major Vihaan, will first destroy B-1
and theJabbar and Idris' B-2 launchpad.
Similarly teams Bravo,
Charlie, Delta,
will destroy their targets
in Lipa, Bimber, and Kel.
On the positive side, all these
targets are quite close to the LC...
which means from landing
to take off, the entire mission...
should last only for 50 minutes.
Which means by 3 am
we should be back in our choppers.
And by 5 am...
we'll be at the Srinagar base.
There will be no
meetings here today.
As you've all been told earlier,
we'll spend a normal day tomorrow...
with the press and public.
On the 28th late night, there should
be no one here from the Ministry.
Other than the Army
Intelligence, only
Arjun and Govind will
be allowed to stay here.
Vihaan, when are
you leaving for Kashmir?
Sir, we leave tomorrow
from the Northern Command.
Vihaan, I've heard that you've promised
to bring all your soldiers back safe
and sound.
Sir, with your permission.
My commandos &amp; I would like to have
dinner with you on the 30th night.
Jai Hind.
Jai Hind, sir.
Capt. Ved.
Akram.
Bali.
You three will lead the Bravo, Charlie,
and Delta, teams.
As soon as we para-drop in POK,
we'll be easy targets.
So we must carefully, and stealthily,
make it to our launchpads.
Once we reach, again...
Outer parameters, Snipers.
Inner parameters, Assaulters.
Every team will be
carrying a signal jammer...
so that they cannot use radio-signals
or mobile phones to call for help...
during the attack.
Remember boys,
our return is the toughest part.
Our backs will be facing the enemy,
and they will be firing at us.
So we have to be quick.
Any questions?
- No, sir.
I've promised that you will all return
with me to India safe and sound.
And I bloody well intend
to keep my promise.
Jai Hind.
- Jai Hind.
Our assets in Muzaffarabad
and Gilgit have sent updates.
It says that India is going to escalate
their shelling at the maximum today.
Excuse me.
Sir.
Commandos.
The time has come
to make them bleed for their deeds.
They want Kashmir
and we want their heads.
Are you ready, boys?
- Yes, sir.
How is the spirit?
- High, sir.
Jai Hind!
- Jai Hind!
Go. Go. Go.
All the best...
- All the best...
All the best... Go. Go.
It was really dark.
I was really doing her hard.
Little did I know
that she was a virgin.
Aasma.
- Yes.
Get some ice for Zameer.
Here. - Aasma, you've kept yourself busy
in the kitchen...
while we're getting
bored out here.
Come and join us.
I can't do two jobs at once especially
when I am cooking this exquisite dish.
I'll join you in a while.
You're looking much better today.
You've been really worried
for the past couple of days.
What can I say?
These Indians have
made my life hell.
I wonder what else they are
planning along with the shelling.
But our spies are
no less than them.
We've taken all the precautions.
Did you taste these dates?
Thank God, food is ready.
Now make me a large peg,
with lots of ice. - Of course.
So Zameer,
how is your better half?
She's in Birmingham.
For the graduation ceremony
of my youngest daughter.
I was supposed to go as well.
But all thanks to the issues on the
LOC,
which spoiled all my plans.
There's nothing we can do.
Well...
Cheers.
Aasma, since when
did you start drinking whiskey?
What?
You normally drink wine, don't you?
So I thought let's give
whiskey a shot instead.
There's something unique about...
women who drink whiskey.
Wow!
Let's go.
- We are taking off.
Salim, Raisina Hills.
Zameer?
Zameer? Zameer?
What was the decision taken
against India in today's meeting?
Were the words "Surgical Strike"
used in the meeting today?
Zameer?
Dear, what are you doing?
- Zameer,
what was the decision
taken in the meeting today?
Zameer?
What did the Minister say?
Radar... AEWAC... radar.
We've received some
Intel from our spies.
They have spotted helicopters near
the LOC painted in Pakistani colours.
Their helicopters were repainted.
Maybe they are planning to fly low from
the LOC and attack our forward posts.
Is there any way we can stop them?
We should launch the AEWAC
radar near the Uri sector.
If the enemy helicopter comes anywhere
within 20 meters of the LOC...
then our anti-aircraft missiles
will shoot it down immediately.
Hello.
- Alpha Team needs to abort the mission.
I repeat, the Alpha
team must abort the mission.
What?
Sir.
We've detected air
activity at the LC.
Keep the anti-aircraft
missiles ready.
Sir.
- Pallavi,
has Vihaan's chopper taken off?
- Yes, sir.
They will cross LC in 10 seconds.
Connect me to Vihaan now.
Vihaan, I've patched
you with Govind sir.
Sir, Vihaan is online.
Vihaan, don't cross the LC.
I repeat, do not cross the LC.
Turn your choppers around.
Turn around! Turn around!
They have launched the
AEWAC radar in Muzaffarabad sector.
That means Alpha
team cannot cross by air.
We'll have to abort your mission.
Pallavi, listen.
During Farooq's
interrogation he said that...
he used to bring terrorists
to India through the caves...
which our army
is keeping an eye on.
Get me the exact
coordinates to those caves.
If we can't go through the air,
then we'll go by land.
But we will complete this
mission today at any cost.
Bravo, Charlie, Delta,
you
three will move ahead as planned.
There will be radio silence
amongst all the teams now.
We'll only be in touch with
the army intelligence directly.
They will keep me posted.
Correct! Bravo, Charlie, Delta...
Your areas are safe
according to Intelligence.
Move ahead as planned.
Sir.
- What's the status?
Sir, we are still figuring out
the coordinates.
Thank you.
- Welcome sir.
Let's go.
Sir, entering a cave blindly without a
recce and monitoring is way to risky.
There might be Rangers or Terrorists
posted for guarding these caves.
Vihaan, wait.
Is Ishaan online? Can he hear us?
Yes, sir. He can.
Ishaan.
- Sir.
Can you see the GPS location
of all the four teams?
Yes, sir. I can see it.
- Good.
From now on you're
going to be their eyes.
Tell the operators
that all the four Garudas...
will stay a few meters
ahead of the team leaders.
And you keep tracking
their position through GPS.
As soon as you sense any danger,
you must inform the team leader.
Sure, sir.
Sir!
Sir, we're in Pakistan
Occupied Kashmir.
Good job, Vihaan.
The other teams are
soon reaching their targets.
Bilal? Dawood?
Say hello to your brothers in hell.
And ask them to hold on
to the celebrations.
We plan to send them
a lot more guests tonight.
Sir, the first
operation was a success.
We've destroyed the B-1 launchpad.
What is the status
of the remaining teams?
Teams Bravo and Charlie have
attacked their secondary location.
Team Delta is preparing to return
after completing their mission.
Not a single casualty.
- Good.
Let's go.
Abdullah!
- Yes.
Come here.
Take Zameer sir home. He's had
a little too much to drink today.
Yes.
Come on... Go out quickly.
Where is Idris?
Camera!
Did you find Idris?
No, sir.
I don't think he's here.
He's here.
Sir, someone has informed the Police.
They are just two minutes away.
Vihaan, hurry up.
Copy, sir.
But Idris has to die.
- But, Vihaan.
Sartaj, move.
You barged into my home
and killed my brothers.
Today I barged into your
home and I'm killing your brothers.
We are the Indian Army.
Indian Army!
Ishaan, where to?
Sir, lower east side. Out
the small door and into the fields.
Who's there? I'll shoot.
Sartaj.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Boys go faster. Faster. Faster.
Sir, be ready. We're getting
a Pakistani chopper along with us.
Vihaan, we're sending
jets to give you cover fire.
They will be at your
location in 10 minutes.
Copy, sir.
Sir, we're running
out of ammunition.
We can't hold them
off for 10 minutes.
Come what may, but every soldier
will make it back home alive today.
Seerat, now!
Jaskirat, this is for you.
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Sir, we did it.
Bravo, Charlie, Delta,
what's your status?
Every mission was a success.
Not a single casualty.
I am extremely
proud of you my boys.
Thank you, sir.
Congratulations, sir.
Sir,
the mission was a success.
Commandos.
- Yes, sir.
How's the spirit?
- High sir!
Jai Hind!
- Jai Hind.
"You go as high as the sun."
"You are born to fly."
"You carry the sparkle in you."
"You are born to fly
as high as the sun."
"You carry the sparkle in you."
"You are extremely passionate."
"There's none like you."
"You are fearless in your actions."
"You are like a storm in the air."
"You are unstoppable."
"Like a storm in the air."
"This is a different experience."
Vihaan.
"It's my heart's desire to fight
for my country if given a chance again."
"My passionate heart is unstoppable."
"It's my heart's desire to fight
for my country if given a chance again."
"My passionate heart is unstoppable."
"Wishes poured in on Jagga's victory."
"He got acclaimed for his victory.
He is brave hearted."
"Surma. Surma..."
"Surma."
"Jagga has written a new story.
Jagga."
"He will stop you if you don't stop."
"We will not fear death and stop.
For the victory is ours."
"Jagga has written a new story.
Jagga."
"Wishes poured in on Jagga's victory."
"He got acclaimed for his victory.
He is brave hearted."
"Surma. Surma..."
"Surma."
"Surma... It's my desire to fight
for my country if given a chance again."
"My passionate heart is unstoppable."
"Jagga's actions are thrilling.
He is filled with youthfulness."
"Jagga doesn't listen to anyone.
He does as he wishes."
"Jagga's actions are thrilling.
He is filled with youthfulness. Jagga."
"Jagga doesn't listen to anyone.
He does as he wishes. Jagga."
"Wishes poured in on Jagga's victory."
"Every drop of his blood
shouts victory."
"He has the power to pull
the world down under his feet."
"Every drop of his blood
shouts victory."
"He has the power to pull
the world down under his feet."
"Don't stop dreaming.
Do your heart's will."
"Don't stay away from your dreams.
Keep the fire burning within you."
"He is brave hearted."
"His brave heart emits fire."
"We will capture what belongs to us.
We won't give up."
"We will break the myth of the
enemies that they can win against us."
"We won't stop
till we destroy our enemies."
"We feel pride in doing so."
"We won't stop
till we destroy our enemies."
"We feel pride in doing so."
"Don't stop dreaming.
Do your heart's will."
"Don't stay away from your dreams.
Keep the fire burning within you."
"He is brave hearted."
"His brave heart emits fire."