I a m retiring tomorrow.
From pa st few weeks,
ma ny people ha ve a sked me...
...tha t Mr. Pra ka sh Ra thod police
commissioner of Mumba i...
...tha t which wa s the most cha llenging
a nd interesting ca se of your life.
I ignored this question.
Every time... but every time
I remembered only one ca se.
This ca se is not registered
in a ny file a nywhere.
There is no record a nywhere.
But it is in my mind...
...a nd some people who were involved
in this ca se unwillingly.
Tha t ba sta rd.
Tha t ba sta rd just ha d guts to wa lk
into our lives a nd blow it a pa rt.
It wa s a Wednesda y.
Hello! Where a re you going?
To file a FIR.
To the right. Room number 3.
Who hit you?
- My wife.
I wa nted to file a n FIR. - Then wha t
is there to be emba rra ssed a bout?
How? - With a cooker.
I wa nt to file a compla int.
Wa it for a while.
I will ca II you. Ha ve a sea t.
Why did she hit you?
The problem wa s... tha t...
Come on. Spea k up. There
a re other people wa iting.
I just told her tha t there
wa s more sa It in the food.
She just fla red up.
There wa s a cooker to her right.
She picked it a nd hit
me on my left side.
Sir plea se... just wa rn her once.
She keeps hitting me.
You should never ever sa y
such things to your wife.
Go home a nd sa y sorry.
Or else instea d of sa It she will
put something else in your food.
Did you understa nd?
Don't ta ke it too seriously. Go on.
Sir, but file a report a t lea st...
- Get lost!
Hey mister, hello...
Mr. Ja mmu Ka shmir plea se come.
Wha t ha ppened?
- I lost my wa llet.
How? Wha t do you mea n by how?
How do things get lost?
I mea n, where wa s it lost?
- I don't remember.
When I checked it wa sn't with me.
Wha t were its contents?
A photogra ph of my wife,
driving license. PAN ca rd.
Ea sy, ea sy. Sorry.
PAN ca rd, ATM ca rd,
a nd credit ca rd.
There wa s a ra ilwa y pa ss.
Some ca sh. My wife's photogra ph.
You ha ve a Irea dy sa id tha t.
- Wha t?
You ha ve a Irea dy told me a bout
your wife's photogra ph.
How much ca sh wa s in it?
- Around 300-350 rupees.
Where is the wa shroom?
- Wha t's your na me a nd a ddress?
Ra jesh Kuma r Sha rma. 301,
Ma na sa rova r Society.
S.V. Roa d, Boriva li (west).
Wha t's your telephone number?
- 9832465784.
Ta ke this.
Ca II up tomorrow a nd enquire.
The wa shroom is to the
right over there.
Tha nk you.
Sir, it's a lwa ys a number from
Ka ra chi tha t fla shes on my mobile.
Initia lly, he used to a ddress
me a s brother, sir or boss.
He ha d sa id his na me wa s lmtia z.
He sa id he wa tches my
films ma ny times...
...a nd tha t he wa s
a grea t fa n of mine.
Then he ca lled toda y a nd
a sked me to pa y up 25 la kh rupees.
Sa id it wa s a n emergency.
Mr. Arjun Kha nna,
wha t exa ctly did he sa y?
Crush, scene 20, shot 20, ta ke 20.
Help me, plea se! '
'Plea se! Help me, plea se! '
Tha nk you so much.
Get up!
Cut it!
Oh god.
Hey get the ta ble. Good shot.
- Yea h tha nks!
Hello! -
Why a ren't you signing Desa i's film?
He is my specia I friend. If I don't
get a ny good news by noon.
I will pa ck
- up your shooting forever.
And keep 25 la kh rupees on ha nd.
I will ca II you up la ter a nd
tell you whom to give it to
25 la khs!
And why the hell do you dela y
so much to ta ke the ca II?
Ma ke sure tha t you pick it up
within two rings the next time.
Hello? - Just checking.'
Ha ng it up now.
Where is Ja i?
You know tha t I don't like your
tra veling in the tra in with the ba by?
If I go by roa d
I will rea ch tomorrow.
Why do you go to your
mom's pla ce so often?
This is the first time I a m
going since she wa s born.
But she'd come to our house
just la st week. - So?
She wa s a Iso there the
week before tha t. - So?
This should stop... Or else
the sub-inspector in...
...your mom's a rea is a
good friend of mine.
Why a re you so sca red of my mom?
Am not sca red. Just
jea lous of her...
...tha t she spends so much more
time with you two tha n me.
Ok I will ta ke your lea ve.
Bye. Ta ke ca re. Bye.
Ca II me up. - Yes, I will
ca II up on rea ching there.
Oka y bye.
- Bye.
See you. Ta ke ca re.
Just 20 rupees! Where is your
pollution certifica te?
Come on, sir. Keep it.
Not even one document you ha ve.
Ta ke out the money.
Where is your license? Look you
don't ha ve license with you.
Now come on, give me Rs. 500.
Come on sir, ta ke it. Keep it.
Hello sir.
Wha t a re you doing?
Sir, I ha ve stopped a sking. But
they keep bribing me willingly.
Ask him... Wa sn't I telling
you not to give me a nything?
Sir, wha t ca n I do if they
give it with so much love?
Too much of such love
ha s ma de you plump.
And you still wa nt some more.
- Sorry sir.
How much did you ta ke? - 20 rupees!
Give it ba ck!
- Ta ke it.
Give him 20 more. - Wha t?
You should a Iso sha re your
love with others. - Oka y sir.
Did you just give me money?
Fa ther wa s right a nd I wa s wrong.
Times ha ve cha nged. The New Age
is here - All right, go on.
This is good! This is good!
This is good!
Come on move a side! Move a side!
Rea dy to move in! Three!
Two! One! Go!
Tha nk you, Deepa k.
This is the sa me electric
pole to which...
...a ma n ha d been stuck to for
15 minutes a nd still survived.
Yes. Sha mbu fell down
in this pothole...
...while returning from
work la st evening.
Beca use of this live wire
he got stuck to this pole.
And it is a mira cle tha t
he is still a live...
...a fter receiving electric shock...
...of such high volta ge for
15 mins. Consecutively.
So let's ta lk to Sha mbu who ha d
experienced this incident.
Mr. Sha mbu, how do you feel?
I feel good.
Tell our viewers how
did you feel when...
...such high volta ge shocks were
pa ssing through your body?
Ca II for technica I sna g
in ten seconds.
Na ina, repea t the question.
Tell us how did you feel when...
...high volta ge shocks were
pa ssing through you?
Grea t! I felt very good.
Now people ca II you
'The Electric ma n'.
How does tha t feel?
Very good.
- Cut it!
Wha t is it, now?
We'll do it a ga in in five minutes!
Give him something to sa y.
He seems to like everything.
He gets drunk a nd fa lls down.
The other da y we both
dra nk together...
...a nd we both fell together
in the gutter but...
...nobody ca red then. Now look
a t him, he ha s become fa mous.
Get me out of here.
They bea t me up everyda y.
Two guys ca me in my cell
yesterda y a nd bea t me a II over.
You'd sa id I would be oka y
if I turned Informer.
But look wha t ha ppened?
I wa s put to rot in here a nd you
were tra nsferred to the ATS.
Arif, either get me out
of this pla ce or kill me.
But don't lea ve me here.
My fa mily is threa tened everyda y.
The consta ble who is supposed to
protect my fa mily ha ra sses my sister.
I ha ve hea rd tha t you a re going to
get tra nsferred somewhere else?
I hea rd it too.
If the depa rtment doesn't ca re
a bout you why will it ca re for me?
Ca n I get a cup of tea?
- Right a wa y sir.
You wa nt to go to the hospita I?
- Sure.
Sta y there for some da ys. I
will ta ke ca re of the rest.
You trust me, don't you?
- I ha ve only you to trust.
Tha nk you, brother.
Who is on duty a t your house?
- Ba dge number 1275.
Sir, I feel tha t I a m
being ta rgeted...
...beca use I belong to
the minority group.
Minority! Mr. Aja y Kha nna, how ca n
you belong to a minority group?
The Kha n's a re in ma jority
in our film industry.
It's just Mr. Amita bh, Abhishek
a nd I on the other side.
Tha t's true.
Sir.
Mr. Kha nna, this is sub-inspector
Ja i Singh.
He will ha ndle your ca se. Be rest
a ssured, we will cra ck this soon.
Sir, I just hope nothing
will ha ppen to me.
C'mon! You a re a hero.
Does a nything ever ha ppen to
our heroes in our films?
Sometimes it does.
Just in ca se a nything
ha ppens to you then...
...I a ssure you tha t we
will not spa re them.
Sir, wha t a re you?
Rela x! Go to work. Nothing
will ha ppen to you.
Tha nk you sir. Tha nk you very much.
It is oka y.
My brother. My brother.
Tha nk you! Tha nk you.
Tha nk you, sir.
- Yea h, mention not.
These a re our heroes. One phone
ca II a nd he gets a stoma ch a che
Some kids from Sha nti na ga r
a re pla ying a pra nk on him.
Pa twa rdha n knows them.
Ask him to stop them or else he
will be wa sting our time needlessly.
Right sir.
Sha mbu, who is responsible
for this incident?
I feel they did a good job by
putting up a n electric pole.
But they should not ha ve
dug this hole.
The government should think
twice before digging...
...tha t a common ma n like me
ca n fa II into this pothole.
Look a round! Toda y there
a re potholes everywhere.
I mea n a re there potholes in the
city or this city is in potholes?
This government should ta ke
responsibility for these potholes.
So wha t do you feel? Why does
the government do such things?
The government likes to dig.
So this wa s Mr. Sha mbu a.k.a.
Electric ma n who...
...ha s given Dea th itself
a very big shock.
This is Na ina Roy with ca mera ma n
Ra j for UTV news.
Sir... sir, why a re you hitting me?
Sir, why a re you hitting me?
Yes, tell me!
- Don't get a nnoyed but...
...I just found out tha t
I don't ha ve...
...some ingredients to
ma ke the rice pudding.
You know very well
Isha a n loves rice pudding.
While coming home bring
some a lmonds, ra isins...
All right I will bring
a II those things.
Don't forget to buy those toma toes.
- No I won't.
I a m sorry. Are you a ngry with me?
Just a bit. But then, I ha ve the
whole city to vent it out.
When will you come ba ck?
Around 7 o'clock.
Come ba ck a nd we'll ta lk.
- Yes.
The government should think
twice before digging...
...tha t a common ma n like me
ca n fa II into this pothole.
Look a round! Toda y there
a re potholes everywhere.
I mea n a re there potholes in the
city or this city is in potholes?
This government should ta ke
responsibility for these potholes.
Sir, plea se forgive me.
Hello.
- Is it Commissioner Pra ka sh Ra thod?
Who's this?
Mr. Ra thod, don't interrupt
a nd just listen.
I ha ve pla nted bombs a t 5 different
loca tions in the city.
All these bombs will
explode a t 6.30 pm.
But this ca n be a voided.
I will ca II you up 30 minutes la ter...
...with my dema nds a nd I wa nt to ta lk
or negotia te with only one person.
Until then you ca n decide
on tha t person.
Hello!
Find out who ha d ca lled
on my mobile just a while ba ck.
Ja i, where is the chief minister?
Hello.
- Miss Na ina Roy?
Yes, who is this?
It doesn't ma tter.
I just wa nted to a sk you...
...whether you a re interested
in some serious news.
Wha t? Is this some kind...
- Just a nswer me Na ina.
This is big. Are you interested?
Yes or no?
Yes.
Then come to the Mumba i Police
hea dqua rters with your ca mera ma n.
This is going to be the most
importa nt da y in your life.
I will ca II you a ga in.
Ra j!
I know this is a n unknown number.
Keep trying. I wa nt to know
tha t number within 5 minutes.
And a sk Kha tri to ta p my mobile
phone immedia tely. Oka y.
Yes Tiwa ri, I a m putting him
on the line. Right a wa y.
Sir, it's Tiwa ri.
Mr. Tiwa ri!
- Yes, Mr. Pra ka sh, tell me.
Where is the CM?
He is in Ba ndra to a ttend
a n importa nt meeting.
Put Mr. Pa til on the line.
Mr. Pa til is a Iso in a meeting.
Tell me, wha t is the ma tter?
It is a very minor thing.
I ca nnot bother you with it.
Put Pa til on the line.
Sir, I hope you understood.
Sir, he wa nts to ta lk to you.
Excuse me.
- Oka y.
Yes, Mr. Pra ka sh.
I don't know how but come to
my office within 15 minutes.
But... - Within 15 minutes.
It's a n emergency.
Ja i, tell Chouha n, Ra mesh a nd Aa ka sh
to come into the WAR Room.
Right sir.
Sir. It is a prepa id mobile number.
It is registered to
one Jignesh Sheth.
He lives in Ma la d. I ha ve informed
Ma la d police sta tion.
This number is unrea cha ble
right now. - Oka y.
Attention guys!
This ma tter should not
get out of this room.
Does a nyone of you wa nts to
ca II a nybody or wa rn a nyone?
No sir!
We ha ve just 4 hours left.
Chouha n, ta lk to Abba s a t intelligence
a nd find out wha t they ha ve.
Tell them you need this informa tion
for verifica tion.
Yes sir!
Va tka r, find out from
our sources whether...
...there ha s been a ny movement
in a ny terrorist module.
Get me a ny informa tion on explosives
being ta ken in a nd out of the city.
Get in touch with your informers.
Right sir.
Aa ka sh, we need to tra ce
the ca II the next time.
Put your best men on the job.
Yes sir!
Mr. Ra thod, how a re you?
- I a m fine. And you?
Fine. Tell me.
Just a while ba ck I received
a ca II on my cell phone.
One ma n...
Oh god. Excuse me.
It could a Iso be a cra nk ca II.
We ca n't ta ke a ny cha nces.
Where is the CM?
He is on his wa y.
Hello!
Yes, Mr. Ra thod. Who is
going to ta lk to me?
Mr. Roy. He will be here soon.
Until then you ca n ta lk to me.
I will only ta lk to the person who
ha s the a uthority to ta ke decisions.
I will ca II you a ga in
in five minutes.
By the wa y let me remind you tha t
you a re wa sting your own time.
Ta ke my a dvice. You shouldn't
buy time on this.
Too short to tra ce. But this is not
the sa me number a s the previous one.
Excuse me sir.
There wa s a ca II from
Ma la d police sta tion.
Nobody na med Jignesh Sheth
lives a t tha t a ddress.
Do one thing, tell Sola nki to
a lert a II the police sta tions.
Sir, the CM is on the line.
Good a fternoon, sir.
- Good a fternoon.
Who is this Roy?
- Nobody.
Who is negotia ting with
him from our side?
Sir, you will. We will pa tch
his ca II to you from here.
Why? - Beca use you ha ve the a uthority
a nd you know how to negotia te.
There is a lot of difference between
giving a Speech a nd Negotia ting.
This is not a politica I ra lly.
Wha t a bout Pa til or Tiwa ri?
Oh my God!
Pra ka sh, I ha ve never seen you
running a wa y from responsibility.
There is a rea son for it.
If this ma n is telling
the truth then to stop him...
...we require a person with
unlimited a uthority.
There shouldn't be a ny
red ta pe or protocol.
He would need a bsolute
a nd complete freedom.
He should not be questioned
a bout a nything.
And I know tha t this is not
possible a nd tha t's why...
...I wa s running a wa y from
responsibility Sir.
Pa til, this opera tion will be
hea ded by Pra ka sh Ra thod.
I don't wa nt a ny compla ints
from him. Do you understa nd?
I'll be there soon.
Yes, sir. Should we
inform the center?
This is our problem a nd
we ha ve to solve it.
Oka y sir.
Come on guys, ba ck to work,
everyone.
Excuse me.
- Yea h.
Hello.
- Mr. Ra thod?
Mr. Roy won't be here. I will
negotia te instea d of him.
How ca n he come there
if he doesn't exist?
Wha t do you wa nt?
Lbra him Kha n, lqla k Ahmed, Moha mmed
Za heer a nd Khursheed La la.
Who a re these guys?
You yourself ha d ca ught two of them.
And the ATS got the other two.
I hope it is not difficult.
Why would it be? We a re used to it.
First we put our lives a t
sta ke a nd ca tch them a nd...
...then when a phone ca II
comes we set them free.
You will do the sa me thing toda y.
They a II a re in different pla ces
right now. I'll ca II you in a n hour.
Till then it is yourjob to get
them together a t one pla ce.
On whose beha If a re you doing this?
Wha t is the na me of
your orga niza tion?
Do you suspect tha t this
is a cra nk ca II? -
I do.
Mr. Ra thod, you must
know by now tha t...
...Jignesh Sheth ha d died
in the la st bomb bla st.
The next number belonged
to Sa nja y Singh...
...who ha d died three months ba ck.
The current number tha t you
will tra ce belongs to...
...Sha bbir Ahmed who ha s a Iso
died a long wa y ba ck.
Any Tom, Dick a nd Ha rry ca n do this.
Yes I a gree. But a ny Tom,
Dick a nd Ha rry...
...ca nnot blow a wa y
the police sta tion...
...which is just opposite
your Police hea dqua rters.
Wha t do you mea n?
It mea ns I ha ve a Iso pla nted a
bomb in the police sta tion...
...opposite your hea dqua rters
just to prove...
...my mettle a nd your helplessness.
You ha ve 20 minutes to
find it. So go find it.
Or else a n hour la ter I ma y
ha ve to ta lk to someone else.
Mr. Pra ka sh, ca n we go
out for ha If a n hour.
Ja i!
- Yes sir!
Are you a fra id?
- No sir.
Are you ma rried?
- Two yea rs a go.
Do you ha ve a kid?
- I ha ve a 3-month-old da ughter.
Wha t ha ppens if you die?
- I don't ca re.
I wa nt tha t bomb found within
ten minutes. - You'll get it, sir.
Give me your ra dio. - Sir.
Hello.
Na ina Roy, someone
ha s pla nted a bomb...
...in the police sta tion opposite
the hea dqua rters.
I thought you'd be interested.
Oh God!
Rela x guys! This ma n wa nts
us to find the bomb.
He wa nts us to ta ke him seriously.
He wa nts us to find it.
We just ha ve one hour. I don't
wa nt to ta lk to this ma n a ga in.
Sir, Chouha n is on the line.
Chouha n, tell me.
Sir, the intelligence ha s
no informa tion a bout this.
Tha t's consistent.
Chouha n, step up security a t a irports,
ra il sta tions a nd bus depots.
Sea rch everything a nd everyone.
Send them in ba tches of 4
to the multiplexes a s well.
I wa nt you to cover up a s
much ground a s possible.
If someone a sks tell them
it is just a police drill...
...or tell them it's the CM's orders.
Get on it now!
All units a lert, sir.
Deshmukh, where is my bomb squa d?
Aa ka sh, ca II up Arif. I
wa nt him here a. S. A. P.
And I wa nt a n upda te on lbra him
Kha n, lqla k Ahmed...
...Moha mma d Za heer
a nd Khursheed La la.
You've got ten minutes.
- Yes sir.
Then send them here!
Bomb squa d! Come in!
Ha s nobody seen Ba bura o?
Yea h Mha tre, come in.
Copy tha t.
Wha t is it?
- Sir, it is RDX.
Come here! A bomb wa s
pla ced right under nose!
Wha t the hell were you doing?
Who is the shift in-cha rge?
Sir, there wa s a shift cha nge
just ha If a n hour a go.
I don't know a nything.
Find him in 5 minutes a nd
send him to me. - Oka y sir.
Sir! We ha ve loca ted the bomb.
It is RDX.
He ha d pla nned to trigger
it with a cell phone.
Good.
Sir, plea se come this wa y.
I ha ve solid informa tion.
There ha s been a pull-up
from the underworld.
He ha d supplied 6 kgs of
RDX couple of da ys ba ck.
He ha s not opened his mouth yet.
On threa tening him he
sa id he ha s ta ken...
...his pa inkillers
just this morning.
Tha t's a new one.
Sir, I don't know a nything!
Did I a sk you a nything?
Nobody ha s confirmed this
informa tion but...
...suddenly there is a lot of
a ctivity in the police sta tion.
You ca n see the bomb squa d
a nd the sniffer dogs here.
They ha ve just come out.
But we ha ve been denied
a ny informa tion a bout it.
We would like to inform our
viewers once a ga in tha t...
...we ha d received informa tion...
...a bout the bomb via
a telephone ca II.
Seems tha t the bomb ha s
been found a nd diffused.
We ha ve not received
a ny confirma tion yet.
But we will keep trying.
From Mumba i this is Na ina Roy with
ca mera ma n Ra j for UTV news. - Over.
I wa nt the forensic report
immedia tely in the WAR room.
Sir! - Oka y sir.
Tha nk you.
Mha tre come in. Copy.
Sir, the Psycho ha s a rrived.
Someone's going to die toda y.
Hello.
- Are you busy?
Yes. Not rea lly.
We ha ve rea ched here sa fely.
How is mom?
- She is fine.
Give it to me.
Wha t is the ma tter?
Are you worried a bout something?
Not a t a II. - I'll ca II
you before lea ving.
Oka y. Ta ke ca re. Bye.
There wa s no direct
conta ct with me.
I only ga ve the delivery.
I got a messa ge to deliver
tha t ba g to Ra fiq.
He wa s Ra fiq's customer.
I a sked Ra fiq who he wa s.
He sa id, your pla ce is behind
a nd a sked me to shut up.
Where ca n I find Ra fiq?
Sir, I don't know.
If I ha d known I would tell you.
Believe me. Sir, I would...
Bohri Ma rket. 4th La ne.
Where a re you these da ys?
I a m with the ATS.
You ha d got me tra nsferred.
Yes. Arif, I wa nt tha t ma n a nd
the informa tion tha t he ha s.
Va tka r will tell you where
to find him. Don't kill him.
I just need the informa tion.
Oka y sir.
- Oka y.
Yes.
- Sir, the bomb ha s been diffused.
Who wa s on duty?
- Pra sha nt.
Tell him to go home. He will receive
his termina tion letter tomorrow.
Tell Ka ila sh to ta ke over.
The media is here. UTV news.
Bring them upsta irs.
- Right sir.
Ibra him Kha n. He ha s links
with the Al-Qa eda.
He wa s hea d-of-opera tions
in India since 92.
This is his designa tion
on their website.
He ha s sta rted 45 ma dra sa s
in the country...
...where little kids a re ta ught
the mea ning of Jiha d.
On his ca pture they will
be wea kened a nd if...
...he is set free then they will
be completely rejuvena ted.
This is their second
a ttempt to free him.
He is extremely da ngerous.
Lqla k Ahmed. Al Qa eda a ga in.
Right ha nd of lbra him Kha n.
He is a former ISI a gent.
The theory is tha t...
...when you ha d na bbed him
he wa nted to get ca ught.
So tha t it would be ea sy
to free lbra him Kha n.
He wa s directly or indirectly
involved in a II...
...the terrorists a tta cks in India
in the la st three yea rs.
He is equa lly da ngerous if not more.
Moha mma d Za heer. He is the number
2 a gent of La ska r in India.
He is a former ISI a s well
a s former Al Qa eda member.
He wa s a softwa re engineer.
Due to systema tic bra inwa shing
he went to Pa kista n.
From there he went to Afgha nista n.
He a cquired his tra ining over there.
He ha s designed a lot
of websites for them.
One of his websites is ca lled
www.india kita ba a hi.com
Very ba sic but very effective.
It registered record number
of hits the da y it opened.
He is in our C-Zone hospita I
since la st week.
He ha d compla ined of chest pa ins.
Khursheed La la. He is a n a rms pimp.
He is not connected to just one
orga niza tion but with a II of them.
If you need a rms a nd explosives
then this is your Guy.
He will supply a ny
qua ntity you wa nt.
No ma tter it is 1993 or 2006.
La la is behind the ba rs or free.
He doesn't lea ve a tra il.
Sir, you ma y remember tha t
even when you ha d a rrested him...
...we ha d only found
a blue-print of...
...the Mumba i city a nd
a revolver on him.
Very soon he will be out on ba il.
Sir, Here is a specula tion.
Look a t this. We don't know his
na me but he is everywhere.
He ha s succeeded to
rema in out of sight.
Our intelligence a gencies ha ve
no informa tion a bout him.
There a re only rumours.
Some sa y he is their CEO a nd others
sa y he is the chief stra tegist.
Sir, he is one a mong the crowd.
Even his wife doesn't know
wha t he rea lly does.
This ma n could be behind this ca II.
He ma y belong to La ska r, Al
Qa eda or some other outfit.
We don't know whether he
is in the country or not.
There must be a couple of people
with him in this opera tion.
They ha ve a Irea dy ta rgeted the
stock excha nge...
...buses a nd loca I tra ins.
I suspect this time they
will go a step further.
Tha t they ha ve come so close
to the police hea dqua rters...
...ha s business written a II over it.
Aa ka sh, this ma n is in the city.
We ha ve to ca tch him.
Sir, wha t should we do
a bout the other four?
We a re a lwa ys two steps behind
them a nd if they a re freed...
Let them be where they a re.
It doesn't ma ke a ny sense
to free La la now...
...he is going to get free a s is.
And by doing this La la will be
rega rded a certified terrorist.
Ma ybe they need La la right now.
Ma ybe.
Uncle! Three tea.
Hey, send money to me.
When did you receive
the first ca II?
Ok Alright then you a nd
your ca mera ma n will rema in...
...in custody until you come
out with the truth.
He ha d ca lled up a t
a round 2 pm a nd...
...he ha d a sked me to come here.
He ha d a Iso sa id tha t
this would be...
...the most importa nt da y of my life.
He is using you.
He is wa tching our situa tion
a nd our pa nic Live on TV.
You a re his bloody eyes.
Sir, he is a round 50. Ta II
ma n. Wea rs a specta cle.
He looks like a clerk.
There is a n under
construction building...
...in Ma la d west behind Prita m
na ga r. Om constructions.
I ha d delivered the
goods on the 12th floor.
Va tka r! - Yes sir. - Ta ke him a wa y.
Hello. Sir, this is Arif.
Yes I got it.
There is a n under construction
building in Ma la d.
Pa tka r is bringing Ra fiq
to the hea dqua rters.
Should I send Ja i?
- There's no need.
I will na b him a nd get
him to spea k to you.
Wha t wa s your na me a ga in?
Na ina.
Na ina, I wa nt you to do me a fa vour.
Sir, until you don't tell me
everything I ca n't help you.
Oka y. Come here.
This ma tter should be only
between you a nd me.
Three. Two. One. Go.
We ha ve just received
informa tion tha t...
...four terrorists whose
na mes a re lbra him Kha n...
...lqla k Ahmed, Moha mma d Za heer
a nd Khursheed La la...
...a re being shifted to
some other loca tion.
The police sa ys it is beca use
of security rea sons.
Right now we ha ve Senior
Inspector Ja i Singh...
...who will give us full informa tion
a bout this ma tter.
Wha t is the rea son behind shifting
these four to some other loca tion?
There a re some security rea sons.
We ha ve orders to do so.
But why such a n order?
We ha ve received orders to do so.
Ca n you tell us whether there is
a ny threa t to them a nd from whom?
It is beca use of some
security rea sons...
...tha t we ha ve received
orders to shift them
As you ca n see, the police is not
giving us a ny further informa tion.
And they a re trying to
a void our questions...
...by ca lling it a security rea son.
From Mumba i this is Na ina Roy with
ca mera ma n Ra j for UTV news.
Cut it!
Sir, plea se don't do this a ga in. My
wife wa tches the news cha nnels.
Tha t wa s good Ja i.
Tha nk you Na ina.
Once a ga in India a pproa ched America
with rega rds to Pa kista n issue.
The government is spending
crores of rupees to sa ve...
...but due to lega I rea sons,
they a re...
Now, for the la test news let's move
to our correspondent Na ina Roy...
Wha t is the rea son behind shifting
these four to some other loca tion?
There a re some security rea sons.
We ha ve orders to do so.
But why such a n order?
We ha ve received orders to do so.
Arif, tell me.
Sir, there is nobody here. But
he wa nted us to come here.
There a re ta gs of 'Do
not disturb' in here.
Come ba ck.
- Yes sir.
Ja i
We ha ve to shift these four
terrorists to a single loca tion.
Sta rt the process.
- Sir.
Mr. Ra thod, Time is running out.
How much longer a re we going
to hide this from the public?
Wha t should we tell the public?
We ha ve no other choice
tha n to ca tch him.
He is regula rly monitoring
us through Na ina Roy.
If we sound a n a lert
then he will know...
Hello!
- Hello.
Yes tell me.
Sir, this is Sa pna from HDFC
Ba nk's credit ca rd division.
We a re issuing you
a credit ca rd for free.
We ha ve a new scheme which benefits
you with persona I loa n, housing lone...
I a m not interested.
Don't ever ca II me.
If you don't wa nt it then sa y so.
Why a re you getting rude Sir?
Hello.
Tha nk you very much.
It's a II right. Wha t
else do you need?
Money! Priva te pla ne! Wha t else?
No tha nks. I ca n a rra nge
for those things.
Just put these four men in a va n
a nd bring them to me.
There is new strip on runwa y
number 4 a t the Juhu Avia tion Ba se.
It ha s not been opened for use yet.
I wa nt these men brought
there a t exa ctly 5 o'clock.
Only two officers should
a ccompa ny them.
Both should ca rry cell phones
with loudspea ker fa cility.
Beca use I will need confirma tion
tha t they a re oka y.
I should a Iso tell you tha t this
a rea is a Irea dy rigged so...
...no snipers, no comma ndoes
a nd no surprises plea se.
No funny business.
I wa nt to know something.
Ask a wa y.
You a nd your orga niza tion a re
under wha t misconception?
You a re a lwa ys hiding
from the police.
Why don't you come in the open a nd
finish this ma tter once a nd for a II?
Mr. Ra thod, we a re cowa rds.
Are you ha ppy now?
Don't wa ste your time in trying
to get me a ggra va ted.
There is a fa ce behind every voice.
I don't ha ve a fa ce.
Tha t's wha t you think.
- No! I know it.
Wha t is the gua ra ntee tha t you will
tell me the loca tion of the bombs?
Gua ra ntee! Do you think I
a m selling you a product?
No. If I ha d thought so I would
not a sk you this question.
Thousa nds of lives a re a t sta ke.
Do you ha ve a ny other choice
tha n to trust me?
I will ca II you a ga in a t 5.
Aa ka sh, tell me.
We ha ve a multiple tra ce.
Mulund, Sa nta cruz, Ka ra chi,
Singa pore a nd South Africa.
This is unique. The ca II
is bounced off...
...a nd ma nipula ted without
being disconnected...
...from different sim ca rds a nd
la ndlines of different loca tions.
The number switches to
a nother every minute.
This is only possible if you route
your phone through a system.
Whoever is doing this
is a very tra ined ma n?
So you ca n't tra ce him?
Sir, to do this we need some
other kind of a n expert.
For exa mple.
- We need a ha cker.
Then get one. Check the booking
list of Juhu Avia tion.
Find which priva te pla ne ha s
been booked by a nd for whom.
Yes, sir. - Sir, there is
a sub-inspector outside.
He ha s seen the ma n.
Sir, I remember very well. He
ha d a bla ck ba g with him.
He ha d come to file a report
a bout his missing wa llet.
Wha t were you doing there?
Sir, there wa s so much security
wha t else could I do?
This is his number a nd a ddress.
I ha d tried his number. Am getting
a, 'does not exist messa ge.'
I ha ve a sked the Boriva li police
to verify the a ddress.
This is not his a ddress.
He is not such a fool.
Ta ke him to a sketch a rtist.
Ma ke his sketch a nd show him.
Where is Ra fiq?
- He is in Room number 12.
Show the sketch to Ra fiq a nd
verify it. - Right sir.
Hello.
I wa nt you to go to the ma in ga te
of Juhu Avia tion a t exa ctly 5 o'clock.
No.
Excuse me! I didn't hea r tha t.
You a re using me.
If you a re not interested then
you should've told me before.
There is no dea rth
of people like you.
I a m indirectly helping you.
I a m being pa to some...
Come on! Come on!
Don't fla tter yourself, Na ina.
If in a cricket ma tch between
India a nd Pa kista n...
...lndia loses then nobody
bla mes the sports cha nnels.
This is not a cricket ma tch!
Yes or no!
I ha ve a dozen phone
numbers with me.
There a re a lot of news
hungry people out there.
Yes or no!
Yes.
Good. Be a t the ma in ga te of
Juhu Avia tion a t 5 o'clock.
Pra ka sh, wha t is the pla n of a ction?
People a re on it. But until we
don't ha ve a brea k through...
...we ha ve to do wha t he sa ys.
This is ridicules! La w a nd order
ha s become a mere bysta nder.
Pra ka sh, why a ren't we a ble
to do a nything a bout it?
We ha ve such a big force, we ha ve
the intelligence burea u...
...we ha ve RAW a nd the ATS.
Why do we a lwa ys become
so helpless?
We ca n't involve the media
or sound a n a lert.
I just ca n't believe this. We
ha ve become just useless.
Sir, we a re doing our best.
But your best isn't good enough.
I think we should ca II
in the a rmy a nd the...
They won't be of a ny help.
Sir!
- Tell me.
I ha ve hea rd tha t ma n. I think wha t
Mr. Pra ka sh is doing is right.
Instea d of questioning his decisions
it would be better if we help him.
And he is competent to
dea I with this crisis.
Which two officers a re going
to a ccompa ny them?
Arif Kha n a nd Ja i Singh.
Pra ka sh, you ha ve senior
experienced officers a nd you a re...
You ha ve Sola nki...
- Plea se trust me.
Pra ka sh, there should not be a ny
bomb bla sts in Mumba i toda y.
There won't be a ny bomb bla sts.
I don't wa nt to ha nd over
the four men to him.
Tha t I will try.
Excuse me. Yes, tell me.
Ok.
Sir, the Boriva li a ddress is wrong.
There is no such building
with tha t na me.
Where is Arif?
- He is a t the a rmory.
Whose fa ce did you first
see when you woke up?
My own.
I a m not surprised.
Are you rea dy?
- Yes sir!
From here you will go
directly to TS Mills.
The four men will be ha nded
over to you over there.
The Specia I Ta sk Force is picking
them up from their current loca tions.
Here a re the tra nsfer orders.
Ibra him Kha n. - Let's go.
He will ma ke a conference ca II.
There is a loudspea ker
fa cility in this phone.
You ca n listen to our conversa tion.
There a re three routes
to rea ch Juhu Avia tion.
You will ta ke the quickest one
which is by the highwa y.
There will a Iso be driver who will
drop a II of you there. - Yes sir!
I don't think they will
ma ke a rescue a ttempt.
Neither do I think they will
risk a public shootout.
There is a da nger to their
lives in doing it.
This is not a pre-pla nned
opera tion. It's a n extempore!
So, tha t's it guys. Just keep
your cool. All the best.
And come over to my pla ce in the
evening. We'll ha ve a drink together.
Sir!
- Oka y.
Ja i!
- Sir.
After everything is over
ma ybe you ha ve to...
...do something... a bout Arif.
You know wha t I mea n.
Understood sir.
Who is this kid?
Sir, his na me is Anuj.
He is a ha cker.
He helps us very often
to cra ck cyber crimes.
Is he tha t qua lified?
He is a college drop out but...
- Anuj!
Do you understa nd wha t this equipment
a nd this setup is a II a bout?
No sir. All this equipment
is outda ted.
You a re still using NCC
3423 models while...
...the S-series ha s been la unched
three months ba ck.
I need some time.
Ca n you ha ndle it?
Hey ba be! Yea h, I a m running
a little la te honey!
Will ca tch you in ha If a n hour!
Oka y. Love you. See you.
Women! Sorry, wha t were you sa ying?
Ca n you ha ndle the job?
Definitely. I a m a
drop out by choice.
Hello. - Oka y sir.
Yes sir.
Get in touch with Chouha n.
Send this sketch to...
...every police sta tion a nd
every a gency by fa x or ema il.
Next check our records.
And then get in touch with...
...the Interpol a nd the FBI.
I wa nt a ny informa tion on this ma n.
Yes sir. - Ba bu, wa it here
for the verifica tion.
Sir.
- Wha t is the sta tus?
We a re on schedule.
Any problem?
- Not a t a II, sir.
Ca II me up when you rea ch there.
- Yes sir.
Wha t is your na me?
- I don't need to tell you.
You a re right.
My friend!
- Wha t?
Wha t do you think
is ha ppening to us?
Lbra him bha i, looking a t
their sca red fa ces...
...I feel we a re going to get freed.
And I a Iso think...
Fire! It reminds me of my youth.
I wa s a Iso like you. Too stubborn
to be a fra id of dea th.
I wa s six yea rs old when my fa ther
got into a n enmity with a few men.
These men kidna pped
me from the school.
They a sked for a ra nsom
in excha nge of my life.
My fa ther pa id the ra nsom.
But they were still greedy.
They bea t me up. I wa s a lmost dea d.
When they got tired they tied a
rope to my leg a nd hung me on a tree.
I ca lled out to them. One
of them looked ba ck.
I screa med tha t if you ha ve to then
a t lea st ha ng me to a ma ngo tree.
He sta rted to la ugh.
He got me down...
...pa tted me on my hea d
a nd sent me home.
I lived.
Four yea rs la ter I killed them by
ha nging them to the sa me tree.
Ca n we kill this guy right here?
Yes!
We a re on our wa y.
Where a re you?
At the ra ilwa y sta tion a nd a bout
to the ca tch the tra in.
I don't know why but there is too
much checking a t the sta tions.
It's just a drill. How is Ka ja I?
Ka ja I is sleeping. Where a re you?
- I a m outdoors.
We will rea ch home before you.
Oka y.
- I will ha ng up now.
Anu...
- I love you too.
I will ca II you when I
get home. Oka y? Bye.
Bye.
Come on!
Arif... - Yes sir.
Sir, we a re there.
Sta y put. I will ca II ba ck.
Sta nd properly.
Hello. - Mr. Ra thod.
Did they rea ch there?
Yes.
I would like to spea k to them.
Wha t is the na me of your officer?
- Arif Kha n.
Wha t ha ppened?
- Nothing.
Hello. - Arif, put the
phone of loudspea ker mode...
...someone wa nts to spea k to you.
- Yes sir.
Arif is on the line. Spea k to him.
Arif, I wa nt to spea k to my friends.
They a re listening. Spea k up.
Greetings Mr. Kha n.
- Greetings to you.
Are you sa fe?
- Yes I a m.
I ha ve been ordered to find out you
guys a re rea I a nd not imposters.
And to find if the police ha s not
ha tched a conspira cy to fool us.
Tha t's why you will tell me...
...your na me a nd your
initia Is one by one.
No need to go into the deta ils.
Just a hint will do.
Ibra him Kha n. Mumba i 93. I a m proud.
Lqla k Ahmed. Guja ra t
2002. I a m proud.
Moha mma d Za heer. Mumba i
2006. I a m proud.
Khursheed La la. 92 to
Your initia Is a re indeed wonderful.
Arif, put the phone on ha ndset
mode a nd give it to Kha n.
Hello. - Mr. Kha n, did they
give you a ny injection...
...or did they ma ke
you ea t a nything?
No. Just tha t we a re ha ndcuffed.
They will be unlocked soon. Give
the phone ba ck to the officer.
Spea k up.
Arif, there a re two
benches a hea d of you.
You will lea ve my four
men over there.
You will free their ha nds
a nd without looking ba ck...
...you a nd your friend will
wa lk a wa y from there.
You will get in your va n a nd go
ba ck to the police sta tion.
You ha ve only ten minutes,
sta rting now.
I don't ha ve to remind you tha t
if you do something foolish...
...then thousa nds of
lives will be lost.
Mr. Ra thod, I will ca II you
a fter Arif lea ves a nd...
...give you the exa ct
loca tions of the bombs.
Do a s he sa ys.
Yes sir.
FBI, Interpol or our Intelligence.
Neither of them ha ve a ny
informa tion a bout this ma n.
We ha ve no choice. We ca n kill
these guys some other time.
Pra ka sh, how ca n we justify
their disa ppea ra nce?
There wa s a sna g in the
security so they esca ped.
You ca n suspend me over this.
Pra ka sh, you a re... - Excuse
me sir. It wa s a loca I ca II.
If he ca lls the next time I ca n
point out his exa ct loca tion.
Are you sure?
Definitely. He is good.
But not the best.
Oka y.
Arif, remove his ha ndcuffs.
This is not right.
If they esca pe a nd...
...they don't tell us
a bout the bombs then...
Arif, it's Mr. Ra thod's orders.
No Ja i. Free the other three.
Let's ta ke him with us.
We will lea ve him
only when we know...
...the exa ct loca tions of the bombs.
I will ca II up Mr. Ra thod.
I will not relea se him
even if sir a sks me to.
Arif, a re you cra zy? Someone
might be wa tching us.
Then he will ca II us when
he sees us lea ve.
Arif!
- Don't a rgue! Let's go!
- You a re ma king a mista ke.
Wha t did you sa y?
You a re ma king a big mista ke.
I like to ma ke mista kes.
Come on!
- Let me go.
Wha t will they do to lbra him bha i?
Nothing. We will get
him freed la ter.
Khursheed bha i, wha t
should we do next?
We will wa it. Someone will
come to ta ke us a wa y.
Arif!
- Wha t is it now?
I ca n hea r a phone ringing.
Ta ke a look.
Pick it up.
Let me go! Let me go!
Let me go! Wa it!
Ta ke him.
Now give me the loca tions
of the bombs.
First ca II up Arif a nd
give me his sta tus.
I wa nt to listen to his response.
Hold him. Hello.
Arif, wha t is the progress?
Sir, I a m confused.
Something else is going on here.
Mea ns? - The pla n wa s not to
free them but to kill them.
A bomb wa s pla nted in tha t a rea.
As soon a s we left,
the bomb exploded.
Both the benches were rigged.
It mea ns, a II four of them...
No. I ha d left only Za heer,
lqla k a nd La la over there.
To secure the informa tion
a bout the bombs...
...I ha d kept lbra him with me.
Yes he is with us. He is a live.
Wha t is ha ppening?
Arif is right, Mr. Ra thod!
Arif, put the phone
of loudspea ker mode.
I wa nt lbra him to listen
to wha t I a m going to sa y.
I did not wa nt to sa ve lbra him
Kha n, lqla k Ahmed...
...Moha mma d Za heer a nd
Khursheed La la but...
...I wa nted to kill them.
And in fa ct you will complete
my job, toda y a nd right now.
Sorry, I did not understa nd you.
Mr. Ra thod, wha t do you do
if a cockroa ch enters you house?
You do not ma ke it your pet,
you just kill it.
These pests were spoiling my house
a nd now I wa nt to clea n it.
Who a re you?
I a m someone who is a fra id to get
into a bus or a tra in these da ys.
I a m someone whose wife
thinks is going to wa r...
...while I a m a ctua lly
going to my work.
She is a fra id tha t I ma y not return.
She ca lls up every two hours.
To find if I ha d my tea.
To find if I ha ve lunched.
Actua lly she wa nts to find out
whether I a m still a live.
I a m someone who sometimes gets
stuck in the ra in or in the bla sts.
I a m someone who suspects the
person ca rrying a rosa ry.
I a m a Iso the one who is a fra id
to grow his bea rd a nd wea r a ca p.
If I buy a shop I a m a fra id
to choose a na me a s...
...someone might see the na me
a nd burn it during the riots.
No ma tter which two pa rties
a re fighting...
...I a m the first one to get killed.
You must ha ve seen a crowd.
Choose a person from it.
I a m tha t person.
I a m just the stupid common
wa nting to clea n his house.
How did this common
ma n suddenly wa ke up?
And tha t too with six kgs of RDX?
Ha s tha t got you worried now?
Do you wa nt me to live my life
a nd die every moment of it?
Mr. Ra thod, this did not
ha ppen a II of a sudden!
I just did not get
the time to do it.
In the process of ea rning my da ily
brea d this work got neglected.
But it's better la te tha n never.
Tha t rema ining cockroa ch
will a Iso die toda y.
Why just these four? There
a re others a s well.
I drew a lottery a nd
I got their na mes.
Are you trying to sa y tha t
if we don't kill lbra him...
...then you will kill thousa nds
of innocent people?
Sooner or la ter they a re
going to die a nd...
...people like lbra him
will kill them.
The la st time they were
killed in a tra in...
...this time it will
be somewhere else.
They will keep on killing until
we lea rn to give a solid reply.
Who a re you?
- Wha t do you mea n?
I mea n a re you a Hindu or a Muslim?
This ha s nothing to
do with my religion.
There is.
I told you, I a m just
a stupid common ma n.
Stupid common ma n!
- Right.
Are you a fra id of getting
ca ught a nd getting killed?
Ma ybe.
Be definite. You a re or you a ren't?
- I a m.
Just remember this fea r. And
don't think you will...
...esca pe punishment by putting this
ga rb of a stupid common ma n.
The thing you a re trying to prove...
I a m not trying to prove a nything.
I just wa nt to remind you
tha t people a re very a ngry.
Plea se stop testing their pa tience.
We a re resilient by
force not by choice.
It took me just four weeks
to render you helpless.
Do you suppose the people who kill
us a re more intelligent tha n us?
Type 'bomb' in a ny internet
sea rch a nd you will get...
...hundreds of websites showing
you how to ma ke them.
All the informa tion is a ccessible
a nd tha t too for free.
Do you know a wa shing soa p
is a Iso a potentia I bomb?
I feel there is no better product
ma de for the common ma n.
The problem with us is tha t
we get used to a II this.
If one such incidence occurs we
wa tch it on a II the cha nnels...
...we send smses, we ca II up people.
We get ha ppy tha t we
a re sa fe a nd then...
...instea d of fighting a ga inst the
situa tion we sta rt to a djust with it.
But we ha ve our compulsions.
We ha ve to ma inta in a fa mily.
Tha t's why we a ppoint a government
to run the na tion.
All of you. The government, the
police force, intelligence...
...is ca pa ble of ca rrying
out this pest control.
But you a re not doing it. Instea d
you a re just supporting their...
...ca use by not doing
a nything stringent.
Why a re you not nipping
them in the bud?
It ta kes you ten yea rs to
prove a person guilty.
Don't you think this is a question
ma rk on your a bility?
All this should stop. This whole
bloody system is fla wed.
If you don't clea n up
this mess then...
...we will ha ve to do
something a bout it.
I know there will be a n imba la nce
in our civilized society.
But wha t ca n we do?
Mr. Ra thod, I a m convinced the
tra in bla sts were notjust...
...a terrorist a ctivity
but it wa s a question.
The question wa s, we a re going
to keep killing you...
...wha t ca n you do? Yes!
They've a sked us this question.
First on a frida y then they
repea ted it on tuesda y.
I a m just replying on a Wednesda y.
Your, a dd-sa lt-to-ta ste philosophy,
is a bsolutely wrong.
This is not the correct a pproa ch.
I know. But right now
I a m not concerned...
...a bout the a pproa ch
but the results.
Did someone of yours
die in these bla sts?
Why? Should I wa it until someone
close to me dies in such a di wa y?
And only then will you feel tha t
this step is justified?
If you wa nt to know then listen.
There wa s someone close
to me on tha t tra in.
A kid... must be a round 21 yea rs.
Don't know his na me.
Used to meet me everyda y in
the first cla ss compa rtment.
While getting into the tra in he
used to greet me with a hello...
...a nd I used to return the courtesy.
There were ma ny such people.
We did not know ea ch
other's na mes...
...Just knew ea ch other
through 'hellos'!
With a smile he ha d shown me...
...his enga gement ring
just a da y before.
He wa s very ha ppy.
The next da y I missed the
tra in a nd I esca ped dea th.
But he didn't.
After tha t when I went by tra in...
...there wa s nobody whom I knew.
The compa rtment wa s
full of stra ngers.
So you a re doing this
for those dea d people.
No. I a m not tha t emotiona I
a nd sentimenta I.
I a lwa ys knew wha t loss is.
I ha ve seen my rela tives die.
But this is una ccepta ble.
None of these b... pa rdon
my la ngua ge...
But none of these ba sta rds will
decide when I should die.
They a re proud of '92
a nd '93 a nd of 2006.
They a re proud of Guja ra t, Mumba i,
Delhi a nd Ma legoa n.
I a m proud of myself tha t
I a m killing such people.
I a m not a sa viour.
And I a m not doing this for
a nyone else but myself.
I only wa nt tha t when my child
goes out he should...
...tra vel without fea r on buses,
tra ins or a nywhere else.
I ca nnot understa nd you.
Tha t's beca use my rea sons a nd
dema nds a re a bit stra nge.
Ma ybe.
Be definite. Yes or no.
Yes.
If they kill 200 of
us then it is oka y...
...but if I kill only 4 of
them then it's stra nge?
This is not your fa ult.
This is wha t is expected
of a common ma n.
Live, tolera te a nd die
like a common ma n.
Ta ke yourself for exa mple till the
time you did not know who I a m...
...you were a fra id of me
a nd ta king me seriously.
And now tha t I ha ve told
you I a m a common ma n...
...you've got ba ck some
confidence in your voice.
You must be thinking this
not a terrorist but...
...just a common ma n. I
will ea sily ca tch him.
No, tha t is not so.
It better not be beca use a II the
bombs a re still where they were.
Mr. Ra thod. Arif.
Now everything depends on you two...
...whether this would be
my la st ca II or not.
Ten minutes la ter Na ina Roy will
rea ch there with her ca mera ma n.
There will a Iso be a doctor
a nd a n a mbula nce with them.
I wa nt confirmed reports on
TV tha t lbra him Kha n is dea d.
If this ha ppens then
I will immedia tely...
...tell you where the bombs a re.
But if it doesn't then you a re
responsible for wha t ha ppens next.
Arif, I'll ca II you ba ck.
- Yes sir.
Now wha t will you do?
First I will clea n my ea r. I
a m finding it ha rd to hea r.
Sir, I wa nt you to
ta ke this decision.
Do we ha ve a ny other choice
tha n to do wha t he sa ys?
No sir.
But it is wrong.
- Tha t it is.
Wha t else ca n I do? -
we ca n do nothing.
Wha t is a II this?
Child, wha t is 2 + 2?
Wha t?
Ten minutes from now you will
go to runwa y number 4 a nd...
...cover a very importa nt news.
Didn't I promise this would be...
...the most importa nt
da y of your life?
Go see for yourself.
Did you just a ddress me a s a child?
You ha ve hea rd right. Bye.
He is a tra itor! He knows nothing.
The ma tter is a bout our community.
Yours a nd mine.
It is a bout my brothers
a nd sisters a nd our home.
It is a bout our rights! If we a re
together nobody ca n ha rm us.
Didn't we tea ch the America ns
a nd British a very good lesson?
Nobody could stop us.
But you ma de a mista ke
by coming to India.
A common ma n got a
bit upset a nd now...
...not only is he stopping you
but he is killing you a s well.
I a m not a fra id to die...
I do not fea r dea th. Why a m I a live?
For a Ca use.
And for tha t ca use I a m willing
to sa crifice myself.
But then I wa nt to live
to wa ge this ba ttle.
And for my brothers a nd sisters,
my community...
Why a re you la ughing?
I see tha t you a re a fra id of dea th.
This is a n a ccident.
- Yes sir, this is a n a ccident.
I must get a deta iled report of
this a ccident by tomorrow morning.
Persona lly.
You will get it.
Sir!
- Hea ds!
Yes sir.
You should've told me first.
We don't ha ve time. Look over there.
Did you tra ce the ca II?
- I a m tra cing it.
Sir, let him go. I wa s wrong.
He's notjust good. He is the best.
Sir, I a m not sure this is the ma n.
How simila r is he?
I ca n... - Is he a t lea st
1 percent simila r?
Sir...
Deepa k, right now I a m a t the
Juhu Avia tion Ba se where...
...four terrorists were killed
while trying to esca pe.
The na mes of these terrorists
a re Khursheed La la...
...lqla k Ahmed, Moha mma d
Za heer a nd lbra him Kha n.
Na ina Roy...
Mr. Ra thod!
- Tell me.
I did not pla nt a ny other bomb.
I know tha t.
- Nice ta lking to you sir.
In this opera tion a police inspector
ha s been seriously injured.
His na me is Arif Kha n.
You ca n see him right
now going into the a mbula nce.
And now we ha ve with us
Inspector Ja i Singh who...
...will give us a II the informa tion
a bout this incident.
Sir, tell us how did this ha ppen?
As a routine process
we were shifting...
...these terrorists to a nother pla ce.
Excuse me!
- Yes.
Wha t's the time? My
wa tch is not working.
5.30.
Your ba g seems quite hea vy.
Excuse me.
Yes, tell me.
Ha ve you left or not?
I wa s just lea ving
when I met someone.
Who is it? A friend of yours?
I don't know yet.
Plea se come home. It's getting
la te. - I a m on my wa y.
Sorry. Were you sa ying something?
I wa s sa ying your ba g
seems quite hea vy.
Ca n I drop you somewhere?
Tha t's my vehicle.
Tha t police jeep?
Yes.
- No tha nks. I live nea rby.
Are you sure?
- Sure.
Pra ka sh Ra thod.
I a m...
He told me his na me...
. but I ca n't tell tha t
na me to a nybody...
A ma n recognizes
the religion by na me.
We a II knew tha t a common ma n
is disturbed by these things.
But never ever ima gined tha t
a common ma n ca n go to such sta ge.
One common ma n ha d the guts.
This incident a nd this ca se
is not registered in a ny file.
There is no record a nywhere,
but it is in my mind...
...a nd some people who were
involved in this ca se unwillingly.
I don't know it is right or wrong...
...but persona lly spea king,
wha tever it wa s. It wa s good.