Team xRG @ desidhamal.com
ln every speck shines
His divine light
Look within yourself,
He isn't far from you
lf you have love in you,
then embrace everyone
Because we are all in
His form. That's worship
What would have happened
if the red-headed man..
..hadn't woken up at dawn
that day to relieve himself?
Perhaps life would have carried on
in Delhi-6 as it had for centuries
Perhaps my life might not have
been turned upside down either
But then again
When you got to go, you got to go!
ln the Treta Age of the Vedic era
The evil ten-headed Ravan was king
His powers were
renowned and he was feared
The Sun, Moon, Wind and
Fire were enslaved to Ravan
Dikpal, Suresh, Kuber,
Varun were scared of him
His abode was Lanka, made of gold
He didn't allow anyone to worship
Hari. He would call himself God
There was unrest in the universe..
Who could save the Earth,
Brahma thought
The hope of happiness was suppressed
by atrocities and sorrows
A divine voice spoke..
"Earth. My dear, Earth. l shall
get you out of this trouble."
"l will be born as Ram
in Awadh to save you"
The tumour is close
to her area of vision
l wouldn't recommend surgery at all
Especially with her history
of diabetes, blood pressure
Open-heart surgery will be too much
Even Medicaid won't cover it
Fatima, ask the fool
how long l've got?
Ma, don't say that! Allah forbid it
ls there any immediate danger?
Look, she will have to accept
this as a part of her life.
From now onwards
Give her a proper diet..
..and strict medication
and above all, keep her happy
l mean, avoid any kind of stress
That should do it for her
Who do you have in lndia?
Did these five years
with us bore you?
No, child. But you must merge
with the soil on which you are born
Ma, these are old proverbs
Son, think of it as my last wish
Ma, you're like a stubborn child
You make life difficult
You know l'll never go back
to Delhi
That's it
Dad, l'll take her
l couldn't see well in
the dark. He was 8ft.2
Covered in black hair
His nails shone like knives
Anyone who dares to sleep is dead!
He'll creep up on you
while you're snoring
He'll kill you. Murder you.
Ask. Who is he? Who is he?
Yes! The murderer is
none other than a monkey
A dark Black Monkey!
The Black Monkey kills.
The Black Monkey murders
Beware! 24/7. From Delhi, Kumar
The first one to welcome me
to Delhi was the Black Monkey
Perhaps destiny
was sending me a sign
Gran! Wait
Would you care for a paan?
Salaams, Mrs. Mehra!
Now l can die in peace
My love dragged you back You
couldn't stay away long - Grandma!
What are you doing?
You just can't leave me like that
l forgot all about you
Recognise him?
At last!
Now my eyes can rest
forever now. Let me hug you
Come on! Give me a hug Good boy
l'm Ali Baig!
Oh, l am so sorry.
l didn't recognise you
Awesome
A flood of people! Delhi is teeming
with life The constant buzz
Everything happening
at the same time.
Yet there is a kind of balance
A balance Amazing
No, no. You can't enter like
this First sweeten your mouth
Mamdu! How are you?
You're back at last!
Salaams, Hina! My sister-in-law
ls everything alright?
Why the long face?
Aren't you looking after her?
Gobar! How are you? Bless you, son
Guess who's here!
My grandson. Roshan
No, thank you
He isn't hungry
Only dogs eat when they're hungry.
Humans eat to bond with each other
You should have one. Have one
Only the lucky few
taste Mamdu's sweets
That's all right - What happened?
Or you can't go through
My beloved has returned home
People have great faith
in this place
They say if you hang a
bell with a pure heart
God will heed you
l hung a bell before
l left and prayed
to return with my whole family
God heard me. At least in part
Lord! Lord! Lord! My Almighty
Home at last! Your Paswaan Lane
lt hasn't changed a bit
- Your phone is ringing
lt's not mine
That's mine
Oh. Got cut.
Hey. Thanks for everything.
Welcome.
You must rest.
l'll take your leave
Have tea with us
- Some other time
Make sure you drop by
- Sure
That's my ball
Got it!
Mrs. Mehra is back
How are you, Rajjo?
- You look lovely
Urmila!
- How do you do?
Welcome to Delhi 6.
How's everyone at home?
- l am Rajjo
Come in. Come in
Rama!
- The blessings - Oh, yes
Rama. Bless you
How are you?
- You have come after long
Here
- You're looking so beautiful
A local speciality
Have one at least
- Home at last!
Are you all right?
Come
Roshan! Unlock the door
Which one?
- The small one
Come on. Come on. Move
The tulsi plant has dried.
Some water
Water
No water now
The tap runs only in the morning
lt's like the government.
Works on a whim
Nothing like Mother Earth!
l was just 16
Your grandfather married
me and brought me here
l'll leave the world
from this place now
Gran
Where's the bathroom?
This way
Don't waste water. lt's precious
Overflowing with emotion.
That's the beauty of lndia for you
Love is never given in small doses
Here, taps may run dry.
But amazingly tear ducts never do
Life is fine
Your grandfather! He never
accepted your parents' marriage
Never listened to anyone
"How is it possible?"
lt chewed him up till he died
He'd say: "How can my
son marry a Muslim?"
l wasn't happy either
But when l spent time
with your mother
l knew l was wrong
Damn it!
Must the power go now?
Your father was just as stubborn
My husband said:
"Get out!" So he left
And refused to come back
He came back once.
For your grandpa's funeral
See God's miracle, Roshan?
You were born on the same night
"Everything that
happens is God's will"
Only his moustache sets you apart
Grandma
Those are some hardcore moustaches
- Hey
You're still not ready?
Ravan is on his way to kidnap Sita
My scarf! Hey, mister
Can't you see?
Shall l buy you specs?
Sorry
Gran!
Lord Ram was born in Awadh
to put an end to all suffering
Lord Ram was born in Awadh..
- Salaam, Mrs. Mehra
Hello
You're so late
- Mamdu? Right?
Devotees' sufferings..
l can't enter without
eating something sweet, right?
Absolutely right. This way
Come. Ganesh.
Get the veneration plate
Bless you!
How are you, Madangopal?
Well. Thanks to the Goddess
Bittu! lsn't she Bittu?
How thin you are.
You were once so chubby and healthy
You're a stick now
- Her American grandson
Must l dance for joy?
Roshan. She's Bittu.
Their daughter
Oh, yes, l know. We've already met
- Okay
Mrs. Mehra
- Yes
Look here
- Rs.20 from me
And a donation of 50 from me
Why be stingy with the
Benevolent One? Right?
Miserly with his sister but loves
showing off in public - Bless you
How are you?
- You brothers never stop fighting.
Have you no shame?
You look dashing!
- Thank you, Miss
Thank you
Young man, not Miss. Mrs!
Oh, l am so sorry
- Myself Jaigopal Khanna,
proprietor Jaigopal
Electrical Works
l won the contract for
all the lighting. Right?
Mrs. Mehra, donation
Gobar! Don't pester her
Hey, Gobar! Come here
Tell me
One ten-rupee note? Or
two one-rupee coins?
One note? l'll take two coins
Well done.
He's got straw for brains
Gobar.
- Hello.
Time for a group photo.
Paswaan Lane! Stand close together
Come. Come
- Sorry
Mr. Madangopal, smile please.
Suresh. Are we in?
- Yes.
My star of Delhi-6. When
are you heading to Mumbai?
l can go anytime. l'm
giving the others a chance
Don't forget the
2500 you owe me! Right?
Jaigopalji, forget about me.
Tell me about your shirt. By God!
Looks like l had
better visit Malayasia too
Look! The moneylender's wife is
decked out like his jewellery store
So our wives nag us
to buy the same jewels
Later, he will give
us a loan against them
Let me photograph you
and your lovely wife
Greetings, Annapurnaji
- Greetings
Pay your respects!
May you both live long!
Lalaji, meet Rajan's son. Roshan
Well!
- Hi
Are you here to stay or
you've come just to drop her off
No. l came to leave her
- What's your name?
Roshan Mehra
How are you? Hi
Any plans for the house?
- Lalaji, l'm still alive!
Let me know. l'll
fetch you a good price
Can family heritage
ever be for sale?
There's no family left
Money is better than
bricks and mortar. Right, son?
Hey, Grandma, isn't this the
bit with the golden deer? Cool.
Hey look, it's a golden deer!
You burger species!
With an arrow as sharp as His
gaze He struck the golden deer
The golden deer
changed into the demon Marich
O Brother Laxman!
Ram is calling for help
As Laxman leaves, the
demon king Ravan appears
Sita hears his cry for alms!
The sage implores: "Give
alms in the name of God"
Mother, alms for the sage.
Stay well
"God keeps you well"
May you always prosper
The sage insists: "Sita,
step out of the ring of fire.
Hand me the offering"
As Sita stepped out,
the sage turned into..
..the demon Ravan
You sinner!
O Lord Ram,
save me!
Ladies and gentlemen
We are proud to welcome
Maitri Devi, the
councillor for Delhi 6
On behalf of
the Ram Leela committee
The honourable lady is here
we'd like to garland her
"May the rule of Ram reign forever.
l may die but
l'll never break a promise!"
Lord Ram who sacrificed
everything in the name of duty
at His feet
l offer donation money on
behalf of my party and me
Please accept it
Join me when l say:
"Long live Ram and Sita!"
Long live Lord Hanuman!
Long live Maitri Devi!
ln lndia, the gods dance
to the whims of politicians
l thoroughly enjoyed the Ram Leela
A great show
But even more
fascinating were the people
l was so exhausted.
But the real drama
was yet to unfold
Hanuman! Go and see.
Two men have entered the forest
Hanuman!
Where are you?
Where has Lord Hanuman gone?
Where?
Hanumanji, it's your cue.
They're looking for you
Hanumanji!
Hanuman. Look at that
Hanuman
A monkey!
The Black Monkey!
You slow poke
Manager! Come here
Stay here
ls he the one?
- No
Balls of a wimp!
lt's not him either.
Aren't you an expert
at grabbing tails?
Carry on!
Whose phone is that?
Whose tail is ringing?
Hello
- Hello
lnspector sir,
the phone belongs to Roshan
Roshan! l've found it
What species is he?
Hey, thanks a lot.
Thank you
Sir, l can't figure it out.
Let me go
Did l give you permission to stop?
Keep going
You don't have the right to
do that. What are you doing?
Who's this?
- Roshan, let's go
Shall l slap his left cheek too?
Know who l am?
No, no. One second
Your uniform tells me
you're a public servant
What? Balls of a wimp!
Do l look like a servant?
lnspector
lndia was surely the most
connected country in the world
Though not many express highways
but there are many shortcuts here.
He doesn't know the law here
There he is
Thank you, lnspector sir
Mr. Baig
Tell him how the wind blows
This is lndia
You bow to a uniform. No choice
Uncle Ali
How did you just pull that off?
l mean, what did you do?
l offered him a paan
Wrapped in a bank note
This is Delhi, my friend
Brother Roshan
Offering you nothing
but love and affection
Bittu
Delhi is a place for
those who love life
A place where crazed lovers live
Delhi is a place for
those who love life
A place where crazed lovers live
Olameno, we know, say Delhi-Delhi
Olameno, we know, say Delhi-6
Delhi is a place for
those who love life
A place where crazed lovers live
lt holds you in a tight embrace
lt lets you hear its heartbeat
Hearts to your left
Hearts to your right
This is not a city but
a gathering of lovers
This is Delhi, my friend
Offering you nothing
but love and affection
Sorry
Sorry? Specs
Do l need them?
Why the toothpaste grin?
Cute, huh?
Wow
Sunita, the scene today is:
show some flesh, hide some
You want 4x6? 5x7?
Laminated? What do you want?
You've wasted my whole day
l have beauty. l have heart.
A pretty face and l'm smart
l, Bittu Sharma, will
be your new lndian ldol
Was good, but loosen up!
Relax. Be a little sexy!
Hey mister, watch your step.
Tread carefully on the path of love
The path of love is strewn
with cheats
Hey mister, watch your step.
Tread carefully on
the path of love
The path of love is strewn
with cheats
Hey mister, watch your step.
- Not bad!
You forgot your lipstick today
No, l didn't. lt got rubbed off
When do my lips try that?
What?
- Your hair!
Your hands are too frisky.
Control them
They have a will of their own.
What a dirty mind!
Maybe they want something
Bittu, you never take me seriously
You'll appreciate me when
l make you the lndian ldol
Hello. lt's made in Paris
Not a bad photographer.
You can cover my wedding
They're in black and white.
No colour
l see life in black and white
But rainbows fill the Mumbai sky
Glamour. Fashion. Models! Money
l must make some money
But to make money you need money
Suresh!
Lalaji! Hello
What a coincidence!
l was coming to see you
Your meter is ticking, Suresh
You owe me 166,000 rupees
Didn't you get the cheque?
l'll clear our accounts at Diwali
You have a week
Or else l think you get it
Got it! You look smart today.
May l take a photo?
Say "ah"
Oh God!
Gran!
Rama is gifted.
She'll brighten her in-laws' home
Oh yes
l can see the lights
Her brothers' quarrelling is
spoiling her chances of marriage
Damn their bickering!
Soon she'll be too old to marry
Come on, Grandma
Age has nothing to
do with finding love
lt's all good, Aunt Rama.
Stay cool
When my beloved teases me,
sister-in-law ribs me
My husband's house is
as lovely as a marigold
When mother-in-law taunts me,
brother-in-law consoles me
My husband's house is
as lovely as a marigold
l left my parents' home so
l could belong to my beloved
When mother-in-law taunts me,
brother-in-law consoles me
My husband's house is
as lovely as a marigold
My husband is a merchant.
He is leaving for the city
When l see him go, my heart sinks
My husband's house is
as lovely as a marigold
When mother-in-law taunts me,
brother-in-law consoles me
My husband's house is
as lovely as a marigold
When my beloved teases me,
sister-in-law ribs me
My husband's house is
as lovely as a marigold
l left my parents' home so
l could belong to my beloved
Wearing a bush shirt,
he happily chews paan
There is no one to
match him in all of Raipur
My husband's house is
as lovely as a marigold
When my beloved teases me,
sister-in-law ribs me
My husband's house is
as lovely as a marigold
l can't swallow a thing
Eating too many betel nuts!
Who's there to stop you?
Aren't you Rama?
Hello
Wow! You've never met us.
But you recognize us
The one and only Rajjo!
How do you do?
ls all well with you?
Your son is a gem
He's one of us now
We're keeping him. Don't
say we didn't warn you!
Keep him! He's yours anyway
You have a Delhi-6 heart.
Tangy and spicy!
Like a Delhi snack
Mother!
What happened?
- Call 91 1 !
Get out of the way!
- Uncle Ali
We're going to the hospital
lrwin Hospital. l will go
arrange things - lrwin Hospital
Get out of the way! - Yes, lrwin
- Get out of the way! Give way!
Mamdu!
She's very unwell
Let us pass!
Get out of the way.
- What's wrong?
Tie this to her wrist
Lord Hanuman will cure her
- Hail Lord Hanuman
We won't let her fall sick
Get out of the way
Gobar, clear the way!
Get out of the way. Get out
of the way. - What's going on?
Why have they stopped
- She's unwell. Move
What's going on?
- Move. Move
Someone see what's wrong
What happened?
- Mother Cow is giving birth
What?
- Yes.
Calf?
- Mother Cow giving baby cow
Move them out of the way. Go on!
Go after them
- Give way. Give way
Clear the road. Clear the road
Clear the road
Move back - You're blessed
to see Mother Cow giving birth
Those who witness the birth
are freed of all misfortune Here!
Mother Cow has blessed you.
Have the sweet
Move back
- Please, clear the road
Can prayer ever be stopped?
Mother Cow is giving birth.
People have gathered
How can the police intervene?
Step back! Everyone stand back!
- What the hell!
There's an emergency case.
Clear the road!
Step back! Everyone stand back!
- Clear the road. Move! Move!
Gran?
Move! Move!
What are you all doing?
Move aside. Let us pass!
lt's having an effect.
lt's having an effect - Move aside!
Hail Mother Cow! Hail
Mother Cow! Hail Mother Cow!
Don't worry.
Her sugar level had
dropped and she fainted
Back in America, we thought Gran
had no one in Delhi
But everyone here is family
Roshan. You have it, Son
Gran is dying, Ali Uncle
The poet Zauq says: "Who can
ever wish to leave Delhi's lanes?"
Just stay
Stay as you are
You are pain
You are comfort
Just stay
Stay as you are
A gentle breeze
A stormy obsession
Smooth as silk.
Jagged as rough cloth
Sometimes you quarrel.
Sometimes you're stubborn
So full of fragrance
l don't want to change you an inch
Without adornment.
Without impurity.
No more. No less
l love you just as you are
- May l? - Sure!
lt's all yours
ln your rainfall,
l want to dissolve
l love you just as you are
ln your flame, l want
to burn and turn to ash
lf you wound me,
soothe me with a balm
l will soon love
the wound you inflict
You are a river.
Let me drown in you
Need a cold beer, boy?
Your father and l had a
great time when we were young
We had a great time
Ali Uncle,
you're a good-looking guy
Yes
No wife and children.
A girl-friend?
Just the one
And?
Your father took her away
My mother? Are you serious?
No way!
25 years ago, if l had
told Fatima "l love you"
l might have a son like you today
But dreams only blossomed
in my heart
Your father had guts
He loved her madly.
He fought everyone
Not caring what they saidabout
Fatima being a Muslim
He fought for love
When l look at you,
l see that love
ln your eyes and in the way
you talk
But then l know
..you will leave us too
Back to America
Ali Uncle, l'm an American
My life is there
All my pleas are written on my face
What can l ask of You, O Master?
You already know what
is in my heart
O Master! My Master
O Master!
Cracks blemish
the line of my destiny
Repair my fate, O Master
l bow at Your door.
My being erased and then remade
Repair my fate, O Master
He who comes to Your
threshold comes to bow his head
He drinks from the cup of ecstasy.
He dances in harmony
He came with throat parched.
And found an overflowing river
He returned bathed in
the shower of Your light
The rich always buy the
best urns. 501 . 95 paisa.
Just feel it
Do you have a gold urn?
With gems and rubies
Why show off in death?
Why save if you're going forever?
A copper urn.
251 . 95 paisa
l want a clay urn for
my ashes. Or l'm off
Yes, l have it
You're so old-fashioned.
Here you are
Specially made
from sacred Ganges clay
151 . 95 paisa
- This is good
Roshan, hold it
Now l can die in peace
Here you are
Only 100?
- You will prosper.
"The tree said to the leaf:
Listen to what l say:
"This is the cycle of life:
A leaf dies. Another is born"
Come on. l am done
l first thought it odd that Gran
was making these arrangements
A bit morbid
Who goes shopping
for your own funeral?
Discussing death like this
Then l figured it out. We can't decide
the manner in which we are born
But we can plan our departure
The rainy season is over.
Autumn is here
Yet l have had no word of Sita
lt pains Laxman to see
His brother suffering
He longs to take away his pain
Fresh attacks in Delhi 6
The dark shadow of the Black
Monkey is cast all over Delhi
Listen carefully
- My heart stopped when l saw it.
lt had bulbs on its chest
When l touched it,
l got a 500 volt shock!
Oh my God!
The earth gets
its energy from the sun
But the monster Black
Monkey's energy is far greater
lt can attack any time
Hence beware and stay alert
- They're all fools
The Black Monkey
- lndia's space mission
lt tore her saree
Got love. Will make you an idol
The pride of lndia
The lndian ldol bus is
coming to your town!
Mumbai. Lucknow.
Kolkata, Delhi, Gwalior
lf you want to be an lndian
idol then call for the auditions
On 5052525. Or SMS ldol 52525
You pierced your navel?
- Sexy, eh?
Had it done yesterday
lt must have hurt
- Nothing is gained without pain
lf the Black Monkey has
glowing lights on its chest
it means it has a mother board
An electric circuit. Right?
Right
- Leave him alone
Don't bore him with your theories
Young man, what happens when water
gets into an electric circuit?
No, you tell me
Short-circuit?
- Right!
Well done! Hear that, Rajjo?
He's smarter than us
Made in America! Right?
So, if you see the Black Monkey's
electric board, pour water on it
Short circuit! Finished!
The end of the Black Monkey. Right?
Brilliant.
lt's time to leave
l'm not blowing my own trumpet.
But no one can touch me
in electronics
Only father's old radio
is beyond me
Until l hear a sound from it,
l won't give up
Right
l'll see you at the prayer meeting
- Yes, yes. See you
All right. Bye
- Bye
Young man, good you're doing this.
The Goddess will rid
us of all problems
Hail to the Goddess!
Sister-in-law!
l don't know what he
was telling Roshan
Something about the Black Monkey's
mother sitting for a board exam
Pour water on him
He said pour water
on him and he's dead
But where do we get so much water?
lt's spicy
- Let Bobby play with me
Stop it!
- Bobby! - What are you doing?
Hello
Yes?
What is it?
- Here.
- Some sweets
Why? Has Mother Cow given birth?
No! Granny is well again.
So we're organizing
a prayer meeting
lt's an invitation
My hands are unwashed
Leave it inside
Yes
Sorry
You're the wife of
Madangopal Electrical.
How can you be so dumb?
You're from America, right?
Yes. For real. Why?
Lightning strikes when it rains?
Yes
- Yes?
Does lightning
short-circuit the clouds?
Never heard such a thing
Neither have l
Throwing water on the
Black Monkey won't help
Stop that damn racket!
Do you think the
Black Monkey is a moron?
A big hero, eh?
Talking rot to the women
- Uncle is right, father
My science teacher told
us about short circuits
Shut up! Son of an ass!
When you're my age, then talk big!
Must you shout in front of Roshan?
Mummy, l'm going out
Serve some lunch to Mrs. Mehra.
Then go to college
All right
See you at the prayer meeting
- Start
Bye
Pour water on the monkey? Ha!
Sorry about that
You Americans think you
own everything
You force your way everywhere.
lnto any country
So shameless.
You Americans never ask for permission
- So, now it's political?
Come on. What's the big deal?
lt's a big deal for us.
We never cross the line
You burger species!
You know why the Black
Monkey wears shades?
- How would l know?
- lt's stylish, boss!
You're smoking lndian
cigarettes when l'm around?
Try this, sir. lmported
Special filter
ls that so?
What a waste
Bobby, come here
Well, Mr Bobby?
You'll get 90%  in your
exams this time. Right?
No.100%
Bravo!
Pulling your uncle's leg! Right?
Who started this round?
Ok! There's a beggar
sitting round the corner
Give this to him. Good boy. Go
What are you doing?
- l'll do what l want
Shall we go in?
Those damn ghosts live there
- Go on!
You come too. Big mouth!
Mother!
Don't be a kid. We're grown up now
- What if we're caught?
- No one enters Dead Souls' Lane
They say scary ghosts roam here
Mummy says cigarettes are bad
But your father smokes.
You coward!
- l am not a coward
-That's more like it!
ln Delhi 6, Jalebi
helps boys become men
Jalebi?
The Untouchable caste sweeper?
- So what! - l'll ask Mummy
You son of an ass! You can't
ask Mummy about everything
Now we're men
Sister! The garbage
Old letch!
Here
Watch out!
Look good!
You girl thief!
You'll be dancing like a peacock
when l shove my broom
Move aside!
The garbage!
What are you doing?
Mrs. Mehra, the flowers
Go in
Simpleton!
You ask
Turn us into men
Who told you l can do that?
Everyone knows
- Sonny, you still wet your pants
Still drinking milk.
You'll be men, will you?
We're grown up. We want to be men
Run. l'll call your mother
Be men! You're toddlers
Damn it!
Wretched parents!
Spoiling their children
The garbage!
Oh, wait. Wait. Wait. l got that
Hold on
ln the name of Lord Ram! Disaster!
- What?
What have you done?
Come on, Gran
Gran. What are you doing?
You all cannot make me..
- Pure of body. Pure of spirit
Come on. Come on. Take
your clothes off -You wish!
So what if Jalebi is human!
She's of the Untouchable caste
You have to bathe.
Come on. Hurry up
Roshan, listen to him.
Do as l say, son
Get real, guys
Shabri, why do you hesitate?
Give me a berry to eat
She tastes the berries and
offers the sweetest to Lord Ram
Without hesitation, Lord
Ram eats berry after berry
Shabri is an Untouchable. Why is
He eating berries she has tasted?
No one is inferior or
superior by birth to Lord Ram
Ramji is God. He is
permitted everything
No one is inferior or
superior by birth to Him
Rambihari
l need company.
Bring Jalebi to me
Hey, mom!
Yes. At the Ram Leela.
You guys!
The boss wants you
The Black Monkey? On CNN?
The key is here
- Didn't you hear me?
You damn sweeper! l'll fix you
Stand up!
l am not going with you
Tell him
Come on
- Let go of me!
May Ravan kidnap your sister
The police!
- Take right
Let go of me!
The Black Monkey?
He'll run over me!
All praise to you!
Where did the balls of the wimp go?
Who?
The Black Monkey! Who else?
Not asking about your father
Pass me the fog horn!
You Black Monkey
Your game is up. The
place is surrounded by police
Be reasonable. Or
else we will shoot you
Sir - Yes? - There.
l think he went up there
There
He tore through the roof
- He must have springs for feet
You saw him? What's he look like?
Who?
The Black Monkey! Who else?
Why are you winding us up?
What happened?
He was invisible, l didn't see
l understood
You understood? - lf he's invisible,
how can he be seen?
The moron drives well too!
Before l knew it
l was adding to the
Black Monkey's saga
What must be the height?
Because of me, now
he was invisible too
Click a snap. You idiot
- Yes. Yes
Move! Move!
- He's an alien
Sir, l.. - Call for the rope - Yes
- Criminal. Criminal. Criminal
ln the dark of the night,
wearing a dark suit and dark glasses
the Black Monkey drives a black Sumo
Once its dark deeds are done
it presses a red button
- And becomes invisible!
lt's an alien
lt attacked two girls in
our area. They were sleeping
We gave chase. But it disappeared
This monkey is driving us crazy
The albatross emits many
sounds while it is mating
lf you breathe deeply,
it'll benefit you in every way
Great importance is
given in Yoga to breathing
Chandrayaan is going to
be launched in some time
Our flag is on the moon now.
All over lndia, the preparations
to go to the moon..
Many Sumo cars
were destroyed in Delhi
But this Sumo belonged
to the Black Monkey.
He has made
everyone's life miserable
- Have you seen the Black Monkey?
- Yes! lt's invisible
lt is an animal.
Animals aren't in our jurisdiction
Not a case for us
A monkey? A criminal!
l will say it takes a lot
of precise manoeuvring there
But once it takes off,
then we know
The vehicle has lifted off!
The monkey is an animal.
Not our jurisdiction!
So? Will you do nothing?
Pointing fingers at us won't help
Look at our track record
We are most capable
- Utter rot!
This case is for
the Animal Ministry.
They must take action
Move! Go home and watch TV
Have you ever seen an
animal with a mother board?
Springs for feet?
No! So how does it
concern the Animal Ministry?
Talk to the Science
and Technology Ministry
lf they stopped lining their
pockets, they'd have time for us
How right you are!
Madangopalji! lt's from the shrine
l'm Jaigopal! For
once get my name right
Look! Look into the mirror
ln every speck shines His light
- Should l come too?
Look within yourself,
He isn't far from you
lf you have love in you,
then embrace everyone
That's true worship
Look into the mirror!
Salaams to you!
- Good morning, boys
Good morning, boys
- Good day, young man
Good day
He's a fine boy
Haji Mian!
- What is it, Mamdu?
Roshan slapped the
lnspector last night
"You public servant"
Yes
- "Do you know who l am?"
"Your uniform tells me
you're a public servant"
"Servant? Do l look like a servant?"
Then our Roshan, tall as
the Qutub Minar, his arm
Swings it around
No, no, no. No, sir
Did l give you
permission to stop? Carry on!
l explained. "Roshan is new in town"
The lnspector can fix anyone.
You don't know him
Don't talk too much
Masakali! Come
Come to me
Come here, my child. Come, sit
Masakali! Masakali!
Move a little. Move a little
Masakali! Masakali! Move
a little. Move a little
Spread your wings
and set the dust free
Fly high! And higher still
Fly over cities, lanes and towns
Fly with grace on your wings.
Follow your heart's every desire
Blend with the wind.
Stylish and swift.
Fly away, you gem
Masakali! Masakali!
Move a little. Move a little
A colony of clouds
is your lovely abode
Turn your head away
from those who can't fly
Fly! Do not be afraid
Do as you please. As you please
Fly away. Don't look back
Fly! Do not be afraid
Do as you please. As you please
Fly away. Don't look back
Smile as you spread your
wings Flap your wings.
Masakali! Masakali! Move
a little. Move a little
Masakali! Masakali!
Masakali! Masakali! Move
a little. Move a little
What do you care about sorrow?
All you hear is the flute in the sky
The wind talking The sun shining
Fly away! Never fear
Do as you please. As you please
Fly away. Don't look back
Fly away! Never fear
Do as you please. As you please
Fly away. Don't look back
Smile as you spread
your wings, Masakali
You should know, says the wind
Masakali! Masakali!
Move a little. Move a little
Masakali! Masakali! Move a little
Hey, you ok?
- What's it to you?
Please just leave me alone. Ok?
Bittu! My child
Rat poison?
l'll pour it in his tea.
Then swallow some myself
End of story
Whose tea?
- That bloated haystack! The suitor
He wants to check me out. Marry me
Check you out? Wow, that's..
that's really
- Cool, right?
You find us so amusing
Look at these backward lndian types
What's wrong?
- l don't want to get married.
But l don't have a choice
l'll have to walk a little.
Sing a little
Pretend l cooked the
samosas Aunt Rama made.
Hurry! Papa is about to have a fit
Yuck!
lf you don't want to get married,
tell them your point of view
Point of view?
Who can dare talk to father?
They're made for each other.
Like Ram and Sita!
The princess arrives!
Hi! How are you? Hi
Excuse me.
May l have a word? lt's urgent
Not now. We have guests
Yeah, l know.
lt's a bit important
l said later!
Do have something
Go ahead, son
l'm really sorry,
especially for you, big guy
Bittu doesn't want to marry him
You insolent boy!
Remember your place
She can't tell you.
Because she's scared of you
Get out of here. l said get out!
Bittu was going to drink rat poison.
And mix it in the tea
l am Sameer Abbas.
You're watching lBN-7
Breaking news from Delhi 6
This is what the
Black Monkey looks like
To anyone who catches
the Black Monkey
The Delhi police
offer a reward of 50,000
Does the monkey man
actually exist in our capital?
The Black Monkey is the latest rage
Along with the Superman,
Spiderman, Batman costumes..
he costumes of Monkey
man are in high demand
Being a responsible officer,
l take the responsibility.
This is how the Monkey man is
Delhi is gripped by fear
lt's mere mention scares people
lt's the fear psychosis
that has now crept it.
As soon as the word spreads that
the Monkey man has come to the area,
There is panic.
An industrial worker actually
jumped to his death in this panic.
Breaking news from Old Delhi!
ln Delhi 6, pregnant woman fell to
her death as she ran down the stairs
She panicked when
she heard people say
the Black Monkey was back
Fear of the Black Monkey
has caused another death
What is the Black Monkey?
Everyone in Delhi fears it
ls it some sort of plot?
Hey! The Black Monkey!
ls it inside? Or is it out?
Find it and you're the champ
lt's wasn't me. l swear. Everybody's
looking for the monkey out there
Blame the Black Money!
Everybody's looking
for the monkey out there
Come! Look into the
mirror Read the signs
Look at our wounded self.
Recognise our true colours
ln the dark of the veil, what
rears its head like a snake?
The whitest of white clothes
covers a dark and muted truth
Suck on it! Suck on it!
Suck on a slice of life
Peep into your hearts too
l heard he's 2 feet tall
And bites off your knees
l heard he's got metal teeth
And wears superman's briefs
That makes sense l saw
him flying last week
He was invisible Someone saw
some movement in the trees.
l heard he's some
experiment gone wrong
A monkey alien that has
been left in the sun too long
l heard he's a cyborg
- You're right.
Made from parts of a
toaster and a nuclear bomb.
But who's actually seen him?
Nobody.
This poor thing seems a little
bit quirky - The Black Monkey!
lt's my kite!
Okay! Chill you guy
Please come, Uncle. Welcome. Welcome
- Hello. Hello
Hail to the Goddess!
- Hail to the Goddess!
Hey! What's up?
Hello
- Please come. Please have some
How are you, Gobar? - Very well.
Please come. - Long live the Goddess!
Long live the Goddess!
Hey, Jilebi
Hello, Brother Roshan - What are
you doing outside? Come on in
No
- Don't feel shy. Come on in
Dot worry. l won't come in
- That's right
Offer flowers to the Goddess from me.
My wishes will come true
No Hell for me
Sita was born to
destroy Ravan's arrogance
Praise the Goddess. Long live!
When we light the
lamp in Your temple..
..our sins are washed away
You shower us with happiness
Lord Brahma chants Vedas at your
doorstep, Mother. Lord Brahma..
..reveres you, Mother Amba. Lord
Brahma chants Vedas at your doorstep
Lord Shiva is
meditating at Mother's doorstep.
When we light the lamp in Your
temple our sins are washed away
You shower us with happiness
When we light the lamp in Your
temple our sins are washed away
You shower us with happiness
Hail to Goddess Durga!
Superb! Superb
Oh God! lt's 8 o'clock
The power cut is always
on time. That's for sure
Hey.
You deserve a thank you
So you're thanking me
Something like that
Right. Then you're very welcome
Did you really mean
to swallow rat poison?
You're a bit slow.
lt was an act. To scare mother
Right
When we light the lamp in Your
temple our sins are washed away
You shower us with happiness
Lord Shiva is
meditating at Mother's doorstep
Lord Brahma reveres you,
Mother Amba
At least someone is in tune
That's why l'll be
the next lndian ldol
You're serious?
There's an lndian ldol?
The only way a middle-class girl
can become somebody from nobody
l want to do something. Be someone
Find myself
l don't want to be the Mrs.
of Daddy's chosen boy
Understand?
Unless you have the
option of rat poison
Enough talking!
You burger species!
My heart..
My heart was lost to me
Without warning
But my eyes are all-seeing
..of your flowing dark hair
ls the place..
..where my heart
found itself confused..
..how unaware you are.
Unsuspectingly, unknowing
My heart was lost to me
Without warning
- Why does my heart quicken?
But my eyes are all-seeing
Pearls over brimming
from the lips of oysters
Prose laced with poetry
Sheltered under a sheet of
waves the ocean slumbers
My eyes have been opened
wide by a flood of drunkenness
Mesmerized.
How unaware you are
Heart..
My heart..
No, Uncle
Look! The Taj Mahal!
The Taj Mahal is a symbol to love.
Making mockery of
the love of the poor
"Beloved, let us meet
in some other place"
Nice! Let's go in
My heart..
Hey!
- Roshan!
Bittu!
Hey guys! Check this out
Echo.
Hello
- Hello
- Bittu
Bittu
Ripping us off. Taking us
for tourists? l am a local
We buy them for l sell for 100
l have to earn at least 5 rupees
l can buy it for 20 in Chandni Chowk
Then buy it there, sister
Ok. Let's go
Come back!
Last price.
Rs.75. Just because
you're from my own locality..
..otherwise l too
have to make a living
Take it. And be quiet
What colour?
For you
l said 75! And you
give me Pay at least 60!
Madam, don't rob a poor shopkeeper
That's more like it
Roshan! ln America, you'll soon be
looking at photos of us
Wow.
Let me see too!
Roshan! ln America, you'll
soon be looking at photos of us
The dawn has broken. l wait for you
My eyes are heavy. Where
did you spend the night?
The dawn has broken. l wait for you
l wait for you
How fortunate is the other woman
The dawn has broken. l wait for you
The dawn has broken.
Your words are all l have
What's up? How was the audition?
Ok
Just ok?
Bittu.
Life is full of highs and lows..
lt's all part of the game.
You know, it happens
l've been selected
Really?
Cool! Well done
Why are you still looking so upset?
l don't know
You got what you always wanted.
Right?
Her wings are tied. She can't fly
Masakali is father's favourite.
That's why
Shall l free her?
Wasn't one slap from
father Enough for you?
l don't want to marry
Then what do you want?
l want to be an lndian ldol
- What?
What? lndian.. - Sister wants to
be on TV. The song and dance show
That blasted TV!
They sent me a ticket.
l'm going to Mumbai
Have you lost your mind?
Get her married at once!
Nothing but bad luck
The girls in this family
of ours are so ill-fated
You only think of yourself
Oh God! Why?
What else can l do? Spend
my life stuck here like you?
l'm sorry, Aunt Rama
The stock market
has opened robustly
Shares are up.
There's brisk trading
Welcome to 'Bazaar Subeh'
Their horoscopes don't match.
Your shares are up.
Do we sell?
She has bad planets
A token of good will
We're giving the boy a Honda
My boy can't be bought for a bike
What are you saying?
You thought l meant a motorbike?
l meant a Honda car.
You choose the colour
Sell or wait?
And a Singapore honeymoon on us.
Sell!
What?
l am Priyanka Sambhav and
you're watching "The Last Deal"
Panditji. Name an auspicious day
Joy abounds! A match made in heaven.
No better day then Diwali
- Excellent!
ls it a done deal?
Done
- Congratulations!
Hey, Ganpat, bring some
Haldiram's sweets for everyone
Bittu's wedding is fixed
Rajjo, see how lovely she looks
- A tip-top princess!
How time flies. Now she's of
age to marry and leave home
Just look at her.
Keep your father's honour
The Black Monkey has struck again
lt has taken 20 kgs. of milk.
12 kgs. of sweets
How much cottage cheese?
- 1 5 kgs
15 kgs. Move it!
What are you doing?
lt took Hina, the poor goat
Where were the police?
At the police station!
How did we know it will attack?
What will you do now?
Everything is under control.
See for yourself.
You can ask him for yourself.
Hey, Mamdu, tell them
Talk to Mamdu
Let's talk to the
shopkeeper whose shop was attacked
Mamdu, how do you feel?
Let him talk to Mamdu!
The damn Black Monkey
is in our area
And the police claim
they're controlling the situation
Today it's Hina, the goat.
Tomorrow it might our women.
Lalaji! Do you think
we're twiddling our thumbs?
We'll take action too. Right?
Long live Shani Baba!
Shani Baba will fix everything. Ok?
- Ok?
Side by side? Bad omen
Really?
When?
Then?
l get it!
Shani Baba will fix everything. Ok!
How is it ok?
Look!
lmages
Listen!
Like songs on the radio.
lmages on TV
They float in the air
Only one antenna can capture them
ln the same way, monkeys' souls..
..float about in the universe
Only Shani Baba can
communicate with them
Lord Hanuman has granted
this power to Shani Baba!
Lord Hanuman!
- May He live long!
Okay
What? ls that the truth?
Oh my God!
Baba will fix everything. Ok!
- Shut up
Three hundred and seventeen
years ago a temple stood here
What are you saying?
Baba will fix everything. Ok!
A curse! A terrible curse
Listen..
The Black Monkey is the latest
Hindu plot to humiliate us Muslims
The Black Monkey
is creating mayhem.
lt has wounded people.
And you call it a plot?
Suleman Sahib..
Why does the Black Monkey only
appear from Muslim neighbourhoods?
What do you mean, Madangopalji?
- lt's Jaigopal
Why are Hindu areas
the only ones attacked?
And during
the Ram Leela performances?
Hina was a Muslim goat!
l mean she belonged to a Muslim
Suleman Sahib! But everyone
knows Mamdu prays to Lord Hanuman
So wouldn't the Black Monkey know?
The Black Monkey can't be a Muslim
We have 1 00% proof
Proof? What proof?
Has anyone ever seen
a circumcised monkey?
l have heard of people
behaving like monkeys
But a monkey being Hindu
or Muslim? That's a first!
This is lndia, my boy! Play
l want a strand of
the Black Monkey's hair
The Black Monkey's hair!
The Black Monkey's hair?
You mean pulling it off
its body? Who will do that?
We will!
- Shut up!
Bring me its hair!
l will destroy it!
End of the menace
End of the menace, ok!
lt'll be destroyed! Ok
Destroyed! Ok
Gobar will get the hair
- Gob..
Brave Gobar!
Why Gobar? Because he's an orphan?
Let the fool be of some use
He's smarter than you lot
Miss Know-All
Gobar, come here
Come on!
- Come on!
Want one ten-rupee note?
Or two one-rupee coins?
Why one note? l'll take two coins
Here, as you wish. That's
why he's the local idiot!
The day l take the ten-rupee note,
the game is all over
Look at her! Sniggering at us
So what if
l belong to a lower caste?
l'm better than you
When you come to me at night,
no problem touching me, eh?
But in the daytime, l am
of a lower caste again!
Speak up! ls a
pacifier blocking your tongue?
Bastard!
l'll put a pacifier in your mouth
What did you say?
The monkey makes you
pee in your pants.
Get lost
- But you can hit a woman. Big man!
Get lost!
Brave Gobar!
- May he live long!
To get rid of an ordinary
monkey prayers are being offered
llliteracy may be the reason
We will hang the monkey and burn it
The government does
nothing but chase votes
The monkeys in the Ram Leela..
We'll kill it!
Never was there a temple here
Nor will there ever be one
Nor will it ever be built here
Their ancestors destroyed
the temple
They'll have to pay the price
All politics!
Lord Hanuman's name
is being disgraced
The monkey is a Muslim terrorist
We'll give them as good as we get
We've been attacked, sir
- You keep quiet
lf you're stubborn..
..you'll invite trouble. Right?
How much more can we tolerate?
Tension in Chandni
Chowk is at boiling point
Push rites and rituals aside
Look inside your homes
Perhaps in some dark corner.
The Black Monkey lurks.
So many veils in this world.
See the life in these lanes
Hiding behind layers and layers
Cloaks concealing cloaks
Somewhere in the folds of the cloak
Pain is veiled. Wounds are hidden
Secrets are trampled underfoot
Aware yet how unaware we are
Mad and innocent we are
Who knows the colour
we're painted in
ln the public bath, we are naked.
We've no orders from above
Mamdu!
Close the door! Hurry!
Jaigopal! Damn you
Close the gates. Quickly
Some sweets for you
- Mamdu
Mamdu, don't
Some sweets for you
- No
Don't you want more of my sweets?
"Mamdu's shop is my shop"
Now try coming to me!
- Mamdu
Try coming to my shop
You spent half your life at my shop
Mamdu, don't
He demolished my shop
Jaigopal believed my shop was his
They spent half
their lives at my shop
The Black Monkey is behind this.
The police are
offering a reward. 50.000.
to catch the Black Monkey!
Fifty-thousand?
Catch the monkey.
And give the money to Lala
That's how much he paid for me
My angel-face!
l'll come with an
army of monkeys for you
We'll catch him with the
help of a very big cage
The Black Monkey!
Lalalji! Save me
Lalaji, save me. Lalaji,
Black Monkey. Save me, Lalaji
Lalaji, black monkey,
save me. Save me, Lalaji
Lalaji, black monkey. Lalaji,
black monkey
Lalaji, save me. Save me, Lalaji
Where is the Black Monkey?
Catch the Black Monkey!
You foreigner!
ls it still 8 foot?
Or is it taller now?
Springs under its feet?
Vanished, eh?
lnto thin air?
What?
- Don't glare at me!
Lalaji's wife was almost raped.
You understand?
Tell me..
Whenever the Black Monkey attacks,
you're right there
What's going on?
Ask the monkey
Monk..
What did he say?
Showing off his English
- ls that so?
Look at his arrogance!
l'll sort him out
Bless you, son!
- Brother Roshan.
Rama..
Have a laddo. Go on!
Bittu is getting married
Rama, sweeten his mouth
They say if you bathe in the
Ganges you're blessed once
And a hundred times if you help the
family of a girl who is marrying
Tell us if there's you need anything
"Cheese"
l really think you should be firm
Why don't you just tell your father?
A father's honour is
in his daughter's hands
Oh, come on, Bittu, get real!
You're talking about your
whole life. Don't be a fool!
Fool? Do l look like a fool to you?
lt's not what l meant
Bhisham Forget it.
You won't understand.
But Suresh does
Suresh?
- l'm going to Mumbai with him
Have you gone insane?
You know what he's all about
Yes! But he cares about my dreams
ls this how you'll find yourself?
Great! Bittu
l thought you'd put up a fight.
But you're running away
You're being a coward
Who are you to talk to me like this?
Yeah, You're right
Do whatever you want.
You want to run from home?
Good luck with that
Bittu..
Bastard! Leading my daughter astray?
Father..
- Your father's dead for you
Take her downstairs! Go downstairs
- Come downstairs
His family specializes
in eloping with girls
Following your father's example, eh?
- Be quiet!
Mr. Fifty-Fifty! Go,
before l lose my head. Out!
What are you waiting for?
Mother, l'm not speaking French
Just ask Dad to book the
tickets and send them to me
What's wrong, Roshan?
- Nothing
Something has happened
Don't worry, son.
Leave everything to God
Oh, great!
Which God?
Whose God? Who should l leave it to?
Leave it to mother's Allah?
Or Dad's Lord Ram?
lt's really amazing, Gran
Paint a stone red
and it becomes a god
This plant of yours is a god too
But never solve your problems
yourself. Pray five times a day
Ring a bell in a temple.
And leave everything to God
We want to do nothing ourselves
lt's rubbish
Don't say that.
lt's our faith
Whatever!
But we're going back to America
Then why did you bring me here?
Gran, l have made my decision
you're coming back with me
Will you abandon your family
in America for these people?
My ashes leave this place
Stop behaving like a kid
Sorry
What's going on, Gran?
l don't understand
Everything will be all right
Don't worry
This is a fight for our rights
A fight for our self-respect
A fight for our honour!
We'll worship Goddess Durga here!
Yes. We'll surely do it!
We'll build a temple
Say with me out, loud,
"We'll build a temple here"
We'll destroy our enemies
Fight in the name of God.
- Fight in the name of God.
We die. Or they die
Sorry, Annapurnaji.
- Hail!
He isn't allowed inside the temple
Meaning?
Blood is blood after all
Don't force me to talk!
This temple doesn't belong to you
Does it belong to
your father? You Muslim!
Anyone who challenges
us will be destroyed!
Let's go, Grandma. - Brothers, this
is the time of examination for us.
We've picked up our weapons..
Roshan?
You're better off
listening to your elders
This is no party.
Too much tension here
Granny! Make him see some sense
He doesn't get it
Have you ever wondered..
..what this good soul whom you
call a madman is trying to say?
What can a mad fakir say?
Why don't you go ahead and tell us?
"ln every speck
shines His divine light
"Look within yourself.
He isn't far from you"
He says everyone has
God's light within him
A speck of Him
lf we look within we will find Him
Have you ever heard
that God hates someone?
l haven't
(He is all about love)
The boy has acquired a taste
for preaching. Listen to him!
Have a look
God is within us all
Stop this nonsense!
Allah is the only God
Look in the mirror, Mamdu
Can you see your God?
Get out of my way, otherwise,
l'll take care of you right here
Step back!
Roshan says God is in everyone.
ln Gobar and this deaf-mute
Garland him! Worship him!
My friend, wow. Amazing
Now watch me! l'm
looking into the mirror
So that means l'm god too!
And l created the world.
l created the world!
Damn it! The world is broken.
lnto pieces!
This world's in pieces
- Gather the pieces
They've turned into animals
The devil is perched
on their shoulders
They care for no one.
And feel no shame
Why did you have to
visit the temple now?
Why did Roshan behave
so stubbornly?
We're unworthy
They showed their true colours
Delhi folk talk of
being large-hearted.
This is what they have
l don't feel like dying here now
Roshan. Take me back to America
l was leaving..
Father, l'm leaving home
l was leaving.
Leaving this madness behind me
l don't know what l want.
But l know what l don't want
Away from Bittu
And perhaps away from myself
But l don't know
why l wanted to stay
l wanted to mingle with them.
And embrace this madness.
Be part of it
Something was stopping me
from leaving
Life is strange
First Gran didn't want to go.
Now l don't want to go
You don't want to go?
Or never want to go?
l never want to go
Despite what happened yesterday?
Because of yesterday
"This is a love that
isn't easy. Remember that!"
We lack food.
So we get by with love
Our homes are small.
So we swear by large-heartedness
A flute sound floats
through the tap. Not water
You will regret it. Stay far away
How can l?
These are my people
Their virtues and goodness are mine
Their flaws are mine too
You're over-emotional, Roshan
No, Ali Uncle, no
lndia works.
The people make it work
People are good
My parents never admit it,
but they miss their life here
They try to recreate
this world in America
But when they open the window..
..unfamiliar air blows in
Deep thinking!
l love her
l love Bittu
Can l tell you something?
This house once belonged to Fatima
Your mother grew up here
Before leaving, her family wanted
to sell the house. l bought it
Don't tell me
Tell Bittu you love her
Or you'll end up
buying empty houses like me
Let your feelings out.
Must they burn inside you?
This is Delhi-Penal
Code 144 has been imposed
This is the shrine
where the trouble started
Curfew has been imposed.
ls this the lull before the storm?
Weapons were found behind this tree
Risking my own life, Kumar
Kulshreshtha, is reporting to you..
This is the same area..
Who gave you permission?
Here's the capable
officer-in-charge, Ram Vijayji!
Uncle! Get the name right.
Thakur Ranvijay!
Yes, Mr. Thakur Ranvijay.
lf we had officers like
you in every neighbourhood..
lt's my duty
- Take his close up
Duty is duty.
Forget everything.
Duty is first come
Bring me a strand of the
Black Monkey's hair. Okay.
Don't be scared.
You are serving all mankind
No
- Come on, you're very brave. Go
Hey
We're trying to explain it to you
as calmly as possible. Better obey
Do as you are told.
Don't you understand?
Go!
Well done! Keep moving
The dawn has broken. l wait for you
l wish l had your guts
Here's some money
Go. Your dreams are waiting for you
Okay?
The dawn has broken. l wait for you
Roshan, Suresh is at the shrine
You oaf!
What are you doing here?
- l have a lot of work, sir
What?
ls everything alright here?
Take me for a moron, do you?
- Sorry, sir.
l'm going home
- Move it!
Pissing in my ear!
Brother Roshan
Bittu has left home
Roshan brother, Suresh is
heading to Dark Souls' Lane
What will happen now?
Let the final battle begin!
Good will win over Evil
today in the ultimate battle.
Today is the day of
the great battle
Hail Lord Ram!
Hail Lord Ram. Hail Lord Hanuman.
Hail Lord Shiva
Hail Lord Shiva. Hail Lord Ram
Let the final battle begin!
Good will win over
Evil today mahasangram..
..today mahasangram..
Hail Lord Ram!
We call upon the Great Allah.
- We call upon the Great Allah.
You morons.
Balls of a wimp! Look up there!
The Black Monkey!
Get him! The witch's son.
Play cricket later.
Go and get the monkey
Come on, let's go.
Don't let him go today
lf you see the Black Monkey,
throw water on it
Come, let's guard the alleys
Throw water!
Get water!
Shani Baba! Go! Or else
the Black Monkey will get you
Throw water!
The Black Monkey's hair
No harm in making fools of fools
Take it
The Black Monkey is on our roof
Where's it?
There! lt jumped from
the other terrace on ours.
l saw its shadow
- Where is it?
Mummy
Hey, kid fell down. Kid fell down
Rajjo! The Black Monkey
threw Bhisham off the terrace
Bhisham
Calls himself a father.
Can't look after his own son
Left him to the
mercy of the Black Monkey
Oh God..
- Call the doctor.
Call the doctor!
Mother Goddess! Save my nephew
- Please call a doctor
Don't lie.
We all have to go to God
Leaving our riches behind
O Lord Hanuman! Keep me safe
O Protector of Lord Ram, save me
Lalaji!
Actually, the Black Monkey..
..is at the heart of
the whole problem
You're absolutely right, Haji Mian
One minute.
l'll go with you
Look at this commotion
Beware! The Black Monkey isn't far
Come here. Come here
l told you to throw water on it
Make him see sense!
All this is because
of the black monkey.
l warned you!
- Don't worry, brother.
Everything will be all right
To save face in the community..
..we'll say the Black
Monkey kidnapped Bittu
lt will shut them up. Right?
Bittu! Where are you?
You sure you have the tickets?
l checked them four times
l landed in trouble.
l had to slap the lnspector
Stop bragging! Let's go
- Let's go
What is it? Hurry!
Suresh!
Let go off me!
Black Monkey
Calm down. lt's me
lt's just me
Oh God..
You!
What have you done?
Why did you need to do this?
l had almost escaped
- With the great Suresh?
He ran and left you at
the Black Monkey's mercy
You're leaving me too. For America
What you talking about? Never
l love you, Bittu
l'm incomplete without you
l'll never leave you
l thought you'd never say it
Hey, it's..
Roshan
- Brother Roshan
Balls of wimp! You've been
messing us around for days
Hit him!
- Let him go!
Don't hit him!
Hit him!
He isn't the Black Monkey.
You disgraced us
Father, stop them!
- Shut up!
Jaigopal! Beat him to a pulp!
You scumbag. You wretch
Creating nothing but trouble
The Black Monkey
He isn't black monkey.
You can't be the Black Monkey
just by wearing a two-penny suit
How is it possible?
Here is the Black Monkey's hair
Shani Babi will fix everything, ok!
The Black Monkey
Roshan
You killed him?
Bravo!
You would've killed each other if
he hadn't posed as the Black Monkey
The Black Monkey is laughing at us
lt isn't dead
lt is sitting inside us
ln some dark corner
ln every one of us
Laughing at us
The Black Monkey killed Roshan
Oh..
He pretended to be the
monkey out of love for us
Out of love for Bittu
Call an ambulance!
l feel so sorry for Mamdu
Mamdu is just like his father.
Too much sugar in his sweets
Grandad! Why bother
how sweet sweets are?
We Delhi folk didn't treat you right
Not at all
They're all good-hearted people
No, the devil is
perched on their shoulders
Not the devil. A monkey
My Black Monkey stayed within me
lf only l could
apologize to your mother
Do it now
You know give her a call.
Sort it out
Call her! Hold on
Cracks blemish the line
of my destiny
Repair my fate, O Master
l bow at Your door.
My being erased and then remade
Repair my fate, O Master
Be careful..
Start driving!
What's wrong?
Give it a push - What's wrong
with the car? - Come on
What's wrong?
Please move aside
What happened?
3.. 4.. 5.. The injection!
1 .. 2.. 3.. 4.. 5
Roshan
1 .. 2..
Roshan!
He's gone
What do you mean?
Gone? Do something
Do something. Roshan
- What're you doing? Stop it
Don't do it! No!
Roshan
We'll meet again
He's come back. Roshan's conscious
- Grandma
Grandma
Hail Lord Hanuman
You'll be all right. You'll be ok
"Who can ever wish to
leave Delhi's lanes?"
Gobar was so right
The Black Monkey or something
like it is within all of us
Whenever there is anger and hatred..
..the monkey becomes more powerful
And then we start using
it to our own advantage
But instead of destroying
the Black Monkey within us?
we kill each other
The Black Monkey turned to
ashes like the demon Ravan
As for me..
l came back home
A scent would fill my breath
l'd lose my way
lt was a web of silk..
..and l'd stare it in its eyes.
Truth was apparent when
l stepped in your alley
The scent was within me..
..that you unveiled to me
O Master! My Master
O Master!
Cracks blemish
the line of my destiny
Repair my fate, O Master
Even l'd raised my head in
anticipation at your doorstep
l'd dreamed a lot and tried a lot
When l came across you
When l came across you,
l met your eyes
ln a moment while l bowed
ln a moment while l bowed,
l got my every wish
O Master! My Master
O Master!
Cracks blemish
the line of my destiny
Repair my fate, O Master
My Master
l know how to break apart in pieces
But l'm not aware of
the grace of worshipping
Take me under your shelter.
l won't depart
lf you deny me this time,
l won't be able to pick myself up
O Master! My Master
O Master!
Cracks blemish
the line of my destiny
Repair my fate, O Master
My Master
O Master! My Master
O Master!
Cracks blemish
the line of my destiny
Repair my fate, O Master
l've bowed before you.
l was destroyed
and created at your doorstep
l've bowed before you.
l was destroyed
and created at your doorstep
Repair my fate, O Master
O Master! My Master