Team xRG @ desidhamal.com
O Almighty.
"Our lndia is the best.."
"..of all the world by far"
"We are its buds."
"lt is our garden, all ours, ours."
"Our lndia is the best.."
"..of all the world by far"
This way.
Our tomorrow is based on our today
What we choose to do
today will decide..
..what happens to us tomorrow.
The choice isn't between
good and evil. That's easy.
The real choices of
life are choosing..
..between the lesser of two evils,
or the greater of two goods.
Now what do you choose,
Zooni, what's your choice?
Oh, leave my little girl alone!
Just listen to your heart dear..
..not your father's philosophy!
Try and take some decisions from the
heart rather than the brain, Zulfi
lf l'd used my brain you
wouldn't be here, Nafisa my love.
So? Zooni?
Papa, Mama, l really can't decide.
l'll do whatever you say.
So that's it. lt's decided.
Zooni will not go to Delhi.
l found my prince.
When will Zooni find hers?
When will some footballer
hit her head with a ball?
Any regrets?
Regrets?
l praise God every day that
the great Zulfikar Ali Beg's..
..penalty kick missed the goal..
..and hit me, square on the head.
lt was my worst kick ever!
Any regrets?
Regrets?
That's why l tended to you
in the hospital for a week.
We must accept that Zooni..
..may have to live her life
without that special someone.
That perhaps she will never marry.
And when we're gone who
will look out for her?
We must give her the
chance to live her life.
We need to support her independence.
Be her strength, not her weakness.
Madam Mehbooba
Bobo, the name is Bobo not Mehbooba
Whatever you command your highness.
By the way, your bags
weigh more than your brain!
Obviously! Haven't
you heard that saying?
Which one? - "The buffalo
is bigger than the brain."
No dummy, it's "ls the
brain bigger or the buffalo?"
Fatty!
- Not Fatty, Fatima.
Don't know why you girls insist on
distorting perfectly good names.
Yes, Ruby.
- Not Ruby, Rubina.
come on.. take the bags at least!
lf we wouldve forgotten the bags..
l told you girls, no bags
on the births. Now, come on.
Pick it up and put it over here.
We have to represent Kashmir,
at a Republic Day performance..
..at the President's Palace, in front
of the chief Minister of Delhi..
..and what do l have to pull
this off? A bunch of wild cats!
lf we're a bunch of wild cats
what does that make our leader?
Who said that? Who said that?
You've carried your knitting?
When we're upset,
we say things to distract
Have you taken your knitting?
Kept your ticket safely?
Don't get off at a
station on the way."
God keep you safe.
Papa.. papa!
When papa's upset,
not just his voice
His walk also changes.
Yes, and he can't even cry
in front of all these girls.
But l have no such problem!
Mother.. mother.
l know you have to do this..
..but l don't know why, l'm afraid.
Afraid of what ?
Loosing me to some prince?
Oh, l wish! One look at you,
and he'll be on his knees
Heaven forbid! Will he be a porter?
Kneel to get my bags? - Hush!
Not a porter, not your bags,
he'll take your heart away.
With some poetry maybe..
.."Every once in a while
l get this feeling in my heart..
..that you were made
for me, all apart."
You were living in the mountains
somewhere before there was me."
You have been called down
to this earth, only for me."
l shall leave now.
God keep you safe, my child,
God keep you safe!
God keep you, mama.
Have a safe journey.
Be sure to say a prayer for me
at the Jama Masjid. - Yes, mama.
Take Zooni for an eye
test in the big city..
..and you, Rubina
take care of my baby!
Relax Aunty. Don't worry,
l'm here aren't l?
That's what l'm afraid of Fatima.
- lt's Fatty, aunty.
Bye dear, Bye Zooni!
Mama! Mama!
Yes, my child !
lf the Prince recites
poetry what should l say?
May my life's breath
find refuge in your heart..
..destroyed in your
love may my life depart."
Bye!
Bye Mama!
Why do you do this?
You can say something as well.
Rao!
Oh my God, coming maam.
- Garbage everywhere.. idiot.
Lord Venkateshwa.
Rao at your service madam.
Now listen up, Rao.
We're here for just 7 days.
5 days to the show,
and 2 for holidaying.
l want to sight
- see Delhi, not your bald head.
Stand straight like a man!
l'm not even a man any more Madam.
After years of bowing
to government officers..
..l have come to this sorry state.
Today if l have children,
even they will be born bent over.
Oh, please. Shut up.
l have no interest in your
family planning program!
Where is that tour guide?
Hey you, cartoon Network.
Aunt.. l am the Balwaan.
Not the cartoon Network.
You are exactly what you look like!
Now tell me what's the problem here?
Where do l start?
From the head light to the exhaust..
..there are problems
and more problems.
You think you are very funny?
- Thank you.
ldiot.
- Mention not.
l mean your tour guide.
Where on earth is he?
Don't look around the city
Forget the wasteland too"
Behold God's greatest creation.
Rehan is just above you."
Rehan..
"Marvelous."
Rehan.. Rehan Khan.
You Mr. Romeo.
Stop this cheap poetry!
l hate late comers.
come on, lets go, girls.
Lets go.
You didn't applaud me,
now at least help me
Oh, you're blind.
Yes, you didn't see that?
Are you blind too?
Thank God, l'm not.
That's a nice thing to
say to a blind person.
lf l was blind..
..l couldn't have seen the most
beautiful thing in the world, you.
"Marvelous."
Your beauty made God make a mistake,
what more can i say?
So that you don't caste an evil eye
on yourself, he took your eyes away."
"Marvelous."
Zooni, where are you?
l'm coming Fatty.
Fatty? ls that your
name or your dog's?
Shut up!
come on Balwante hit the gas!
"lll lay my life for you."
"lll do such a thing."
"Friends, where will l go?"
..if l dont get
peace even after death."
"lll lay my life for you."
"lll do such a thing."
Heavenly!
..if l dont get
peace even after death."
lf wish l was a roll of wool..
..wrapped around her fingers..
lf you were a roll of wool,
with the needles.. l'd..
l wish she'd make a sweater out of
me, wear me, even in the summer.
Wow! What a thought!
Zooni, stop encouraging
his nonsense.
l am not the flower jasmine,
l am the flower rose.
l am your lifelong admirer,
not of your friend sitting close."
Hey Mr. Guide, your cheap poetry
is going to get you nowhere.
So, who are you
knitting this sweater for?
She's knitting it for a prince,
not for a devil like you.
And if she was interested in you ..
..she would speak up not sit silent.
Oh, so she does speak?
l knew she was blind,
thought she was mute too
Zooni! Don't talk to him,
You don't know these men..
Looks like you know men very well.
Shut up!
lf you sit there in silence,
regret it you will.
So often after silence love
has awakened, stronger still."
Wonderful!
Bobo!
Tommy, quiet..
There is no limit to human desire..
There is no limit to
human desire, no dearth.
After 2 yards of burial cloth,
we still want 2 yards of earth."
Superb!
Superb! Outstanding!
l'll look pain square in the eye,
face every test laid out for me.
For the sake of your friendship..
..dear friend,
l'll even love my enemy."
Oh yeah, l love your style!
The emperor Shah Jahan once
walked these lanes of the Red Fort.
And so did Mumtaz, his very,
very beautiful wife.
careful!
l can manage myself.
But how will l manage myself,
around you.
Ms. Bobo. Excuse me.
Shall we?
Bobo, tell me,
what does he look like?
Killer, girl, a real killer.
"Marvelous."
He's simply obnoxious!
He looks ok, so l thought
he must be a nice guy..
..but he called me a
stupid girl.. so..
And forget all his sweet talk..
.. the way he looks at women,
its shameful!
And he told me he doesn't believe
in God, can you imagine that?
Look even the crows
are cawing. lt's a sign.
Stay away from that Rehan guide.
How can you stay away
from me and go?
How can your heart forget me so?
That fragrance on your breath is me.
How ever will you stop,
not breathe?"
Great! Fabulous!
come on, let's go.
- come.
"Marvelous."
"lf the moon was to recommend me."
"This is what he'd say to you."
"l want to drop
the veil of decency."
"l want to cross
the line with you."
"l insist on destroying myself."
"On destroying myself in you."
"lf the moon was to recommend me."
"This is what he'd say to you."
"l want to drop
the veil of decency."
"l want to cross
the line with you."
"Your charms are
like a gentle breeze."
"Let them touch me as you pass."
"Your every move a graceful branch."
"Please move into my heart."
"come into my arms,
any excuse will do."
"For l must,
l must destroy myself in you."
"lf the moon was to recommend me."
"This is what he'd say to you."
"l want to drop
the veil of decency."
"l want to cross
the line with you."
"Marvelous."
"lf l tell you my true intentions."
"l'm sure they'll make you blush."
"lf l make you hear my heartbeats."
"l'm sure they'll
leave you flushed."
"But l cannot hide
my feelings true."
"For l must, l must
destroy myself in you."
"lf the moon was to recommend me."
"This is what he'd say to you."
"l want to drop
the veil of decency."
"l want to cross
the line with you."
"l insist on destroying myself."
"On destroying myself in you."
Stand straight. Looking at
you l'm getting a backache.
And you Mr. cartoon Network..
..we have to leave for the
rehearsal at exactly 9 AM tomorrow.
So then leave.
lt's me. Rehan.
l know. Only you can be so impudent.
l want to be even more impudent.
l want you to run away with me.
l want to show you Delhi.
Without your bodyguards..
..don't say no,
not without thinking atleast
You'll anyway be
thinking about me so..
God forbid, the crows are cawing.
l'll wait for you after the
rehearsal tomorrow. With these crows.
"Marvelous."
You have had more girls in your life
than there is mileage on my bus.
Why do you want this blind girl?
What can l do Balwante,
everyone wants the moon.
There's just one headlight in
the sky, that shows us the way.
Now you want that too?
They say in love you
always loose sleep.
l wish someone would love me,
l bloody sleep and sleep and sleep."
Let's go.
Zooni! You must be tired,
go to sleep.
l feel awake after so many years.
l can't sleep now.
l want to be even more impudent,
l want you to run away with me.
Why aren't you concentrating?
can l use your phone?
Pick up, mama!
This is one decision you'll
have to take on your own Zooni .
Oh Lord, how silly of me.
Of course there's no point in your
going sightseeing when you can't see.
No maam.
- Whats the point..
..when you cant see the sights.
Okay. You can go back to the
hostel after the rehearsal.
1 , 2..
Fine! At least you'll be
away from that Rehan guide.
Brother, tell me something.
You stand here all day.
Don't you wish you were
inside on the President's chair?
Why should l think that?
ln the police department
we regularly get promoted.
But once you're President, there's
no scope of promotion at all!
You're a very jolly man!
All thanks to my grandfather.
Grandfather? - My grandfather
worked for the British.
All day long he
would hear them say..
..'Jolly Good' this and
'Jolly Good' that.
When l was born he
was losing his memory.
All he remembered was 'Jolly Good'.
So that's what he
named me. Jolly Good.
Yes, yes have a laugh at me.
Even the officers
that pass by here say..
.."Jolly Good..
Singh" laugh and move on.
l think that's great.
Thanks to you,
the country is run in good spirits!
Thats Jolly Good Singh.
Rehan..
l felt God himself had blessed me.
When all she did was to address me.
Jolly Good
Rickshaw!
Hello.
Look, l sent Rana with
Balwaan and the bus.
No, l'm not coming today.
So what if l didn't tell you earlier.
l'm telling you now.
Let's go.
- You left work without permission?
So?
My father says that if a person
can't be loyal to their work..
..they can't be trusted
for anything.
Very good.
l've left work for you and you're
giving me a speech on loyalty?
My mother says there is
nothing bigger than loyalty.
lf you're done with your mother
and father's sermons can we go?
Why am l saying all this to you ?
Why are you saying all this to me?
So that l go back to work?
Yes.
Think about it, if l go
today l won't come back tomorrow.
l'll go back to the guest house,
you'll go back to work.
Tomorrow you'll take the day
off and then we'll go, ok?
Not okay.
You've heard what your
parents have said. Now hear me.
lf l go today l will
not come back tomorrow.
You'll come. Let's go.
l don't live the life of
the selfless..
..nor do l grab another's wine.
lf she has love let
her come and declare it..
..to ask her,
to follow her, l decline."
God be with you.
"Marvelous."
Greetings Ms. Zooni.
Greetings Mr. Jolly
l am wishing you and
you are wishing me.
Jolly good. Jolly good.
You know what happened yesterday?
Yesterday l said good
morning to 20 people..
..and they all said good
evening to me instead.
How can so many people be wrong?
lt was my watch that was wrong.
lt stopped in the morning..
..so l said 'good
morning' to people all day long!
l can't see Rehan today.
l can't see him either.
l think he's like me.
completely clean at heart..
..and completely muddled
in the head.
l couldn't quench my thirst with
water so l set off for the bar.
l gave up
complaining to God about you..
..for He is most
smitten by you, by far."
Jolly good. Jolly good.
"Marvelous."
l'm with you now.
So, how are you going to
show Delhi to a blind girl?
can you see me?
No.
What's my voice like?
Like the thunder before the storm.
What do l smell like?
Like the earth after
the first rain.
What do l feel like?
Like a prince in
a beggar's clothing
And just like this
you will see Delhi.
Watch out! This is the
Gateway of Blood.
The emperor
Aurangzeb had his brother..
..Dara Shikoh beheaded,
and hung his head up here. - there.
Exactly where you are standing.
And the British
government killed two sons and..
Rehan! -..a grandson of Bahadur
Shah Zafar, right there, behind you.
Rehan!
Please. That's enough.
Let's leave from here.
This is the bloody history of Delhi.
The Mughals, the British, a lot
of bloodshed had happened here
That's why, till today, tears
of blood flow from these walls.
Scared? What did you think?
l wouldn't get back
at you for yesterday?
And what did you think,
l'd get scared so easily?
When l have never seen any colors
how can the color of blood scare me?
Now you're scared.
"O Lord."
l'm going. l'm going to Delhi,
to get her back.
lt's been 4 days. That's enough
to understand life. - Zulfi.
What'll be happening to
her without us? Just think?
She's brought up on home food,
she must be starving.
The Delhi crowds, who
will look out for her?
l'm not there.
"Marvelous."
l can't take her agony
any more, l'm going.
Are you going for her
sake or for your own?
Lets go.
You were right, Rehan.
You did show me Delhi.
"Those people fall in love.."
Here is your rolled bread.
They say, the feelings
one gets for the country..
..in front of the
Eternal Soldier Flame..
..one gets for love in
front of the Taj Mahal.
Feelings, love,
that's all just talk.
When it comes down to basics
then needs are everything.
Needs of the stomach,
needs of the body
So you believe needs
are everything..
..and feelings are nothing?
- Yes.
So all this time
you're spending with me..
..is this also to fulfil some need?
You shouldn't tease a man
like me. My needs are great.
Even one chicken is not enough.
Even one girl is not enough.
So, Mr. Rehan, how
are things with you?
And how are you Zeenat?
Forgotten how l am?
come and meet me, l'll remind you.
lt's my fault actually.
He's been busy with me.
That's what makes
Rehan guide so special.
So, when do you plan on
being busy with me again?
l can't explain the ways
of this market to you,
He who is sold, can't
ever be a buyer anew."
You'll never improve. Ever.
Good evening.
You seem to know her very well.
That's me.
l told you l only believe in needs..
..not in feelings or love.
And l only believe in love.
Meeting that guide on the sly.
Forget Helen, l can't
believe you lied to me!
This is just why l lied to you.
You're less of a
friend and more of a Hitler.
Hitler? l was just protecting you.
Not me. You were
protecting my blindness.
Zooni, how do l explain it to you?
He just isn't right for you.
Perhaps, but when l'm with him..
..l feel happy, feel alive.
And this feeling is special.
Very special.
But l don't like
that Guide. Not one bit.
And l don't care what you say.
l'll never let you
go with him. Never.
Turn off your light.
Good night, Fatty.
Hello, dear. good luck.
- Thank you, Mr. Jolly.
Jolly Singh! could you please allow
my good luck to come in? Please?
Don't insist. This tough
Sikh has a soft heart.
l'm sorry but rules are rules
and rules are never Jolly Good.
lt's ok. l know you're
only doing your duty.
But still,
l will be singing for him.
Thats Jolly Good.
Thats Jolly bad, l say.
check her properly.
People say that after so
many years of lndependence..
..our Republic Day
has lost all meaning.
That it's just another holiday.
But it's not just a holiday for me.
This day marks the
birth of my country.
They say that the state
of our country is like..
..that of our old monuments.
What's beautiful
was only in the past.
l am blind so l don't see
the faults in my country..
..but why can't those who see,
see the beauty here?
What Emperor Shah Jahan had
said of my home state of Kashmir..
..we believe that's
true for all of lndia.
lf there is a heaven on earth..
..it is here, it is here,
it is here.
"The earth here
changes color at every step."
"The language here has
all the colors best."
"The earth here
changes color at every step."
"The language here has
all the colors best."
"The climes wear green
on their head."
"The sky lays a blue
sheet over it's bed."
"Golden river, Green ocean,
Every part so dressed."
"My colorful, colorful country,
my country full of color."
"Motherland, l bow to you."
"The sun with its
rose-tinted neck plays around."
"The yellow scarf of
flowers covers the shy ground."
"color in the veil,
color on the mound..
..bright, bright color all around."
"My colorful, colorful country,
my country full of color."
"Bright red faces all around,
smiling and glowing in fervour."
"colorful laughter,
colorful happiness..
..relationships full of color."
"color in promises, color in
memories, color, color, more color."
"My colorful, colorful country,
my country full of color."
"The color of love here runs so deep,
once its on it's there for keeps."
"The color of true love so still
simply glistens does not spill."
"color in charm, color in manner,
all colors full of flavor."
"My colorful, colorful country,
my country full of color."
"The earth here
changes color at every step."
"The language here has
all the colors best."
"The climes wear
green on their head."
"The sky lays a blue
sheet over it's bed."
"Golden river, Green ocean,
Every part so dressed."
"My colorful, colorful country,
my country full of color."
Go Zooni, he's
waiting outside for you.
Thanks, Ruby.
- Hes so sweet.
He said l am the
cutest of all the girls.
After you of course, Zooni. Go.
Stop. You're not going anywhere.
Fatty.
certainly not like this.
With your hair all over the place.
You haven't even worn
your stole properly.
l can't let you go like this.
You're really..
Ok, Ok, that's enough of that.
Go now.
So sweet, Fatty.
- Bobo.
Let's go.
The fire is in the sun, but it's
the earth that does the burning.
The eyes fall in love..
..but it's the heart
that does the suffering."
You're looking exceptionally
beautiful this evening.
Really?
You're looking exactly
the same to me.
You have brought me here? You ?
l thought you don't believe in God.
Will you just keep quiet for a bit?
Shut your eyes now.
Rehan, my eyes are always shut.
Rest your eyelids
They say this blessed
water does miracles.
l hope that's true.
No one has ever asked
for such a blessing for me.
l'm not asking for you,
l'm asking for myself.
Perhaps if your eyes are open
you'll keep your mouth shut!
lt's so loud!
This is the real Delhi.
The quiet museums, Red Fort,
that's not the real Delhi.
This is the sound of Delhi.
the essence of Delhi
l wish l was deaf as well ..
Just a minute. Wait here.
Hello.
- Rehan..
Yes, it's me.
Rehan.
Yes, yes, l got it alright.
Rehan, you're watching me,
aren't you?
Rehan..
Zooni!
What's this madness?
l just wanted to show you.
Show what? That you're such a fool?
No..
- l'll call you later.
Boys, and girls you know..
..they impress each other on
their first dates. So l too.
l am so sorry.
Your life is very precious Zooni..
..don't waste it on anyone.
certainly not on me.
My mother says, to gain something
you have to loose something.
Oh God!
Mother says this, father says that..
..where is Zooni in all this?
What does Zooni say?
Nobody's ever asked Zooni
l'm asking you. Tell me.
l like you.
Let's go.
Now you're scared.
"O Almighty."
Our destiny has brought us
these precious moments today
Look at me up close,
imbibe me in every way
You're still scared.
Just in case your fate
has another card to play
Think we'll never meet again,
just suppose..
..not till this lifetime
is forever closed
l'll manage from here.
come in to my arms, hold me close..
..we may never again
have this night's repose
Think we'll never meet again,
just suppose..
..not till this lifetime
is forever closed
come in to my arms, hold me close..
..we may never again
have this night's repose
Think we'll never meet again,
just suppose..
not till this
lifetime is forever closed
"Embrace me."
Where is Rehan the gorgeous?
What's the time, Bobo?
Ten thirty
My watch is fine, why is he late?
lt's our last day.
Maybe he's getting you
a gift, so he's late.
He himself is a gift.
No news?
No.
No Fatty. Nothing yet.
Mama.
Zooni!
How are you my child?
We saw the performance on TV.
lt was fantastic.
When everyone stood up to clap.
Your father and me..
l want to speak to
you about something.
What is it? Tell me.
When papa and you first met.
After he tended to
you in the hospital..
..if he had suddenly disappeared.
What would you have done?
l would have asked him
why he was misbehaving.
And told him to stop
his nonsense immediately.
Misbehaving? Who is misbehaving?
So is that what l should do?
Who is he?
- Who is who?
Rehan.
Rehan?
- Rehan?
So, do you love him?
Do you love him? What are
you saying? Give me the phone.
Just a minute. - Give me the phone.
l'll deal with this.
Yes.
- So what have you decided?
Nothing. l don't think he loves me.
Just remember one thing dear..
..give your life for the
one who gives you his love..
..but give your
self-respect only to..
..the one who is willing to
be destroyed for your love.
This is Humayun's tomb.
lt was constructed for
him by his wife Hamida.
Take a look at what a
wife made for her husband.
And you can't even
make me breakfast.
Don't worry, l'll start
building your tomb right away.
come.. - l am blind and you
are the one who can't see me..
lf by mistake l have made a mistake..
..then please consider it
a mistake and forget it.
But only forget the mistake..
..even by mistake
don't ever forget me."
Heard that? Great!
Take them ahead.
Let's go.
- But our guide?
No but! Only Jat!
Move it! Look here,
the Qutub Minar.
No Zooni, Fatty was right.
You should love a prince,
not a devil like me.
lt's too late now. Now
this devil is my prince.
l can't give you anything.
Remember l told you, l believe
in needs, not in feelings or love.
Women are like cities for me.
l spend some time in one.
l get to know it,
get immersed in it..
..and then move to another city.
This is me, and l can't change.
Look Rehan, all this stuff
about princes is good..
..in dreams and stories.
ln reality l have found you.
We haven't met by chance,
we've met by destiny.
lf not the rest of our lives..
..we can spend the next
1 2 hours together, can't we?
Perhaps that's all we have,
just today, just now.
Don't come close to me,
this storm will destroy you.
May my life's breath
find refuge in your heart
find refuge in your heart.
Destroyed in your love
may my life depart."
"O Almighty."
How can you love me so much?
How can anyone love
another so much?
l promise you this Zooni Ali Beg..
..the next 1 2 hours will be
the most beautiful of your life.
"The raindrops have a conspiracy."
"They have a silent wish, a plea."
"Look, just see."
"Softly, slowly this gentle breeze."
"Says so much, listen please."
"Why the distance
between you and me."
"Look, just see."
"Rain."
"Never again will the
winds be this shameless."
"Never again will our
steps falter so blameless."
"Never again will the
winds be this shameless."
"Never again will our
steps falter so blameless."
"This rain is not so straight,
it has a twist."
"lt's telling us
something as it pours and mists."
"Just understand it."
"Softly, slowly this
gentle breeze."
"Says so much, listen please."
"Why the distance
between you and me."
"Look, just see."
"Desire, like a fire-fly,
glows bright then dim."
"lt's such a sweet
predicament that we're in."
"Desire, like a fire-fly,
glows bright then dim."
"lt's such a sweet
predicament that we're in."
"Don't discard the request
from our lips like this."
"Don't call this wish
of our breathe remiss."
"Just touch, Feel this."
"Softly, slowly this
gentle breeze."
"Says so much, listen please."
"Why the distance
between you and me."
"Look, just see."
Rehan! Wake up. Wake up.
Rehan! Wake up.
My train is at 1 0. lf you don't
wake up l'll miss it.
l spoke to Fatty and she's
bringing my things to the station.
We don't have to go to the
guest house. You Sleep so much!
Wake up! Don't you have
to go to work as well?
And don't you dare miss work today
See l forgot, Mama had told
me to get the eye test done.
And Papa has asked for a chess set.
can we stop and get one on
the way? Do we have time?
Rehan! Are you listening?
Oh, l didn't even say
goodbye to Jolly Good Singh.
You please tell him for me.
Here's my address..
Will you write to me?
ls this your wife's first
visit home after marriage?
l want to say..
No, Rehan.
You made no promises and l
will not ask you for anything.
l always wanted love to be the
most important thing in my life..
..and now, thanks to you, it is.
You were wrong Rehan.
l am not destroyed in
your storm l am rejuvenated.
Now your picture will
remain with me always.
And now l can't leave.
Not until you step off my stole.
God be with you Rehan, be happy.
Zooni!
"O Almighty."
Now can l say l told you so
No
l won't say it. l'll never say it.
May my life's breath
find refuge in your heart."
Rehan.
May my life's breath
find refuge in your heart.
Destroyed in your love
may my life depart."
Zooni..
- Rehan!
Fatty! lf not for me at least
pull the chain for Zooni.
With pleasure.
What's going on?
What is the guide doing here?
The brave heart is
taking the bride.
"Marvelous."
He wants to marry you?
What? Who is he? Where is he from?
What does he do? What does he
look like? He wants to marry her!.
They love each other.
So what did you say?
What could l say? l said
he must ask my parents.
What did she tell him?
She's our daughter..
..she wouldn't give any
answer without our consent.
Zooni, l have complete
faith in your choice.
Yes, my darling, tell him yes.
And we're coming to Delhi
right away to get you married.
come quickly mama, l miss you.
Now where are you off to?
We're going to Delhi
aren't we? We'll need tickets.
As usual he runs away the
moment there are tears in his eyes.
God keep you mama, God keep you.
God keep you my child, God keep you.
Our daughter has found her prince.
She has found her prince.
When did you last
get your eyes checked ?
l don't remember.
Many years ago in Srinagar.
This is the problem.
We doctors go on about
checkups and no one listens.
These days science
has progressed so much.
What was impossible 5
years ago is possible today .
What do you mean?
Retinal replacement can help you.
The chances are very slim..
..l warn you, but
there is still a chance.
Are you saying Zooni
will be able to see?
There's a chance..
We'll take the chance doctor.
l'll check the first available date.
There won't be any problem doctor?
The operation must go well.
Don't worry our best team is on it.
l'll meet you after the operation.
Thank you.
Rehan! You're hugging
me for the 1 0th time.
l'm not complaining,
but please don't worry.
l'll be fine.
lf you're so worried then why
didn't we wait for mama and papa?
We could have done
this after the wedding?
Let's go, it's time.
Don't forget to get mama
and papa from the station.
And Jolly Good wants to
come here later as well.
You're going to the
President's Palace, right?
Yes.
Zooni!
l love you very much.
l know.
After the bomb blast in Peshawar..
..Pakistan the lndependent
Kashmir Front has demanded..
..that both lndia and
Pakistan leave Kashmir.
They want an lndependent Kashmir..
..or else there will be
many more attacks to come.
The chief Minister is alive..
..but as per early reports, 8
security officers have been killed.
And at least 1 5
others are badly wounded.
The main building has
not been harmed very much..
..but the left side of it
has been completely destroyed.
2 terrorists have been
captured and..
..the lKF have claimed
responsibility.
Their demand is that lndia
and Pakistan leave Kashmir.
Maam.. move aside.
And let it be
an independent country.
Zooni..
Mummy.
My child
Mama l can see, l can see.
- Yes, my darling.
Papa l can see.
You can cry in front of
me now papa.
l can see you cry.
But where is Rehan?
He's not with you?
Didn't he get you
from the station?
Papa, where are they taking us?
Why has your breathing
changed papa?
Why? l don't understand.
Mama, where is Rehan?
Why aren't we waiting for him?
Mama why are you crying?
Mama? Papa?
Why are you crying mama?
Papa where are we?
Please let me go from here.
ls it necessary to do this now?
- Yes Ma'am.
What do we have to do?
Why can't we wait for Rehan?
Papa, where are we? Papa?
l'm getting suffocated here papa.
Please let's go.
Mama let's go. Please.
The bomb blast
at the President's Palace.
What do we have to do with that?
We don't know anything.
You're still crying mama,
please don't.
Please, papa get me out.
- Doctor?
Zooni..
l was going to identify him, but
his state was such that l could not.
So you have to identify him,
Zooni. ls this Rehan?
"O Almighty."
No! lt can't be Rehan. lt can't!
Please, don't make my
daughter go through this. Please.
l am sorry, sire.
lt's compulsory.
Zooni my darling,
even this is life.
lf only l was a roll of wool..
..wrapped around her fingers..
'That fragrance
on your breath is me.'
'How ever will you stop,
not breathe?'
'How can you love me so much?
How can anyone love another so much?'
"O Almighty."
'Don't come close to me,
this storm will destroy you.'
'Think about it, if l go today
l won't come back tomorrow.'
Rehan!
At this time we are at the
Bureau of Military lntelligence.
There is not much information
forthcoming on the blast..
..but here is the head of
the Anti-Terrorist Unit.
Mr. Susheel Rawat. Mr. Rawat.
What can you tell us
about the blast?
When we know more.
We'll tell you more.
But something to go on,
who is responsible.
Thats all l can tell you now.
These media people.
They start 24 hour channels and
then get after us to fill the time.
Dont worry, sir.
Everything is under control.
Sir, Tyagi has been called
from intelligence agency RAW
Tyagi? Now things
will be out of control.
So Tyagi, case solved yet?
So what does your
psychology mumbo-jumbo say?
This is his work.
Who? Who are you talking about?
These two are telling the truth.
They haven't seen him.
They were simply given instructions.
The master planner is someone else.
Do you need an invitation to
tell me his name? Who is it?
This man has changed
the face of the lKF.
He has taken a rag-tag group and
made it a professional organization.
A group on par with the
most deadly in the world.
On par with the best intelligence
agencies in the world.
lt's because of this
man that 8 ships and..
..a large part of the
Bombay port are under water.
lt's because of this man that
lslamabad airport's new wing..
..was destroyed even
before it could be completed.
He has changed the face of
terrorism in lndia and Pakistan
Those blood shot eyes and..
.. fanatical terrorists
are a thing of the past.
This man is a thinker. A planner.
No one knows his name.
No one knows his past,
or where he comes from.
He can be anyone.
The man sitting next
to you on the train..
..or a bank teller, or even
the cigarette seller outside.
He is intelligent and he's
dangerous, and he can be anyone.
We have to find him.
For if we don't, he can take
terrorism to a level beyond..
..our imagination because our
imagination is nothing like his.
l'm sorry Grandfather, the mission
was not entirely successful.
l had set everything.
Those fools just didn't
follow instructions.
Not everyone can be like my grandson.
A perfect soldier.
But even he slipped this once.
That too for some woman.
lt's very unusual that you
were carried away like this.
And the woman what about her?
She is with God.
Now listen to me.
You don't have to worry
about this soldier Sir.
My concentration was, is..
..and will always
remain on our independence.
l am a soldier and nothing else.
That's all l wanted to hear my son.
Now l'll meet you after
the Bangkok operation.
May God keep you safe.
You had taken me to my goal, Zooni.
should never have
taken you off that train.
But l became weak.
And l fell in love with you.
l hope you can forgive me.
l should never have
brought you into my life. Never.
Sorry, l fell in love with you.
Sorry, Zooni.
God be with you, Zooni.
"O Almighty."
You are the Defence Secretary.
You must be having some powers.
Do something. Get
that Tyagi off my back!
Last year the Al-Qaeda's
attempt on Delhi airport ..
..was foiled by Tyagi.
She got lucky, once.
And now she thinks she's a
big shot intelligence officer.
l can't do anything now.
The Defence Minister himself
has asked her to be on this case.
Sir, it's nothing less
than the Armageddon.
The press shouldn't
even get a whiff of this.
This lKF has made our life hell.
First the President Palace
bombing then Karachi Oil refinery..
..and last year it was
the plane hijacking.
And now we hear
they've stolen parts..
..from us Pakistan and Russia..
..and are ready with
a nuclear missile!
Sir, This is their way of
forcing lndia out of Kashmir.
When Kashmir's ruler, Hari Singh,
decided to join lndia in 1 947..
..then why this talk
of independence now?
But the Kashmiri's had
also been promised a vote..
..a referendum to decide
whether they wanted to stay..
..a part of lndia, join Pakistan
or then be independent.
All these years later they are
still to get that referendum.
What referendum
are you talking about?
When half of Kashmir is occupied
by Pakistan, how is it possible?
A referendum needs to
include all of Kashmir..
..why should it include only half?
Mr. Rawat.
This is not an lndia-Pakistan
issue any more.
lKF wants both lndia and
Pakistan to leave Kashmir.
They want a separate country.
An independent Kashmir.
Please, l know the
history of lndia and Pakistan.
Tell me about this bomb.
How powerful is this bomb,
Mrs. Tyagi, and what are the dangers?
ln the last few years over 1 5,000
people have been killed in Mumbai,
Oklahoma city, New York, Bali,
Madrid and London.
And losses have run into millions.
But if they use this bomb
5 million people can die.
An entire city can be destroyed.
That city can also be
our capital, New Delhi.
We must stop this bomb.
Whatever it takes.
But Sir, this bomb
is useless for them.
What do you mean?
The missile needs a special,
lndian made trigger.
lf they don't have that,
they can't use the bomb
Only until they get the trigger.
Only until then.
Sir, there's nothing to
worry about. Outside Delhi,
We have 6 triggers at various
military bases around the country.
ln Rajasthan, Kutch, Darjeeling,
Amritsar, Leh and Kashmir.
They are safe there.
l want all the
triggers brought to Delhi.
ln the next 1 2 hours
they will all be here, Sir.
Get me the Defence
Minister of Pakistan,
..l want to share this
information with him. - Yes, sir.
We can be sure. Just as we are
taking steps to secure the triggers,
lKF's mastermind will be
taking steps to steal them.
Pass. Pass me.
Pass here, come on.
captain Ranjeev.
Hit! captain Ranjeev!
Major Suraj!
Brigadier for you, sir!
- coming!
Yes, sir. l understand, sir.
My unit has a 1 00%
success rate on missions, Sir.
And l will bring this
trigger to you myself.
Be alert. lKF will be
after you at every step.
lf the weather holds up, the trigger
will be with you in 3 hours, Sir.
Glory to lndia! - Over and out, sir.
Glory to lndia!
captain Ranjeev.
This is the day
every soldier lives for.
The last time you
saved me from the lKF.
Today we both must save
the country from the lKF.
This soldier is ready to take
lives or to give his own life.
Anything for his motherland, Sir.
Get the boys ready.
- Yes, sir.
Good news.
The trigger will be with us soon.
God keep Rehan!
God is great!
captain Ranjeev.
Thank you.
Hi, baby.
Mummy is fine. How are you?
Mummy will save the country
l know you wanted custard.
But Grandma has made rice pudding
with so much love, so please eat it.
What have you brought?
Rice pudding or custard?
We've checked the list of
officers coming from Kashmir.
Everything is okay.
How can it not be ok?
l have hand-picked these officers.
They are the army's
very best, elite forces.
Ok, so that's where he is.
- Who?
An ace officer from the Jat
Regiment Sir, captain Ranjeev.
His wife reported he hadn't
called her for a couple of months.
She wanted to know if he
was on some secret mission.
That's wives for you.
Am sure she was after him
with some pudding or such.
Poor man must have
needed a break from..
..all that so he
didn't call, understandable.
He didn't call his
wife for two months?
Just find out, was his last
mission to do with the lKF?
Right, maam.
Yes Ma'am. Major Suraj's
regiment was surrounded by the lKF.
At the last moment captain Ranjeev's
regiment got there and saved them.
Everyone from captain
Ranjeev's regiment was killed.
Only he survived.
Oh my God.
That's him! We have to stop him!
Sounds like the base
is trying to contact us.
The signal is too weak.
Alpha 1 to Eagle. Do you read me?
lt's amazing isn't it? Such a small
thing can take so many lives.
Our lives too, in it's defence
- So?
l'm not afraid of dying Sir,
But it's better to kill for
your country than be killed
You want to kill people? Make
them eat your wife's cooking!
Santosh!
Ajay!
Eijaz!
Ranjeev!
You are dying the
death of a brave soldier.
He who dies on the
battlefield goes to heaven.
God keep you.
Grandfather. l am not empty handed.
Praise be to God! You don't have
just a trigger there with you.
lt is our decades long dream.
We have sacrificed so much for.
You must get that
trigger to us now at any cost.
Kill, or be killed.
Yes, grandfather.
l will meet you in 3 hours
At Shikara 1 pick up point.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
l was right. That was no accident.
He was in the helicopter.
Jam all the phone lines
in the area,..
..mobiles, satellite, internet,
everything.
l want a communications blackout.
We can't jam radio signals, we have
military operations in that area
lf you can't jam them, you can
at least monitor them, can't you?
Search the entire area.
come on, boys. Lets get going!
- Yes, sir.
How far is the road unit?
No! He's still alive.
l don't care how
many bodies you saw.
l know Rehan will
reach the pick up point.
l have not given him permission
to die. He cannot die.
Rehan!
Quickly, call Grandpa. Go. Fast.
Papa!
- Grandpa!
Hand me the scissors, please.
Who is this, mom?
Rehan, l don't know. Go,
please sit over there.
ls he also dead like Grandma?
Quiet! Little monkey
His pulse is quite weak.
Try the phone. ls it working now?
No papa. lt's still dead.
We've done the best we could.
l'm no doctor.
What can we do?
You can't go and get a
doctor in this weather.
Not for 50 kilometers
in this storm. No way.
Mom! Please leave Rehan.
Rehan!
- Mummy.
Nothing darling. Nothing
Now it's up to you young man.
We can only pray you
have some reason to live.
lt can be two days?
lt can be two weeks?
How can you not know
when the storm will pass?
l want an update every hour,
you hear?
can't you do anything right?
Till l don't see a body
l can't believe he's dead.
Don't do that Rehan.
What are you up to?
l can't hear his heartbeat.
There is no heartbeat.
Rehan wants to hear his heartbeat,
like he hears Grandpa's.
The heart is not here, it's there.
Forgive me Zooni. l have no choice.
Do you know the
cricketer Rahul Dravid?
Rahul Dravid is Rehan's father.
Because Rehan's
father is dead you see,
..so mom said Rehan
could choose any father.
So Rehan chose Rahul Dravid.
Are you Mr.
Dependiddle like Rahul Dravid?
can you also be completely
trusted like Rahul Dravid?
That outhouse of
yours is falling apart.
Look, look the dead man is awake.
Don't talk like that.
When the weather is better we'll
get it fixed. lt's freezing. - Yes.
Before you thank me.
come and eat something.
Don't drink so much
you'll become a hittototomas.
Not hittototomas, kid. Hippopotomas.
And where did you learn this word?
From colonel uncle. Hitto.
Hittototomas.
Hippopotamus.
Would you like something?
l'm sorry l didn't get your name.
captain Ranjeev!
lndian Army.
l didn't know there were
military operations here.
There are such few of us here.
What will the militants do here?
They can hide.
Rehan.
The dead man stinks so
Rehan thought.. - Rehan.
So sorry.
Strange, when Zooni couldn't
see she didn't bang into a thing.
And now that she can see, she's
constantly walking into things.
Thank you for saving me.
You were lucky, so you survived.
What did l do?
ls it just the 3 of you here?
Zooni's mother died a
couple of years ago.
And left me all alone.
And before that her
husband died in a bomb blast.
l don't know why, but Zooni
blames herself for his death.
When will this storm end?
l must leave from here.
lt's hard to say. lt might
stop tomorrow or maybe a week.
Don't think of leaving
in this weather though.
certainly not in your state.
Rest a while. You are our guest.
captain Ranjeev..
cheers.
Dispenser of lndia's destiny.
You keep teaching me things.
So boring. Tell Rehan a story.
..Dispenser of lndia's destiny
You're not a good mother.
You never tell Rehan stories.
l don't know any stories.
- Bad mummy.
Not me. You. You're a bad boy.
Go. l'm not talking to you.
Rehan loves you more
than you love Rehan.
But mom Rehan already
knows the national anthem.
Let's hear it.
Thou art the ruler of the
minds of all the people.. Dravid,
..Orissa and Bengal.
Dravid, Orissa and Bengal.
You and your Dravid fixation.
Do you know the national anthem?
No.
See even the dead man
doesn't know the national anthem.
Please tell mom,
not to teach Rehan.
The phone's dead.
Tell her not to teach Rehan.
What's this?
Which soldier doesn't
know the national anthem?
Why are you lying to the child?
l am not here to teach
him the national anthem,
..and l'm not here
to play with him.
l don't care if l lied to him..
..l'm a soldier on a
mission not his father!
come here immediately!
Why, grandpa.
lf you don't eat vegetables
how will you slay the dragon?
So, you must have it.
captain Ranjeev, come and join us.
Tell us about your life.
l've heard soldiers have
fascinating stories to tell.
l'm not hungry thank you.
l'll just go to bed.
Your bed has been made upstairs.
The room on the left.
Dead man made mom cry.
Eat your food.
What's this?
Mom has sent it for you.
So you'll get better
faster so you can leave faster.
But what is it?
Poison.
Milk with turmeric.
And don't try and throw it
in the Wc, it stinks it up..
..and mom finds out.
Don't throw it out either,
the snow gets yellow.
And in the wash basin the color
stains it, you'll get caught.
And yes! lf you find
some other way.
Please, tell Rehan.
Next time Rehan will do the same.
Okay? Goodnight.
lt really is poison.
"come closer now, l will not
come back again and again"
"Put your arms around me,
so l can cry again and again"
"Love from your eyes.."
'lf only l was a roll of wool..
..wrapped around her fingers..'
"Think we will never meet again.."
"..just suppose, not till
this lifetime is forever closed"
"come into my arms, hold me close.."
"..we may never again
have the night's repose."
"Think we'll never meet again,
just suppose.."
"..not till this
lifetime is forever closed."
"Think we will never meet again.."
"..just suppose, not till
this lifetime is forever closed"
"O Almighty."
Thank you.
l am sorry.
Yesterday l was very rude.
Actually, l'm not
very good with children.
Am not very good with words either.
But l am good with a hammer.
Give it to me.
Not everything can be done alone.
Rehan doesn't have a father..
..so he sometimes..
he won't trouble you again.
lts okay.
He's a good kid.
So have you forgiven me then?
Thing is, l spend
so much time alone..
..that l don't know how to
behave in company any more.
Like this one time l went to..
..my friend Mihir Wohra's
house for a party.
l asked his wife how she
likes being wife number 2.
Turns out she was wife number 1 ..
..and had no idea
there was a wife number 2.
After this l decided l
would stick to safe topics.
So l asked my colonel how
his son was doing at school?
Now that's safe? Right?
Wrong. Just that day his son
had been thrown out of school..
..for biting his teacher's bum.
And not just that.
He was sent back to apologise the..
..following day and he ended up
biting her other bum.
close your eyes.
Rehan doesn't want to wash his hair.
You have to wash your hair or you'll
get such big, big insects in it.
Let them come Rehan will take
the insects for a walk every day.
Rehan doesn't want to wash his hair.
- May l help?
Give it a try.
l'm not talking to
you l'm talking to him.
Dead man is on my side!
He's such a sweet kid.
Why are you bothering him.
But he has to wash his hair.
He'll wash it
when he feels like it.
cheater!?
Dead man is a cheater!
Rehan! Look up.
You were right.
Everything can't be done alone.
come on, Rehan.
Dead man is funny.
Don't call him dead man, son.
Rehan likes the dead man.
can l help you?
l'm fine. Thanks.
Everything can't be done alone.
You told us
some good stories today.
Why have you stopped
telling stories?
Your father talks a lot
after a couple of drinks.
Earlier l couldn't see.
Now l've seen too much
to believe in stories.
Your family must be worried.
You've been missing for a few days.
l have no family,
l never met my parents.
They died when l was 3.
l'm sorry you're so lonely.
Not at all. Why do you say that?
Your smile doesn't
reach your eyes.
A soldier's life is like that.
There must be someone else
hidden behind that soldier
Perhaps.
But, l don't think
l really understand him.
Sometimes to understand
yourself..
..you need to see yourself
from someone else's eyes.
l could never get
that close to anyone.
Why? You couldn't trust anyone?
l don't trust myself.
And then everytime,
a new mission, a new city.
l couldn't be in any
one place for too long
Sometimes you seem very familiar.
"The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief"
"The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure."
"The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief."
"The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure."
"A difficult song this is,
can you sing it for me pure."
"Moon blooms sugar sucking
creams the thieving thief."
"The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief."
"The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure."
"Surly Khadak Singh simmers and
stutter sputter go the shutters."
"Stutter sputter go the shutters
making surly Khadak Singh simmer."
"Surely Khadak Singh simmers and
stutter sputter go the shutters."
"Stutter sputter go the shutters
making surly Khadak Singh simmer."
"A difficult song this is,
can you sing it for me pure."
"Stutter sputter go the shutters."
"Surely Khadak Singh simmers more."
"The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief."
"The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure."
"The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief."
"The silly ant sucks sugar,
illy sugar sucking ant for sure."
"Ripe Papaya upon the ripe tree."
"Tree ripe or ripe Papaya?"
"The ripe tree Pinkoo picks."
"Pinkoo picks the ripe Papaya."
"Say it."
"Ripe Papaya upon the ripe
tree picks 'Pinkoo ripe kapda'."
"Kapda? cloth?"
"Ripe Papaya upon the ripe tree,
pick on tree or Papaya ripe?"
"Pinkoo picks the ripe tree,
pinkoo picks the Papaya ripe."
"A difficult song this is,
can you sing it for me pure."
"Pinkoo picks the ripe tree
Pinkoo picks the Papaya ripe."
"The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief."
"The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure."
"The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
if fright freaks the thieving thief."
"The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure."
"A difficult song this is,
can you sing it for me pure."
"The moon booms blooms, balloons
of fright freaks the thieving thief.
"The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief."
"The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure."
Rehan will not call
him dead man any more.
You're my good son.
can Rehan call dead man, papa?
Please?
close your eyes.
So tell me captain Ranjeev,
have you ever loved..
..a woman so deeply that
her smile made you breathless?
l..
l loved my Nafisa like that.
She was..
Heavenly!
- Papa, you've started again.
l've told you not to drink
in front of mama's photograph.
Let me sit and drink
on the Mosque ground..
..or show me a place
where God is not found"
Fantastic! Superb!
ln this life without
you l have no..
complaint."
No complaint, l have no complaint.
Enough papa, enough.
What are you doing?
We're having such a nice time.
Let's go, papa.
Let me finish this drink.
"ln this life without
you l have no complaint.
But this life without
you is no life anyway.."
l wish l could bury my head in
your veil and cry, just cry.."
Are you sure your eyes
themselves don't lack in tears..
..are dry, just dry?"
The letter 'H'
How do you do, dear one?
How do you think, dear one?
l'm just happy oh ho ho.
So, you've slipped then aa ha ha."
What if l let my
heart live in your eyes?
What if l close my eyes,
and punish your heart?"
What can l say in praise
of the one who made you?"
These nights, this clime,
this river side, this playful breeze"
Time has given us
such beautiful pain.
..l am not me anymore
and you are not the same.
Our hearts tremble
now as they meet.
Like they were never
apart for even a beat.
But you got lost and so did l.
After our travel together..
Now you're scared.
Who are you?
How do you know all this?
You can't know.
What's happening to me?
l hear him in your voice,
your breath, it's all the same.
Zooni.
lt's me. Rehan.
Your Rehan.
What l did to you.
l've never forgiven myself for it.
l promised myself
l'd stay away from you.
l didn't want to cause
you more pain.
Perhaps it was God's justice
that l had to die at your doorstep.
But you kept me alive.
And now l want to live.
l want to live for you,
for our son.
Rehan.. You are Rehan?
My real name is Rehan Qadri.
Kashmiri?
Yes.
- Go on.
When l met Zooni
l was on a mission.
And that's why you fell
in love with my daughter?
Promised her marriage?
Was that all a part of
your mission?
That was my weakness.
l was not free to love.
l am deeply sorry and
ashamed about my selfish love.
And you've come back
to repeat that mistake?
My mission is not complete yet.
After this storm, it will be.
Then l will stay with
Zooni for the rest of my life.
Mission! Mission! What
is this great mission..
Because of which you're
playing with all our lives?
l can't say.
- What?
l know my silence
can go against me.
But l do not want to lie and
l cannot tell you the truth.
All l can say in my
defence is that my love is true.
l have given you a lot of pain..
..still l am asking
you to fill my wounds.
l know l'm not worthy
of your forgiveness..
..but l stand before you with
the hope that you will forgive me.
l would not have left
my Nafisa for anything.
God came in the way otherwise
l would've still been with her.
There is no reason to believe him,
but there is also no reason not to.
lt was your decision then
Zooni and it's your decision now.
7 years!
7 years l have lived with the guilt
that l sent you to your death.
Every day l curse my
self for sending you there.
Do you know what it's
like to live with that?
Look at this!
When you were off
being a great soldier ..
..on your missions
this is what l was doing.
l was taking parts of all these
faces, trying to make one face.
Your face.
So l could have something to cry in
front of, something to show my son.
To tell him this is your father.
And now you say all those tears,
all that pain was for nothing?
No!
Why should l open myself
to pain again Rehan?
Why should l take you back?
Give me one good reason..
..why l shouldn't
believe you are still dead.
Give me one good reason.
l don't have a single good reason.
They are all bad.
Each and every one.
l was taking parts of all these
faces, trying to make one face.
Why are you going?
Because l can't play
cricket like Rahul Dra?id.
Don't worry. Rehan will teach you.
l am not dependiddle either.
l can't be trusted.
No you are dependable for Rehan.
See Rehan has learned
how to say dependable.
Rehan will never trouble you again.
He won't call you dead man.
He will have a bath himself.
He will not give you milk and
turmeric, but please don't go.
Rehan loves you more
than you love Rehan.
Sit properly!
Eat!
Why are you venting
your anger on him?
The one who deserves it has
left without saying a word.
He must be in his room.
Go tell him breakfast is ready.
l'm not going to stand around
in the kitchen all day for him.
He's gone. He said
goodbye to Rehan. Not to you.
No, he can't go.
He can't go.
Rehan!
Stop! Rehan!
How dare you leave me again?
How dare you?
Your life is mine now, do you hear?
You can never leave me and go.
Never!
"O Almighty."
Papa!
"When l have your hands in mine."
"l have with me the heavens divine."
"When you're close,
this world is naught."
"Destroyed in your love,
a triumph sought."
"When l have your hands in mine."
"l have with me
the heavens di?ine."
"When you're close
this world is naught."
"Destroyed in your love,
a triumph sought."
"When l have your hands in mine."
"l have with me
the heavens di?ine."
May my life's-breath
find refuge in your heart.
Destroyed in your
love may my life depart.
"As close as
fragrances are to breath."
"As close as songs are to lips."
"As close as sleepless
nights to memories."
"As close as arms are to embraces."
"As close, as close
as dreams to eyes."
"Be that close to me,
oh love of mine."
"When you're close
this world is naught."
"Destroyed in your love,
a triumph sought."
"When l have your hands in mine."
"l have with me the heavens divine."
Let my eyes swell with tears,
let me cry today.
Take me in your arms,
get drenched today.
The sea of pain trapped
in my heart will explode.
l have so much pain your
veil will be drenched.
As close as secrets
are to heartbeats.
As close as
raindrops are to the clouds.
As close as the moon
is to the night.
As close as kohl is to the eyes.
As close, as close as
the waves are to the ocean.
"Be that close to me,
oh love of mine."
"When you're close
this world is naught."
"Destroyed in your love,
a triumph sought."
"When l have your hands in mine."
"l have with me the
heavens divine."
My breath was incomplete, heartbeat
incomplete, incomplete was l .
But now the moon is full,
complete in the sky..
..and now with you complete am l..
Give us some good news Aakash.
can we go any further?
Sorry ma'am, we'll have to
wait another 2 or 3 days.
But we have to do something Aakash.
We can't just stand around.
No. Not the press. We can't talk
to the media about the bomb yet.
The order's come
directly from Delhi.
We can't talk about the bomb
but we can talk about him.
Aakash! lnform the press.
Newspaper, Radio, TV.
The search is on for a terrorist
hiding in the outskirts of Srinagar.
This terrorist is badly wounded
and is wearing an army uniform.
He is also carrying
an electronic part.
lf you have any information
on this man please..
..contact your nearest
police station immediately.
come on Rehan, drink your milk.
Rehan loves you more
than you love Rehan.
No, l love Rehan much more than
that and he has to drink this milk.
And what about this Rehan?
At this time?
colonel? At this time?
What's the matter?
l have risked life and come
here for a very important reason.
What? come inside.
l've run out of rum!
The games destiny plays with us.
And if one is in the army their..
..destiny is not in
their hands anyway. cheers!
Rehan, if you like you can come
to my house and radio your unit.
You have a radio transmitter?
Meet the man who lives
in the middle of nowhere..
..and keeps a radio to
keep in touch with people.
Always wonder
why he lives out here.
lt's late today. lt'll be
dark by the time you return.
lt's dark already.
Ok, so it's night already.
come tomorrow.
The weather should be clearer as
well. come and radio your unit then.
There's no need for that.
- Why not?
He has just returned after 7 years.
l don't want him to
disappear for another 7.
You are trying to guard
a soldier is it?
Rehan, do you want me
to radio them?
No, l'll have to do it myself.
Of course, of course.
Let him give his
status report then you..
..can keep him imprisoned
here forever, right Rehan?
Fine, now no more discussion.
What do they say in Punjabi?
Let's have a whopper of a drink.
cheers, pal.
- Excuse me.
Where's your father? He was
to take me to colonels' house.
Do you really have to go?
Just this last bit of work.
Papa takes a while to get ready.
He'll be down soon. Papa!
Rehan!
Once upon a time there was a prince,
and a princess who was blind.
Mom, you are telling a story?
One day the princess
met an ordinary man who..
..followed different
monuments in different cities.
But the princess saw the
prince hidden in that ordinary man.
What was the prince's name?
Rehan.
The prince saved the
princess from a huge, scary dragon.
The dragon had a big, red face.
Every time he opened his mouth..
..gigantic balls of
fire would come out of it.
What was the dragon's name?
Grandpa!
come on Rehan, let's go to the
colonel's and radio your unit.
The search is on for a terrorist
hiding in the outskirts of Srinagar.
This terrorist is
wearing an army uniform.
He is also carrying
an electronic part.
Grandpa..
Grandpa, Rehan loves you very much.
l will have to go for a couple
of days to hand in my resignation.
Whether or not you're
on this mission..
..the lKF will definitely loose.
Terrorists can never win.
That's the thing.
These people are not terrorists.
They are fighting
for their independence.
And who will run this
country of theirs? The lKF?
No. Whoever the people of
Kashmir elect. ln fair elections.
lt seems youre not
against the lKF, youre for them.
You are a traitor. You may
be my daughter's husband,
..but l'll gladly kill you.
l was doubtful when l saw the news on
the Tv, but by then it was too late.
l had my doubts.
But today l was certain..
..when l found this
trigger in your pocket.
You can't do anything now.
l am going to radio the
military and hand you over.
colonel! colonel!
Please Sir, give me that trigger.
No! - All this will be
over in a couple of days.
Then l can stay with
Zooni and Rehan forever.
l'd rather they be dead.
l'll never give you this. Never.
No! l wont give you!
Don't you dare, Rehan!
No!!
Shalimar 1 Shikara come in.
Hello, Shalimar 1 we read you.
- Shalimar 1 Shikara come in.
My son. Rehan! God be praised
a million times. You're alive!
Do you have what l want?
Yes, l have it with me.
What's the matter?
l'm tired that's all.
l just want all this to end.
Look here..
- l know what l have to do.
come here and take
what it is you want.
The coordinates here
are loc rep 34,74,..
..mount 2730, 500 house.
That was him. Thank God he
hasn't reached his people yet.
There is very heavy fog
right now. We'll try and be..
..there tomorrow morning.
God be with you.
Sorry ma'am he gave his
location in code.
We'll need some time to break it.
Darn! Darn him!
Give Ranade the code to break.
Keep the ground search going.
And continue monitoring
the frequency he called from.
We only have till tomorrow morning.
contact the base camp.
Are they ready with the sketch of
the imposter of captain Ranjeev?
Papa!!
Papa! Someone help us please!
Mom, what's happened?
Papa! Papa!
Mom! What happened?
Nothing, go watch some TV.
Rehan. Papa..
l've just left him at colonel
uncle's. They're both drinking rum.
He said he'll stay there tonight.
The search is on for a terrorist
hiding in the outskirts of Srinagar.
This terrorist is badly wounded
and is wearing an army uniform.
He went missing 8 days ago.
He has an electronic part with him.
This is a sketch of
him provided by the army.
lf you see this man anywhere please
don't try and catch him your self.
He is armed and dangerous.
Please contact your nearest
police station immediately.
Or call this number.
colonel uncle!
Hello! Hello! can someone hear me?
Ma'am someone is sending an
SOS from the same frequency.
Hello. Hello. Yes we read you.
- Hello.
Hello?
- Hello, can someone hear me?
Hello, yes, we can hear you.
l am Malini Tyagi from the
anti terrorist special forces.
Who is this?
l am Zooni Ali Beg.
My husband. l thought he was dead.
But he came back 9 days ago.
l think he's the one
you are looking for.
He may have killed my
father and my uncle. Or not.
l don't know.
l don't know. Just please help us.
l am alone. lt's just me and my son.
Zooni, Zooni don't panic.
And listen to me carefully.
Does your husband have some
sort of an electronic part?
Yes, l saw it on TV.
lt's with me.
lt's him. Your husband is
the one we are looking for.
He is the terrorist.
Listen to me carefully Zooni.
l am going to tell you the most
important thing you will ever hear.
lf he leaves with that trigger,
if he joins his comrades they will..
..use a nuclear bomb
over our country.
Millions of lndians will die.
One of them can be my daughter.
Another can be your son.
There will be complete
destruction,..
..and the only one who
can stop it Zooni, is you!
But, he is my husband.
Tell me you will help us Zooni.
Tell me you will stop him.
Whatever it takes.
Tell me, Zooni.
Yes.
We have your location now Zooni.
We know where you are..
..we'll be there tomorrow morning.
Ok.
Zooni!
Who are you running away from?
From me? From your Rehan?
l have only one Rehan. My son.
Papa? What happened?
Nothing son. Everything is fine.
Go to sleep.
What's the point?
You'll kill him as well.
l'd rather die first.
You killed Papa quite easily.
l didn't kill him.
lt was an accident.
And colonel Uncle?
Give me the trigger Zooni.
No.
- Zooni!
Give me that trigger!
What will you do?
Kill me as well? Kill me.
l've already died once because
of you, why not once again.
Zooni, despite all my lies.
Despite all the pain
l have given you.
Do you believe that l love you?
Then for the sake of that love.
You have to do what l say.
lf you don't give me that trigger..
..then they will torture and
kill Rehan right in front of us.
Then they'll kill you
in front of me.
Then if they have any mercy,
then they will kill me too
And the person to do all
this will be no stranger.
My own grandfather will destroy
his family with his own hands.
l don't care about myself Zooni,
..but l am not willing
to sacrifice Rehan or you.
This is the only way.
This is the only way we'll be able
to live our lives in peace again.
And what about the lives of those
millions that will die from the bomb?
No one will use the bomb.
lt's just a threat.
The governments of lndia and
Pakistan will have no other choice..
..but to give in.
After all your lies,
how can l believe you now?
Grandfather
Or the lndian army whom l called.
No. Grandfather.
You can't leave.
Take care of Rehan and yourself.
l'll be back tomorrow.
Rehan! Please for
our son's sake. Stop!
l love you, Rehan.
l love you.
Rehan!
Why Rehan? Why?
Rehan loves you more
than you love Rehan.
Don't say that. Please don't.
Now l'm not scared.
Rehan..
Rehan!
"O Almighty."
"When l have your hands in mine"
"l have with me heavens divine"
"When you're close
this world is naught"
"Destroyed in your love,
a triumph sought"
lt's easy to choose
between right and wrong.
But to choose the greater of two
goods or the lesser of two evils.
Those are the choices of our life.
Was Rehans father a bad man?
Sometimes, one might be right,
but other might take him to be bad.
Your father did what he felt right.
Rehan loves you very much
And Zooni loves Rehan very much.