2nd June 1 947, WaS that date
in the HiStOry Of India . . .
. . . When it WaS decided
that an agreement, . . .
. . . WOuId fOrm the baSiS
Of Our Independence.
At the VicerOy HOuSe, . . .
. . . COngreSS, MuSIim League,
and LOrd MOuntabatten . . .
. . . Signed a bOnd, Which
divided India intO twO partS.
The Other part became PakiStan.
The agreement Stated
a cOnditiOn . . .
. . . that the WhOIe pOpuIatiOn
WiII nOt be tranSferred.
In Other WOrdS, if a muSIim
Wanted tO Stay in India, . . .
. . . and a Hindu Wanted
tO Stay in PakiStan, . . .
. . . they WOuId be aIIOWed tO dO SO.
But thiS did nOt happen.
AII the HinduS Of thiS
area are being infOrmed . . .
. . . that tOday evening
frOm PipIa StatiOn, . . .
. . . a SpeciaI train
WiII Ieave fOr India.
AII are requeSted tO take
OnIy What iS neceSSary.
And Ieave the reSt behind
With yOur name and addreSS.
SO that Iater On it WiII
be eaSier tO Send it . . . . .
Ive Said SO Often,
that We ShOuId gO tO AmritSar.
Even Kaka WaS aSking
uS tO cOme tO AmritSar.
But yOu juSt dOnt
IiSten tO anyOne.
HOW did I knOW, that the
PakiStan GOvernment . . .
. . . WOuId betray uS.
It WaS decided that the HinduS
in PakiStan cOuId Stay back.
But everything haS changed.
I WOnder What WiII happen nOW.
I dOnt knOW in What
cOnditiOn WOuId my SOn be in?
Take thiS, dear.
- Biji, What iS thiS?
- I cant give it.
StOp, SantO.
What are yOu dOing?
Have patience.
Give it tO me.
GirIS, thiS iS pOiSOn.
If yOu are in trOubIe, have it.
But dO nOt Iet any muSIim
defame yOur dignity.
O GOd! What a time haS cOme!
That a father cannOt even bIeSS
hiS chiIdren With a IOng Iife.
BrOther GuIIu!
DOnt cry, SiSter.
NO, father.
I WiII nOt Iet yOu gO frOm here.
SO What if Kake iS nOt here.
YOur SecOnd SOn GuIkhan iS here.
I SWear On the HOIy GOd.
I WiII nOt Iet yOu gO frOm here.
My dear, aII the emOtiOnS
Of Our heart have IOSt.
OnIy the preSent
cOnditiOnS, have WOn.
COme On, IetS gO.
Pick up the Iuggage.
PIeaSe dOnt gO.
In thiS manner,
IakhS Of Hindu famiIieS . . .
. . . Were uprOOted frOm their hOmeS,
. . . and Went Wandering
arOund aII Over.
The train Of eight bOgieS
WaS at PipIa StatiOn.
And there Were 1 0,000 peOpIe.
AS if deStiny and GOd
had turned a deaf ear.
LOOterS have cOme.
Save yOurSeIf.
KiII the OId and yOung.
Pick up the WOmen.
DO nOt Spare anyOne.
Take aWay aII their beIOngingS.
Father!
In thiS manner, dead bOdieS
Of the HinduS and SikhS . . .
. . . frOm the variOuS partS Of PakiStan,
Were Sent tO India.
IndianS Iearn tO SIaughter frOm uS.
Let everyOne greet each Other.
The HinduS and SikhS Iiving
in India Were furiOuS.
And even thOSe WhO cauSed
thiS cOmmunaI viOIence . . .
. . . cOuIdnt eScape frOm it.
What nOnSenSe iS thiS?
Why are yOu nOt
underStanding Our difficuIty?
I am a WeII knOWn
buSineSSman Of thiS cOuntry.
It iS the duty Of the
gOvernment tO prOtect uS.
PIeaSe reach uS tO
the DeIhi AirpOrt.
If One had tO gO by rOad,
hOW far iS LahOre frOm here?
JuSt 35 tO 40 miIeS.
If yOu gO by rOad tO DeIhi,
it WOuId mean death.
BrOther, thOSe . . . .
Why dOnt yOu Speak, What happened?
BrOther, the Hindu and Sikh mObS
Set fire tO the manSiOn, . . .
. . . and murdered the
WhOIe famiIy there.
ThOSe peOpIe can cOme here anytime.
CIOSe the gate firmIy.
Put the chain.
InSpectOr, Im Warning yOu, . . .
. . . that if One man
dareS tO enter, . . .
. . . then I SWear by GOd,
yOu WiII Iearn a IeSSOn fOr Iife.
ThOSe WhO cauSed thiS,
are themSeIveS frightened it?
BrOther, mind yOur Ianguage.
YOu are On duty.
UnderStOOd!
I am On duty, thatS Why
I am quiet, Or eISe. . .
Or eISe, What WOuId yOu have dOne?
YOu are nOt fit even tO IOOk uS.
WOuId yOu raiSe a hand On uS?
ThiS iS nOt the time fOr
yOu tO IOSe yOur temper.
OnIy 2 hOurS are Ieft fOr
the AmritSar-LahOre . . .
. . . SpeciaI train tO Ieave.
COme On gO SOOn nOW.
III- mannered!
Even Sarfaraz haS rung up SO
many timeS frOm LahOre, . . .
. . . tO Ieave immediateIy.
HOW cOuId I gO, Ieaving
aII the buSineSS in India?
We had given SO much mOney
tO the MuSIim League . . .
. . .and had tried SO hard tO get
entire Punjab intO PakiStan.
But everything Went futiIe.
They gave uS PakiStan aS
if they are giving aImS.
If anOther One Or twO yearS
had paSSed, We WOuId have . . .
. . . SOId Our Iand and buSineSS,
and gOne tO PakiStan.
O GOd!
Wait a minute.
BefOre anyOne attackS, III take
yOu Out frOm the back dOOr.
What iS it?
COme On, hurry up.
Where iS Sakeena?
Shaku, Where Were yOu?
COme On.
COme On, get in the truck.
Shaku, be carefuI.
COme On, everybOdy.
Let the paSSengerS gOing tO
LahOre, bOard the train SOOn.
One mOre train carrying
HinduS haS cOme frOm PakiStan.
KiII theSe muSIimS.
- Hurry up.
- GO SOOn.
COme On, kiII him.
He iS AShraf, . . .
. . . WhO Wanted PakiStan.
KiII him.
Get in.
MOther.
Father!
My daughter iS Ieft behind.
MuSIim?
ThereS a beautifuI IaSS here.
COme On.
COme.
NO.
HeIp!
Tara! Save me, Tara.
She iS a MuSIim.
She iS Our prey.
NO One WiII tOuch her.
He made uS run SO far.
And yOu Want tO take her?
COme On mOve aWay.
Ive Said , nO One WiII tOuch her.
I knOW her.
What dO yOu knOW her!
They tOrtured Our WOmen.
MOve aSide.
I WOnt Spare her.
What are yOu dOing?
YOure fighting amOngSt yOurSeIveS.
He iS Tara Singh.
He hOIdS cOmmand Of
the tranSpOrt buSineSS.
- DOnt yOu underStand?
- AIright.
We WiII SettIe it tOgether.
Hand Over thiS girI tO uS.
Tara, have yOu gOne mad?
YOu WiII fight With each Other,
that tOO fOr thiS girI?
DOnt fOrget that She iS a MuSIim.
YeS, She iS a MuSIim.
She iS MuSIim?
WeII nOW She haS becOme a Sikh.
NOW if anyOne caStS an eye
On her, I WiII behead them.
Tara haS cOme.
`PIeaSe cOme tO me, my beIOved
Dharma, get up. YOure StiII SIeeping.
Weve reached cOIIege.
YOu fOOI.
What have yOu dOne?
I WaS SIeeping.
I heard yOur vOice and I gOt up.
I am SOrry.
AII the henS fIeW aWay.
And eggS . . .
GO, IOOk after the henS.
III gO and meet the MajOr
at the canteen. Okay?
A canteen haS a manager,
and nOt a majOr.
A MajOr iS One WhO targetS
the enemieS With buIIetS. . .
WhiIe Darmiyan Singh iS One
WhO getS thingS Off the truck.
- COme On, catch the chickenS.
- YeS, my dear.
They make me dO aII
the canteen WOrk.
- GreetingS!
- WhatS the matter?
YOu are IOOking duII? - I am iII.
- YOu are aIright nOW?
- YeS.
AIright, dO One thing.
Get me a gIaSS Of Water . . .
- . . . and take the thingS
Out Of the truck. - Okay.
ShOuId I unIOad firSt,
Or give yOu Water?
Have yOu nO brainS?
It WiII take yOu
twO hOurS tO unIOad.
ShOuId I remain thirSty tiII then?
GO and get Water firSt.
- AIright, brOther.
- AIright, brOther!
GreetingS!
I gOt WOrried IiStening
tO EngIiSh SuddenIy.
YOu knOW that my EngIiSh
iS a IittIe pOOr.
- Mr. Tara Singh, Our . . .
- YOur thingS?
I have brOught it.
HereS yOur IipStick.
YOur bangIeS, and yOur `bindi.
We give yOu a IOt Of trOubIe.
WhatS the prObIem in thiS?
YOu Stay far frOm the city.
I have tO cOme Once
Or twice a Week . . .
. . . tO SuppIy thingS fOr
the canteen, iSnt it?
- YeS, yOu Were SuppOSed tO gO
fOr a fiIm? - WhatS itS name?
`FirSt LOOk
HOW WaS the mOvie?
- It WaS aII abOut rOmance
and IOve. - ReaIIy?
But a neW Singer MukeSh
haS dOne WOnderS.
- He mOved my heart.
- ReaIIy? - YeS.
` If the heart IamentS,
Iet it dO SO
`DO nOt Shed tearS,
nOr make any requeStS
WOnderfuI.
YOu are aIWayS praiSing me.
But in the annuaI functiOn
yOu never Iet me take part.
GOOd, yOu reminded uS.
We WiII intrOduce yOu tO
a neW muSic teacher . . .
. . . tO heIp yOu Sing
in the annuaI functiOn.
- We WiII intrOduce him, right?
- YeS, Of cOurSe.
ThatS a SmaII prObIem.
Our neW muSic teacher
cant hear prOperIy.
Ive been Singing in a
IOud vOice Since chiIdhOOd.
- ISnt it, SO?
- YeS Of cOurSe.
Hearing hiS IOud vOice, the
neighbOrS WOuId get irritated.
- They WOuId have big fightS.
- Shut up!
He iS a IittIe crazy.
YOu idiOt!
- WeII, Mr.Tara Singh.
- YeS?
COme tO the muSic rOOm On
Sunday at Sharp 1 2 nOOn. . .
. . . fOr a meeting.
AIright?
Thank yOu.
LOOkS Iike I WiII SureIy
Sing at the annuaI functiOn.
YeS, buddy.
If OnIy the muSic teacher
dOeSnt put a brake in between.
I ShOuId becOme a muSic teacher!
I dO nOt Iike tO make
a fOOI Of SOmeOne.
Sakeena, yOu are a Student
and nOt a principaI.
SO yOu ShOuId pIay
prankS SOmetimeS.
He SingS WeII.
But at functiOn in the Stage . . . ,
. . . and that tOO in frOnt
Of PrincipaI MrS. PintO.
YeS, Ive underStOOd.
YOu Want him tO give
up Singing fOrever.
He ShOuId never taIk abOut
Singing in the annuaI functiOn.
YeS.
BecauSe Weve tOId him . . .
. . . that Our muSic teacher
haS a hearing prObIem.
Tara haS cOme.
GreetingS!
TaIk a IittIe IOudIy.
Madam, I am Tara Singh.
What? Say a IittIe IOuder.
Mr. AWara Singh.
NOt AWara Singh,
I am Tara Singh.
If yOu are a bacheIOr,
What can I dO?
She cant hear my vOice.
HOW WiII She hear my SOng?
She WiII.
Speak a IittIe IOuder.
LOuder!
Madam, MS. Kanchan haS Send
me tO yOu tO Iearn muSic.
FOOd?!
If yOu Want fOOd, gO tO the canteen.
Why have yOu cOme here?
NOt fOOd, I Want tO Sing!
SOng!
Say SO.
But have yOu ever Sung a SOng?
SOng!
- In the viIIage . . . .
- What?
When I Sing in the fieIdS,
the entire viIIage iS OverjOyed.
They WhiStIe.
- Then Sing a SOng.
- Sing?
Sing.
DO everything in Iife,
but never Sing a SOng.
What iS thiS!
TOday, One feIt aS if there
WaS duSt in the carburetOr!
Give me the bOttIe.
Here, bOttIe.
ThatS better.
Darmiyan, What are theSe piIIS fOr?
- TheSe are nOt Ordinary piIIS.
- IS it?
DOctOr BhOjraj Khanna Of
RaWaIpindi, gave theSe piIIS.
- IS it?
- YeS.
LaSt year On BaiShaki, that
famOuS Singer ROIan Singh . . .
. . . IOSt hiS vOice On the Stage.
He tOOk twO Of theSe piIIS.
He Sang SO many SOngS, . . .
. . . that We had tO give him aneStheSia,
tO end the functiOn.
What abOut buddy?
FIy aWay O IittIe bird,
III be gratefuI
Carry my meSSage,
Spring iS in the air,
everyting iS in fuII bIOOm
Life iS ShOrt,
and nightS are IOng
COme hOme SWeetheart,
We Share a Iife
The SeaSOn Of IOve
danced intO Iife
EyeS On the rOad . . .
. . .Waiting fOr my beIOved
YOur thOughtS keep
me aWake aII night
My SOngS became my deSireS
Great! YOur vOice
reaIIy tOuched my heart.
I didnt knOW yOu Sang SO WeII.
SO, WiII I get a chance tO
Sing at the annuaI functiOn?
PIeaSe fOrgive uS.
SOrry!
ActuaIIy aII Of uS
Were fOOIing With yOu.
I am nOt a muSic teacher.
I am a Student.
My name iS Sakeena.
Buddy, thiS . . .
Can I Say One thing?
I am very happy tO meet yOu.
I prOmiSe that III taIk
tO the principaI, . . .
. . . SO that yOu can take
part in the annuaI functiOn.
Madam, juSt a minute.
Madam, even I am very
gIad tO meet yOu.
At IeaSt yOu thOught fOr
a pOOr perSOn Iike me.
Thank yOu very much.
A truck driver Singing
at Our cOIIege functiOn.
We feIicitate theSe IOWIy peOpIe.
ISnt that aII?
MS. Kanchan, I recOgnized
yOu even frOm a diStance?
Take thiS.
PeOpIe queue up fOr thiS
SWeetS at NathuS SWeet ShOp.
I bIeW the hOrn cOnStantIy,
and made him give it quickIy.
IS it?
Where iS MS. Sakeena?
`Why iS my heart becOming crazy?
`Why iS my heart fuII Of deSireS?
` I dOnt knOW What my heart WantS?
Mr.Tara, yOu?!
YOu danced SO WeII that . . .
. . . yOu even Ieft the fiIm
herOine Savita Devi, Way behind.
YOu dance SO WeII.
YOur taIkS are very SWeet.
I dOnt reaIIy taIk.
Whatever my heart SayS,
I Speak Out.
Madam, give the thingS.
Madam, I Want tO Say
SOmething tO yOu.
Madam, I Want tO Say that. . .
I had tOId yOu that Im nOt madam,
Im Sakeena.
But fOr me, yOu are madam.
HaS that matter Of
mine gOne ahead Or nOt?
- Which matter?
- I mean abOut the Singing?
- Mr. Tara.
- YeS?
WeII, I . . . .
ActuaIIy, Our
principaI Said that . . .
. . . Since yOu dOnt Study here . . .
. . . SO yOu WOnt be aIIOWed
tO Sing in the prOgramme!
ThatS right.
I am a crazy man.
I cOuIdnt underStand
Such a SimpIe thing.
I dOnt Study in the cOIIege,
that I can Sing at the functiOn.
Madam, yOu dOnt need tO feeI SOrry.
YOu did try, didnt yOu?
AS it iS, I Sing aII time.
III See yOu at the
functiOn tOmOrrOW.
GOd bIeSSeS OnIy a
feW With a taIent.
And thiS iS the theme Of
Our tOdayS prOgramme . . .
. . . Which WiII be
preSented befOre yOu . . .
. . . by Of finaI year Student
Sakeena and her grOup.
Madam, yOu dOnt need tO feeI SOrry.
YOu did try, didnt yOu?
The theme abOut Which
MrS. Lamba juSt SpOke.
We are gOing tO
preSent in a neW fOrm.
A fIOWer WhiIe giving fragrance, . . .
. . . Or the Sun WhiIe
giving Iight, . . .
. . . Or a chiId WhiIe SmiIing . . .
. . . dOeSnt cOnSider
the perSOnS StatuS.
SimiIarIy, nature giftS
the taIent Of muSic . . .
. . . WithOut any diScriminatiOn.
Such an artiSt iS amOngSt uS tOday.
Mr. Tara Singh.
PIeaSe cOme Mr.Tara.
Madam haS given the permiSSiOn.
- GO, buddy.
- PIeaSe cOme Mr. Tara.
GO, my friend.
`Why did yOu take pity On me?
`Whatever I had,
yOu tOOk aWay frOm me
COme, Tara Singh.
DOnt be afraid. COme.
DOnt be afraid.
YOu had Said that When yOu Sing
the WhOIe viIIage iS enchanted.
Sing SOmething Iike that.
Sing.
I Ieft driving my truck
On the Way, On the rOad . . .
. . . came a beautifuI turn,
and I IOSt my heart
GOd knOWS, When I
paSSed AmritSar. . .
. . . When I reached LahOre
I IOSt my heart
On that turn I met my darIing
I Went crazy
Under the Shade
Of her treSSeS . . .
. . . I had SOund SIeep
When I WOke up,
I brOke dOWn . . .
. . . aII crOSSingS,
aII hurdIeS
I IOSt my heart
I tOOk One IOOk at her
Her image dWeIIS in my heart
WOnder What her name WaS
She became my Iife
I SaW a dream
The twO Of uS . . .
. . . became One
I IOSt my heart
She baShfuIIy retreated
When She WOke
frOm her SIeep . . .
. . . I caIIed her
She WithdreW,
getting Scared
She thOught,
in her hOuSe . . .
. . .SecretIy,
SneakiIy . . .
. . . a thief had cOme in
I IOSt my heart
Madam, . . . madam.
Tara Singh, yOu?!
I gOt Iate becauSe I had
gOne tO buy a gift fOr yOu.
- Gift?
- YeS.
- When peOpIe gO aWay,
they give giftS. - ReaIIy!
Madam, it tOOk me
twO WhOIe nightS . . .
. . . tO think What gift
ShOuId I give yOu.
SO that the gift ShOuId be
beautifuI and pure Iike yOu.
Take thiS.
ThiS iS fOr yOu.
FOr me? Thank yOu.
Madam, Weve reached hOme.
FreShen up,
III get cIOtheS fOr yOu.
She iS a MuSIim?
NOW She haS becOme a Sikh.
Madam, cIOtheS fOr yOu.
NO madam, dOnt miSunderStand me.
I had tO marry yOu tO prOtect yOu.
LOOk at Our StatuS, OtherwiSe.
I knOW that I cant reach
the SkieS even if I Want tO.
DOnt WOrry.
YOu are fuIIy Safe here.
COme On, bring her Out.
Keep quiet.
She iS the madam frOm ShimIa.
She may be a madam fOr yOu.
FOr uS, She iS the daughter
Of that ScOundreI AShraf AIi.
Death did nOt Spare him.
That ScOundreI AShraf AIi iS dead.
SO Why iS She aIive?
Bring her Out.
He haS gOne mad?
Beat him!
Hey, yOu ScOundreIS!
Run!
I WiII kiII yOu if
yOu cOme here again.
Madam, dOnt cry.
It iS pOSSibIe that
Whatever they Said iS a Iie.
And Attari StatiOn iS juSt nearby.
COme, III take yOu there.
The BritiSherS have ruined India.
They have cauSed partitiOn.
- Sir, actuaIIy I . . .
- I have underStOOd.
BOth Of yOu havent cOme here
aS tOuriStS in thiS SituatiOn.
YOu juSt Want tO check,
if there are any SurvivOrS . . .
. . . in the train Which
Ieft AmritSar yeSterday.
WhO can Survive in thiS bIOOdShed?
ThiS iS nOt pOSSibIe.
The BritiSherS have
deStrOyed India.
COme.
TheSe are the thingS
Ieft behind Of thOSe, . . .
. . . WhO Were kiIIed yeSterday.
YOu can check if anything
beIOnged tO yOur dear OneS.
The BritiSherS have
deStrOyed India.
Father!
ThiS iS nOt pOSSibIe.
Madam!
- What Were yOu dOing?
- I Want tO die. I am a MuSIim.
COntrOI yOurSeIf, madam.
SOmeOne WantS PakiStan
and SOmeOne WantS India.
Human beingS dO nOt
need each Other.
YOu Were aISO kiIIing
the muSIimS, . . .
. . . but Why did yOu Spare me.
I aISO Want tO die!
I underStand, madam.
When circumStanceS change,
human beingS becOme mad.
They are ready tO die and kiII.
DO yOu remember, thatjOviaI Tara?
He had everything.
But I IOSt everything
in theSe riOtS.
I WaS Ieft With nOthing.
I IOSt my parentS,
SiSterS, everything.
I have Seen my parentS being
cremated With my OWn eyeS.
ThOSe pyreS have turned tO aSheS.
But I am StiII nOt at peace.
ThiS iS nOtjuSt yOurS
and my StOry.
But Of thOuSandS Of SikhS,
HinduS, and MuSIimS.
They are Iike Iiving cOrpSeS.
Theyve IOSt the zeSt tO Iive.
HOWever bitter Iife may be, . . .
. . . One haS tO Iive.
` I have yOur memOrieS With me.
`TeII me What ShOuId I dO?
I WaS hiding in the gOdOWn fOr
4 dayS With the fear Of riOtS.
- My back iS . . .
- Keep quiet and get the bOx.
My name haS a big
tragedy attached tO it.
Whether it iS Darmiyan
Singh, Or Darmiyan Khan.
If the muSIimS catch me, they
Say burn the Sikh feIIOW aIive.
If the HinduS SikhS catch me,
they Say that. . .
. . . One dOeS nOt becOme a
Sikh by keeping IOng hair.
YOu are a MuSIim,
Dharmiyan Khan. YOu WiII . . .
YOuve made it intO
an EngIiSh tabIe.
But What WiII I dO With thiS?
- YOu fOOI!
- YeS?
Madam WOnt Sit On the
fIOOr and eat Iike uS.
Did yOu See in fiImS,
hOW rich peOpIe eat?
- YeS. - A feW ServantS
Serve fOOd in cIay pIateS.
- I tOO WiII Iike tO eat Iike that.
- Keep quiet.
GO and Serve fOOd.
- Madam WiII have it Iike that.
- BecauSe She iS madam.
Madam, pIeaSe eat fOOd.
Drink Water.
Buddy, Ive . . . .
That feIIOW ShOuId gO tO heII.
He made muShrOOm curry,
inSpite Of fOrbidding him.
DOnt WOrry.
ThiS iS a Strange iIIneSS.
OnIy Dr. KeemtiIaI can treat thiS.
III gO and bring him.
IIIneSS?!
- COme in.
- Where iS the patient?
What iS yOur prObIem?
They are peStering me
after I had muShrOOmS.
They WiII peSter yOu
if yOu WhiStIe SO much.
NO, dOctOr.
A girI iS nOt peStering him.
. . . the WhiStIeS are haraSSing him.
DOnt WOrry.
I WiII StOp it quickIy.
- Meaning? - I WiII StOp
hiS WhiStIeS. Lie dOWn.
DOctOr, iS Darmiyan aIright?
HOW nOt he?
What are yOu Saying?
ASk Darmiyan.
What dO yOu Say?
- My beIching!
- Are yOu aIright?
I think SO.
FirSt I WaS Suffering With One,
nOW Im Suffering frOm bOth.
The baIance iS equaI.
Buddy, Our Scheme iS a SucceSS!
YeS. Madam Iaughed.
What ShOuId I dO?
Madam, dOnt cry.
YOu IOOk gOOd When yOu Iaugh.
He ShOuId have thOught abOut Other.
He brOught a muSIim girI hOme.
III gO and Set him right.
- Hey, hurry up.
- Aunty haS cOme.
Aunty! What ShOuId I dO?
- Aunty WiII kiII uS.
- She haS cOme.
YOu StOp her.
Im cOming.
Aunty!
- MOve aSide. - COme in.
- YOu ScOundreI!
- Where iS that muSIim girI?
- The pickIe bOttIe?!
YOu idiOt!
I mean the muSIim girI.
Which girI?
I dOnt knOW anything.
YOur uncIe WiII teach yOu a IeSSOn.
DO yOu think Im a fOOI?
- Aunty, bIeSS me.
- SOn!
SOn, bIeSS yOu.
May yOu Iive IOng.
- IS everything aIright at hOme?
- NOthing iS aIright.
It WOuId be aIright When yOur
uncIe WOuId cOme tO thraSh yOu.
I StOpped him. I Said I WiII
atIeaSt find Out Whether, . . .
MOve aSide.
I WOnt tO find Out Whether
Ramrakhi WaS Iying . . .
- . . . that the muSIim girI. . .
- Aunty!
ShaII I get yOu buttermiIk?
- MOve aSide.
- LiSten tO me, III expIain . . .
- COme Out.
- She iS Sakeena madam.
She beIOngS tO a rich famiIy.
She iS a victim Of the riOtS.
She IOSt her parentS.
O GOd, SheS Ieft aII aIOne.
O GOd!
My SOn, yOu Want tO
heIp her, dOnt yOu?
Then Send her tO the muSIim camp.
Hey! I am taIking tO yOu.
Did yOu underStand?
YOu are crazy.
YOu Send her, WOnt yOu?
The entire neighbOrhOOd
iS curSing uS.
Are yOu IiStening?
I fOrgOt that Ive
gOt SWeetS fOr yOu.
Give them tO me.
Stupid feIIOW iS hOIding them.
I made it mySeIf With
aImOnd and pure ghee.
YOu WOnt fiII hungry
the WhOIe day, . . .
. . . if yOu eat One With
miIk in the mOrning.
One cant be Sure abOut yOu.
YOu are aIWayS SO buSy.
Take thiS, eat it.
Give her a feW SWeetS aISO.
SheS unfOrtunate.
- COme On.
- Where?
COme On, get me a rickShaW.
III drOp aunty,
dOnt finiSh aII the SWeetS.
- COme On.
- Im cOming.
Madam, dO nOt feeI bad
abOut What aunty Said.
She iS very kind-hearted.
YOur aunty iS right.
I dOnt Want tO be a reaSOn fOr
yOur humiIiatiOn and prObIem.
Leave me at the muSIim camp.
They WiII Send me tO my
uncIeS hOuSe in LahOre.
We have a big hOuSe there.
YOu are right.
Anyway thiS pIace iS nOt fOr yOu.
But in the refugee camp . . .
NO, madam.
III Ieave yOu at LahOre.
NO. GOing there in Such
circumStanceS . . . .
NO, yOu . . .
DO nOt WOrry.
III get ready.
FOr Sakeena madam.
`Are yOu Iike a
bOuquet Of fIOWerS?
`Or a garden Of rOSe?
`ThiS pOOr feIIOW IOSt hiS
heart When he SaW yOu.
` My deStiny iS juSt tO IOve yOu.
`And yOu ShOuId be mine,
iS a deSire.
`YOur memOrieS are my heart beatS,
` In every heart beat,
yOu Iie, my dear.
I knOW thiS very WeII, madam, . . .
. . . that even if I Want
tO I cannOt tOuch the Sky.
She iS a muSIim?
But nOW She haS becOme Sikh.
NOW if anyOne dareS
tO IOOk at her, . . .
. . . I SWear by GOd,
I WiII behead him!
I dOnt mind. I WiII chOp
vegetabIeS fOr tOmOrrOW.
I WiII put SpiceS and put
it On the fire fOr cOOking.
Then I WiII IOad in the
truck When it iS ready.
- What dO yOu . . .
- Keep quiet.
Madam, I have made aII
arrangementS tO gO tO LahOre.
My truck iS fuII Of
dieSeI and Water.
TOmOrrOW earIy mOrning itSeIf,
WeII Ieave fOr LahOre.
Madam, can I aSk yOu One thing?
After gOing there, yOu WiII
think Of me, WOnt yOu?
Im a fOOIiSh feIIOW.
I aSked a Stupid queStiOn.
Madam, after gOing there,
yOu WiII remember me, right?
. . . everything iS in fuII bIOOm
Life iS ShOrt, . . .
. . . and nightS are IOng
COme hOme SWeetheart, . . .
. . . We Share a Iife
. . . We are aII chiIdren
Of One GOd . . .
We are decedentS Of One GOd
WhO iS right, WhO iS WrOng
PraiSe the LOrd . . .
Hey Darmiyan!
COme SOOn, Ive tO tie the turban.
COming.
Give it tO me, tOday
Iet me tie yOur turban.
Madam, dO yOu knOW
hOW tO tie a turban?
YeS Of cOurSe.
Once in a cOIIege drama,
I had becOme a Sikh.
Sit, III tie it fOr yOu.
Can I aSk yOu One thing?
Why dOnt yOu get married?
WeII madam, I am Iike a gypSy.
I am aII the time On
the mOve With my truck.
Then WhO WiII marry a truck driver?
If SOmeOne dOeS marry me,
I WiII make her dO aII the WOrk.
I WiII make her cOOk, Serve me.
I WiII SIap her tOO
if the need ariSeS.
See hOW have I tied the turban?
WhatS the matter?
Havent I tied it cOrrectIy?
- It iS tied very WeII.
- Why have yOu remOved it?
JuSt Iike that.
I dOnt beIieve that yOu
can hide SOme thingS.
Madam, I can never Wear thiS.
- I WiII aIWayS keep it
SafeIy With me. - Meaning?
PartitiOn haS taken pIace.
GOd knOW Whether
We WiII meet again.
Whenever I think Of yOu,
III IOOk at thiS!
O traveIer WhO iS Ieaving . . .
O traveIer WhO iS Ieaving,
never tO cOme back
LetS Ieave everything . . .
. . . tO GOd
YOu Spit On me!
Hit him!
With great difficuItieS,
in the heart . . .
. . . peOpIe treaSure their dreamS
TheSe dreamS are
made Of gIaSS . . .
. . .they Shatter and make uS cry
They SecIude they heart . . .
. . .theSe dark fOrbidding thOughtS
LetS Ieave everything . . .
. . . tO GOd
TheSe timeS WiII never cOme back
YOu WiII miSS . . .
. . .the StOrieS Of
the OneS WhO Ieft
GOd knOWS What I
am Ieaving behind
It iS breaking my heart
I have nO StOry tO teII . . .
. . . even then I have
tearS in my eyeS
Neither WiII I fOrget . . .
. . . nOr WiII yOu fOrget
LetS Ieave everything . . .
. . . On GOd
I WiII nOt gO tO LahOre.
Madam, WhatS the matter?
Why dOnt yOu Want
tO gO tO PakiStan?
Ive tOId yOu, I dOnt Want tO gO.
Madam, Ive underStOOd.
YOu are afraid that in Such
circumStanceS, I WiII . . .
YOu WiII nOt marry becauSe
yOu are Iike a gypSy.
And even if yOu dO, She WiII
cOOk fOr yOu, and Serve yOu.
And yOu WiII SIap her,
if She actS tOO Smart. ISnt it?
Madam.
AIright.
I am ready tO Serve.
I WiII even cOOk.
I can even bear SOme SIapS.
RaScaI, hOW did yOu have the
cOurage tO bring her hOme?
UncIe . . . .
The cOmmunity that
divided the cOuntry, . . .
. . . kiIIed my brOther Gurdeep,
my SiSter-in-IaW and my nieceS.
YOu Want tO marry her?!
I WiII nOt Spare yOu.
I WiII kiII yOu.
- What are yOu dOing?
- Leave me.
Tara iS Our SOn.
YOu WiII SpOiI yOur heaIth.
He haS maIigned the WhOIe famiIy.
And thOSe WhO kiIIed Gurdeep . . .
UncIe, take thiS, kiII me.
But remember One thing.
Hatred OnIy deStrOyS.
Whether it iS SOmeOneS
heart Or hOme, Or a cOuntry.
And becauSe Of thiS hatred
I had becOme viOIent.
If IOve WOuIdnt
StOp me On time, . . .
. . . even I WOuId be dead tOday.
UncIe, yOu Want tO
See me SettIe in Iife?
ChiIdren cant Iive peacefuIIy
WithOut the bIeSSingS Of eIderS.
WhO eISe dO I have in thiS WOrId?
YOu WOnt IiSten tO me?
AIright.
Tara, dOnt gO.
StOp him.
Tara, yOu Were gOing tO Ieave me?
We have a grape
vine in Our veranda
The bOy SeemS aS taII aS a tree
They dOnt make a gOOd pair
The girIS iS aS
deIicate aS a fIOWer
What kind Of a bOy iS thiS
They dOnt make a gOOd pair
We have a pOmegranate Orchard
LOOk hOW the bOy SquintS
They dOnt make a gOOd pair
The mangOeS in Our
Orchard have ripen
The nightS Of IOve
have becOme IOng
Have pity On me
O GOd, have pity On me
The beauty Which I WaSnt
deStined tO IOOk at, . . .
. . . it iS mine tOday.
DeStiny feIt SOrry fOr me, madam.
NOt madam, Sakeena.
I am a uncOuth feIIOW.
Aunty had Said that tOnight
I had tO bring yOu a gift.
But I havent brOught a gift.
GOOd. NOW I can aSk fOr
a gift Of my chOice.
Sing that SOng inStead, Which
yOu Sang, When We firSt met.
OnIy if yOu WiII Sing With me.
FIy aWay O IittIe bird,
III be gratefuI
Carry my meSSage,
Spring iS in the air,
everything iS in fuII bIOOm
Life iS ShOrt,
and nightS are IOng
COme hOme SWeetheart,
We Share a Iife
The SeaSOn Of IOve
danced intO Iife
EyeS On the rOad . . .
. . .Waiting fOr my beIOved
DOnt taIk abOut SeparatiOn tOday
We WiII taIk Of IOve OnIy
Father, father.
Father iS aIive.
I am caIIing frOm the
PakiStani COnSuIate in DeIhi.
I Wanted tO Speak tO Mr.AShraf.
Madam, there iS a
Iady here WhO SayS . . .
. . . She iS the daughter Of Mr. Khan.
YeS, Speak tO her.
HeIIO, mOther.
HOW are yOu?
Im fine.
We thOught that yOu Were. . .
I am aIive, mOther.
Im aIive.
HOId On, I WiII caII yOur father.
TaIk tO yOur aunt untiI then.
- Are yOu aIright, chiId?
- YeS.
LiSten, Shaku iS
caIIing frOm India.
She iS aIive and fine.
COme quickIy.
Our daughter iS aIive.
- COme SOOn.
- Shaku iS aIive! My chiId!
Father, Im Sakeena.
YOur Shaku.
We IOOked fOr yOu everywhere.
We tOId everyOne that Our
Shaku WiII SureIy cOme back.
We WiII SureIy get her back.
I am back.
I Want tO meet aII Of yOu, father.
- Married?!
- YeS. And I have a SOn tOO.
YOu WiII be pIeaSed tO meet him.
HiS name iS Chiranjeet.
She haS a SOn, tOO.
I Want tO meet yOu, father.
I WiSh tO meet yOu right aWay.
ItS been SO many dayS.
AIright, appIy fOr a viSa
in the cOnSuIate there.
I knOW quite a IOt Of peOpIe there.
I cant teII yOu hOW happy I am.
YOu knOW, father did nOt
ceIebrate Id aII theSe yearS.
And he Said that he WiII
Send a pIane fOr uS.
- MOther, We WiII gO by pIane?
- YeS SOn, by pIane.
WeII gO by pIane.
What iS thiS?
There iS nO Signature Of
the PakiStan COnSuIate . . .
. . . On the chiIdS viSa.
ShOW me.
Oh nO! Sir fOrgOt tO Sign here.
ThatS aIright, but IegaIIy,
I cannOt permit the chiId . . .
. . . tO bOard the fIight
WithOut prOper SignatureS.
What are yOu taIking Officer?
HOW can We gO WithOut him?
Sakeena iS the daughter
Of the MayOr Of LahOre.
She iS gOing hOme tO ceIebrate
Id there after many yearS.
If She dOeS nOt reach in time,
everyOne WiII be diSappOinted.
Mr. IqbaI, iS it pOSSibIe
tO get the SignatureS nOW?
That iS pOSSibIe OnIy
after three dayS nOW.
The Officer in charge haS gOne . . .
. . . tO ceIebrate Id
With hiS reIativeS.
Father WaS SO happy that We
Were cOming there. But nOW . . .
Sakeena, yOu carry On,
We WiII fOIIOW after twO dayS.
Tara iS right.
I WiII get the chiIdS
viSa and Send them Iater.
- Give me yOur paperS.
- Give him the paperS.
I WiII get yOur bOarding cIeared.
It iS OnIy a matter Of twO dayS.
Even I WiII gO.
- My chiId!
- I WiII aISO gO With yOu.
Sakeena, yOu gO.
III take care Of him.
I WiII gO in the pIane.
I Want gO tO grandmaS hOuSe.
SOn, dOnt cry.
GOOd chiIdren dOnt cry.
- StOp crying.
- I Want tO gO With mummy.
We WiII gO after twO dayS.
COme, I WiII ShOW
yOu the aerOpIane.
StOp crying.
Father, yOu?! !
- Father!
- Shaku, my chiId!
If We had nOt had
a viSa prObIem, . . .
. . . even Jeetu and my huSband
WOuId have cOme aIOng With me.
LOOk, they are StiII
Standing there.
Father, yOu came here and did
nOt even get Off the pIane?
If I had Stepped On
the SOiI Of India, . . .
. . . it WOuId have reOpened
a thOuSand WOundS.
ThiS Iand haS even Snatched
my SOn ASIam frOm me.
And anyway, neither thiS Iand, . . .
. . . nOr the cOuntry and
neither itS peOpIe are OurS.
Our mOtherIand, Our peOpIe,
Our cOuntry, iS PakiStan.
It iS gOOd the MayOrS
daughterS arrivaI time . . .
. . . WaS nOt pubIiShed
in the neWSpaperS . . .
. . . Or the WhOIe city WOuId
crOWd here tO WeIcOme her.
YeS, Of cOurSe.
Sakeena deServeS Such a WeIcOme.
NOt OnIy iS She the niece
Of a pOIitician Iike me . . .
. . . but a daughter Of PakiStan, . . .
. . . WhO, deSpite being in the
cuStOdy Of a Jat fOr yearS . . .
. . . and bearing hiS atrOcitieS . . .
. . . did nOt fOrget her rOOtS,
her cOuntry, her reIigiOn.
SiSter-in-IaW, Where did VaIi gO?
Where did VaIi gO?
Find that mad feIIOW!
Mad? WhO iS mad, Sir?
My eIder SOn.
IS Nehru cOming?
Nehru? What nOnSenSe
are yOu taIking?
I aSked, iS Nehru cOming?
IS there gOing tO
be a pubIic meeting?
What nOnSenSe are yOu taIking?
YOu BritiSher. . . BritiSherS, gO back!
India beIOngS tO uS!
WhO iS ShOuting SIOganS
Of India in PakiStan?
- VaIi, What are yOu dOing?
- Take care, brOther.
BrOther, pIeaSe dOnt mind.
He WaS hit On the head
during freedOm StruggIe, . . .
. . . thatS Why he SOmetimeS
gOeS back in time tO 1 946 . . .
. . . When the cOuntry had
nOt been partitiOned.
- PartitiOn?
- There iS nO partitiOn, brOther.
LetS gO, Sakeena iS cOming.
Sarfaraz,With SakeenaS return,
my Iife haS becOme meaningfuI.
I WiII nOt miSS ASIam nOW.
I underStand yOur feeIingS.
My OnIy WOrry iS that
SakeenaS paSt . . .
. . . ShOuId nOt cOme in
the Way Of her future.
Sakeena iS my daughter,
She WiII nOt diSObey me.
YOu are Saying thiS even
after knOWing the truth?
That WaSnt the truth,
it WaS yOur heIpIeSSneSS.
Our cOmmunity IOSt SO
much in thOSe riOtS.
I StiII cannOt fOrget the
daStardIy kiIIing Of ASIam.
Right befOre my eyeS, he WaS. . . .
YOur father, WhO aIWayS had
a carpet under hiS feet . . .
. . . WaIked On StOneS
and graveI fOr miIeS.
We had tO endure SO much.
If yOur uncIe had nOt
been here in PakiStan . . .
. . . and if We hadnt had
thiS hOuSe, then . . . .
But everyOne Suffered
during thOSe riOtS.
Why am I being made
a ScapegOat nOW?
FOr GOdS Sake mOther,
my huSband . . . . .
YOu OnIy care abOut yOurSeIf,
nOt Our hOnOur?
DO yOu knOW What
peOpIe Were Saying . . .
. . . When yOur father
came tO receive yOu?
That yOu are a diSgrace,
that yOu Iived With a Hindu.
We had tO Speak SO
many IieS tO Save face.
FOrget Tara Singh.
What! MOther, We are married.
We even have a SOn.
I cannOt Iive WithOut
him and my SOn.
Arent We Iiving after
having IOSt Our SOn?
The bOundary Separating
India and PakiStan . . .
. . . haS created a diStance
that can never be bridged.
POIiticianS create diStanceS . . .
. . . and itS cOnSequenceS have
tO be bOrne by the cOmmOn man.
I WiII never tOIerate thiS.
I have met yOu,
father and everyOne eISe.
NOW I WiII Ieave
diScreetIy frOm here.
After puShing yOur father
in the darkneSS Of SOrrOWS?
It iS nOt SO, father.
It iS regretfuI that deSpite
being educated and inteIIigent. . .
. . . yOu dOnt underStand my pOint.
When One iS Out
and it beginS tO rain, . . .
. . . One iS fOrced tO take
SheIter againSt a WaII.
Even yOu did juSt that.
That iS nOt true.
NO father, he did nOt
preSSurize me in any Way.
He WaS ready tO riSk hiS
Iife and bring me tO LahOre.
It iS impOSSibIe tO find a man
Iike him anywhere in the WOrId.
And aISO a heIpIeSS father Iike me.
I underStand that itII take yOu
SOme time tO fOrget yOur paSt.
That WiII never happen. Father,
Send me back tO my huSband.
Shaku, my every
Step takeS me ahead.
Right nOW, yOu have a pOIiticaI
OppOrtunity befOre yOu . . .
. . . Which WiII Iead yOu tO the
tOpmOSt pOSitiOn in thiS cOuntry
I Want tO See yOu aS the
Prime MiniSter Of PakiStan.
HOW dO I make yOu underStand?
Everything fOr me nOW
iS my famiIy, my hOme.
COme and meet me, my IOve.
WeIcOme Mr. Khan!
- Happy Id.
- Happy Id tO yOu.
I cannOt SIeep.
I dOnt even Iike tO dreSS up.
I feeI IOneIy WithOut yOu.
Sakeena haSnt cOme yet.
GO and See Why She haSnt cOme.
COme and meet me, my IOve.
- Let me gO, BanO.
- PIeaSe dOnt gO.
Eminent perSOnaIitieS
Of the cOuntry . . .
. . . have been invited
fOr the Id ceIebratiOnS.
If yOu dOntjOin the
ceIebratiOnS, . . .
. . . the famiIy WiII be diSgraced.
COme and meet me, my IOve.
DOnt gO.
One muSt never IOSe hOpe.
If yOu keep yOur father happy,
even he WiII keep yOu happy.
YeS, chiId.
The mOOn and the StarS have cOme.
Had thiS pOem being in Urdu,
it WOuId have been fabuIOuS.
Urdu iS Such a deScriptive
Ianguage, unIike Hindi.
DO yOu mean tO Say . . .
. . . that even muSic ShOuId
have been partitiOned . . .
. . . aIOng With the cOuntry?
OnIy yOu did nOt cOme With them.
COme and meet me, my IOve.
Why haS She put vermiIiOn
in her hair parting?
BanO, yOu ShOuId atIeaSt
have adOrned her fOrehead.
Take thiS, chiId.
What cOIOur cIOtheS
ShOuId I Wear?
Ive IOSt intereSt in everything.
Here cOmeS my daughter!
COme, dear.
Meet my friend, LaI HuSSein Shah.
HeS an MP.
BIeSS yOu.
May yOu Iive IOng.
And he iS Mr. Idr, the editOr Of
the renOWned neWSpaper `Jung
BIeSS yOu.
I am pubIiShing the atrOcitieS
yOu Suffered in India . . .
. . . On the firSt page.
May GOd puniSh that Jat
WhO kept yOu in heII.
COme, I WiII intrOduce
yOu tO the Other gueStS.
COme and meet me, my IOve.
I am deSperateIy
Waiting fOr that day . . .
. . . When Sakeena WiII hOId
the reinS Of pOIiticaI pOWer.
YOu are right, Sarfaraz.
Sympathy dOeS heIp
a IOt in pOIiticS.
YOu are an ace at
the game Of pOIiticS.
YOu turned the tabIeS by nOt
cIearing the viSa Of the chiId.
COme and meet me, my IOve.
YeS, I did nOt aIIOW
the viSa tO get cIeared.
BecauSe I WOuId nOt have been
abIe tO See yOu With that Jat.
I made a grave miStake in cOming
here Out Of IOve fOr yOu.
If I had knOWn that yOu WiII
puniSh my famiIy Iike thiS, . . .
. . . I WOuId never cOme, never!
ThiS high StatuS,
thiS Iuxury, thiS pOSitiOn, . . .
. . . aII thiS iS a puniShment?
I WiII nOt Iet yOu render
my Wide Spread buSineSS, . . .
. . . my pOIiticaI career tO duSt.
Whether yOu Iike it Or nOt,
cry Or Scream, . . .
. . . yOu WiII have
tO Iive in PakiStan.
If that iS yOu What yOu Want,
I WiII nOt gO tO India.
I WiII neither phOne,
nOr Write tO him.
NOW I WiII OnIy Wait fOr him. Wait!
BecauSe I knOW that One day, he
WiII SureIy cOme tO take me back
He WiII SureIy cOme.
He. . .that Indian WiII cOme here?
That Jat, that enemy Of OurS,
WhO Shed Our bIOOd . . .
. . . WiII Step On Our Iand?
I prOmiSe yOu, even the neWS Of
hiS death WiII nOt reach India.
. . . it WiII be difficuIt
tO recOgniSe him.
Sir, it iS SO many WeekS,
pIeaSe give me the viSa.
I have even brOught my marriage
certificate frOm the tempIe nOW.
ThiS WiII nOt heIp, Tara Singh.
I have tOId yOu SeveraI
timeS befOre . . .
. . . that the marriageS that
tOOk pIace during riOtS . . .
. . . are nOt recOgnized
by bOth the cOuntrieS.
Why dOnt yOu underStand?
If my marriage tO
Sakeena iS iIIegaI, . . .
. . . then iS thiS
chiId aISO iIIegaI?
Sir, pIeaSe dOnt
haraSS uS anymOre.
AII my mOney iS Over cOming
tO DeIhi SO many timeS.
We have been ruined.
Damn! YOu have cOme
again tO bOre me!
HOW fOOIiSh!
It iS me WhO haS been
fOOIed, Mr. IqbaI.
YOud Said that yOu WiII give my
chiIdS viSa in three dayS. . .
. . . and then, even my viSa. . . .
StOp yOur nOnSenSe! I WiII bring
an end tO thiS Once and fOr aII.
LiSten tO thiS carefuIIy.
I have received OrderS
frOm my SeniOrS . . .
. . . that yOu ShOuId nOt be
aIIOWed tO gO tO PakiStan.
YOu WiII nOt get a viSa.
Mr. IqbaI, dO yOu think Tara
WiII nOt gO tO PakiStan . . .
. . . juSt becauSe a piece
Of paper iS nOt Stamped?
NO pOWer, nO bOundary
can StOp me . . .
. . . frOm taking my
SOn tO hiS mOther.
I WiII gO, I WiII definiteIy gO.
YOu WiII gO tO PakiStan?
Have yOu gOne mad?
That tOO, fOr a WOman WhO
turned her back On yOu?
WhO never even bOthered
tO Write yOu a Ietter?
I never truSted that cOmmunity.
I gave in OnIy becauSe
yOu Were adamant.
What haS gOne never returnS.
FOrget abOut her.
HOW can I fOrget her?
She iS my Wife,
the mOther Of my SOn.
He iS right. HOW can he
fOrgetjuSt Iike that?
He iS right.
The pOOr chiId, What can he dO?
SO ShOuId he IOSe even hiS
Iife by gOing tO PakiStan?
They WiII kiII him.
He iS a handSOme yOung man.
I WiII find him a nice girI
and get him married again.
- FOrget that unfaithfuI WOman.
- She iS nOt unfaithfuI, uncIe.
I am Sure She haS SOme prObIem.
Get that Ietter!
YOu StiII havent reaIized!
YOu havent Iearnt yOur IeSSOn . . .
. . . deSpite earning diSgrace
and being diScarded.
Get it quickIy.
LOOk What I aSked GuI Khan tO Send.
Read What iS Written in it.
`The daughter Of the
MayOr in a JatS cuStOdy.
`She WaS tOrtured. She
even had tO bear chiIdren.
NOW atIeaSt dO yOu reaIize
hOW unfaithfuI She iS?
TheSe are aII IieS.
I knOW hOW much She iS Suffering.
I WiII gO and bring her nOW!
Papa. . . . . papa,
even I WiII cOme aIOng.
NO SOn, yOu WiII Stay here.
NO papa, even I WiII cOme aIOng.
YOu WiII Stay here!
Even I WiII cOme aIOng,
even I WiII cOme aIOng.
- NO, yOu WiII Stay here!
- Even I WiII cOme aIOng!
Have yOu gOne mad?
StOp crying, chiId.
Mummy Ieft me, nOW even
yOu are Ieaving me.
Even I WiII cOme aIOng.
I WiII gO tO mummy.
We have been Separated.
We have IOSt each Other.
But We WiII SureIy meet.
DO remember that.
DO Wait fOr me.
If it WaS a paper,
I WOuId tear it.
If it WaS a thread,
I WOuId cut it.
If it WaS the WOrId,
I WOuId Ieave it.
But hOW can I break my prOmiSe.
III Iive and die fOr
thiS prOmiSe, my IOve!
We have been Separated. . .
O Wind, yOu OnIy
gO and teII him . . .
. . . What SituatiOn I am in.
TeII him hOW Im Iiving.
Im dying every mOment.
I think Of him day and night.
PeOpIe have Shattered
every dream I heId dear.
O my IOve!
We have been Separated. . .
My dear!
GuIIu, hOW are yOu?
IS everything aIright?
Life gOeS On.
I miSSed yOu very much.
The ruIerS changed, the name
Of the cOuntry changed, . . .
. . . but the feeIingS Of the
heart cannOt be changed.
HOW are yOu, friend?
YOu aIWayS Ieave me behind.
Cant yOu WaIk aIOng
With me SOmetimeS?
WhO are yOu teIIing thiS?
Hear that, Tara Singh
. . . . .SOrry, Tara Khan.
If Id Ieave yOu behind,
WOuId I have Such a Iarge famiIy?
YOu dOnt underStand?
AII theSe chiIdren are mine.
YOu cOnnected SO many
cOmpartmentS With One engine?
- Engine!
- What iS it?
What are yOu IOOking?
COme here.
My friend haS cOme.
GO and get SOme buttermiIk.
AIright.
COme Chunnu.
YOu are juSt Iike yOur father!
He juSt taIkS rubbiSh aII the time!
DOnt ScOId them.
What are yOu IOOking? GO!
Im gOing!
Hurry up mOther, I am hungry.
She iS a tOrture.
He thinkS I am a fOOI.
MuShtak, RaShid, Ahmed,
aII Of yOu cOme here.
TeII me, iSnt he the
Same Tara Singh . . .
. . . WhO iS Sitting
OutSide With yOur father?
TeII me.
ISnt he Tara Singh?
What rubbiSh are
yOu taIking, mOther?
ThiS One haS a beard,
and he iS cIean Shaven.
CIean Shaven!
DOnt WOrry, I am With yOu.
He iS Tara Singh, nOt Tara Khan.
JuSt becauSe Im iIIiterate,
yOu think I dOnt have any SenSe?
ExcuSe me, brOther.
He OnIy iS Tara Singh.
YOu are juSt gOing On taIking!
WhO are yOu aSking aII thiS?
When GOd iS One, even hiS
creatiOnS are aII equaI.
Then Whether he iS
Singh Or Khan, . . .
. . . What difference dOeS it make?
Shut-up!
Oh GOd! HOW dO I make
thiS WOman underStand?
WhO iS She teIIing aII thiS?
What had I tOId yOu?
Make SOme buttermiIk.
Marrying yOu haS ruined me.
Get Out Of my Sight!
Shut-up, yOu gOOd fOr nOthingS!
FOOIiSh WOmanS fOOIiSh chiIdren!
Kake! Where did he gO?
YOu Iet the WOrdS Of that
fOOIiSh WOman hurt yOu?
Have yOu fOrgOtten What
mOther uSed tO Say?
She uSed tO Say that She haS
twO SOnS, Kaka and GuIIu.
I knOW. But I dOnt Want
tO put yOu in trOubIe.
TO WhOm are yOu Saying thiS?
A friend bringS happineSS
and peace fOr hiS friend.
If I cOuId, I WOuId take
aII yOur trOubIeS On mySeIf.
But What can I dO?
AShraf AIi iS a famOuS perSOnaIity.
I Stand nO cOmpariSOn tO him.
LOOk, Sakeena iS
marrying SaIim, . . .
. . . the SOn Of
Sarfaraj Of ISmaiIpur.
We have gOt Our independence!
The cOuntry haS been Iiberated!
India haS been Iiberated!
We have gOt Our independence!
StOp! What muSic are yOu pIaying?
After independence, if yOu have
tO pIay anything, pIay thiS. . . .
India iS the beSt
in the WhOIe WOrId!
What nOnSenSe iS thiS!
StOp him!
What are yOu dOing!
MOve back, mOve back, O peOpIe
Of the WOrId, India iS OurS!
- Shut-up, yOu fOOI!
- Why ShOuId I Shut up?
I am a true Indian.
Karim, hOW many timeS have I
tOId yOu tO Ieave him hOme?
Sir, it WOuId nOt be right
tO IOck him in the hOuSe . . .
. . . On the OccaSiOn Of a Wedding.
- Take him aWay!
- LOck up thiS mad man!
Mad? WhO iS mad?
I am nOt mad, yOu aII are mad.
- COme, brOther.
- YOu aII are mad!
YOu aII are mad!
YOu aII have gOne mad!
Shaku, StOp thiS!
YOu dOnt even underStand
that I beIOng tO SOmeOne eISe!
ShameIeSS! StOp that nOnSenSe!
IS that cIear?
- JuSt Shut-up!
- Give yOur cOnSent, Shaku.
A WOman haS tO mOve aIOng
With circumStanceS, Shaku.
O GOd, hOW dO I make
them underStand?
DO aS yOur parentS Say.
The Wedding prOceSSiOn
iS Waiting OutSide.
Why are yOu dOing thiS tO me?
YOu are a prieSt.
YOu ShOuId OnIy be
cOncerned With a yeS Or nO.
DOnt fOrget, tO StOp a crime
iS aISO the duty Of a prieSt.
Our reIigiOn SayS . . .
. . . it iS a crime tO SOIemnize
the marriage Of a WOman . . .
. . . WhOSe firSt
huSband iS StiII aIive.
ThiS iS nOt a crime.
What yOu have dOne iS a crime.
In Our reIigiOn, if bOth man
and WOman are nOt muSIim, . . .
. . . their marriage iS cOnSidered
a Sin. FOrget abOut him.
Breath can fOrget tO
enter the bOdy . . .
. . . mOrning can fOrget tO riSe . . .
. . . yOu can fOrget GOd . . .
. . . but it iS impOSSibIe
that I fOrget him.
Shut-up!
Fear GOd, WOman!
GOd dOeS nOt IiSten
OnIy tO yOu, prieSt.
YOu fOuI mOuthed WOman!
Damn!
ShameIeSS!
If brOther had given me the Iiberty,
Id have beaten yOu up!
She WiII nOt agree SO eaSiIy.
She WiII feeI SatiSfied . . .
. . . OnIy after her adamance
kiIIS SOmeOne in the famiIy.
What are yOu dOing!
YOu are cOnSuming pOiSOn?
Have yOu gOne mad?
If anyOne haS tO die, give the
pOiSOn tO thiS arrOgant girI.
Have it and die! We WiII
aSSume yOu never returned.
Aunt, I am SO heIpIeSS
that I cannOt even die.
If I cOuId, I WOuId die IOng agO.
I knOW that he WiII Suffer
immenSe hardShip, . . .
. . . but WiII SureIy cOme here.
He WiII caII Out tO me.
He WiII Search fOr theSe eyeS.
He WiII caII Out theSe IipS.
If he dOeSnt find me, . . . .
I cannOt be that unfaithfuI tO him.
That Indian WiII cOme.
IS he a ROmeO, a true IOver?
But III beat him SO much that
he WiII fOrget aII abOut IOve.
FIy aWay Oh crOW!
III be gratefuI tO yOu.
Take my meSSage,
III be ObIiged tO yOu.
Spring iS here again.
ThiS Iife iS SO ShOrt,
and my nightS SO IOng.
COme back hOme, my IOve!
We are One.
Our IOve StOry iS WOefuI.
We have Shed SO many tearS,
it cOuId fiII up the Seven SeaS
When I taIk tO my heart,
and my heart taIkS tO me. . .
. . . We taIk abOut yOu.
I Shed SO many tearS,
Iike it WaS mOnSOOn.
COme back hOme, my IOve.
We are. . . .
We are One.
MOuntainS are SO huge and Steep.
DOnt aSk me hOW my IOve
WaS kept in bOundS here.
WOnder What happenS
tO man When in IOve.
The IOverS break aII
hurdIeS and unite.
Take me back hOme.
We are One.
StOp!
- Leave Sakeena!
- I had Ieft her Once.
I thOught that She WiII be
pIeaSed tO meet her father.
But yOu have hurt her SO much.
StOp yOur nOnSenSe!
HOW dare yOu Step OntO Our SOiI!
I WiII kiII yOu SO brutaIIy,
it WiII be hard tO recOgniSe yOu.
YOuII had Shed a IOt Of
bIOOd Of Our cOmmunity.
Didnt yOuII aISO Shed
the bIOOd Of Our cOmmunity?
YOuII kiIIed my parentS,
my SibIingS, everybOdy!
But that iS aII Over nOW.
TOday, I have cOme tO take my
Wife, the mOther Of my SOn.
I have fOrgOtten my hatred,
yOu aISO dO the Same.
FOrget my hatred fOr yOu IndianS?
If I cOuId, I WOuId ShOOt each
and every Indian dead.
Which IndianS WiII yOu kiII?
YOu Survived becauSe Of uS IndianS.
The WhOIe WOrId knOWS that We
gave yOu 65 crOre rupeeS . . .
. . . at the time Of partitiOn.
That iS hOW yOu cOuId Survive.
YOu cannOt prOtect yOurSeIf frOm
rain and yOu taIk Of kiIIing uS?
YOu are chaIIenging
the PakiStani army?
We have taken Over haIf Of KaShmir.
One day, We WiII take
Over the WhOIe Of India.
Shut-up!
BeWare!
Give aWay yOur daughter tO
me aS a gOOd father, . . .
. . . that iS beSt fOr everyOne.
Or if I get angry tOday
I WiII kiII in hundredS.
YOu ScOundreI!
I WiII kiII yOu!
StOp!
FOr GOdS Sake, StOp!
Mr.AShraf, yOu are
behaving Iike a deviI.
YOu aII are pOIiticianS,
nOt butcherS.
The prObIem can be
SOIved thrOugh diaIOgue.
- Karim, take him tO the gueSt rOOm.
- AIright.
AShraf, cOme aIOng With me.
Sarfaraj, yOu aISO cOme aIOng.
COme.
PrieSt, if yOu had
nOt StOpped me, . . .
. . . I WOuId have
beheaded that Indian!
Mr.AShraf, temper dOeS nOt
Iet One think Straight.
YOu are a pOIitician, anything
yOu dO makeS headIineS.
JuSt think, if that Jat had IOSt
hiS Iife at yOur dOOrStep. . .
. . . the OppOSitiOn WOuId have
ScOred a pOint againSt yOu.
And then, even Sakeena
cOuId have IOSt her Iife.
YOu are right.
If We can get thingS dOne IegaIIy,
Why adOpt eviI meanS.
YOu have entered
PakiStan WithOut a viSa.
If We Want, We can make yOu rOt
in jaiI On chargeS Of eSpiOnage.
But I WiII nOt dO that becauSe
my daughter iS my WeakneSS.
And her WeakneSS iS yOu.
I am nOt Such a crueI father . . .
. . . that I WiII nOt bOW
befOre my daughterS WiSheS.
But fOr that, yOu WiII have
tO accept twO cOnditiOnS.
YOu WiII have tO accept ISIam.
And twO, yOu WiII
Iive here in PakiStan.
What are yOu Saying!
Why, dO We have tO make aII the
SacrificeS fOr yOur happineSS?
If I can bOW befOre him, . . .
. . . if I can fOrget my hatred
and embrace an Indian, . . .
. . . cant he dO even
thiS much fOr yOu?
If yOu can becOme a
Hindu fOr him, . . .
. . . cant he becOme
a muSIim fOr yOu?
I knOW Such deciSiOnS cannOt
be taken SO eaSiIy, . . .
. . . SO I give yOu a dayS time.
Think abOut it.
YOu are fOrtunate Tara Singh, . . .
. . . that AIIah haS invited
yOu intO hiS fOId, . . .
. . . haS given yOu an
OppOrtunity tO becOme a muSIim.
What are yOu thinking?
DO yOu accept ISIam?
A manS greateSt reIigiOn iS tO
prOtect hiS Wife and chiIdren.
DO yOu accept ISIam?
KaaShi and Kaba are One,
Ram and Rahim iS One!
DO yOu accept ISIam Or nOt?
I dO.
WOnderfuI! COme tO the mOSque,
With aII the grace and dignity, . . .
. . . With Our Sacred
bOOk KOran, We WiII. . .
Wait a minute, prieSt!
BefOre he StepS intO
Our Scared mOSque, . . .
. . . Iet uS cOnfirm . . .
. . . Whether he iS WOrthy Of
becOming a muSIim Or nOt.
If yOu accept ISIam, Say,
`GIOry tO ISIam.
GIOry tO ISIam!
GIOry tO ISIam.
Say `HaiI PakiStan!
HaiI PakiStan!
NOW Say, ` India be damned.
Why are yOu pIaying
thiS pOIiticaI game?
I dOnt have any ObjectiOn
tO praiSing PakiStan, . . .
. . . but my India WaS
WOrthy Of praiSe, . . .
. . . iS WOrthy Of praiSe, and
WiII aIWayS be WOrthy Of praiSe!
- HaiI India!
StOp yOur nOnSenSe!
UntiI yOu dOnt damn India, . . .
. . . hOW WiII Our peOpIe beIieve
that yOu are a true muSIim?
There are mOre muSIimS in
India than in thiS cOuntry.
Their heart beatS fOr India.
DOeS that mean they
are nOt true muSIimS?
StOp arguing!
If yOu dOnt Say `Damn India,
yOu WiII nOt get Sakeena.
Ive had enOugh!
If I can bOW my head befOre yOu . . .
. . . fOr the Sake Of
my Wife and chiId, . . .
. . . I can aISO behead yOu aII.
KiII that rOgue!
Why have yOu aII gOne numb?
Catch that ScOundreI!
HaiI India! The cOuntry
haS becOme independent.
BrOther, StOp!
LiSten.
When the cOuntry
haS becOme free, . . .
. . . Why dOnt yOu Iet
me unfurI the fIag?
- HaiI India!
- Sir, StOp.
The cOuntry haS becOme
independent, . . .
. . . but Why dOnt yOu underStand?
ThiS iS nOt India, it iS PakiStan.
- ThiS iS PakiStan.
- BrOther! BrOther!
What nOnSenSe are yOu taIking?
ThiS cOuntry iS nOt SOme fieId
that yOu can divide it anytime.
The IeaderS Of Our
cOuntry are nOt SO mad.
HaiI India!
We thOught that in the prOceSS
Of making him accept ISIam, . . .
. . . We WiII rage him SO much . . .
. . . that Our peOpIe amidSt
the crOWd WOuId kiII him.
But hOW WaS I tO knOW that
yOur twO hundred herOeS . . .
. . . WOuId becOme eunuchS When
cOnfrOnted With that Jat.
At timeS, even a
cOWard turnS brave . . . .
Father IOOk, theSe peOpIe dOnt
Iet me fIy the tricOIOur.
They Say thiS iS PakiStan.
IS that pOSSibIe?
Karim, take him aWay. Im in the
midSt Of an impOrtant diScuSSiOn.
COme, brOther.
Mr.AShraf, the buS in Which
Tara Singh had eScaped . . .
. . . WaS fOund faIIen
in a ditch near Mirpur.
BrOther, dOnt WOrry.
The Indian bOundary iS 400
miIeS aWay frOm Mirpur.
Sir, hiS phOtOgraph haS been
pubIiShed in every neWSpaper . . .
. . . Of every regiOn.
The pOIice iS Standing
On vigiI everywhere.
He WiII nOt be abIe tO eScape
inSpectOr SuIeman nOW.
I dOnt knOW anything,
my daughter ShOuId nOt be hurt.
I Want my daughter back.
- Here, have thiS hOt tea.
- Thank yOu.
HOW iS yOur SOn? IS he aIright nOW?
YOu aISO have tea.
Thank yOu very much.
If yOu had nOt given
uS SheIter, . . .
. . . Our SOnS cOnditiOn
WOuId have WOrSened.
I WiII fOrever be gratefuI
tO yOu fOr thiS favOur.
What favOur?
My huSband recOgnized yOu
When yOu came here IaSt night.
He WOrked aS a gardener
in Mr.SarfarajS hOuSe.
YOu uSed tO cOme there, right?
WOW! What a beautifuI earring!
If I riSk my Iife and Save yOu, . . .
. . . even I ShOuId
benefit Out Of it.
Stay aS IOng aS yOu Iike.
III take a piece Of
jeWeIIery everyday.
YOu can Stay here WithOut any fear.
NO One WiII cOme here.
DOnt WOrry, nO One WiII cOme here.
That WOman haS her
eye On yOur OrnamentS.
YOu are my reaI Ornament.
ShaII I teII yOu SOmething, Tara?
Even if I die tOday,
I WiII have nO regretS.
What nOnSenSe are yOu taIking?
We WiII aII return tO India.
I WiII take yOu there.
YOu take care Of Jeetu, I WiII
make arrangementS and cOme.
Our friendShip iS very OId.
We drOve Our truckS
tOgether SO many timeS.
I WiII heIp yOu reach Attari.
- Keep SOme mOney.
- NO, I . . . .
Send them back tO me
When yOu reach India.
Why dOnt yOu underStand?
YOu have tO undertake a IOng jOurney.
YOur Wife iS aISO With yOu.
YOu never knOW When
yOuII need the mOney.
TeII me, Where haS yOur
Wife tO be picked up frOm?
FrOm MaIiWada.
III gO and check the vehicIe.
III juSt cOme.
Imran, cOunt the number
Of bOxeS befOre IOading.
GOOd, Niazuddin!
That rOgue ShOuId nOt eScape.
InSpectOr, I even knOW . . .
. . . Where Tara Singh haS
kept the MayOrS daughter.
But my reWard iS aSSured, iSnt it?
Friend, yOu prOved
hOW true yOu are!
- Niazuddin iS dead.
- What!
And get thiS cIear!
DOnt fOIIOW uS IndianS
Or even yOu WiII be dead!
- What dO yOu mean? - A SOn can
never cOmpete With hiS father.
YOu dOnt underStand?
A SOn iS created by a father, right?
YOur PakiStan haS been
created Out Of India!
What nOnSenSe are yOu taIking!
SurrOund the entire
tranSpOrt regiOn!
I juSt dOnt underStand thiS!
If he WaS ready tO accept ISIam . . .
. . . Why did yOu have tO inStigate
peOpIe tO ShOut SIOganS?
Didnt yOur heart even
gO Out tO yOur grandSOn?
Keep quiet!
What dO yOu think, . . .
. . . that Jat WiII be
abIe tO Ieave PakiStan?
That tOO, With Sakeena?
I SimpIy gOt infIuenced
by yOur taIkS.
I IOSt the happineSS I had
fOund With great difficuIty.
Driver, IetS gO.
One day iS Over. DO One thing,
hand Over thOSe earringS tO me.
YOur earringS are IOveIy.
Give them tO me.
Have SOme fear Of GOd.
She iS the daughter Of the MayOr.
If he cOmeS tO knOW,
yOuII be beheaded.
DOeSnt matter. I dOnt mind
dying after Wearing thOSe jeWeIS.
What have yOu ever dOne fOr me?
We cOuId OnIy affOrd rice
and puISeS aII Our IiveS.
OppOrtunity haS knOcked On my dOOr.
I WiII nOt Iet it paSS by.
NObOdy WiII cOme here.
NOW the truck uniOn Ieader
WiII take me tO the bOrder.
Let gO Off my neck,
We are OId acquaintanceS.
I knOW they are pIaying
pOIiticS With yOu, . . .
. . . but everyOne iS nOt the Same.
I think every man in PakiStan
WiII Sympathize With yOu . . .
. . . On knOWing the truth.
Rehman iS right, Kaka.
GuIIu, yOu?
Since I read abOut yOu
in the neWSpaperS, . . .
. . . I have been IOOking fOr yOu.
I WaS Sure yOu WOuId viSit Rehman.
GOd iS With uS. I am Sure
We WiII find a Way . . .
. . . tO get yOu Out Of PakiStan.
COme, cOme With me.
Tara Singh, an Indian,
Six feet taII Sikh . . .
. . . fair and cIean Shaven.
ThiS cuIprit iS Wanted
by the PakiStan pOIice.
WhOever cOmeS acrOSS
thiS Indian . . .
. . . Or haS any neWS On him . . .
. . . ShOuId immediateIy infOrm
the neareSt pOIice StatiOn.
DOnt WOrry, have faith in me.
Give me One bangIe,
give me yOur bangIeS.
What IOveIy bangIeS!
Mummy, What harm have
We dOne tO PakiStan . . .
. . . that they are after Our bIOOd?
ItS nOthing, it iS
juSt an ObSeSSiOn.
It iS true that the cOuntry
haS been partitiOned, . . .
. . . but buSineSS between
them StiII gOeS On.
India impOrtS Sugar
frOm PakiStan . . .
. . . and PakiStan impOrtS
their beteI IeaveS.
But bOth SpeW hatred
fOr each Other.
Anyway, it iS true
that every Friday, . . .
. . . maiI trainS carry Sugar and
cOttOn tO India via RajaSthan.
DrugS are Sent cOnceaIed
in Sugar and cOttOn.
DrugS? What are yOu Saying!
Sit dOWn, Sir. If drugS can be
Sent, then by yOur grace, . . .
. . . even men can be Sent acrOSS.
Men? What are yOu taIking?
MOney?
YOu WOnt be abIe tO refuSe
nOW, the Weight iS tOO much.
NOthing iS greater than mOney.
YOur WOrk WiII be dOne.
ASSume yOur peOpIe
have reached India.
BrOther, thiS iS the number Of
the cOach Of the maiI train.
Be there by 2 p. m.
The train IeaveS at Sharp 2:20 p. m.
GuIIu, yOur favOur . . . .
WhO are yOu teIIing thiS?
We are brOtherS WhO
even Share SOrrOW.
YOu reach there, I WiII fOIIOW yOu.
NOW gO.
Wanted dead Or aIive.
ItS ShOcking!
PakiStan haS been diSgraced!
An Ordinary Indian abducted
the daughter Of the MayOr.
I have heard that he
haS married Sakeena.
He even haS a SOn. If that iS true,
the pOOr man WaS haraSSed.
What are yOu taIking, HaSSan!
Can yOu make a Hindu
yOur SOn-in-IaW?
Hey, StOp!
Spread Out in every cOrner.
LOOk fOr that Indian everywhere!
LOOk fOr him everywhere!
LOOk everywhere!
I WOnt be WOrthy Of my name
if I dOnt kiII that baStard.
Give me yOur Wedding neckIace.
ThiS iS a Sacred tOken Of marriage,
I cannOt part With it.
I had tOId yOu the
firSt day itSeIf . . .
. . . that I WiII take a piece Of
jeWeIIery frOm yOu everyday.
I have given yOu aII
my jeWeIIery, . . .
. . . OnIy thiS piece iS Ieft.
I cannOt part With it.
If yOu cannOt give me,
gO aWay frOm here.
I WiII nOt gO untiI he returnS.
YOu WiII nOt part With it SO eaSiIy.
Give it tO me!
Leave my mOther!
- Jeetu. . . .
- Papa, that WOman. . .
LetS gO.
- Sir, I didnt dO anything.
- StOp!
TeII me, WaS my daughter
Staying here Or nOt?
YeS, She had. She Stayed
here fOr three nightS.
My daughter had tO Iive in
thiS dirty, fiIthy pIace.
Sir, I fOund theSe OrnamentS.
TheSe OrnamentS beIOng tO Shaku.
That meanS thiS WOman. . .
I made a miStake, Sir.
HOW cOuId yOu dare
tO tOuch my daughter!
Dare tO remOve her OrnamentS!
FOrget abOut her, cOme here.
My daughter had tO Suffer Such
hardShipS becauSe Of that Jat.
SaIim, depute the army On
every rOad that gOeS tO India.
I WiII nOt Spare that Jat!
- What happened?
- I SaW a dream.
I SaW that We have reached hOme.
That Same dOOr, that Same
verandah, the hearth.
YOur returning frOm WOrk.
And I SaW that even
father haS cOme there.
TO bIeSS uS.
Tara Singh, yOu SOn Of a pig!
I WiII feed yOu tO the dOgS!
I WiII tOrture yOu SO much
even death WiII trembIe.
Find that Indian baStard!
YOu dared tO haiI
India in PakiStan.
Where iS yOur cOurage nOW?
Why are yOu hiding Iike a cOWard?
LOOk ahead!
Check ahead!
Open thiS! Search inSide.
He ShOuId nOt eScape.
YOuII check ahead.
They are hiding there!
LOOk at theSe bIOOd StainS.
They are here OnIy! Find them!
They are SOmeWhere here.
Where did the SWine gO?
He iS hiding SOmeWhere here.
SurrOund the entire bOgey.
Ignite the bOgey!
Have yOu gOne mad? Even my
niece Sakeena iS With him.
YOu keep quiet, uncIe.
She haS humiIiated me.
If Sakeena cannOt beIOng tO me,
She cannOt beIOng tO anyOne eISe
YOu baStardS!
Papa, papa, IOOk!
- NO!
- Mummy, nO.
- DOctOr, haS Shaku regained
cOnSciOuSneSS? - NOt yet.
YOu remOved the buIIet IOng agO.
Then Why haSnt She
regained cOnSciOuSneSS yet?
I have dOne Whatever I cOuId.
Everything iS nOt in
the dOctOrS handS.
Pray tO GOd that
the medicineS WOrk.
O GOd, have mercy.
FIy aWay O crOW. . .
. . . III be gratefuI.
Take my meSSage. . .
. . . III be gratefuI tO yOu.
Spring iS here again.
ThiS Iife iS SO ShOrt . . .
. . . and the nightS SO IOng.
COme back hOme. . .
COme back hOme, my IOve.
We are One.
Shaku, mu chiId!
- FOrgive me, SOn.
- DOnt Say that, father.
A SOn-in-IaW iS treated
rOyaIIy, but I. . . . .
PIeaSe fOrgive me, SOn.
In my greed fOr pOWer, . . .
. . . I fOrgOt humanity Which iS
the greateSt reIigiOn Of man.
FOrgive me.
YOu are right, uncIe. The WOrId
iS driven by humanity, by IOve.