"Desires, thousands of them..."
"desires I could die for"
"I had so many desires..."
"and yet, so few they were"
"Dear Gita, Calcutta was
awe-inspiring"
"I'm now back in Delhi,
my beliefs totally strengthened"
"We have to change the world.
And change it fundamentally"
"I always knew the facts, but when
I met some of the mothers..."
"and widows of thousands of students
who had sacrificed their lives..."
"during the Naxalite movement,
I felt completely humbled"
"They were the best and
the brightest of Bengal"
"But instead of taking
the comfortable roads...
"that their parents
had laid down for them..."
"they went down the dirt and
the muddy roads to the villages..."
"to end the vulgarity
of oppression"
"The violence of the oppressed
is right"
"The violence of the Oppressor
is wrong"
"And to hell with ethics"
"I mean, weren't Bhagat Singh's
actions correct?"
"It made me think
of ourselves"
"I mean, who do we think
we are?"
"Strutting around, sprouting radical
jargon, a little politics..."
"some rock-n-roll...
but mostly shock value"
"Isn't it shameful that I,
Sidharth Tyebji..."
"son of a Muslim father and
a Hindu Bengali mother..."
"neither can speak
Urdu nor Bengali?"
"My parents did not give me the
one thing of value that they could"
"This has to change"
"Gita, I have now become
a card-holder of the Party"
"Eventually, you must also.
More when you get back"
"Love - Sidharth"
"Dear Gita, first things first.
I still love you"
"I'm still stuck in Meerut because
the trains have been cancelled..."
"due to the Hindu-Muslim sibling
rivalry that has flared up again"
"This time it's not so bad.
Only 38 dead"
"Two of them were eaten by the
circus lion, when one rioteer..."
"chased his victim into
the lion's enclosure"
"But most of the town
doesn't give a shit"
"An announcement:
The town is under curfew"
"Citizens are requested
to stay indoors"
"What really gets everyone here
excited is the news..."
"that the local hardware merchant's
daughter ran away with their cook"
"Some of the family members finally
caught him and put him in a pot..."
"and boiled him.
Just kidding; they only castrated him"
"This state of affairs
only worries my father..."
"thirty of his Gandhian colleagues,
seventy socialists..."
"and a hundred and two others
no end"
"But being worried is my
father's main profession"
"He should have been more
worried about us, though..."
"and we wouldn't have been stuck at
the lower-end of great middle-class"
Not now. Go away
"Which is why I can't understand
you rich kids playing..."
"the let's-change-the-world game"
"While you're looking for a way out,
I'm looking for a way in"
"Into your heart, I mean"
"See you soon.
Love - Vikram"
Is your hero through
Uncle...
Here's some yogurt for luck
Look after yourself
Don't worry. It'll be all right.
- It won't
But you concentrate
on your studies
Enough of this filial love!
Come on now
Move it. If anyone asks, say you're
dropping my nephew at the station
Father, I'm leaving.
Why enact this farce?
You know who started it all
If everyone shirks responsibility,
then God help us all
Go on, you're getting late.
Write to your mother as soon as
you reach Delhi
What does he want me to do? Become
a martyr and die in this shit-hole?
What's up? Your wife threw you out
early in the morning?
No, it's because you're
going to Delhi
So I thought why should I waste money
mailing this letter?
At least you'll deliver it,
safe and sound
Give this letter to Randhir bhaisahab.
Tell him everything is fine here.
St. Stephen's College
New Delhi, 1969
Kiddo! Come on, pick up my bags.
Damn you, it's my room too.
You haven't even unpacked and
your guests have taken over
When you meet someone after a long
time you're supposed to say hello.
I can't even sit alone in my own room?
It'll do you more good to sit
with them than to jerk off.
They are Youth Congress...
lots of power, kiddo!
Randhir bhaisahab!
- Hey kiddo!
I've been scratching my balls,
waiting for the last two hours
Where have you been?
- The train was late...
Screw the train.
Hows everyone at home?
Fine. The riots are also under control.
- Screw that too
So, where's my letter?
- How did you know about it?
Back home, if you shit and don't wipe
your ass, the boss gets to know
Otherwise, he couldn't have
led a political party
And engineered the riots too?
- Balls
The boss hasn't budged from here
for the last nine days.
Now tell me, what's all this?
No Gandhi, no Nehru, no Subhash...?
And what's going on downstairs?
Some rock show,
your room-mate told me
Saw some weird-Iooking girls...
eminently screwable,
each one of them
Wow, what a jeep!
You like it?
- Yes
Keep it.
To all you fans of Jimi Hendrix
and Bob Dylan...
who fought against injustice
in their own country...
we want you to think, question.
Don't just listen, not even to us
But what would Daddy say?
- Tell Daddy life's not just fun.
Tell Daddy there's a famine in Bihar.
Tell Daddy people are dying
in the countryside.
Tell him that he's
responsible for this.
Because he's a collaborator
in a state...
which is a state of big landlords
and bourgeois capitalists.
And tell Daddy that life's not just
about getting proper English education...
earning a fat salary
and loving one's parents
There are countries in this world...
where people have
established a new order.
China... Vietnam... Telengana!
Once upon a time, a princess was
walking down the street all alone
Abandoned by her prince...
when a gallant knight rode up
to her on his royal steed.
He swept her off feet and
they rode into the sunset.
Not every story has a
happily ever after, Vikram.
Well, because every story
has its Sidharth, right?
Come on, I'll drop you
Your knight in shining armour
will escort you to the lion's lair
As long as you don't keep me
from the lion, Sir Knight.
Wow, and these guys are
supposed to be Marxists!
Ah... come on!
Join us for a drink.
No, I'll go upstairs and
meet Sidharth. I'll join you later.
I think I will also
leave in a little while
Listen, you have to drop me home!
If we are really convinced...
if we are really moved...
then let's go and take some
affirmative action.
If we want to make a change, we
must go and work in the villages.
Look at Castro and what he did
in Cuba
Cuba is small.
We're an enormous country
We have Probir-da here.
He has worked in villages all his life
Instead of letting him speak,
we're getting into this intellectual...
Probir da...
Gandhi understood the importance
of villages before much Mao
He said no revolution was possible
without organising the rural poor
But what social revolution
did he bring?
That's exactly why
our party has gone much further
Alongside the worker,
the rural poor must also be armed
Did we bring any changes in
those villages.
All that M.K. Gandhi did was to become
a guest of big Marwari businessman.
Don't you have anything
to say, Gita?
What can I say?
- Why?
I've lived all my life between
England and Delhi.
I've never been to a village leave alone
know anything about their problems
But you people seem to know
everything. So why ask me?
That's not the attitude to have
How will you ever learn
if you don't discuss...
Do you love me, Sidharth?
What?
- Just answer. Do you love me?
Yeah, sure.
Do you really love me?
I just said so.
Say it.
I love you.
Sorry.
- It's okay.
We're going to join the
University strike tomorrow
You're with us, aren't you?
- I think it's load of shit
I don't know what you're
trying to accomplish
We're not trying.
And even if doesn't work...
Sidharth says, it's worth it.
At least we're there...
Sidharth was born with a silver spoon
in his mouth. His father is an ex-judge.
He can afford to think
the way he does. We can't
Why are you so against him?
- I'm not against him
Personally I'm just worried about you;
you're too gullible
These guys have
their dads' connections
...and, there's your dad.
I appreciate your concern,
but I can take care of myself.
Sorry... sorry.
Forgiven?
Dad, that's Vikram.
He looked after me last night
Ask him in for a cup of coffee.
Come inside and have a cup of
good South Indian coffee
These are my uncles.
These are my aunts
Grandma!
Is he the one?
- No, grandma, he's not the one!
Political parties are just
interested in getting our votes.
They have become pimps
for the management
And let me warn you about one thing
Many parties attach the word
"Socialist" to their names
but that doesn't make them socialist
Even Hitler's party was called the
Nationalist Socialist Party
Who's Hitler?
- Who knows? Wasn't from my village
See, they don't understand
what's happening here...
Until the workers are organised...
The management is trying to
intimidate us with strong-arm tactics!
Let's get out of here!
I have to leave.
- Where are you going?
I'll tell you later
Rajan, take the bag.
Leave!
Get out of here!
This is preposterous!
Only I have a right to question
whom my son brings home
And who the hell are you to
talk about my son's character?
It looks ridiculous coming from
people like... anyway, never mind
We've taken enough shit
from you, sir
We had information that your son
was hiding anti-social elements
We have a search warrant
If you still have a problem,
talk to my superiors
What is it?
We've got to search the place.
- Go ahead
Come
This son of a bitch
is a total degenerate.
That's an understatement.
The jerk's got it all.
- And here we are tickling our balls.
Lucky bastard!
Thanks... for stopping the cops.
It's getting chilly, why don't
you take your grandmother inside?
She insists on sleeping
in the open
It's an old habit
In her father's house,
the kids always slept on the terrace
What will she do when you leave?
So are you serious
about this Bihar thing?
I'm serious about going
to Bihar... yes
Of all the stupid...!
Sorry.
Can I ask, why?
You mean you don't know why?
- No, educate me
Because I'm sick of people like you who
sit and pontificate about India...
its problems... the oppressive political
and social systems and...
then do nothing about it
So you have faith in an ideology
that talks of annihilation...
and the murder of people as an
acceptable way of changing the system?
What gives you that right?
I met a couple of Englishmen
They say a revolution in our country
is just not possible
I told them to come with us
to Calcutta...
where thousands of students have
laid down their lives
It's amazing how ignorant they are
They'll get a shock when
they see that forty boys come...
from a single hamlet in Bihar.
- I talked to the student leader
He said that around 15 students
are coming from his college
It's a pity.
- Why?
There's just eight of us.
- So what?
Comrades, Prahlad called...
- Where is he?
He said he's not going...
- What do you mean?
The upper-class bastard!
- Look man, things are not easy
I mean this whole business
about the cops...
Why are you justifying that punk?
- Look, I'm also not going. Okay?
There's this West Indian poet
coming to the British Council...
What...? What?
If my brother finds out I'm going
to Calcutta, I'll get screwed!
So this's the level of your commitment?
- This thing is too dangerous, man!
I have to think about my future!
What about documenting our
struggle and all that?
Sidharth, even I'm not going
I know you'll be very upset,
but my parents...
Sidharth I'm not going!
- It's okay
Probir-da, we don't need these guys.
Prahlad, Amit... we don't need them
Police!
Hey Vikram.
I just got my U.S. Visa
Hey Pablo...
- Got into Brooks, still photography
Take care
This is Vikram Malhotra
speaking, sir
I'm a friend of Mehmood
Tyebji's son Sidharth
Could you do me a favour, sir?
I wish to speak to the Finance Minister
Sidharth would have himself called,
but he's not well
Only for five minutes...?
Yes, I'll hold
Hey Sidharth, I'm sorry
I wanted to be with you all
I still believe in the ideology
But my dad's just too rich...
I can't give up all this, can I?
So you're leaving on the 17th?
- Yes
I have just applied for my M.A.
Good. I mean, that's the
right course for you
Good, yes
We might not see each other
for some time
Maybe
Gita...
sweetheart, I'll be back
in about six months time...
it's not the end of the world, is it?
No
It's not the end of the world
May I have the next dance with you?
- Sure
"I'm crazed at heart,
I've lost all sense of reason"
"It wakes all night,
my crazed heart"
"A thousand desires..."
"desires I could die for"
"So many desires I had..."
"and yet, so few they were"
"My crazed heart,
it won't be placated with you..."
"what does it seek...?"
"Dear Gita..."
"You'll probably tear this letter
without reading it"
"But you have to let me
try and explain myself"
"I know I said I'd be back in
six months and then disappeared"
"But you must realise that
when I left for Bhojpur..."
"I didn't really know what
I was getting into"
"Bhojpur and Delhi are not separated
merely by a thousand miles..."
"but also five thousand years"
"You must have heard of exploitation,
disease, lawlessness and apathy"
"There's all that here and much more"
"But once you've been here and seen
the despair, you cannot leave"
For how long are you going to
take this shit from the landlords?
You can't even sit in their presence
even if you are about to collapse
Raping your womenfolk
is their birthright
"Here, I am on the run.
An extremist in the eyes of the law"
"Member of a banned party attempting
to galvanise a people..."
"subjugated for centuries"
Raise the Red Flag! It's a fight not
just for land, but for our dignity!
"It's really complicated.
Let me try and explain"
"One day the untouchables in
the village were up in arms"
"The landlord's son had raped
one of their girls"
All right, maybe my son
has made a mistake
So what are you going to do?
Kill him?
"They had all gathered outside the
landlord's house..."
"to chop off his balls"
"The feeling was overwhelming"
"To my naive mind it seemed
the revolution was at hand"
"Then suddenly, the cursed landlord
had a heart-attack"
Are you okay, saheb?
- My chest is hurting very badly...
What happened father?
- Shut up, you bastard
This is all your fault
"The lower-caste villagers who had been
screaming for his blood a minute ago..."
"were suddenly overcome by some
ancient dutiful urge to save him"
"After all, he and his family had been
their lords and masters for centuries"
"So, a jeep was despatched
to summon a doctor"
"Being lower-caste, the only doctor
they knew was also a lower-caste"
"So here's the problem"
"The landlord's son did not want a
lower-caste doctor touching his father"
"But the father who was dying,
didn't give a damn"
"At that moment, he'd have eaten
goat-shit if the doctor asked him to"
"This strange compassion of the
villagers towards their oppressor..."
"in his moment of need,
taught me something"
"What...?
I'm still trying to decipher"
"Please try to understand.
There's no place for you here"
"Our paths must necessarily
be different, Gita"
"I'll write again, if you do
- Sidharth"
New Delhi, 1973
I spoke to Daddy about your idea
about the hotel deal
He thinks it's a waste of time.
- It's not
Converting an old palace into
a hotel is a great idea.
So screw what Daddy thinks
It's the deal of the year
if I can clinch it
Oh, shit!
- What happened?
I just remembered... I've got a
meeting with these Bombay builders
And I've given my car for repairs
- That's okay. You can keep the Chevy
Dad's going off tomorrow
so the Mercedes is there
Shall we go to Shimla some day?
Just you and me
What happened?
Someone died?
Your girl ran away...?
What are you giving
cheques like that for?
Where is the money
going to come from?
We've already paid the prince
50,000 rupees...
to convince his dad about the deal.
But he's not calling!
We're doomed... we're finished!
You worry too much
Sometimes, there's nothing to do
but wait for the phone to ring
This phone has not rung
for the past two weeks
It'll ring, it'll ring
- Yeah? When?
It'll ring now...
Just count to three and
this phone will ring
One...
two...
three
If the mountain doesn't
come to Malhotra...
Malhotra goes to the mountain
Tell them I'm busy...
- Are you crazy?
Tell them I'm busy in a meeting!
Ask them to call later!
He's a little busy
Will tomorrow be good?
That's the place where
we dispensed justice
Flogging? With whips?
No, actually an elephant used to
crush their skulls
Much better system, don't you think?
- Why not? Makes it easier for vultures
This is not right
Vikram, when we make this hotel,
this damn thing has to go
Don't tell my father that...
we still have an elephant here
If he loses his temper,
there's no saying what he'll do
This is the harem
Seven hundred wives,
my great-grandfather had
My father studied in England
and dropped the custom... pity
So, what did the wives do when
the King was not with them...?
They did it with the palace staff...
anyone who got caught
had his balls cut off
So what did they do
with the balls?
Bloody hot, what?
Hello Dad, I've been
taking them around
This is Mr. Wadhwani...
- How do you do?
Dad, this is Vikram Malhotra.
He's...
What do you do, young man?
- I fix things, sir
Oh... a fixer...
- Fixer, dealer, broker, pimp
Depends on your point of view, sir
Cocky... good for you!
Go away... this is my home!
This is my house!
My younger son...
he's not quite... right.
But sir, if you take the price of
land itself at about 5 million...
The price of land is not
more than 3 million
30? What are you saying?
This is royal land, not some
servant's field or something
We're giving you a good deal
at 3, Maharaja
Nonsense! This land is priceless!
History lives in this place.
You're right, Maharaja. And we're
willing to pay for that history...
for your memories,
for your tradition...
but I'm afraid it's worth
30 million only
Enough! I have had enough!
Excuse me...
- Do something, please!
My father's final offer
is 35 million
Done!
Good God!
Dad, what happened to you?
That bloody idiot fired a potshot
at me from the roof! Stop him!
Who was it?
- Your brother, you fool!
Brother...!
Dhani Singh, go up there
and bring him down safely
Can you give me a job
in your hotel?
Welcome Vikram,
welcome Randhirbhai
Randhirbhai is too busy
for us these days
Vikram is the boy
I was telling you about
He got me the hotel contract.
Now we go for the big one!
The kid's got real talent!
- What talent?
His job is the most simple one
Everyone in this country
is totally corrupt
Not everyone, sir.
The trick is to know who is
That's where I come in
Come and see me sometime, Vikram
Where have you been?
You were supposed to pick me up!
I got stuck with these
political types...
I was telling them
how to run the country
Now can we dance?
- After you.
Howre you doing...?
- With fancy girls, Balbir!
What happened?
- I just remembered something...
Excuse me. Can I take this handsome
man away from you for just 5 minutes?
Get Anita out of here
You've found someone again?
I'm not doing it!
What do you take me for?
A bloody pimp?
Just do it, kiddo
Hey, Dumpy, son of a...!
Sorry, I thought you were
an old college friend
It's alright
Vikram Malhotra.
I say, Paddy Malhotra
from Doon School?
No, Vikram Malhotra from
Jabalpur Municipal School
I'm Arun Mehta, I.A.S.
Finance Ministry...
...junior in the ranks
but getting there
Someone was talking about you
Aren't you the chap who fixed
some deal for Wadhwani?
Jolly good, my man!
We need people like you...
people who can get things done.
Keep it up, my man...!
Gita, over here!
Hey, that's Gita Rao!
She was in college with me
My God!
You look like an upcoming tycoon!
Well, he is...
Haven't you heard?
This is the chap who got
Wadhwani his deal
Really...? That's wonderful!
And you look even more beautiful,
if such a thing were possible
Hello, what's this?
An old college romance?
Well, we all had a crush on
Gita in college
She didn't have good
taste in men those days
Oh well, all that has changed.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to get a drink.
Anyone...?
I was just going to ask
Gita for a dance.
Excellent!
Excuse me
Once upon a time, there was a young boy
who wrote many soulful letters
Once upon a time, there was a girl
who was very lost
Between university in England
and a year in Nairobi...
she didn't know how to
respond to those letters
So what did the young boy do
in the meantime?
Oh, he pined and he drank,
and he yearned and he drank.
In the meantime, he decided to make
pots of money anyway he could
I'm sorry
So, where did the lost soul
meet her Prince Charming?
England
He had everything a girl
could possibly want
Oh, come on, we're having
such a good time
I think we should leave
But can we go to the
Narain's party for a bit?
Sir, I take your leave.
It was lovely meeting you
Nice to meet you too
I'll just say bye to Mrs Wadhwani
I'll see you later.
- Come, I'll drop you
Have you been in touch
with Sidharth?
Bye Vikram. See you later
Hello...?
No, Madam Gita's just left
No, she's not coming in tomorrow,
she's going to Bhojpur
Yes, she'll be staying at
the forest rest-house, I think
Who should I say called?
Got word from the District Magistrate
sahab that you'd be coming
We've been waiting for ages
If you want anything,
you'd better tell me now
As it is, the sahab
gives us so much work
I shouldn't be doing this
I shouldn't be doing this.
Sidharth... Arun loves me
This is wrong
That's the problem with poverty!
This road is too long
I don't know how long
my struggle will last...
But I'm not running away like Rajan
What are you looking at?
I was thinking...
- What?
You frown too much
Coming
What's this?
I didn't order this.
Just as well,
'coz it's not on the menu
So the lost soul continued her search
in the heartland of India...?
Sidharth, no...!
It's Vikram!
Are you going to say it...
am I?
What the hell are you doing here?
I heard she was here.
I thought I'd stop by
Well, thank you very much.
Now get lost
I'm hurt!
After so many years,
such animosity?
Listen, I'm not going to tattle
I understand. You guys meet,
old passions ignite and...
Let's get together
and have a drink
To pee under the open sky!
If there is bliss...
it is this!
None but this!
I've always wondered...
whether this chap was
a clown or an asshole
Now I know. He's both
You know something, Sidharth?
You should work on this place
Make it into a home
for retired people
Small cottages, small farmhouses...
You do it, Vikram. I have slightly
different ideas about this place
What?
That all the peasants will rise up
in revolt some day...
and there will be peace
and prosperity in the world
It's a load of shit!
I'd like to kill him...
maybe I'll just leave
So leave!
Who the hell are you anyway?
Bloody coward!
Privileged man's son playing
games with the poor!
Sidharth, wait. I'm coming
Sidharth, I'm sorry.
I got carried away
I'll shut up.
I'm sorry, I say
You guys know me. Come on now.
Forget it... come
Forget it
To the revolution!
Had too much to drink
last night, sahab?
Is Madam still sleeping?
She left early. With some asshole
Tell me something, what's the
price of land in these parts?
Welcome to India
"Your man is away in Calcutta,
O fair maiden"
I have to go really far.
I'll call you
What happened?
The landlord's men have lynched
and hung four lower-caste men
They weren't letting me
into the cinema hall
I wanted to know which jerk
could stop me
The cinema was goddamned full.
I asked for the bloody manager
I said, "recognise me?"
And he shat
One scene was worth the effort
Lighting...!
Rain...!
A girl... What legs!
Her navel... totally exposed!
She squealed "where are you"?
The bastard's telling them
about a movie
The villain jumped on her
and tore her sari
I thought... what a shit film!
But then suddenly,
the real hero appeared
He said, "Hail Mother Goddess"
and charged at the villains
Stop farting around and tell us
how many people can we mobilise
Now how many are there
from the cobbler caste?
There are many
People are really charged up.
We just need some more arms
I'm not in favour of this, comrade
Do you think these people are ready?
Can they stand up against the police
and state machinery?
They'll all be butchered, comrade.
And we'll be responsible
Fed up of the movement?
- I'm not talking about running away
I haven't come here for this
I'm talking of a different strategy...
of expanding our mass base
We broke away from Somu Chatterjee's
group for precisely these reasons
Have you forgotten?
We must prepare the villagers first
Till that happens, will the police
sing hymns in their praise?
I'm not against specific actions
for self-defense
But I can't knowingly lead them
towards their death
I'm sorry comrade...
it takes time to bring about
a revolution
And I can give that kind of time
The question is whether you can
This can't be just our
decision, Sidharth
"Dear Gita..."
"I will not be able to meet you
next month"
"We have to shift base to somewhere
close to the Nepal border"
"I'll tell you the details later,
but at the moment..."
"things are extremely tense here"
"Scores of our comrades have died
and our organised is split"
"Probir-da and some others have
accepted my point of view"
"We have to rebuild
our organisation"
"Till we meet again...
Sidharth"
I'm D.K. Manchanda
And you?
I'm a first class gazetted officer
with a bank
Are you married?
- I'm expecting
So friend, all well?
Shall we call your wife?
What did I do?
I'm just reading the paper
So, you finally need
me for something?
Yes, I need to make use of
your agile mind
Let me guess. Something financial?
No... wrong
It's just... silly
What are you doing, Vikram?
- You're not saying anything, Gita!
I'm leaving Arun.
It's just not working out
And it was all a big mistake
C'mon...
- No
Arun, please... no!
Okay, what is it?
Is it my drinking?
Because if it is, I can stop.
I want to stop...
seriously, I can stop...
Listen, please
You don't like my friends,
I know that
I shouldn't have brought
home those bores
Please stop torturing yourself.
It's not about you
Gita, it's not fair...
you can't do this...
There is nothing wrong
with our marriage
You can't just walk
out of a marriage
Who is it?
Who are you screwing with?
Here, householder
From now on, this piece
of shit belongs to you
So here's where the sparrows shit
You can tie your buffaloes here
I don't want to hurt Arun
You bastard!
You're screwing my wife!
I could... I could... kill you!
I don't know if this is
going to comfort you
but Gita is not sleeping
with me
Unfortunately
Vikram! How are you?
Gita, look who's here...
Mr. Fixit himself
Hi, want some coffee?
Guess what?
Arun paid me a visit
He asked me if I loved his wife...
I said yes
Thanks, Vikram. I was just beginning
to get horribly sentimental!
So, Vikram, wine bottles
instead of commissions?
With commissions.
- Lucky. Smoke?
Gita, you haven't unpacked yet?
- Actually, I'm not staying
I've just been thinking about it
for some time
I think I'm going to leave
Vikram, imagine, actually going
in a village and living there
To a village near a
forest rest-house...
Look Vikram, if I don't go now,
I never will
I know you went through so much
trouble to get me all this...
I'm really sorry
Well, life goes on folks...
I'm getting married!
What?
- I'm getting married!
"Dear Vikram..."
"Once upon a time, there was
a girl called Gita. Remember her?"
"She was arrogant, opinionated and
thought she could change the world"
"And so she came here to Bhojpur.
And then... what happened?"
"I don't know. It's too
difficult to describe"
"Guess what?"
"I've started an adult literacy class
for tribal women here with Darryl"
"Remember him,
my editor friend?"
"Sidharth says our set-up is
a bourgeois feel-good scheme"
"This naturally forms the basis for most
of the unnecessary tensions in my life"
I haven't seen my husband for months
One of these days, the villagers
will betray the Naxalites
Then we'll be there
to perform the last rites
What's happening there?
"Our school is serving as a hospital
because of the malaria epidemic"
"14 people have died so far"
"It looks like the worst is over,
but then again..."
"you can't be sure
of anything here"
"You know something Vikram? Nobody
gives a damn about this place"
"It's as if it doesn't exist"
"Still people here laugh sometimes"
"Now enough of my rural trivia"
"The major news is that our son
Chetan was born last week"
"By the way, it was
very generous of you..."
"to offer that we name the boy after
you, but Sidharth wasn't too keen!"
"Well, what about you and Anita?
You better have a large family"
"So you can do justice to the
wealth and fame you've amassed"
"Drop by my father's
house sometime"
"We've sent them a
photograph of Chetan"
"It'll be worth the effort for you"
"He looks just like me - ha ha!
I have to go now"
"Be good and write to me"
"Love, Gita"
Go and see what's happening
When I shove it up your ass,
you'll stop coughing
You think because you keep
changing your names all the time...
we don't know who you are?
You're the one who's
instigating the villagers
Troublemaker!
Get the hell out!
Else, I'll shove some
saw-dust up your ass!
So, madam?
There's no basis for the arrest
of these men
They are simple labourers!
They're not as simple as they look!
These vermin killed a police officer
near the rail track last night
That's ridiculous,
there's no evidence to support that!
So you're going to teach me
about evidence?
You know how serious an offence
killing a police officer is?
Gita, the officer they've accused
the villagers of killing is outside!
Bastard, always lying drunk
at that whore's place!
The bastard keeps getting suspended,
but it still has no effect
I'll get you transferred this time!
Laxman, take him to the quarters.
You beat up and tortured
an entire village for nothing!
Don't show off your English!
Someone was killed, wasn't he?
It could've been anybody!
It could've been a guard
who fell off a train!
It could've been anybody!
They're blind!
Blood-thirsty beasts, all of them!
Who do you think you are?
God?
Are you sure they
are influential in the government?
Go right in.
They're waiting for you
We can't be sure of anything
Mr. Taneja
I don't want any trouble
There will no trouble
Why are you scared?
You're doing it for the
interests of the nation
We'll get him a medal for this
I came because Mr. Malhotra said
Relax, Mr. Taneja
But an overdraft is illegal
- What illegal?
It's just a question of a couple
of months. No one will get to know
As long as we're there,
it'll be okay
That's all right, but...
- But...?
Suppose you're not here anymore?
I could be in...
Not here? Do we look like the kind
of people who won't be here?
I'll call you
Vikram is a good boy,
not like those other bloody rats...
deserting a sinking ship
Is the ship sinking?
Well, that's what they say
That's what they think.
By the way, one of the biggest rats...
is your friend Randhir Singh
Just in case you ever
thought of denying it
He's an old family friend.
- Sure
Besides, I don't agree with him
In the land of Mahatma Gandhi,
in the land of Subhash Chandra Bose...
it's Hitler who rules
Friends, don't be blind agents
for that dynastic party
Wake up!
Down with corruption!
Long live Randhir Singh!
I wouldn't have missed this
for the world!
Stop screwing around with me
Aren't your new colleagues the ones
you were abusing yesterday?
Oh yes. Times change. People change
So you won't be needing
this cheque anymore?
Kiddo, the wheels of progress and
revolution need to be greased
So when the revolution arrives...
remember, we too were revolutionaries
That's the problem. You businessmen
think of only your own interests
And we have to think of
the entire country...
we have to awaken people's...
what do you call it... conscience!
What would your kind
know about socialism?
Sure, so now Hindu Fundamentalists,
Muslim Fundamentalists...
Capitalists, Socialists and
Communists will all work together
It's possible. Why not?
Yes, and a true Congressman
like your father. See
Forget it, father...
You know it's Pablo's birthday
Why screw it up for him?
Then why do you talk about things
you don't understand?
Who are your friends to talk about
all this? And who the hell is Sadiq?
I just know him. Since they run things
in the party now, they want change...
What do you mean?
Change doesn't mean that you will
appoint goons...
as office-bearers of
the Congress Party
If you must, appoint those
who have worked among the people...
and we willingly step aside.
- Okay, I'll talk to them
You'll talk to them...?
So you will now talk
on my behalf?
Hey guys, listen to this.
It's finally happened
"It has now been confirmed, that
a state of National Emergency...
has been declared in India"
"In a midnight swoop, all the top
opposition leaders have been arrested"
"This includes the Gandhian leader..."
"who spearheaded the anti-corruption
movement against the congress Party..."
"and its supreme leader
Mrs. Indira Gandhi"
"This follows the Allahabad High Court
judgement against Mrs. Gandhi..."
"which indicted her
on corruption charges"
"Calling the opposition agitation as a
conspiracy to destabilise the nation..."
"the Congress Party spokesman said it
was necessary to save the country..."
"from total chaos and anarchy. He also
labelled the opposition call..."
"to the country's armed and
civil forces an act of treason..."
You're trying to tell me my father's
a threat to national security?
What nonsense!
Just get the hell out!
Perhaps, you haven't heard the news.
Send him outside
Else, we'll have to use force.
I'm waiting outside
Father...!
Give me my diary
Let me talk to Sadiq
and put an end to this nonsense
No photographs!
Confiscate his bloody camera
Get the hell out of here!
Where the hell is everybody?
Can't get through...
The bastards have kept
their phones off the hook!
You don't know what you're doing!
You're making a big mistake
You're arresting a man who never
bothered about his own interests
He has worked all his life for
the good of the country!
If you want to arrest someone,
I'll tell you whom to arrest
Govt. Sterilisation Camp, Bhojpur.
Bihar 1975
What petition has she brought
this time?
She claims we're using unhygienic
equipment to sterilize the men
Things are getting
really dangerous, Gita
Run"! It's the police!
- Someone has surely tattled!
The police are out there
Now look, this is too much!
- If you go out, you'll be killed.
Listen up!
You better give up
your urban comrades.
I've warned you before no
Naxalite activity in my area!
You've seen for yourself...
the dirty politics of getting
involved in naxalite politics
He lost his life overnight
But you still didn't see sense
Your crops were ready
to be harvested
You could have had
your daughters married.
I wanted everything to
go off peacefully too
But you guys have made
life difficult for me.
What do you want me to do...?
Beg you with folded hands?
This is a habit you can't
give up easily!
Once something goes wrong...
Just some old crazy women...
Listen kiddo, those bastards came to
my house with a warrant yesterday...
- Don't worry...
- What do you mean, don't worry?
If they arrest me...
You don't know them...
Listen... do something... tell them
I'm from the same caste...
from the same village...
my grandfather's uncles
are the Home Minister's third cousins...
you talk to him, he'll help me...
What happened to your conscience?
To hell with conscience!
Is this any time for jokes?
Why is that cop staring at me?
He's not...
He's just here to pray that
he gets transferred...
to the Connaught Place
police station.
Never mind. If they agree to
take me back into the party...
Listen, I'm not coming empty-handed
I have my entire constituency.
Otherwise, I'll tell them about
the funds you gave our party...
Tell them.
Help me... you must...
for old times' sake...
I'm like your brother...
I was your father's student...
Don't talk about him.
He's is jail.
But unlike you,
he's not shitting in his pants.
He doesn't wish to see anyone.
He has a slight fever.
He's grown taller,
have you noticed?
I messed up your life, didn't I?
I'm sorry, Gita. I...
You could've left me.
Sidharth...
it's not only about you.
I want to be here.
I love you.
Time to go.
Say bye to Chetan.
I've arranged for him
to go back.
Try and understand.
It's just not fair to keep
Chetan here anymore.
I've spoken to my parents, they're
coming to pick him up now.
Hello... Mr. Tyebji. This is
Vikram Malhotra speaking.
I was in college with
Sidharth and Gita.
How are you sir...?
I hadn't heard from them
for a long time, so I thought...
If you could tell them
that I'd called... Goodbye.
Friends, I have this great
urge to express...
my feelings in a couplet...
I, Jhanda Singh,
Senior Inspector In-Charge,
Badhaiya police outpost,
on the day of 7th July,
1975, at 12 noon,
All of us had gone to enquire
after a fellow officer
who had diarrohea.
Taking advantage
of our absence,
the local populace attacked
the extremist Naxalities...
who were in custody at that time.
Probir Mitra and Sidharth were
badly beaten up by villagers.
Also, Gita Rao who has been carrying on
subversive activities in the name of...
running a school also had to
bear the brunt of the villages' outrage.
Fortunately, we arrived
just in time
and prevented the matter
from getting out of hand.
Station-in-charge Badhaiya.
Jhanda Singh.
Sorry, Mehmood.
Please be sited.
As you know,
we're expecting Madam soon...
Grandpa, Fluffy's
run away again...
Oh dear, just a minute,
I'll have him found for you
Hey... is somebody there?
Rashid... come here
You know, my son...
the over-zealousness of youth...
I tried to stop him
so many times.
Now, I believe
he's been arrested.
Where's he now?
Don't know, in some village in Bihar.
Please do something...!
Just 5 minutes,
we'll handle it...
I'll try my best... We don't
control things anymore...
A younger lot has taken over...
They say it's for the better...
All these problems are arising
because...
nowadays, I'm handling
trade unions.
But don't lose hope
Hello, sir.
Remember me?
I was in college with Sidharth...
Are you okay, sir.
- How are you?
- I'm fine, sir.
Have you heard from
Sidharth or Gita?
They've in jail...
somewhere in Bihar...
I want Gita Rao found.
How ought be every leader?
- Like Indira Gandhi
Sorry sir, but we got information
from our local intelligence...
Here she is, sir.
Come.
Vikram told me where you were.
Leave me...!
- It's okay.
It's okay, Gita, but I may not
be there the next time.
Look at me!
Do you know what they could
have done to you in there?
You have any idea.
Oh, you poor thing!
Arun, will you do something for me?
- What?
Find Sidharth for me... please!
Did you know I'm Married now?
I have a kid.
It's lovely.
But you haven't charged a bit.
New Delhi, 1976
I thought you wouldn't come...
What's up?
I just wanted to thank you...
that's all
Give me another...
Howre you?
I'm alright... I'm okay.
You?
Me? Well,
acquiring wealth and power
at an alarming rate!
Yes, that figures.
So... where's Sidharth?
I don't know...
I'm okay
Come on!
Hurry up!
Gita there is bad news for you.
Sidharth and Kiru were shot at.
Kiru survived... but...
Those bastards...
Call me, if you need something...
Stay... please...
"Vikram, as usual,
thanks for everything"
"I thought about it, but
I'm going back to the village"
"It's for the best.
I will write to you"
"Gita"
What are you guys upto...?
Hey you, stop that! Playing with
the gun will explode in your ass!
Is there a holiday? Some kid is
fiddling with my gun...
and you're sitting pretty here.
Could you please there are patients...
- What please, go, do your work.
So much tension...
The wound is dry now.
You were fortunate that those
cops brought you here.
But these ones are different.
They were talking of finishing you
off on the way to the police station.
Who are you?
Save yourself, Comrade.
Bullet?
Soldier?
Don't want to tell...
I'm on my way... Soon I hope...
Please comrade... call Delhi for me...
my father... the number is 273857...
Tell him he has to get me out of here...
Tell him they're going to kill me...
and give him the district magistrate's
number as well.
- Hello, is Gita there?
- No.
Oh no, sir!
- Who is calling?
I have a message.
Please inform her somehow.
Someone just called from
a hospital in Bhojpur.
They said the police is going
to kill Sidharth sahab.
What do you mean...?
Is Sidharth alive?
I'm just a servant sir.
Sidharth saheb's father has had
a stroke. They're all at the hospital.
I don't know what to do.
Well, neither do I.
Gita's already left, son.
Please do something...
You have so many contacts...
You only can do something.
Just half an hour for the presentation.
What are you doing? Hurry up!
Hello, yes Randhir...
find out the Member of Parliament
from Bhojpur, Bihar is...
What are you doing? I don't want
to be treated here...
get me a taxi, bike...
whatever you have.
Look how dirty this is...
I'm going to catch some disease
if you keep me here for another minute.
I want to make a call...
take me to a phone...
Sorry, the phones have
just gone dead...
What do you want? Money?
Here, take as much as you want...
Please Vikram, don't go...
You shut up! Jerk,,
this is all thanks to you!
First, I get the news that you're dead.
Then, you're alive.
What was I supposed to do?
Have you checked for
the air bubbles...?
We'll nave to keep you
under observation.
Tomorrow, doctors from the
Bhojpur Hospital will come.
Then it's between you and them.
I understand why you're
angry with me, but...
Look at me, man.
I'm in deep shit.
Don't bloody well faint on me again!
Hunh...
We've come to pick you up.
We're all here, no problem now.
How about the cop?
- One's drunk
One moment, there's Vikram.
Let's move, he's not in danger.
Eh... get up!
Shit! I took a nap for just
two minutes... goddamned hell!
Who asked you to drink...?
- You needn't say that to me!
Look they took away the whole bed.
And nobody is saying anything.
He was talking to this jerk!
I've got little kids. There won't be any
complaint against me, I hope...?
You'll be sterilized!
- But I'm a government employee!
To hell with you!
Go and ask him where he is...
Hey, tell me, you bastard...!
They carried him away
And this guy was lying here,
sozzled to his eyes
Save my skin, please!
I think they must've been
partners or something.
Move it... c'mon!
- Let me go!
Let me go! Leave me alone!
Where are you taking me...?
The other guy's escaped!
But his friend is here.
We'll just shoot him and
throw some acid on his face,
no one will recognise the face...
they don't walk around checking.
What are you doing?
Come on, go ahead, shoot...!
I'm Vikram Malhotra...
I know your Member of Parliament
Surender Singh, he is my friend...
I'm not Sidharth
that insurgent...!
Go on, just shoot...
It's empty...
- Where are the bullets?
Shit, my kids must have
taken them to play with...
Hit him harder... We'll have
to finish him off like this...
Stop!
What's happening here?
Not my mistake.
This guy asked me to bump him off
He was escaping from custody, sir
I can't fool myself any longer.
I just can't do this.
They would have killed you...
- They should have.
I mean it, they should have.
Will you come with me Gita?
"Dear Gita..."
"what can I say?"
"Sorry"
"Our parting, I guess,
was inevitable"
"Maybe, even necessary"
"You have to, I suppose..."
"get over your first love,
in order to be free"
"Thank you for sending Chetan
to London with my father"
"It was inexplicable, the feeling
of seeing him after all these years"
"The last time I saw you
at your father's house..."
"I was too wrought up inside"
"The world hadn't changed in the ways
that I wanted it to"
"I know that you're right,
it has"
"That no one can rape a lower-caste
in those parts that easily anymore"
"He might get a certain
body part chopped off"
"And I know that's a leap of
about five thousand years"
"But still..."
"Anyway, Probir-da is still there"
"And... you"
"By the way, please give him
the book I am sending you"
"And tell him that I'll
write to him soon"
"As for me, you know
I'm studying medicine now"
"I'm the oldest student
in my class"
"Maybe the mysteries of the human body
will be less confusing"
"And someday, I will return...
maybe"
"Gita, I often think of Vikram"
"Pablo told me that his wife had put
him in some specialised institution"
"But when Pablo went to see him,
the authorities told him..."
"there's no one by that name"
"I smiled when I heard that"
"I think I know where he is"