# Subtitles by  $ ShabbaMechstar $
There's a thin line
separating a fool from a moron...
...on one end of the line lies the fool
and on the other, the moron.
Snap the line
and you don't know who's who?
Thats the million dollar question,
my pretty polly.
Let us to see who the pretty groom is?
I'll be damned!
Is it not Mr. Fool himself?!
Ya ya!
To become a true moron
you've to at least be married...
and by the look of things,
you're not getting married in a hurry.
Ya ya!
Yes Sir! There's been
a change in the schedule.
The half-caste's abducting
your bride even as we chat.
Brother Omi?!
Ya ya!
"Hail Friendship"!
As a friend, it was my duty to warn you.
Grab that moped and run like the wind.
If you've got what it takes,
go save Dolly.
Now scurry!
Your wedding march past is over!
Ya ya!
Aren't you a charming one?
Ya! Right... Liar.
If I lie,
then I make love to a filthy bitch
and if not,
then that bitch is your mother!
Your wedding march is history!
The marriage party's stopping here!
Grab the phones darling!
What the hell could've held them up?!
Can't even get through the bloody phones!
Omi Shukla has abducted Dolly!
Wait! Not the red one, hit the green.
- Screw you!
- Now what?
Come on Langda...
be a sport!
What happened, big brother?
Forgot your tools at home or what!
Your mother's borrowed them... swine!
Stop screwing around now.
I'm sick of your bloody red, blue, yellow!
Decide your colour once and for all...
then sit back and watch daddy play!
Not bad, champ! Go flick the yellow one.
Ringa Ringa Roses!
Pocket full of poses!
Bingo! Go stuff yourself... loser.
When it comes to marbles,
No one screws with Langda Tyagi...
Anyone got the guts to doubt that?
Where is Omi?
Where the hell is he?
You Anglo shit!
Even dogs show more character... Omi!
Was my daughter
the only girl left in the province?
Actually, it's my fault...
had forgotten that you are
a half caste.
That bloody slave girl
had borne you... right?
Bloody bastard!
You're right as always sir...
Wish you knew that your own daughter's
heart beats for this half caste.
Bastard!
Bhaisaab's calling... May I?
Regards Bhaisaab, that's right...
They here... both of them.
Lawyer sir?
He's threatening to blow
Brother Omi's brains out.
One shot and... finito!
Ya Bhaisaab... One sec!
So, what's going on over there?!
Lawyer sir?
Omi?
This silence is getting boring friends.
Someone's got to speak up.
Big brother, this sonuvabitch abducted
my daughter on her wedding day.
So I heard. Now let me update you...
Your prime eyewitness Jalaluddin
has returned from Muscat!
The case is slated
to be heard next week...
So do postpone your shootout
for tonight...
Or meet him up in Court next week.
That will be all dears.
Have a good day.
The news is confirmed Bhaisaab...
Indore Singh had gone to Muscat himself.
And now Surendra Captain
has become his General.
They are hiding him
behind the brick kiln in Pilakhwa.
Why in the world is Indore Singh
rushing to his grave?
Whenever a bitch goes down to pee,
every dog thinks its his lucky day.
All Visitors are warned
that anybody carrying any kind of...
alcohol, cigarettes, narcotics etc
will be found punishable by law.
Any kind of weapon, matchboxes or
mobile sim cards is also prohibited,
strict action will be taken against...
Psst... I happen to be carrying
all of the above.
What are you gonna do?
- Liar!
Get lost sonuvabitch... stamp this!
Have known Omkara
since his childhood...
but never heard anything
about him being a womanizer.
You've even known Dolly
since she was a toddler.
You think she would've eloped
with this gangster willingly.
Our home fire's
been hushed since yesterday...
the whole community's slandering us...
how can you expect me to hand over
my precious jewel to that monster?!
He's a damned half caste at that!
I have no more will to live...
I need justice, Bhaisaab!
Brother Omi! Please come.
If I've done this out of lust.
Call me a eunuch.
If his daughter says I'm a liar,
Omkara will cut his tongue off...
and shine Lawyer sir's shoes with it
for the rest of his life!
Don't be scared... speak your mind.
Has anyone... and I mean anyone,
forced you into any kind of submission?
I've always followed the tune of my heart.
Papa... please forgive me.
I can't live without Omkara.
"Don't trust what your eyes say.
Your eyes will betray you."
God knows how it all began...
how I lost my heart to Omkara.
I was in love... but it was too late.
I remember feeling like a blind bird
plunging down an empty well...
everything seemed hopeless...
And then I decided
I'll end my wretched life...
But then there was no point to it,
When who I was dying for
didn't even know why.
Rajju will marry me dead.
Since you won't in this lifetime,
let me confess...
I'm yours and yours only.
Put me down in your list of slain.
Let bygones be bygones.
Both of you should now
seek blessings from the elders.
Now don't you dare get married
before I'm released.
See, I'm not averse
to this prison life.
But if that blasted evidence
reaches court...
the Parliament will annul
my election nomination.
And what if they don't see reason?
Well then... go ahead.
General... may you never forget
the two faced monster a woman can be!
She who can dupe her own father,
will never be anyone's to claim.
Fill in whatever amount you want.
Bloody hell! Got away!
Kichlu... me thinks we're not cut out
for these over the table deals.
Don't rush to your grave Captain.
Quote your price.
The Parliament seat.
The one Indore sir's been slogging
his ass off for the last five years.
Even if he polishes it
for the next five lives,
he won't be able to defeat Bhaisaab.
Truth be said...
but only if Tewari Bhaisaab
contests in the first place.
It was a small nick...
but its gonna bleed as hell.
Got it?
Omi... Come break bread with us.
Have got special homemade food.
Holy cow!
Bloody hell!
How many will you smash, Captain?
Our guys are stationed
outside all TV channels.
Don't miss the climax.
Sorry Captain sir! But you should
teach Brother Indore a thing or two.
Bastard's not even wearing a condom.
Who is this chick by the way?
Indore bro...
...pray which meeting
did you attend last night?
Hmm... the fund raising one
or the skirt raising one?
Now watch the parliament on the bloody TV
for the rest of your life.
Omi brother... hats off to you.
I concede. You are the biggest General
in the province.
'Even your pee
can flush out all your foes'
But before leaving,
I have a poser for you...
Kichlu and I have had a bet...
for 100 bucks.
This one says that you'll marry
Raghunath's lass for sure...
and I feel that Omi's
still got his wits about him...
he just wants to wham bang her... right?
I win that 100 bucks, sonuvabitch.
Grandma! Go tell the village
that Captain's lost his bet.
Take your 100 bucks from Captain.
Let go, Omi!
Next time round, bet on horses...
not tigers.
"The drums salute the greatest..."
"the greatest warrior
of them all... Omkara!"
The battle is over
The tables are turned
The righteous is out of prison
And the enemy is burnt
As per the high Command's wishes...
...I will be contesting
for a parliament seat this year.
I hereby appoint
youth leader Omkara Shukla...
...as my successor in the local assembly
And Bhaisaab, who will replace Omkara?
Who will be the new General of the party?
Hello?
Can't hear a word... Hello?
Bhaisaab?
- What was the question?
Think its disconnected!
Brother Langda! Brother Langda!
Where are your glorious feet?
They walked off
to buy some slippers... Moron!
Let me kiss them once.
Please just once!
Don't hold me back!
- Buzz off! You scum!
My my! The new General is a tyrant!
What?!
Hail General Langda!
Kesu Firangi!
All the college students
are under his command.
The elections will be
a cakewalk for us.
And Langda?
He's like a brother.
He'll understand.
Hail Kesu Firangi!
Run Golu! They're here!
Move out of the way!
Not bad at all!
May you be protected from all evil...
Talk about a match made in heaven...
like milk in a pot of coal.
Sorry Omi bro! My tongue slipped...
More like a candy in a crow's mouth!
OK OK! I give up!
Like sandal shining
in the darkest night!
Please brother!
I promise... no more jokes!
Please let me go.
Like a magic flute
in the hands of the Dark lord.
What're you staring at, Grandma?
- Staring at your luck!
How in the world did you get such a
fair girl in these parts?!
I said good morning!
Bro... Rajju's come to visit.
Let them in... but grab their weapons.
Righto.
Get going.
You wait.
When will the priest be here, sis?
My high priestess,
this is an inauspicious month.
Our bride-to-be
will have to be more patient.
Not bad at all! That smells good!
You turned out to be quite some cook...
what's the secret?
My grandma's formula...
She told me that the way
to a man's heart is through his belly.
What bull! My Grandma
always told to me to aim a bit lower.
Papa's sent this little gesture
for the elections.
But that's a long way off...
Ya ya! It's me who's
stayed away too long!
Brother Omi! I had nothing to do
with that marriage fiasco.
If I'd had any inkling,
I'd have peed over the holy fires myself.
I'll take your leave then.
Wait! It'll be dark
by the time you reach.
Stay back. We're celebrating
Golu's birthday tomorrow.
Golu's happy birthday!
How many years old
will the little man be?
Er... Golu?
Must be eight... or is it nine?
O...! Listen!
Just taste this once...
Sweet enough?
Just twirl your finger once more
in the pan, it'll be perfect.
My Romeo! Mix some water
in your booze at least.
Here... have a swig.
My dear friend...
I gave you one chance...
But alas... you don't have the guts...
I do dammit...!
That blasted moped got a puncture that day,
else I would have shown you guys.
I can lay down my life
for Dolly... understood?
That'll be the day!
Stop drinking now...
I'm serious... I can
give up my life for her!
Give the bottle first!
I'm not joking... really!
I'll jump into the river!
- Ya ya!
I'll really jump!
No one's holding you back... sissy!
Go jump!
'Dolly' my ass!
Jump... chicken shit!
Bloody hell! You don't know how to swim?!
What the...!
What do you have to say now... brother!
It's not a question of guts...
Its a question of business...
if I run amok, my father's
booze contracts will be snatched.
And you, Brother sir Langda?!
Who are you to talk about nerve?
What guts did you display when Omi
publicly chose Kesu as his successor?
For the last 15 years,
you've been faithfully serving
that half caste on a leg and a half...
Hail Langda General!
Hail General Langda!
That pretender Kesu
comes out of nowhere...
and coolly snatches the
bone out of your mouth.
Where did your guts go walking then?!
Company garden?
You know Rajju,
you are finally making some sense.
Both of us are damned
to lead donkey's lives!
God bless your filthy soul...!
Good lady!
Langda! Help me!
Help me please!
Think I've caught the chill.
The water was freezing.
Look at it this way...
now you know how to swim.
Now I'll teach you how to fly...
like pigeons in the sky.
Bye Bye baby bird...
fly away with Dolly.
Far far away!
To a galaxy someday.
Eh? Eh? Eh?
Buzz off... liar!
If I lie, then I make
love to a filthy bitch...
and if not,
then that bitch is your mother.
And isn't it Mr. Busybody himself?
Lower your eyes while
addressing the new General.
But of course...
my adorable bastard!
I'll slice your tongue out.
In your dreams!
Won't even let you lick it.
Hey Billo Chamanbahar...
You know why I love you Billo baby?
Why?
Cos' you're the biggest tease
in the world.
And you know why
I'm crazy about you?
Hmm?
Cos' you say this to every
third girl you meet... bloody lech!
You still haven't answered.
- What?
Will you marry me?
Let go... creep!
This house hadn't had an heir for years.
Then Pa fell in love and I was born.
My mother belonged to a lower caste...
that's why they call me a half caste.
A crescent, though half,
is still called a moon.
Ouch!
What happened?
My back caught a catch this morning.
What is our new General up to?
Seems to have vanished.
He's at his usual score...
composing duets inside.
General sir!
Grace us with some time please.
Do not forget your subjects
in such a hurry.
Perch your behind please.
What brother Langda?!
Not having any fun?
What should your honour be served with?
- No thanks. My tea's on its way.
Tea?! No hard stuff for our lord?
That's one thing I can't handle, bro.
Uh oh...!
Mental...
Run and get a bottle of milk
for our General here.
And make sure
its one of those nippled ones!
Here... put this on.
Whose jewel is this?
It's not a jewel...
its our family heirloom.
Its adorned the brides
of this house down the ages.
Keep it. It's yours from today.
Treasure it with care!
Put it on and show me first.
First shut your eyes.
Could we have
that 'beedi' number please?
There's a slight problem
with that request.
I've forgotten the words
to that song...
We'd love to be of help.
"No quilt in sight... this cold breeze
arouses the hell out of me."
"It's best to share somebody's quilt."
"Go borrow heat
from the next fellow's oven."
"Light your fags with the heat
of my bosom..."
"its burning up inside me!"
"Let smoke not slip out of your lips...
the world's smoked out already!"
"No crime's been charged...
why do I still feel sentenced to death?"
"Haul me to your court one afternoon."
"Handcuff me with my anklets."
"Haul me up in the afternoon"
"Sentence me... punish me severely."
"Light your stoves with the heat of
my bosom..."
"its burning up inside me!"
"No knife's sharp
enough to match your nibbles."
"The way you leave
your teeth marks behind..."
"farmers would forget
how to cut their crops"
"Please Billo... would you settle down
with a brute like this?"
"Nobody warned me...
nobody woke me up."
"Suddenly you come into my quilt..."
"trying to impress me
with your clove breath."
"Burn your coals with the heat of
my bosom..."
"its burning up inside me!"
"It's best to share somebody's quilt..."
"go borrow heat from
the next fellow's oven."
Bastard! I'd asked you not to smoke!
Let go man... you're piss drunk!
Brother Omi...
Is somebody going to bloody own up?
Who the hell started
this brawl? Langda?
Let it go Omi bro...
We'll sort it in the morning.
Don't rush to your grave...
answer the bloody question.
Whose fault was it?
It was booze.
Partly booze... partly my fault!
This poor child had warned me
that he can't hold his drink...
I fingered him and he got plastered.
I should be punished... not him!
General! Its neither booze...
nor Langda!
It's my fault... for having
chosen you as the General!
Stay out of my sight for a few days
else I'll skin you alive.
Don't worry.
Omi's anger is like camphor.
It'll vanish in no time... eat something.
Not bad!
I've been toiling away
at these chappatis...
and nobody cares a shit!
Why are you taking it out on the food?
Eat up now!
If your face stays bloated like this
the fat chappatis will start blushing.
Not bad at all!
That's a rare smile in this weather...
Don't worry... I'll speak to Brother Omi.
"I'll speak to Brother Omi"
And he'll listen to you?! Surely...!
Now Omi's not going to listen to anyone.
There's only one voice
of reason that can help...
Dolly's voice.
And if I'm not mistaken,
isn't she a bum chum of yours?
We're visiting Bhaisaab over the next
2-3 days... some election work.
By the time we're back,
get Dolly in the loop.
Cool?
It's cooler than the coolest!
Now... lets see those molars.
Have you ever fed me...
with half this love?
Bugger off!
Don't panic now! I'll be there soon.
Auntyji's worried about my safety.
The C.I. D says that I might be attacked.
She wants me to come to the capital
for 2-3 days... till it tides over.
2-3 days?!
In the meantime, we can start
fund raising by ourselves... right?
Sounds fine.
Then?
Pull the chain son.
Any problem Bhaisaab?
Reverse the train.
These gentlemen have to be dropped back.
Sorry?
You heard me!
Golu! When you feel like a glass of juice,
what do you do?
I massage Omi Uncle's head!
And Indu, when you want a new sparkler,
what do you do?
Heaven only knows!
Have to massage half a leg all night!
So your job will be done...
But it's not gonna be for free...
What say Kesu sir?!
Whatever her highness demands.
It's a deal then?
- Deal.
Now you sing.
Everything else's fine...
except its pronounced 'bottom'.
That's what I said-'bottom'.
Fine! Will do!
- What now?
Shit! Omi bro's back!
Langda said they'll be back in 2-3 days.
I'm screwed now!
Hang on!
Lets sort this once and for all.
No way! He'll skin me alive
and hang it out to dry!
Wasn't that Kesu?
Leave the poor boy alone now.
Why in the world would he come
to see Dolly in your absence?
But it did look like his bike.
Come on bro, Kesu's our own.
Why would he run
like a thief on seeing us?
He's in town.
I'll just make him speak to you.
Hello Mental!
Just pass the phone to Kesu.
I see?
Fine then... text me later.
What happened?
God knows! Sonuvabitch's not starting up.
Not the car... what about Kesu?
Kesu?!
There... its started!
Hey Langda! What's the big secret?
Can't believe that was Kesu...
What in the world could he be up to
with Dolly at this hour?
Dolly!
What was Kesu doing here?
And why did he take to his heels?
What now?
Speak up! What's so funny?
Every time I look into your eyes,
this single thought crosses my mind.
What thought?
You're either one hell of a fool...
or one hell of a witch.
"O my love..."
"let it last forever today!"
"Come lets still the day!"
"Lets chase the sun away!"
"Keep the shadows at bay... O my love!"
"O my love...
"Let me scold you whilst
you pretend to get scared..."
"let my love fall
in sweet tears from your eyes..."
"my body stitched to yours..."
"turn your back and
you will tear me to shreds..."
"I will take you away with me...
my body your soul"
"Where I end and you begin"
"O my love..."
"let it last forever today!
Now tell me... why am I a fool?
Cos' what's a gorgeous girl like you
doing with a brute like me?!
And witch?
Cos' at times I feel, deep down,
...your beauty's all evil and twisted.
"O my love... let it last forever today!"
"Never ever let me out of your sight!"
There's an animal caged inside you!
Ravenous!
Ravenous what...
Cheetah?
Wolf?
Serpent?
Chamaeleon?
Nope... You are my bunny rabbit!
What would you like for dinner?
I'd like to drink some blood.
"Wake up little princess!"
"Your eyes like sweet petals!"
"Eyes that hold me in their spell."
"May I never be away from their sight!
"The dawn blushes pink on your cheek"
"Craving to caress you...
come now wake up...
"Your sweet flesh beckons
Comes hither a bee to tickle you"
"Come now my darling wake up."
"Ask for your heart's desire,
I give my word in blood"
"Just for this once... open your eyes"
Here! I'm up.
Can I really ask for anything?!
Think again.
Forgive Kesu this one time.
What happened?
That's not possible!
- But why?!
If I let him off lightly,
he'll never learn in this lifetime.
So you'll be pissed
with him all your lifetime?
Next time please don't
make any false promises!
"I give my word in blood"
Fine. I'll forgive him
on the wedding day.
Do I call the priest then?
Meanie...?
According to the charts, the 3rd month
of our calendar is an auspicious time.
What date will that be?
- The 30th of next month.
Did you hear?!
The 30th of next month is...
...the auspicious date for the wedding...
which means Kesu gets your favor
in exactly 5 weeks!
Kesu gets his pardon in 5 weeks!
She seems happier with the forgiving
than with the wedding... isn't it?
Dolly really dotes on our Kesu.
They've known each other a long time?
- They both went to the same college.
No wonder!
No wonder what?!
Nothing nothing!
Me and my filthy mind... that's all.
Langda! Tell me what's on your mind!
No... its just that
Dolly's such a stunner...
and you know how Kesu is!
Bloody flirt!
Just wondering if he ever had
any designs on her?
On second thoughts,
what a silly idea!
Kesu is a sweet soul but
he strays around too much... bloody slut!
It won't be a bad idea brother if we keep
a close watch on Dolly till the wedding.
The world is full of big bad wolves
and our Dolly is too too naive!
Brother Kichlu!
Patience son...
We should lie low till the polls.
If we keep silent,
we'll be labelled cowards.
Indore Singh's days are numbered!
Fine... at least wait till
your wedding's past.
Wedding?!
Hmm... isn't there
a date for next month?
How did you get to know?
- I told him.
The way you people dashed off
the other day,
I got really worried.
I called for Kesu and
thankfully he got me here.
Good show!
First stop Kichlu,
then goes Indore Singh.
Langda... you hit town
and sniff out Kichlu.
Mental! Take Babulal's help and
get me Indore Singh's final itinerary.
Anything for Kesu, bro?
Somebody's got to hand out
the wedding invites!
Can't you see...!
I'm on the phone...
Your pain is your own...
for no one else to see...
The truth is no matter
how much I assure you,
I won't be able to understand
your suffering.
Wait a sec!
Bloody mother of...!
What a brainwave, Sir Langda!
Why don't you hunt down Kichlu
instead of me?!
Just drop him in Omi's lap.
Kichlu's gone underground, but if
you wish, you can get to him in a flash.
Ask how?
Ask how?!
- How?
That Billo Chamanbahar of yours...
She's the ace private dick of our trade.
Had bought it for Indu,
but you gift it to Billo.
But this looks very expensive, brother?
If it can help a friend,
its worth is priceless!
Brother Langda...
you are a true friend...
Come come... Don't be shy!
Kesu doesn't hold anything to heart,
likes giving it on the face.
Will you have a small one?
Moron! Forgotten that
day's thrashing or what?
But what do we do about the wedding cards?
- Rajju will hand them out.
Won't you, pretty polly?
And this won't be the first time
you'd be doing it... eh...!
The sun is going to rise
from the south tomorrow.
Why so?
First you took me to the multiplex...
bought me popcorn and lunch,
Then ice cream at the lake...
topped with a walk on the mall road.
Its time to call it a night
yet you're not dragging me to bed...
What's the big idea?
I'm tired Billo.
I've tired you out... no?
Nope... its my loneliness...
You haven't answered me yet.
What?
Will you marry me?
Are you nuts?!
All this marriage talk!
Remember the saying 'Horses without reins
don't get lassoed easily!'.
This is not a joke Billo...
I'm tired of all this straying.
It all seems futile.
Just want to settle down with you now.
Got something for ya...
Still don't quite get it...
Anyway, you've managed to impress me.
Swine!
My adorable swine!
At least now tell me
what your scheme is?!
"My tongue longs to taste the spice...
The spice of your love!"
"Lover I can never get enough...
"They all tease me...
this gang of rakish cops."
"They spoil me with their gifts...
the grocers on my street."
"Big spender... spend a penny on me."
"A sweet lick of honey from your fingers...
Grant me."
"Your spice leaves me gasping...
smoldering me to death."
"I spent the night craving...
The spice of your love!"
"My brute... your breath
tunes me up like a flute."
"Your passion can make me
do anything that you can imagine."
"At times they sip from your eyes...
Later they want to drink
from your lips."
"Sometimes it feels nice to die...
Sometimes its too painful to live."
"I toss and turn all night. Is that
my lover who tiptoes to my bedside?"
Your spice leaves me gasping...
smoldering me to death.
"My lover... let me have a bit
The spice of your love!"
Lets go, bro!
Lets go!
Take Billo and vanish
for a day or two!
We'll meet directly
at the village for the wedding.
2 am in the morning?
Ya man... middle of the bloody night!
Tring Tring... Tring Tring...
I immediately went for my gun...
but the 'General' promptly stops me!
Smiling wickedly,
he says "It must be Billo"
And lo and behold! The doors open.
Enters a fuming Billo Chamanbahar...
strung like Lord Rama's bow!
On seeing her temper, I immediately tucked
my head in and pretended to be asleep.
Somebody come and pump this.
But as my good luck would have it,
there was a hole in the quilt.
Now I'm human after all...
and a little perverted at that.
It was a cold winter night!
Kesu starts getting all horny
but Billo doesn't even let him peck her!
Kesu then takes out this glittering
jewel from the box...
this sparkling gorgeous waistband!
Glittering gold jewels!
Never seen anything so beautiful!
No way?
- Yeah...!
The way the waistband glowed in the dark,
you'd never need a lamp again in your life!
Then?
- What do you think then?!
The waistband was all
she was left wearing!
Both sang nonstop duets till the morning!
Creak! Creak!
Forgive Kesu!
I called for Kesu and
thankfully he got me here.
Kesu gets his pardon in 5 weeks!
What took you so long?
I had been waiting for you...
Why weren't you taking my calls?
It was on silent mode... sorry...
Want some dinner?
- No!
I'll go get some water.
What happened?
Where is the waistband?
Sorry?
The waistband!
Oh... must be lying around here...
Here or elsewhere?!
Must be in the house somewhere.
Fine. Go put it on.
Don't be naughty now!
Wait till the wedding.
I asked you to go put it on!
And I... asked you to wait
till the wedding!
Now... means now... dammit!
Haven't you kept the token
of my love real carefully?!
Maybe the chest gobbled
it up or was it the famished almirah?
A generations old heirloom, and it
takes you precisely three days to lose it!
Sure you haven't gifted it away?
Who in the world
will I gift it to... Omkara?
Who do I have besides you anyway?
Have left my whole world to be with you!
"The wood burns into charred coal...
"My heart burns into emptiness."
"Don't burn my heart away...
"Don't pawn my heart away."
Now what?!
The sun's also started getting up late!
Not bad! Looks like someone
didn't get any rest all night!
Save up some of that passion
for your wedding night, my princess!
What happened now?!
Speak up!
If you keep crying like this,
you'll flood the whole village!
Oh! Missing your papa... are you?
Sober up now dodo!
I'll take care of you.
I'll be your pa, ma, bro, sis...
everything rolled into one...
now stop crying!
What's this now?!
Did you fall somewhere?
Did Omi hit...?!
You just wait here!
That sonuvabitch...!
Hit me out of love...
I'll tell you a little secret.
My grandma always told me to keep
these men slightly hungry.
Else the day they get satisfied, they'll
puke you out like nobody's business!
Got that!
Now... that's a rare smile in this weather!
About time! Forever thirsty... this guy!
It's Babulal!
Where's he going running off to now?
It's inauspicious to leave
in the middle of the ceremony son...
It burns me up!
Ooh! Aah! It burns me up!
The train's left the station.
Indore Singh's in the fourth wagon...
Will you drink some?
What's Kesu up to nowadays?
God only knows!
Every time you call him,
his phone is permanently out of LBW...
But Dolly will surely know
his whereabouts.
They are constantly in touch
over the phone.
Langda!
Yes brother.
Will you tell me the truth?
Ya bro, of course I will!
I want a clear-cut yes or no.
Of course! Please to ask!
Is there anything going on
between Kesu and Dolly?
May my tongue fall off
before I utter another word!
Yes or no?
I regard you more than my life...
forgive me...
Yes or no?!
Don't be so cold blooded
with your own brother.
Yes or no?
Game, set and match!
Let's leave!
Yes or no?
Yes or no?!
No...!
That's what you wanted to hear?! No!
Do you have the courage
to hear the truth?
What truth do you want to know?
That during the Kichlu episode,
when I stayed over at Kesu's house...
I heard him mutter in his sleep
"Dolly... if our love has to live,
we'll have to hide it
from the entire world."
Was there any other witness there?
No!?
When you see your dreams...
you see it alone.
When you hear your dreams...
you hear it alone.
When I look into Dolly's eyes,
your entire Bible sounds phony!
Now go get some proof before the
wedding... understood?!
And if you don't, I'll wring
your corpse limp... Bastard!
What the...?! Stop this racket!
Who are you playing here for...
is it the Lord's wedding...?
Take all your shebang
and come to our place...
the girl's house.
And isn't it Rip Van Winkle himself?
What do you think you're up to, eh!?
Come home... there's lots to be done.
Get a bath and do something
about your lovely face!
As if it wasn't pretty enough,
Sir's gone and had a facial in the city!
Bitch and a half!
The horse's here.
Start dressing it up.
When I woke up this morning, saw the word
'fool' tattooed on my forehead.
Do what I say... else you'll find the word
'moron' tattooed tomorrow morning.
"Don't you want Dolly... eh...?"
That's enough anger
for a lifetime Omi bro!
Today you have to keep
your word and pardon me.
Hey! Don't set up
the barbecue near the loo!
Take it away...
who the hell's in charge here?
Kesu?
Kesu's not here. Who's on the line?
- Billo
Billo ma'am!
Kesu's occupied right now.
Call him on the phone
I'm sorry... we're not allowed
to disturb him.
I said just call him
As I've already explained,
we're not allowed inside.
The room is locked tight.
Who's there with him?
Can't tell you the truth.
And my lies won't assure you.
Hello Hello... any message?
Don't be a fool!
It's just a bogus omen.
Don't let it bother you...
stop crying!
It's not nice to be mourning
on your wedding day.
Lets get you dressed now.
Will you get ready now
or should I call Omkara?
Should I?!
Call him if you please!
At least I'll get to know what is the
grave sin that I've committed?
This is not the same Omkara for whom
I gave up home and hearth.
My Omkara used to shield me
in his palms like a precious petal.
What happened... but?
I don't know...
he's always annoyed at me
That day I lied that
he'd hurt me out of love.
He hit me because
I misplaced something.
What thing?
Whatever it is, you don't
have right to hit anyone!
You once lost Golu at the fair!
Did I utter a word?
It's time I had a word with him.
Don't worry
Look here dodo!
Men and women have always
had a pan and ladle equation.
Alone, they stay miserable...
and together, they make one helluva racket!
Cling Clang Cling Clang!
Not Bad!
Now... that's a rare smile in this weather!
For our silver jubilee anniversary,
I took my wife to Timbuktu!
- Timbuktu?!
What're you planning now
for the 50th year celebrations?
Thinking of getting her back from Timbuktu!
Now it's my turn to crack one.
Now that's a joke in itself!
There was this man who once got married.
Then?
That was the end of it.
You can lie to the whole world but
I don't get fooled that easy.
Your eyes give it away...
Won't share it with your own sister?
What demons are you
carrying around in your head?
Her father's voice keeps ringing
in my ears all the time...
"She who can dupe her own father
will never be anyone's to claim"
Two faced character... no?
When the scriptures themselves
have sullied women,
who can blame mere mortals
like you, brother?
We renounce our homes and walk into
your lives with bare empty hands.
But even after the holy fires
approve us,
we're regarded disloyal
sooner than loyal.
There's time yet, brother!
If you have the slightest of doubts,
please do not stoop to attend the marriage!
We'll take care of Dolly...
you don't worry about her fate.
If I don't get the proof I'll make sure
he never misses his father.
Ya?
Billo's looking for you in the village.
At this hour?
- Ya... she seems to be in one foul mood.
I sent her to Langda bro.
I think you should call him.
Ya Kesu?
- Is Billo around?
Ya she's upstairs.
Your sweetheart's
not looking very happy, I fear.
God knows why
the bitch's always in heat?!
This blasted affair!
What affair?
This 'love affair'
is a bloody bore!
The 'wham bang' days
were much better!
If she's so turned on before the wedding,
imagine how she'll devour me after?
I told her we should avoid doing it
on the wedding night... but no luck!
You here?!
Who are you flirting with...
this late at night?
Don't you dare disconnect!
Finish your damn love chat!
You're misunderstanding the whole thing.
Ya right! I've understood you enough!
You are a compulsive womanizer!
Given a chance, you'd take
Your own mother to bed!
That'll be enough!
Shut your mouth!
Whose wife did you strip this away from?
- Billo... listen to me for a minute!
Sorry honey... we're finished!
Don't get crazy, girl!
Wait... listen up please!
Do we have to do this?
Lets go now, please!
Won't you wait for dessert, my friend?
Go stiff him a couple from point blank,
else the 'ex-General'
will suffer all night.
Go Champ!
Your lover's history!
What?
Your lover...
Kesu...
Poor soul couldn't
even carry your keepsake.
Where did you get this
blasted thing?
Hey meanie!
Stop play acting now.
You've been stripped naked.
Your 'innocence' makes me want to puke.
Since when have you been
warming Kesu's loins?
OK... at least tell me when was
the first time you slept with him?
Just for the record?
Are you carrying his baby by any chance?
See... the deal is - accept it,
I'll spare you your life.
Thanks for the offer but...
you are free to take my life.
Did I lack anything?
Huh?
Omi bro!
Omi bro! There's been a lot of bloodshed,
please rush!
Omi brother... are you listening?!
She looks so childlike in her sleep...
She who can dupe her own father
will never be anyone's to claim.
Two faced character!
I stole this.
Brother Omi!
Go home.
Go home you bitch!
Didn't you hear me... whore?!
Langda!
She's lying Omi bro...
God knows why she wants me dead!
Seems she too is having an affair...
I regard you more than God!
I'd never...
Think what you must.
My truth and my lies have
all got blurred.
Go shoot me in the head! Release me!
Death will only help free your body...
...but our souls are forever damned...
We won't find redemption...
not in this life!
"Wake up little princess!"
Your eyes like sweet petals!
"Eyes that hold me in their spell."
"May I never be away
from their sight!"
"My little princess...
my sleeping doll wake up."
"Wake up little princess!"
"Your eyes like sweet petals!"
"The dawn blushes pink on your cheek"
"Craving to caress you...
come now wake up...
"Your sweet flesh beckons
Comes hither a bee to tickle you"
"Come now my darling wake up."
"Ask for your heart's desire
I give my word in blood"
"Just for this once... open your eyes"
"My little princess...
my sleeping doll wake up."
"Wake up little princess!
Your eyes like sweet petals!"
Open the door, Omi Bro!
How did you ever think...?
Hush now!
One more word and its all over.
Isn't it all over anyway?
No, it isn't over yet.
Forgotten how I pasted
the Army Guy in court?
Bang on the temple... Boom!
And our friend Indore Singh?
Shoved the gun right
up his mouth and... Boom!
And Thakur?
Right through his heart....
# Subtitles by  $ ShabbaMechstar $