If yet your bIood does not rage, then
it is waterthat fIows in your veins.
For what is the fIush of youth,
if it is not of service to the motherIand.
Just a minute Mr. McKinIey,
one revoIutionary is meeting another.
Thank you.
ShaII we go?
I'm sorry it had to end this way.
This isn't the end Mr. McKinIey.
This is just the beginning.
There wiII be others after
we have gone. Many others.
Shove it.
Get out of the way! Scoot!
You come India first time madam?
Yes!
Sorry about the short notice.
Gosh! Your Hindi has
reaIIy improved.
Don't worry,
aII the preparations are done.
Hey Sue, no need to worry..
..everything has been taken care of
posters have been put up everywhere.
It's aIso been announced on radio.
..just see, they'II be Iining
up forthe auditions.
What's wrong?
I didn't teII you.
The truth is that I've come aIone.
..no money, no producer is going to arrive.
You knew it!
After AIice, there was a
caII from a certain Beth WiIIiams..
..she informed me of the canceIIation
of the show and aIso my services.
... did you abuse her in Hindi?
She wanted to know what it meant.
I expIained to her in graphic detaiI.
You are amazing... Sonia.
This is DeIhi University.
Let me heIp you with your Iuggage.
How much?
- Ma'am I've aIready ToId you.
Ravi, pIease get aII the
Iuggage to our room.
Get some rest now.
I'II see you tomorrow..
..If you need anything
you have my number.
Let's go Ravi.
I can't do this.
I deserve a roIe because
I have dimpIes just Iike Priety Zinta.
Don't sing. Just recite ''Vande Matram''.
- Vande MaTram?
Raise your hand and say VANDE MATRAM!
VANDE MaTram!
Speak IoudIy, VANDE MATRAM!
Vande MATRAM.
LoudIy and proudIy, VANDE MATRAM!
Vande MATRAM
VANDE MATRAM!
Vande MaTram..
I have dedicated my Iife
to the freedom of this nation.
I know you want me to get married.
..but FREEDOM is my bride.
I know.. I know.. that..
I know.. that you want me to get married..
..but my bride is FREEDOM
..but my bride is FREEDOM.
Your obedient son, BHAGAT SINGH.
BHAGAT SINGH.
BhagaT Singh.
My name is Bhagat Singh.
Tea!
Thanks.
Depressed huh?
One ortwo of them can
be used for minor roIes..
..but no one's even cIose for
Azad or Bhagat Singh.
I guess it's aII my fauIt.
No Sonia. You're my rock.
Sue, don't get so dejected.
Let's go and have some fun.
I'm in no mood Sonia.
Hey AsIam.
AsIam.. Sue McKinIey.
You too study at the University?
Wow! Her Hindi is great.
We Iive there, eat there but no one
has ever accused us of studying there.
What are those maniacs upto?
That's DJ..
DJ I Iove you!!!
That's Sukhi.
I Iove you too baby!
Damn exhibitionists.
The idiots wiII never change.
Come on dude, Iet's rock it!
Sukhi I Iove you!
Is he OK?
That's his naturaI state.
Sukhi, aII parts working?
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Sue this is DJ.
DJ this is Sue.
Hi!
Sue? She's so pink her name
shouId be GuIabo (Rose).
She's quite hot..
Perfect forthis coId.
Karan you saved my Iife.
I Iove you!
AsIam..
..you too saved my Iife,
I Iove you too!
It's ok.
She must have saved my Iife too..
No! Sukhi!
She didn't save your Iife.
No probIem. One day
she'II save my Iife.
ReIax Dude!
She is your sister-in-Iaw.
LOOSE CONTROL
I'm a REBEL.
There's aren'T any sTudenTs here,
no Teachers To suffer.
IT's a schooI wiThouT ruIes ouT here
Hey Genius, go figure.
Sukhi you just sit and
watch Iike a dumb-ass..
DJ doesn't waste a second.
He's a stud.
Hi! How's everybody?
Hi RahuI! What's up?
Got a few gigs Iined up.
How's your radio thing going?
Did anything work out?
AII India Radio has
given me a night sIot.
CooI...
Not reaIIy. When the whoIe worId's
sIeeping I'm on air.
But peopIe stay up Iate..
CriminaIs, insomniacs,
watchmen and idiots!
Have yourfun at my expense.
Speaking of expenses..
Can I..
See you guys.
Got a cigarette?
FabuIous!
It's my Dad's money.
He's got Iots of it..
Stop this Western music,
this obscenity!
How many times do
I have to make you understand this!
PoIIuting the cuIture of this country...
Leave this pIace right now.
LEAVE!
Can't you understand, idiot!
This is your Iast warning..
..from now on, nobody pIays
any Western music out here.
No Iewd dancing!
or I'II break your Iegs.
Who are you to warn us?
If you don't Iike it, don't come here.
You bIoody Pakistani!
Let's finish it.
Last warning! Got it?
Long Iive India!
You touch AsIam and
see what I do to you..
..even your mother won't recognize you.
Ever seen a baboons arse? Yours wiII
be as red after I've finished with you.
Sir, I'm sure we can work it out.
Keep this..
Anyone hungry? I'm famished.
How're you?
Hey honey! Come here you..
If something happened to you,
I'd have kiIIed you.
Is this any way to greet your boyfriend?
How're you?
Hurry guys, I'm famished.
You won't get any food here.
Stay away!
..I carried you in my stomach
for nine months..
..and washed your bum foryears.
Get Iost!
Does anyone botherto check
if Mitro is aIive or dead?
What's up?
You're drunk again.
No. No. No.
First give us food ma,
and then yeII at us aII night.
None of you have eaten?
Sonia you've Iost even more weight.
ReaIIy.. Mitro
The girIs of today have
more bones and Iess fIesh..
How wiII you bear chiIdren?
AsIam, how are you my son?
He is my true son
who bothers to check on me.
And you...
Look ma, what I brought foryou.
Your daughter-in-Iaw.
Her name is Sue.
What? Aforeigner?
Brought her especiaIIy from London.
That's why I was away for so Iong.
Give me your bIessings Ma.
Your son's such a brat.
God! She understands Hindi!
You reaIIy understand everything?
Yes.
I'm going off to sIeep. Your beds are
aII ready. No need to drive so Iate at night.
Sue, where are you?
WiII you guys act in my fiIm?
What?
Hey, why are you guys Iaughing?
I'm the hero of herfiIm.
Yeah we guys are champions
when it comes to acting..
..cIowning around is aII they do.
The four of you wiII be
perfect forthe roIes...
And Sonia wiII be my Durga Bhabhi.
She reaIIy knows Hindi!
AII this taIk of patriotism is boring.
Boring? These guys gave their
Iives forthe freedom of your country.
What freedom? Have you seen
the state of this country?
Excuse me! I beIieve in this country, Karan.
Otherwise, why wouId
I be fighting for it?
Maybe because it's cooI!
Being a piIot.. fIying an expensive pIane.
You get to wear sexy jackets..
And the women..
women Iove men in uniforms.
Sure I Iove being a piIot.
Sure it's cooI.
But I aIso feeI proud of my country,
and I can give my Iife for it.
Proud of what?
..this country's expIoding popuIation?
..or unempIoyment..
or corruption?
Which of these are you reaIIy proud of?
No country's perfect Karan.
We've got to make it better.
Right.
Ok, Ajay you make
this country perfect.
The minute I get my degree
I'm out of this dump..
You won't be abIe
to Ieave us and go.
She speaks Hindi so weII!
Why didn't you teII me you idiot.
I was making a fooI of myseIf.
At Ieast ask them once.
So you won't give up.
Ok. But nobody wiII turn up.
I'II get them. That's a promise.
Karan put your cigarette out.
Grandpa!
God bIess you.
When did you come?
Just Iast night.
Good morning Karan.
Back so earIy?
I didn't know you were in town.
Just arrived an hour ago.
It was a Iong fIight..
Everything Ok at coIIege?
Everything's fine Dad.
Have you decided which American
university you want to go to next year?
Michigan, Carnegie,
MeIIon, Wharton...
I know the Iist.
HeIIo...
Karan wait!
I can't hearyou cIearIy
caII me Iater.
I know that you know about the Iists.
But Iife doesn't just happen to you.
You've got to pIan it..
Every second someone
is born in this country.
Nobody cares about them.
Neitherthe government nor God.
Do something.
Or eIse you wiII be one of them.
PIease, don't start with your Iectures.
SMS generation.
Any conversation that goes beyond..
..four Iines becomes a Iecture.
SignaI's weak here. Give me a second.
Excuse me Karan.
The deaI is off then,
we are not interested..
You know Russian quaIity is doubtfuI,
they can't afford to be arrogant.
Anyway in the open market they'd not get
anything cIose to the price we're offering.
And you know how many fathers
there are to every deaI in India. Nothing.
TeII them we won't bargain,
they shouId wire the money to us.
I did try to warn you..
they won't turn up.
DJ promised me.
Oh! DJ promised you!
So you reaIIy are a fiImmaker?
Karan... Why are you so Iate?
And where are the others?
The Young Guns Of India.
Very dramatic.
Where are you going?
WeII that's one part cast.
I am sure Karan can teII us
where his friends are.
She's an eight. Yeah!
Wow! Nine.
What a girI!
Oye ChoTu..
..get me a cup of tea..
Two, Iooks Iike she's got the fIu...
Six..
Ten!
WhaT?
Dude.. Iooks at those Iegs!
Shake it baby, shake it..
Oh shit!
Don't be siIIy,
that's at Ieast an eight.
Thought I'd find you
stuffing yourfaces.
You Iazy good-for-nothings.
We were about to come... but..
...we are waiting for Karan actuaIIy.
Oh! So you were waiting for Karan.
Yeah!
Karan was there on time.
We are waiting for him here
and he was waiting for us there.
What confusion..
You're AshfaquIIa Khan.
You're Rajguru.
The hero righT!
And you know who you are?
The Master of Disguise
and Deception.
Chandrashekhar Azad.
What Iips...
Learn the Iines properIy,
we meet tomorrow.
8 a.m. sharp!
Nine.
Sharp aT eighT.
That's fine.
We've aIready wasTed a day..
AsIam, your sister-in-Iaw Iooks
even better when she's angry.
What are you doing Laxman?
Greetings Mishraji.
Party High Command is reaIIy
happy with your work.
These demonstrations that you have
started against Western cuIture..
..they've heIped us
overshadow other parties.
This is foryou.
And this is foryour boys.
It's not necessary, Mishraji.
I'm not doing this for money.
I reaIIy beIieve in the
principIes of my party.
That's fine Laxman..
..but every movement
needs fueI.. Keep it.
There is nothing
you can do to break me.
''Because I have made pain my friend.''
''..As I hoId Death's fingers.''
DJ idiot, don't spoiI my concentration.
Look, Death's finger.
''I've committed my Iife
to the freedom of this country.
..I know you want me to get married,
but I have made freedom my bride..''
''Your obedient son, Bhagat Singh.''
Who taIks Iike this for
God's sake?
My bride is freedom..
I think it's a good Iine for Sukhi..
Since no girI is ever going to marry him..
Let freedom be his bride.
Laugh bastards, Iaugh.
This is the sari round
of the Miss Freedom contest.
Just thought it wouId heIp
me get into the character.
Look guys this isn't going to work.
You have to work hard to bring
out the characters.
UnIess you emote from within..
..you won't understand these characters.
Try.. it wiII come from within you.
BURP
See, he's got a hoId of his character aIready.
You understood the character pretty fast.
See! Now you Iook Iike a revoIutionary!
Whateveryou say GuIabo,
you need me to create the mood.
DJ watch it.
Now she's upset!
Those are the words of a 23 year oId.
That's how oId Bhagat Singh
was when he died: 23.
Those were different times Sue.
Today, if you teII peopIe that
you want to give your Iife foryour country..
..they'II caII you nuts.
ExactIy.
I don't think I can reIate to this..
That's it. Don't think.
FeeI. Just read the words,
FeeI them.
Why don't we try again?
Let's try again..
I've committed my Iife to
the freedom of this country.
..a job..a weII settIed Iife..
these things don't matter anymore.
..I know you want me to get married,
but I have made freedom my bride..
I swear on Mother India...
This AsIam is a reaI stud..
Take a Iook at the packaging.
Poetry, paImistry!
DJ, I'm scared at times that
I'II remain a bacheIor aII my Iife.
Trust me I won't Iet you die a bacheIor.
Promise?
It's DJ's promise.
You'II be writing peopIe's destinies...
Your Iove Iine is very strong..
The man of your dreams wiII come
aIong in a bIack T-shirt and say:.
Do I even have a Iove Iine?
You must have washed it off in the Ioo.
''Defence Minister Shastri has aIso been
impIicated in the MIG-21 kickbacks scandaI,''
This is reaIIy depressing.
''This is a bIatant Iie.
I am ordering an investigation.''
See you guys.
You're my buddy..
I'II drop you home.
I don't need any heIp,
it's just two Ianes away.
We aren't so drunk..
that we've forgotten where you Iive.
Idiots!
You're very Iucky to
have friends Iike them.
One day this wiII aII end.
We'II aII go our separate ways.
But you can aIways keep in touch.
Doesn't happen.
Life gets busy.
Too many probIems.
Getting a job, a house, money.
In coIIege we are the
masters of our destinies..
But after coIIege we have
to dance to fate's tune.
You know GuIabo.
I passed out 5 years ago...
..but I stiII hang around..
I don't understand.
..I don't ever want to Ieave coIIege.
Why?
At Ieast in the campus
I'm someone.. peopIe know me.
DJ's somebody...
PeopIe expect me to do
something big in Iife.
But when I'm out on the streets..
I'II just be Iike the rest of
the sIobs in this country.
NameIess. FaceIess. Scared.
Just waIking the streets..
It's the beer...
Everything came out.
You know what eIse
I'm scared of?
Acting in yourfiIm.
Don't worry.. you're in safe hands.
Where have you been?
HeIIo UncIe.. How are you?
We'II catch up tomorrow AsIam..
You've been drinking?
Dad, you know I don't drink.
Good-for-nothings..
WhaTever, They're my friends.
Friends! They feeI no
shame standing in front of..
..yourfather with aIcohoI on their breath.
Why can't you get friends
in your own community?
Why do you make friends with peopIe
who corrupt you, disgrace your reIigion..
This has nothing to
do with reIigion, Father.
Shut up! Don't raise your voice
in the presence of yourfather.
He's right.
This country has never accepted
MusIims and it never wiII..
How can you be so passive!
Do you ever see me
mixing with a Hindu?
I'm not you and I don't want
to be Iike you brother.
I can't fiII myseIf with so much hate..
Coward that's what you are.
Stop it!
I feeI suffocated in this house.
It's the same oId thing every singIe day..
CarnivaIs wiII be heId on our
graves every year,
That's aII that wiII be Ieft of us,
when we die for our country.
WeII said Ashfaq Sahab..
If the EngIish couId hearyou they
wouId Ieave this country in a moment.
So what has been decided?
We'II steaI the Empire's money
from the train that passes Kakori.
And with that money we wiII buy arms.
BismiI wiII expIain everything.
Yes BismiI.. Where is my Ram?
Ijust can't find my
Ramprasad BismiI.
ReIax. We wiII find him.
But where? How?
Very soon. Don't you wo..
You won't get Ramprasad
BismiI out here.
You need a true Indian.
How can you find Indian
revoIutionaries amongst..
..peopIe who want to be Westerners?
Ignore him. Let's go.
Ramprasad BismiI wished to
be reborn a hundred times..
..so that he couId give his Iife for his
country a hundred times over.
Let's go Sue.
So where do you think
I can find my BismiI?
I don't beIieve this.
This day, we waIk aIong with death,
and Iaugh at its paIe spectre.
We wiII not fearthose crueI swords,
our courage is far sharper.
Mistake not our siIence for submission.
For beneath Iies Iava, moIten.
O Martyre, O men of vaIour.
One day The enemy wiII sing your praises.
We wiII show our mettIe
when the moment of truth arrives..
..for courage Iives in deeds,
not boastfuI Iies.
We've gathered in the enemy's Iair,
my friend..
In the hope of dying for our motherIand.
We wiII not fearthose crueI swords,
our courage is far sharper.
This day, we waIk aIong with death,
and Iaugh at its paIe spectre.
We wiII not fearthose crueI swords,
our courage is far sharper.
Sue, this isn't London.
You don't know what kind..
..of scum, men Iike Laxman Pandey are.
Look Sue if he is a part of this,
then I can't do the fiIm.
If you have any probIems
with me say it on my face.
Don't stab me in the back Iike a coward.
Pandey Ieave!
We don't want troubIe..
Speak you coward.
What were you saying?
AsIam, where are you going?
Coward, what were you saying?
Hey you! How dare you hit AsIam?
SUKHI
Thrash him.
I'm sorry,
I took you guys in my fiIm.
God knows what made me come here..
You know we've got a probIem
with Pandey. There's a Iot of bad bIood.
And if I stay, it's sure to happen again.
No, Sue.
We've worked it out.
You won't have any probIems.
Sue.. we aII know how much
this fiIm means to you.
We want to heIp you finish
what you came here to do.
Everyone wants you to stay.
I want you to stay.
Say something...
Don't worry, you're in safe hands.
Come on.. Get up. ..Come here.
She's not going anywhere.
Now just chiII.
Take some soiI of my Iand,
The scenT of This air..
Add The breaTh of my being,
The Throbbing of my heart..
And The zeaI, ThaT
races Through my bIood..
Take aII These, and sTir iT.
Then waTch as iT brings ouT The coIour..
WaTch as iT brings ouT
The coIour of paTrioTism, my friend.
WaTch as iT brings ouT The coIour.
BismiI's sent a message...
...that the Lucknow train...
...carrying the Empire's money...
wiII be Iooted by us in Kakori...
...whiIe eating Kakori kababs.
And we wiII buy bombs with that money.
Leave her aIone...
She wiII stop giving miIk.
Give coIour To your dreams.
And Those of your peopIe.
Give coIour To your happiness.
And your sadness Too.
Give coIour To generaTions..
Give coIour To The fieId..
Give coIour To The beaT of your heart.
And ThaT of your music.
Give coIour To every cheek.
Give coIour To your eyes..
WaTch as iT brings ouT The
coIour of paTrioTism my friend.
WaTch as iT brings ouT The coIour..
Take some soiI of my Iand,
The scenT of This air..
Add The breaTh of my being,
The Throbbing of my heart.
And The zeaI, ThaT races
Through my bIood.
Take aII These and sTir iT.
Then waTch as iT brings ouT The coIour.
WaTch as iT brings ouT The
coIour of paTrioTism, my friend.
WaTch as iT brings ouT The coIour.
Hey Short-stuff!
Did you get BismiI's message?
No.
No! Then LisTen..
The train that's Kakori...
wiII be Iooted in eight days.
It's Ioaded with the Empire's money.
WiII you Ioot it?
No.
We wiII be buying arms from it.
What wiII we buy?
Arms..
Yes.. Very Good... go now.
On a sIow fire, won'Tyou,
puT This passion To cook.
Then as iTsimmers,
add a babbIing brook.
Add a river, and an ocean.
Maybe a poT of waTer.
Then sprinkIe a biT. STir iT aII up.
And waTch as iT brings ouT The coIour.
WaTch as iT brings ouT
The coIour of paTrioTism, my friend.
BismiI has sent a message...
...the Lucknow train...
...which carries the Empire's money...
..wiII be Iooted by us in
seven days, in Kakori...
And we wiII buy bombs with that money.
Now painT The whoIe Town wiTh iT.
PainTyour very being.
PainTyour every vein wiTh iT.
PainT iT wiTh a smiIe.
PainT Those chiIdhood years, won'Tyou.
PainT The fIush of youTh.
Don'T hesiTaTe, my friend.
PainTyour paTrioTism over everyThing.
WaTch as iT brings ouT The
coIour of paTrioTism, my friend.
Take some soiI of my Iand,
The scenT of This air.
Add The breaTh of my being,
The Throbbing of my heart.
And The zeaI,
ThaT races Through my bIood.
Take aII These and sTir iT.
Then waTch as iT brings ouT The coIour.
WaTch as iT brings ouT The
coIour of paTrioTism, my friend.
WaTch as iT brings ouT The coIour.
WaTch as iT brings ouT The
coIour of paTrioTism, my friend.
British Officers...
around 20 to 25 of them.
We have to caII it off! We've nearIy
reached Kakori. Stop Ashfaq, quick.
Ashfaq, stop!
It's too Iate to back out now...
Come on... Move!
Get inside!
Keep the windows shut...
Come on!
The keys!
You won't get away with this.
Give me the keys!
- I don'T have iT.
Banwari get the sIedge hammer.
I'II handIe them.
You go get the money...
I've committed my Iife
to the freedom of this country.
Comfort, and other worIdIy
desires do not attract me.
I know you want me to
get married and settIe down...
...Iike aII parents do.
But freedom is my bride.
I hope you'II forgive me.
Your most obedient son, Bhagat.
Let's take a break.
Breakfast?
No...
Put it there.
GeneraI Dyer? How can one even think
of doing something Iike this?
I can't beIieve that he actuaIIy kiIIed more
than 400 peopIe at JaIIianwaIa Baugh.
379... that was the officiaI figure.
ActuaIIy nearIy 1000
peopIe were butchered...
Last year at the tomb of Peer Sai,
I prayed for DaIjeet's weII being.
Who's DaIjeet?
We were the epitome of toIerance.
Even an ant reacts. But we are conditioned
to take everything Iying down.
Rubbish! It's today's generation
which Iacks the wiII to do anything
Have you ever heard of
Shaheed Uddham Singh?
He went aII the way to London
and kiIIed that Dyer.
...because he was aIso a part
of the JaIIianwaIa Baugh massacre.
Eat it Sonia.
The butter wiII strengthen your bones.
In Punjab every mother sends
at Ieast one son to the army.
Why shouId we retreat?
Sacrifice runs in our bIood.
OnIy idiots Iike DJ retreat.
Why does it aIways come back to me?
Shut up and eat your paratha.
What is the most used word in this country?
ADJUST!
Six peopIe sitting on a seat forfour...someone
wiII squeeze in and say - 'PIease adjust!'.
Hey! Why are you adjusting?
Strange. Isn't it?
We are being hunted Iike
animaIs in our own country...
...Ashfaq you shouId cross the border
and get to Afghanistan...
...We have many MusIim friends there.
You wiII be safe with them.
After aII, you're one of their own.
One of their own?
Hmm...
Why don't you think of me
as one of your own?
Ashfaq... I never meant...
...Ashfaq...
I didn't mean to hurt you.
This is your country as much as it is mine.
You have a right to fight and die for it too...
...Forgive me.
Ram, Iet us not taIk of dying...
I pray, that we aII Iive to see
our grandchiIdren grow up in a free country.
Ram run!
Where are your otherfriends?
Where's Azad?
Our bIood ia ranging.
It'a fIowing through the atreeta.
But it won't go in vain
Our eyea are bIood ahot for a purpose.
A cauae we wiII attain.
It feII from our bodiea,
embraced the earth.
Went winding through atreeta.
A river of courage
...it aurged and awept.
It fIowed to make a new
beginning
From gaping wounda,
and gaahea Iarge,
it oozed, aIowIy and ateadiIy.
WhiIe the pointing fingers,
got fiata in repIy,
yet, our bIood waa raging.
It fIowed not in vain
but with a reaaon.
A cauae we wiII attain.
Our eyea are bIood ahot
for a reaaon.
A cauae we wiII attain.
Our bIood ia raging.
It'a fIowing through the atreeta.
...it aurged and awept.
It fIowed to make a new
beginning
Yet, our bIood waa raging.
Someone get a doctor! Quick!
We'll take it from here.
They were beating up
innocent people...
Why didn't you
stop them?
You protested against
the government, our own party...
That's unacceptable.
The protest was not
against the government...
...it was forthe truth.
So many pilots have died...
...young innocent boys who were fighting
for our country... killed...
...so that someone in the
government could make money.
And our party office doesn't
do a thing about it.
Come... Sit down.
Have some tea.
Laxman, in politics there's
no place for emotions.
We have big plans foryou.
Big plans.
Only dogs salivate when
you show them bone Mishraji.
How's Aunty?
They're doing an MRl.
She's slipped into a coma.
Severe skull damage,
coupled with the shock of her son's death.
That's an ugly gash.
You need attention.
Aslam...How's he?
What have you come for?
Haven't you done enough damage?
Uncle, it isn't
what you think.
l'm not interested in what you think,
ln what you want to do...
l'm just going to say this once.
Aslam doesn't
know what's good for him.
He's an emotional boy, always has been.
He listens to his heart, not his head.
These are bad times,
for people like us.
Don't take him
down with you.
He's inside.
Go on...
All parts working?
Don't make me laugh, idiot.
lt hurts
How's Aunty?
She's in a coma.
How can this be
happening to us?
Some dinner?
No, don't worry Aunty.
We just came to see Aslam.
We've got to get back to the hospital.
Take care.
Listen...l...
...l'm sorry.
Please eat.
Everything's falling apart...
...and all l can do is
stand and watch.
People like us don't count
out here.
This system is so messed up, a hundred more
Ajay's can die and nothing will change.
Ajay did everything right,
all his life...
...he was a good pilot,
a good friend, a good son...
...he never harmed a soul.
...he didn't deserve this...
...Sonia didn't deserve this...
Hey Karan...they've
spoilt your jacket.
Long live lndia!
The scoundrel got
away with it again.
There's nothing can we do...
...when the law of the land protects
people like the Defence Minister.
We have to take
drastic measures.
What do you mean?
Do what?
Kill him.
What?
Kill the Defence Minister!
Are you crazy?
We aren't killers Sonia.
But they are.
Have you lost it Karan!
lt's not a blood lust...
...it's a matter of justice.
l'll get the gun.
Don't fuel things, Pandey. We can't
start killing people for any small reason.
You think Ajay's death
is a small reason?
Ajay's mother is
a small reason?
You've got to understand Karan.
Lala Lajpat Rai's death
has to be avenged.
Scott has to be killed.
But...
l always thought we didn't
believe in anything.
So did l. Until now.
Have we all gone crazy?
He takes a morning walk at 8 a.m. everyday,
We'll kill him then.
Who's we, huh?
Who's going to pull the trigger?
l'll do it!
Even though the morning security is relaxed
there is still a danger of getting caught.
There is no looking back now!
The Defence Minister was on his morning walk
when two unidentified gunmen opened fire.
He was hit by three bullets in his chest,and was
declared dead as he reached the hospital.
No group has yet claimed
responsibility forthis incident.
Government spokespersons believe that this is
an attempt to destablise the government.
The country has lost a great leader
because of the cowardly act of some terrorists.
He was a true soldier, a true patriot.
His contribution to the country
cannot be described in words.
Sukhi!
Meanwhile our sources have
discovered a telephonic conversation...
...involving middle man Rajnath Singhania
in an arms deal.
This conversation took place just a few days
before the Defence Minister's assassination.
The Russians want us
to reduce our commission.
Didn't you tell them,
its not a defence deal, but our deal.
That's why l told them. - ''Take it or leave it''
Let's go.
Paaji, where's DJ?
They were just here.
He hasn't come home all night.
ls everything alright?
Yes, ask him to call me.
He said he'd be
spending the night at DJ's.
Have you seen DJ?
ls everything alright?
Come with me...
Don't worry... nothing
will happen to those boys...
Daljeet has always
been a brat..
...he used to disappear
on his bike for days...
l'm scared...
Don't be afraid...
God will take care of everything...
God watches over
the people we love.
Defence Minister...
the martyr...
...one of lndia's favourite sons...
Scoundrel!
They're honouring him
with the National Medal of Honour.
All our efforts, wasted.
People need to
know the truth.
...and who's going to tell them the truth?
We have to
surrender ourselves.
What?
Terriffic! You want us to walk right
in and give ourselves up!
And who should
we surrenderto?
The police are
mere puppets.
Should we just
sit back?
No! Let's kill
them all!
Right Pandey?
Someone make
him shut up!
You always knew that
yourfather was in it.
You knew everything.
No Sukhi...
You're lying!
You always wanted to take
revenge on yourfather.
Sukhi, shut up!
Who am l to say anything?
DJ he's used you...
...he's used all of us...
Mark my words,
his father will bail him out.
But we'll get caught.
And l don't want to die DJ...
l don't want to die.
We did all this for Ajay.
What will happen now DJ?
You've decided?
l need to know the truth...
don't worry.
l'm not worried.
Just don't be late.
Nothing will happen
to you Karan.
That's a promise.
Just give me the
names of the others.
l'll get you the best lawyers,
pull all the strings possible.
You were forced into it, do you
understand? You were forced.
Do you get me?
Yourfather's reputation,
his life's work is at stake.
Why did you do it?
Why did you do it, Dad?
What did l do?
Ajay always said,
''l'll give my life forthis country.''
''...l'm not afraid of death.''
Ajay was burnt alive... and all you can
think of is sending me out of the country...
You killed him!
You made a joke of his death...
l know you're very disturbed...
Relax! Let me
handle things.
l'll find a way out.
Really Dad?
ls there a way out?
Of course.
You don't have
to do this...
Sukhi, this might
end badly.
Without you guys it will
end for me anyway...
ldiot.
Ajay's death, won't go in vain,
Ma. l promise you.
This is Rahul, and you've tuned
in to yourfavourite radio show...
Hey Karan!
What're you doing here?
We need a favour.
Sure!
l need you to
put us on air.
Put you on air?
Yeah, now!
That's impossible man...
l'll lose my job.
...as it is, they
don't pay me.
lt's payback time.
Hey! Whateveryou say DJ!
lt's your station.
Gun... He's got a gun!
Karan you go in.
l'll handle it.
Keep the show on.
Don't mess with us.
Come on... leave.
Paaji is anyone inside?
Uncleji run. Don't stop.
Gun... Security he's got a gun!
Don't be a wise guy.
Everybody leave!
Out! Move!
Don't panic we won't
harm anyone.
Move! Move! Move!
Hurry up, quick!
The time is 6:05 a.m. And you're listening
to ''The night is still young''.
Today l've got a
surprise guest foryou.
An old friend of mine Karan Singhania, who just
dropped in to say something to all of you...
My name is Karan Singhania... My friends
and l... we killed the Defence Minister...
l repeat we killed
the Defence Minister...
Ravi take me to the radio
station quickly. Hurry up!
We are not terrorists. We aren't
backed by any foreign organisation.
We don't even belong to
any political group...
We're just five students
from Delhi University.
We killed the
Defense Minister because...
...he murdered ourfriend Flight Lieutenant Ajay
Rathod and many other Air Force pilots...
We killed him because after he
murdered Ajay, he murdered his name...
Ajay's mother, right now,
is fighting for her life...
A Defence Minister is supposed to
safegaurd a nation. Not sell it.
Men like the Defence Minister
aren't just above the law...they control it.
We killed him because someone
had to say, ''Enough!''.
We might be wrong...
...because its a sin to
kill someone.
But we couldn't tolerate it anymore.
Today we are here to confess to our sin.
Today we are here to tell everybody
that something has to be done
lt's got to be done.
We've just received news that Defence Minister's
assassins are hiding in All lndia Radio building.
Karan Singhania and his friends are still
with us. Listeners can call in on 3291777.
Until then, here is
''Roobaroo''
lt's done.
Hey, dude!
I juat reaIized.
There'a a fire
burning within me.
It'a a new dawn,
I can feeI ita Iight
Burn ao bright, I couId,
acorch the aun
'Cauae I'm face to face
with the Iight
The dream I once Iost,
I've found.
It'a bIooming,
it'a meIting,
notea re-arranging,
into a whoIe new meIody.
Will they give us
good food in jail?
Food?
Next he'll want beer.
You guys have become famous. Calls are
pouring in from all overthe country.
Come on!
They want to talk to you...
Police!
This is unreal man. Where
did they come from?
This will ruin my career...
Shut up!
Karan you get on air...
We don't have much time...
Take care.
The Delhi police have reached the spot and are
rescuing civilians trapped in the building.
...reporting from
Mumbai's Churchgate area...
Cotton College, Guwahati.
...reporting from
S. P. College, Srinagar...
Lucknow University...
Hi, my name is Prakash.
And l want to congratulate you.
You did the right thing by killing him.
All our ministers should be lined up and shot.
Prakash, who all
will you shoot?
These corrupt ministers are a reflection
of our society. We've chosen them.
We need to change ourselves
to bring about a change.
Hello! This is
Principal Sharma from lndore...
You have set a terrible example by
taking the law into your own hands.
You're right sir.
We're sorry.
But give me the name of one
politician who has gone to jail for his crimes.
Who else is on
your hit-list?l
We have no hit-list.
How do you feel after
killing the Defence Minister?
We did not kill him out
of any blood lust...
lf you get caught you'll be hanged.
Aren't you afraid?
No.
The college students who
have claimed responsibility ...
...are still inside.
Karan, while we applaud your courage,
do you think you'll escape?
lf we wanted to escape, we wouldn't
have been here in the first place.
Shit! They're shooting at us DJ!
They're shooting at us!
Shut up for a second!
They're mistaking us forterrorists.
They think we're armed.
Wait a minute!
l'll try to handle it.
No Sukhi!
What did you do!
Shit DJ! Just when l was getting
good with the girls...
My name is lndra.What's the difference
between you and a terrorist?
There's a big difference.
Terrorists kill innocent people. we didn't...
Aslam, close
the door. Quick!
We are not terrorists.
Why don't they...
lt's not a lust for blood ...
it's a matter of justice!
Why are bullets being used when its
clearthat these are college students?
No matter what you do, this country
will never change. lt has no future.
No country is perfect.
You've got to make it perfect.
Join the police,
military, lAS...
Become a part of
the political system..
This country will change...
We will change it!
lf you believed the Defence Minister
deserved to be punished then...
...what about the allegations against
yourfather? Why such double standards?
We'll find a way
to fix this.
There's just one way
to fix this Dad.
l'm sorry Dad...
My name is Daljeet Singh.
There are only two
ways to live your life.
Tolerate things the
way they are...
...Ortake responsibility
to change them.
Karan Singhania killed his
father before coming here.
Shit DJ!
You're bleeding badly!
Relax! lt got tired of flowing in my veins.
lt just wanted to be free.
Aslam...Laxman...Sukhi?
All gone.
...Karan, l think l'm in love...
... l nevertold you dude...
...l can't stop thinking
about her...
l know...she's something else.
You two'll make
a great couple.
There's just one problem though. l don't know
Whetherthe kids will be black or white.
Let me go!
They're just boys, damn it!
We'll turn this spark into a raging fire.
This will swell like a wave and
will bring an end to corruption.
lf we want to shake the entire population out of
their slumberthen we need an explosion like this.
When we grow out of this, well be a nation
which is beautiful and free of corruption.
Lord, accept the sacrifices of these children.
Come Bhagat..
Dad, what are you doing?
l'm sowing mango seeds.
lf l plant one, a thousand will grow.