"The moon will stealthily enter
through the window in bare feet"
"O beloved, listen to me,
listen to me, my darling"
"The moon will stealthily enter
through the window in bare feet"
Hey, what are you watching?
Is this a Ramlila?
Hey, you. Stop. - Sir, I've got to
go to the station.
Do I have to write it down for you?
Can't you hear?
Sorry sir, Sorry.
- You can't go from here.
There has been an accident.
Take a U-turn and go back. Go...
Today 6.30 p. M Marine Lines Station
What are you doing here?
Waiting for Suhani?
Like always.
If you'd married me, you wouldn't
have had to do all this.
If she doesn't come in the
next ten minutes...
We'll run away to a temple
and get married.
Let's go.
Is Suhani there?
Did she say where she was going?
Are you sure she is not somewhere
there... in the hospital?
Okay, I'll disconnect
the phone.
2 years before in Naangav
"It overflowed... the water from
the pitcher overflowed"
"It overflowed, for the
eye could not hold"
"Mother said, don't go.
Brother, I didn't listen to him"
"Father said, just one day more.
And it overflowed"
"Gudda said don't go.
Guddi too said the same"
"Friend said, just one day more.
And it overflowed..."
"The water from the
pitcher overflowed"
"It overflowed, for the eyes
couldn't hold"
There goes one more.
Another one bites the dust.
He used to be quite a happy guy.
Now he's gone and stuck his
head in a noose.
Why? What's wrong with our girl?
- Your girl?
So big? How old are you?
It's the magic of LUX beauty soap!
What else?
Are you done speaking?
- Yes.
What was it you were saying about
putting his head in a noose?
When it comes to
wearing the garland...
Why'd you all stick your heads
out like tortoises?
It's just that this tortoise did not
know that you live in this village.
I am very pleased to meet you.
What's your name?
Ruin.
What's the matter Adi?
- I thought marriage was ruin.
Ok. So what if it's not you.
There are other men who will
willingly die for me.
Hey, you mirchi (chili)
Here's a bitter gourd.
Eat it. You and your disciples.
Adi, what's she saying
& going away?
Don't put your lips to it.
She's quite bitter.
"As she walked, she said
your house was small"
"I left my songs behind.
Under the wings of a bird"
By the way, who is this girl who
just gave this shagun?
Why? Do you also want the shagun?
- No... no.
She talks a lot.
Quite a wily girl.
Listen Mister,
she's my daughter.
Daughter!
No, I meant she is very gifted.
Faux paus... I'm dead meat.
By the way... what is her name?
Boy, if you weren't a guest I would
have made mincemeat out of you.
Get lost... mannerless.
"And the water from the
pitcher overflowed"
"It overflowed, for the eyes
couldn't hold"
"Mother said don't go.
Brother said I didn't listen"
"Father said just one day more.
And the water overflowed"
"The crow said don't go.
So did the saint..."
"The crow said, just one day more.
And it overflowed"
Oh Ruin, I was looking for you.
Even my father is looking for you.
- Oh God... Escape!
You have a great smile.
I had heard that village girls are
very simple and innocent.
Shy!
Excuse me aunty! Here, she is both
simple and shy.
Great son! - Greetings.
"Father... I left your courtyard"
"Your courtyard...
I left it behind"
"When I come home next time,
bring a diamond ring"
"My friends will play with it
on their laps..."
"A bouncing bonny baby"
"When the monsoons come this time"
"Another kind of separation
will have its say..."
"Separation from my beloved"
RAILWAY COLONY, MUMBAI.
Close the book and
open your mouth and eat.
This way nothing will go in either
your mouth or your brain.
Oh mom, if I fail, you'll haul me
over burning coals.
No. I'll eat you raw.
The things your father has to
endure for your studies.
Please quit fighting.
- What else should I do?
Now, why are you not eating?
The paratha is so oily and
the yogurt is so sour.
Then, how come Dina ate it?
Oh God! Dina! Dina! Dina!
She's the only one you like.
The rest are all second rate.
Now, will you two stop it?
Mom, she has an exam today.
What should I do with this girl?
Hey, where're you going?
You carry your anger on the
tip of your tongue.
Once you become a doctor,
your patients will die without a hiccup.
If something happens to me,
don't ever take me to her.
This girl is a real burden.
So why don't you give me
away to him?
To whom?
He who believes that a girl
is a burden.
Do your exam well.
Dad! Good I met you.
Now my paper will go off well.
Your blessings are very important
for doing well.
Go via the temple.
Here, keep some money.
Dad, she sends others to the
temple for her.
You are so pretty.
One kiss on this cheek.
Your beard is hurting.
My beard hurts... let it.
Some things also hurt me...
Hurt me a lot.
Hi uncle. - Hi Pinks.
And rub yourself clean.
The smoke must have
clogged your pores.
Do you know what your son did yesterday?
- Why, is he not your son?
I saw him on a motorcycle...
with a long haired woman.
Both of them were in flames.
Even smoke was coming out
of their mouths.
Dad! Why are you beating about the bush?
Get to the point.
Mom, Dad saw me smoking a
cigarette yesterday.
Cigarette!
They were smoking a cigar.
A Peace pipe. He would take a drag
and pass it to her...
She would take a drag
and pass it back.
What a good for nothing. Son, I've.
Who was she? - Like a brother.
Adding glitter to the Gold.
She is just like a boy.
She must have been Meera, mom.
Even you scolded her for
talking like boys.
And if I smoked one cigarette,
what great sin have I committed?
You have done a great deed.
"It overflowed... the water from
the pitcher overflowed".
"It overflowed for the
eye couldn't hold".
You don't know anything about her...
And you want us to find one girl
in a population of 12 million.
What's the population of Bombay?
- 12 million.
How many of them will be women?
- 50%
6 million approximately.
Out of these 6 million, how many
would be college going?
Hardly 10%
- No no, less than that.
Let's assume 10% So how many is that?
- 600,000.
Out of these 600,000, how many
would be medical students?
So, she is a doctor. Lets say 1%
How many? How many?
600, no no no. 6000.
- Your maths is very weak.
Out of this 6000, how many
would travel in a local train?
Only in the city of Bombay?
Most would travel by car.
Leaving out buses, taxis and autos,
at least 1% will use local trains.
So, how many does that leave us with?
- Barely 60.
So, out of 60 medical students.
Is it so difficult... to search for
1 medical student?
Come quickly.
"Life is a pleasant journey"
She is looking at you.
"What happens tomorrow,
no one knows..."
"Sing and dance through your life...
don't bother what the world has to say"
Don't bother. Correct.
I think you are in love.
There is no such perversity in my mind.
- What do you mean?
I mean I have not lost my bearings.
All that is for the unoccupied.
Mister, this is not love.
This is lust.
It's also called desire or hunger.
Now repeat what I said.
Shut up Mr. Psychic.
Look son, after seeing this girl's body
once... you've lost your balance.
After seeing her gait... you've
forgotten where you are going,
Do you call this love?
So what do we call it?
- As a famous poet once said:
"What we call love is nothing
but a perversity of the mind"
What do you mean perversity?
In medical terms...
It means that your hormones
are working overtime.
Shut up.
In Hindi, that means keep your
nonsense to yourself.
Your face is saying it all.
- What?
That I've lost my bearing!?
It looks like there is a fire in you.
- Shut up.
"This life is a pleasant journey..."
Shut up Dina, let me sleep.
He's not here.
Get off the train.
Why don't you look on top.
Maybe he's dancing on the roof.
Very funny!
By the time you see him,
the train would have started.
Look there. Over there...
your lover boy.
Aren't you going to get off?
Hello!
Hi!
Who are you looking for?
- Nobody.
That girl there?
Whose taking off her...
Taking the clothes off the line?
Do you know her name?
Do you know how to whistle?
...Like this? Good.
You look like a decent man.
Make some noise...
What? - Accelerate your bike.
Dina
See. It worked.
What are you doing there?
Coming, I was just showing
him the way.
Poor thing, didn't know where to go.
Dina, are you coming up or not?
This life is a pleasant journey.
Where? - Who?
Why are you singing this song now?
Life is a pleasant journey.
Miss. Suhani, I miss you very much.
Morning, noon and night...
your face haunts me.
Either stop haunting me or tell me
what we both should do.
Miss. Suhani, I miss you very much.
Morning, noon and night...
your face haunts me.
Shut up Dina. He's mad.
He's even landed here.
- He's the same chap, isn't he?
Yes. The madman has come here also.
Excuse me.
Yes, I'll give her moral support.
Where are you going?
- Body Guard.
No, you come here. Come with me.
What's your name?
Aditya.
Are you after girls leaving
your studies behind?
Looks like your father has a
lot of money to waste.
Yeah. That's just,
what he says too.
How many times have you failed
in your class?
I haven't so far. But may be this time
it'll happen.
"Dear friend..."
"Your soft, lilting laughter"
"I heard it and drank it all up"
"May you always laugh like this,
and blush shyly"
"And light and darkness meet on the
nape of your neck, under your curls..."
"May your fragrant laughter grow
and envelop me..."
"Don't go in the garden dressed
in yellow sunshine"
"The bees will tease you,
so don't go among the flowers"
"Laugh softly again...
your beautiful laughter..."
"Lying on the lawn,
like freshly fallen leaves"
"There are seven hues in one sensuous
move of Spring"
"The rainy season... it's all you"
"Laugh season to season...
that soft laughter of yours"
"Dear friend..."
"Your soft lilting laugh"
"I heard it, and drank it all up"
"Come, let's roam around
in the blue skies sometime..."
"If we find a speck of cloud by chance,
let's shower it on earth"
"Your ear-ring is quivering...
somewhere morning has broken"
"Somewhere evening has fallen"
"In the shelter of your hair,
we will spend the night"
"Your jet-black eyes
hold a glint in them"
"In exchange for a smile from you
take this earth of mine..."
"And this sky too"
"Oh dear friend..."
"Your soft, lilting laughter...
dear, dear friend..."
"I heard it, and drank it all up"
"Snow has fallen in the valley..."
"Cuddled in white woolen"
"Snow has fallen in the valley,
and your laughter hummed through it"
"Cuddled in wool..."
"Talk and words come out as vapor"
"Hot, steaming vapor...
yet soft and gentle"
Who's speaking?
Tell him: Call Suhani
from no. 105
Call Suhani from No. 105.
Who's that? - This is Pinky.
Pinky? - He asks Pinky, who?
Tell him her friend's sister.
What work do you have with her?
Uncle wants to talk to her.
Brat. Say what I say.
- Brat, say what I say.
You shouldn't talk like that.
Say, go and tell Suhani...
that there is a call for her.
Why are you abusing the kid?
I am not abusing her, madam.
He is my nephew.
Give me the phone.
Uncle, my ten rupees.
You promised me.
Here. Now, run away.
Hi Jeevan Uncle, whose phone is it?
- It's some friend's, uncle.
Suhani? - You! Where did you get
my number from?
Listen, I have something to tell you.
- What?
Tomorrow there is a function
at our house.
Be here sharp at 9 am.
Me? Why me?
Why? Because you sing very well.
- So what?
Look, I am not asking you to come
with me to Khandala, am I?
I'm only asking you to come
for our family function.
But, why should I come
to your house?
Because if you don't come
to my house,
I will bring everyone
to your house.
You are mad.
You've totally lost it.
I am mad for you.
At least write down the address
of my mad house.
63, Silverine. - Listen.
At least listen to me.
OK, do you know Worli dairy?
Take a 'u-turn' from there...
Close to it is a garden,
our house is just next to that.
Adi? Who's this Adi in our house?
"Looking into my eyes..."
"meeting my gaze..."
"Looking into my eyes, betrayal and
deceit he gave me..."
"He held me captive
in his eyes"
"I lost all sense of myself.
I was in a trance..."
"He sure had cast a spell on me..."
"with a mere touch"
"Deceit and betrayal is what I saw him
overflowing with..."
"When he looked into my eyes..."
"when he looked into my eyes"
"He held me captive in his eyes"
Who are those girls?
She's the one I am going to marry.
Which one?
That one in the cream sari.
Adi, are you really going to
marry that girl?
Absolutely aunty. So far
we haven't fixed a date...
But, once it's fixed.
You will be the first to know.
Adi's marriage has been finalized.
Adi's engagement has been fixed.
She's Adi's fiancée.
Congratulations. - Congratulations.
You didn't tell us Aditya's marriage
has been fixed.
Who's, what has been fixed?
- Adi's... Marriage.
Really. With whom?
- With that girl.
The one in the cream sari.
Congratulations to you also.
She won't ask for any dowry,
I hope...
You are very amusing.
Yes.
Who's that?
I don't know.
- What do you mean?
Why did you say that
I am going to marry you?
When did I say that
you are marrying me?
I only said that
I am marrying you.
Did you ask me?
How can I? That is the work
of the elders in a family.
But if you are insisting, why don't I
ask you? Will you...? - Very Good.
Then tomorrow morning, I'll send mom
and dad over to your place...
Everything can be finalized there.
Why would I want to marry you?
No no no. You should ask,
why would I want to marry you?
Why?
Because...
What?
Should I...?
What is that?
What do you mean? - Yes
What do you mean...
- What do you mean...?
I love you... it means
I can do anything for you.
Can you jump from the
train for me?
Sure. As soon as it stops,
I'll jump off.
And as soon as you jump,
I'll marry.
It's simple.
Do you like him or not?
My final exams are approaching,
and then I have to intern.
And I have to prepare for my M.D.,
as well. I don't know.
But answer me.
Do you like him or not?
How can I? Before me, you have to
get married... we'll see after that.
Give me a straight, yes or no.
- No.
Alright, then, My way is clear.
Don't blame me later.
What do you mean?
Meaning, you don't like him
but I like him a lot.
What do you mean by that?
- Simple. L-like-him-a-lot.
So, you want to have your cake
and eat it too.
Dad, if there is a proposal from a
rich family, what would you do?
What?
- What are you muttering?
I am just asking.
If there is a proposal then...
What sort of a proposal?
- Obviously a marriage proposal.
Now, someone isn't gong to come
and get a rakhi tied from you.
If she is saying something,
let her finish it.
Dina, stop throwing the trump card.
I got a jack,
so I am throwing a jack.
Excuse me. I have to study.
It's your turn. - Yes.
A family is going to come with
a marriage proposal...
Not for me, for Suhani.
- All right, but who is it?
A barrister... his son is Aditya.
No one has sent any word.
They won't just land up just like that?
That's what I am doing.
Informing you.
Is this why we pawned our jewellery
and sent you to college?
Did we sent you to
college for this?
Mom, I haven't done anything.
Neither am I marrying... nor have I asked
anyone to come with a proposal.
If someone wants to pile on,
what can I do?
You must have done something.
Otherwise no one piles on
just like that.
Please, come in.
Barrister Om Sehgal.
Your bell is probably not working.
That's why, I had to use my hands.
I did call the electrician,
but he hasn't shown up.
How do you do?
- How do you do?
Please, come this way...
I hope you didn't have a problem
finding the house?
It was a bit of problem.
All these houses look so alike...
Like compartments of a train.
After all, it is a railway colony.
He loves to joke.
All middle class houses
look alike.
Maybe you have never seen them...
Come Suhani.
Sir, these are my daughters.
Dina and Suhani. Come in... Sit.
Both of them sing very beautifully.
I've heard them when they came home.
Really?
They've been brewing
their own broth quietly.
Times and customs are changing.
Parents today are just figureheads...
to endorse the wishes of their children.
These children do as they please, we no
longer have a say in anything.
Now, I told Aditya that I agree
that it's my money...
But the lungs are yours,
but where will he quit smoking?
By the way, between these two
which one is the one Aditya wants...
He is very forgetful by nature.
If I happen to overstay...
at my parent's house.
He'll ask me at the door
"Who are you?"
"Whom do you wish to see?"
Quite an entertaining man.
He must keep everyone
occupied at home.
Why don't you get some tea
for everyone?
Suhani is the younger one.
She and Adi are in love
with each other.
And the elder?
- Dina is the elder one.
She isn't married yet.
- Why?
Is she waiting for someone
who won't ask for dowry?
You are quite rude,
Sir, What do you think
my daughters are?
We might be poor, but we've brought
them up like princesses.
Please don't misunderstand me.
I was saying it's good...
That the girl's parents don't have to
worry about dowry now.
Anyway we don't expect anything...
from you.
No, if you have any expectations,
do tell us.
What expectations
can we have from you?
We don't have any from
our own son.
We've given him good education...
that's enough.
He's an adult now.
If he even picks up someone
from the street...
We cannot do anything about it.
One minute.
Do you think we are auctioning
our daughters on the roadside...
For the first available groom?
Dad, what are you saying?
- You keep quiet.
Mr. Advocate here can argue with
a magistrate...
But he does not know the courtesies
to talk to his in-laws to be.
You are unnecessarily
twisting the issue.
I did not mean that at all.
- There is nothing more to be said.
We do not want to marry our daughter
in your family.
What has happened hasn't happened with
either your consent or mine.
Let it be, this is no time
for sweets, let's go.
I'm glad we're under
no obligations.
Suhani... Listen...
What happened?
What had to happen has happened.
Let's finish this right here.
Dad went to meet your father.
What happened?
Yes, they met.
Like Musharraf met Vajpayee.
It was like reliving the Agra summit.
- This marriage is not between...
A Prime Minister and a President for the
decision to be taken in Parliament.
We have to marry.
It's for us to decide.
What will we decide?
By seeking their permission...
we showed them our respect.
The respect we got... from your
father is more than enough.
We don't want anymore.
So, my love for you comes
to nothing?
How long have you known me?
20 weeks?
They have nurtured me for 20 years.
I cannot leave them for you.
Suhani, I can leave everything
for you. Everything.
Today, you can leave
everything for me...
What is the guarantee that tomorrow you
will not leave me for another girl?
What is this inverted logic?
In the end... why do I have to
be the scapegoat?
Why are you making a mountain...
out of a molehill?
You saw me, chased me,
professed your love...
That's all. What if I had refused you
right in the beginning?
Then, I would have called it
your bad luck.
So, do that now.
Ok... ok... you were right
and I was wrong.
At least listen to me, Suhani.
Please. Just one minute.
See, what is the hurry to decide?
Give it some time.
10 days... Only one week...
till the 15th.
Think about it.
If you still think that...
How will one week change anything?
Just leave it.
Give it some time.
Anything can happen. Please.
I might fall in love
with someone else.
You love me, don't you?
Today 9.50 p. M Marine Lines Station
Going fine, sir.
How is Dr. Suhani?
We never get time to talk to her.
Before it's 5.30, she has already
left the hospital.
Is it?
This evening, I told her to wait for me.
I had some work.
I got delayed by 10 minutes and
she was nowhere to be found.
Sir, I'll talk to you later.
What happened? - He doesn't know.
She left the hospital at 5.30.
Call Rajee. She must have gone there.
She's just had a baby.
Hi Adi... long time no see.
You and Suhani don't come over often?
In a day or two.
And listen... - Ok, bye.
Aditya, this relationship
is not possible.
Lives don't change in 8 or 10 days.
And I heard that lives
change in a flash.
Mine didn't.
You didn't miss me at all?
No, there was no reason to.
And there is so much to do.
Household chores. Studies.
You want to think again?
- I've thought already.
Always stay like this.
How? Weeping?
Laughing.
How long will you evade it?
...I mean, the train?
How long will you avoid train?
I might even forget,
only if you let me.
Take it easy. It's a computer...
not your grandfather's typewriter.
Like Billu, even we'll have our days...
- Who's Billu?
Good old Bill Gates, who else?
You should come quickly to take
your calls, especially at night.
Uncle, your phone.
What are you doing?
What's the matter?
Has it got disconnected?
Then, why don't you talk?
I am not listening.
Who are you looking for?
- Do you know where Suhani is?
Hadn't you both broken up?
Broken up... yet...
Do you know where she is?
I've been looking for her for many days.
- She's gone.
Gone? - She's gone to the US.
US? - No, she has gone on
a Medical camp.
When is she returning?
- In 3 weeks.
3 weeks?
Three weeks is too long, isn't it?
What will you do with 2,000 rupees?
I am going out.
Where? Outside Bombay?
Yes... I'll be back soon.
What if your father finds out...?
Please handle him.
Are you going with Suhani?
To find her.
"The sky was barren"
"When I went in search of you,
my dear beloved"
"I walked many miserable miles.
"It's all such a waste"
"It's all a wasteland, so futile..."
"Let me meet my darling...
Let me meet, just once"
"O my dearest one,
I scanned the skies minutely..."
"and plucked the broken stars"
"This starlight till the dawn,
my eyes get no sleep"
"Just to hear your footfall..."
"I have even borne the silence of
the stones and the statues"
"I now find only dejection"
"Look at the fate that is
etched on my brow"
"Whenever I saw footprints,
I've bowed my head there"
"How many times must
I call out to you?"
"Your name is what
I find everywhere"
Why did you take so long to come?
I can't live without you...
not a single day.
Not a moment.
Can you do anything for me?
Should I jump off a moving train?
Marry me.
We'll marry and stay
in our own homes.
We won't tell anyone yet.
Not a soul? - No.
When the time is right,
we'll disclose it.
What happened?
What are you thinking?
I am very scared.
Never mind. Then, get married
in a state of scare.
Don't be silly.
I am really scared.
I'll give you one slap
and it will be alright.
I warned you 10 times.
Think before you say yes.
And every time you told me
to shut up.
I'm in a dilemma.
I've thought about this
very seriously.
If I felt it was wrong I would
never let you do it.
Now come on or you'll miss the bus.
Come on.
How come you're wearing
a sari today?
Isn't she looking pretty?
Of course.
But she suddenly looks like, it's time
for her to get married.
Why don't I get her married, then?
Let's hurry up.
We're sure to miss the bus...
We'll go by an auto.
Where are my princesses going
dressed like this?
We are getting late.
- I am glad I met you...
God bless you.
I'm late today.
Adi... which way are you going?
Why don't you carry on...?
Aren't you very late today?
Yes, we were discussing
the Gazdar case.
Where are you going in
such a hurry?
Close by... to meet a friend.
Get in, I'll drop you.
- No, it's OK.
Get in, you'll waste money on
a taxi otherwise. Sit down.
You haven't informed their
parents, have you?
No, just a few college friends.
Very good. I am tired of marrying
couples in the court.
We're crossing the court,
let's cross it fast.
And Mr. Aditya,
what's cooking nowadays?
Nothing at all, dad.
I am aware of everything
that is happening.
What?
You haven't completed
your law studies,
And you've started a
computer business.
Oh, that! - What oh...?
Where will you get the capital from?
The Bank is ready to give a loan.
- Really?
Only, if you sign the guarantee...
- Of course. It's your right.
We have a debt to repay to you.
Isn't it our duty?
Where is the groom?
This is going to be interesting.
Aditya, what are you doing
in a temple?
So, this is a temple?
- You don't believe in God.
So, what are you doing here?
You must have a reason.
What can I do, aunty? You have to
come here to get married.
Oh shut up! Anyway, God will
do his justice.
Does he do his justice
in English or in Hindi?
"O beloved..."
"Listen, my darling.
Listen my dearest"
"The moon will stealthily enter
through the window, barefoot"
"Listen, my beloved.
Listen my love"
Now, the fun starts.
My wife has gone and all I am left with
is a receipt for our marriage.
Have patience for a few days.
How many days? ...4... 5... 6...?
First, let Dina get married at least.
- Then, ask her to get married.
Why don't we get her married
next week itself?
First, let me finish my internship
and in the meanwhile...
You must establish your business.
- You are being so cold.
Do you know today is
our nuptial night?
Can we meet somewhere?
Right now, I am at
Jeevan uncle's stores...
Asking the rates for food grains.
- You are so unromantic. So unromantic!
What good night?
All alone...
It's a lonely night.
Remove your hand.
People are watching. - So what?
You are my legal wife.
Here's the certificate.
Why are you carrying this around?
- What can I do?
This is the only substitute I have.
Why are you going on and on with wife?
Wife...? Take off your hand.
Is she your wife?
- No, she is my life.
Sit properly.
This is a public bus.
Are you married?
- Yes, since 15 years.
I pity your husband.
Nothing...d
Suhani, there is a call for you.
What is it?
I told you I love you.
- I know.
Then, you should also know that
we both have the same address.
Yet, we are both so far.
Tell me, you love me.
Tell the doctor to check
his patients.
I say, hang up...
Sir, it's an emergency case.
We'll have to keep him
in intensive care.
He sounds a little mad.
She didn't say it? - Run.
Sorry. You had to wait for 2 hours.
To catch a glimpse of you,
I can wait for two lifetimes.
I've got to go. - No.
People are coming to see Dina.
- No.
"Come everyday to me
turn the night into a day"
"On the sly, under the
sheet of the night"
"Where even the moon can't approach"
"Let's go behind a cloud"
"Where every drop pines...
every drop is in turmoil"
"Where time stops still"
"Give us a hug under the
sheet of the night"
"In the warmth of the
winter's sunshine"
"Look at me with lowered eyes..."
"from behind your hand"
"Blow hot and cold. Ever so softly
in the raag Marva"
"Let not the day set.
Nor the night fall"
"Let not the sun set"
"And if it does, let not the
morning break"
"Let the night go on and on..."
"Lying to friends,
in somebody else's name"
"About you and me.
All through the night"
"You're away too long.
It's so difficult..."
"to just sign and be contented"
"When will the separation end?"
"Come every day to me and
turn the night into a day"
"Without you, this wind from the east
seems silly"
"It rushed into my scarf'
"You also come and embrace me
like this wind, some day"
"Come and embrace me,
like this wind..."
"Listen, dear friend"
"If I can't sleep tomorrow,
call me to you"
"Keep my head your lap
and sing me a lullaby"
"Hug me to you under the sheet of the night,
on the sly"
"Where even the moon can't approach.
Behind a cloud"
Dina, unlike me, is not so quiet.
She talks a lot.
She knows a lot.
Don't go by what she says.
Dina is very simple... very tolerant.
She has taken the responsibility
of the entire household and...
...she never complains. Isn't it?
In fact, it's the same case
with Raghu.
See, he hasn't even opened
his mouth so far.
Raghu... say something.
If you say yes...
For us everything is alright... Why?
- I am agreeable too.
But, you should ask Dina as well.
- Don't worry about that.
We called you only
when Dina said yes.
When you give your consent...
We'll get an auspicious date fixed.
And you've told that you're
not superstitious.
Can I say something
if you don't mind...?
Your younger daughter and my younger son
are both studying medicine.
What's it called?
Bio-Technology.
- Yes, Bio-Technology.
He's doing a Masters degree.
We haven't asked Kartik, but...
We'll ask him and
you ask your daughter.
If they agree then, its God's will.
Both brothers and sisters...
Can stay in the same house.
What are you saying, mom?
How can this be?
If it can, what's wrong with it?
It's like a yard sale.
Buy one, get one free.
We are not selling our daughters.
They haven't even asked for a dowry.
The boy is well educated.
This is a stroke of good fortune.
Why are you attaching my fortune with his?
- Speak softly.
Wear this. - What's wrong in
what I am wearing?
I won't do it.
Mom, I cannot marry.
It seems you're going to ruin
Dina's fortune. Wear this.
She got scared hearing about
her marriage.
Even, I'd gotten scared.
If I had any inclination that something
like this would happen,
I surely wouldn't have come.
But, that's how my father is.
Are you OK with it?
I am already married.
My parents don't know.
I married secretly in the court.
11.30 PM, Marine Lines Station.
Railway Colony, Mumbai.
Is Suhani here?
There is no one by that name here.
Get lost.
Where is Suhani?
Where is Dina?
- She's not at home.
I am asking you to tell me
where Suhani is.
What's happened to her?
I don't know.
She left the hospital at 5.
It's 11 now...
there is no news of her.
I've gone home twice.
There is no news of her.
So, where has she gone?
You must have said something to her.
22 years. Height 5 feet.
- And 2 inches!
Height 5 feet 2 inches.
Wearing a light brown Sari.
A doctor's coat, hand bag,
stethoscope.
Sir, there is a hospital
ID card as well.
Hospital ID-card. Yes, just check
and call me.
Uncle, are you going? - Yes.
Leaving home and going away?
- Yes.
She's the one who should cry,
whose marriage you have broken.
I don't want to marry.
Yes, why would you want to marry?
She is the one in a hurry
to get married.
The elder one is still unmarried and
the younger one has no patience.
In six months she'll be abandoned
and be on the streets.
Get lost. There is no place for
you in this house.
Be sensitive,
he's leaving the house.
Whose house? When was this his house?
This is my house.
Aditya, don't go away.
Anyone who is stopping him
can leave with him as well.
Get out.
Let it be.
Get out of my house.
From this day, we will have
no dealings with this house.
Promise me. We'll never show
our face to them again.
We both are enough for each other.
- OK.
Take me to the temple.
Why? Do you want to marry again?
- Shut up and get in.
Okay, let's go.
We carry the burdens of the world
on our heads.
What are you doing? Be careful.
- Thank you. At least you noticed.
The stove is a gift from me.
Buy yourself your own gas.
I can gift you a matchbox.
What is all this?
- It belongs to my brother.
Does he drink here?
All this will get shifted inside.
He'll drink in his section.
This part of the house
belongs to you.
Hey kids! There is a great advantage
in eloping with a girl.
The girl doesn't threaten to go back
to her parents every now and then.
That is true.
She won't threaten.
Yes, but there is also a problem.
- What's that?
Eloping with girls...
will become a habit and...
He'll keep running away
with all and sundry.
Did you weigh your profits and losses
when you eloped with aunty?
No, no. It was she who
made me run away.
Really? How did that happen?
I'd had a bit too much to drink.
I got emotional.
Let's go.
- There is some left...
What's the matter.
You seem to be very happy.
Excited?
"Soaring..."
"Are my dreams"
"my heart dreams...
of colourful nights"
"The light mist that
descended last night..."
"left my eyes brimming..."
"as it pattered on my hands"
"The joy of getting drenched in the
first rains of the season"
"I was drenched in the first rains,
without a regret..."
"all over town, without a regret"
"Like her plaits in knots,
coming free..."
"it poured all night"
"At times, coaxing.
At times, tormenting..."
"like the moods of my beloved"
"When I tease her out of love,
sometimes... she sulks"
"Even when I let go in
a fit of anger,
"I have a battle on my hands"
"Even if I simply kiss her,
I still have a battle to cope with"
"The light of my eyes
means the life to me..."
"in my eyes I preserve this life,
it's only for you..."
"Few are the moments of life
to spend them in disagreement"
"I have been through death to put
our fragile hearts together"
"Ask for anything and
I can present it to you"
"But, do consider... there are very
few stars in the sky anyway"
"The light of my eyes
means the life to me..."
"even though my eyes have often
seen a sweet bitterness..."
"this life, this life of mine..."
"without a regret..."
"all over town, without regret,
only for you"
"Like her plaits in knots,
coming free..."
"it poured all night"
"Coaxing, tormenting...
like the moods of my beloved"
"Soaring..."
"are my dreams"
"my heart dreams...
of colourful nights"
Don't see through your right eye.
It's inauspicious.
Where is the newspaper?
I have been waiting for 15 minutes.
Hoping that when you get up...
you will see me first.
And all you want is the paper.
OK, I've seen you.
Now, where is the paper?
At night you were making many promises.
What happened now?
Really? What was I saying?
- Liar.
You aren't worried about your wife
But, you want to know...
what's happening in Patna.
Please give me the paper.
- You won't get it.
You can't get your wife and
the news together.
Suhani, where's the paper?
But, what's happened in Patna?
- Riots have broken out.
Where is the paper?
Here's your hot news.
- What madness is this?
Hey kids! What's going on?
- Nothing.
Why are you burning the house?
All this won't do in someone else's house.
But, this is my house...
- How's it your own house...?
That will happen when you pay the rent.
What did you tell Pushy?
That you'd pay 5 months rent
in advance. Where is it?
I said on the 1st... - The 1st went by
long ago. What's the date today?
No, I meant the 1st of next month.
- Uncle, the tea is getting cold.
Do you want to mix it?
In front of this girl,
I cannot argue.
Poor thing has left her parents house.
- And poor me.
Even I have left my parents house.
- Left the house...?
You must have been thrown out.
- Uncle, have your tea.
Meera, what happened to
that Sintel file?
Bhaskar is working on
some more details.
Are you people following it up
properly or not?
Of course we are. But, there has been
no response from their side.
But, what is the problem?
Until their American Co-coordinators
don't approve the project...
The deal cannot progress.
- Show me the file.
No. Wrong number.
Some Anil Mehta.
I had gone to buy vegetables.
I've been waiting for you for an hour.
- Sorry.
If you were going to take that long,
you should've left the keys with someone.
With whom? Pushy Aunty?
And what if she'd asked
for the rent?
So, should I just keep sitting...
until her Excellency arrives?
Do you think I went for a stroll?
I had gone to shop for our dinner.
But, what's the idea of making me
sit like a guard?
Why are you splitting hairs?
Before marriage... you could wait for me
for hours at the station.
Did you become a ticket checker
because of that? Come on.
It was another thing then. - What?
How was it different then?
Open the door.
We weren't married then... that's why.
- No... yes...
And now we are married. So, you don't
care for me any longer?
When did I say that?
- But, that's what you implied.
Give me the key.
Don't change the topic.
Why don't you say it clearly...
that you don't need me anymore.
Now, why are you splitting hairs?
Give me the keys.
I won't give him any food.
Once he sleeps hungry,
he'll realize.
And remember this incident.
- And even you remember this... - What?
Every time you fight with me,
I'll keep on making up
with you like this.
Let go of me. Leave me.
Not right now. Get lost.
That's what you said before
marriage also.
Exactly. Because unlike you,
I've not changed after marriage.
Now, what is this?
The days that you fight with me.
I will mark the calendar. - Why?
To prove that getting married
is very risky business.
That is true. Considering the way
you fight with me at night...
And bite and claw me...
Should I show you the marks?
Do you want to see them?
The mood is pleasant...
What's it?
Are you trying to find me?
I am here.
Where is my mangalsutra?
Forget it, I am alive right here
and ready to be hugged.
You took it out at night
saying it pricks.
I am the symbol of your marriage.
Why don't you hug me?
You prick even more.
Where is my mangalsutra?
Aunty... she'll ask for the rent.
Leave me, you shameless!
How was it last night?
- What?
Dhansak. Did you not eat it?
- Oh that! That was great.
She cleaned up all of it.
Now, you don't even need to
clean the utensils.
Why don't you go and take the recipe
from Aunty this evening?
What is this mangalsutra
doing here?
Suhani, this should not be taken off.
- Yes.
I have been searching for
this all morning.
It has to be your doing.
You must have hidden it.
Why should I hide it?
I thought I should wear it.
Sometimes even the man should
look married.
How much sugar?
- One spoon.
Here comes our friend. Wait and see.
He's going to start a fight.
Wait for a minute.
How are you? - Fine.
Hello wife... how are you? Having tea?
- I'm fine.
I'll just be back.
As long as you don't start it.
Suhani, where is my
project report file?
Are you listening to me?
Where is my file?
I've told you so many times...
not to move my things around.
Why are you laughing...?
Please stop it. Don't inject him anymore.
- Suhani, take her out.
Please come with me... come.
- No, I won't go.
Come with me... Let the doctor
try at least.
He's here for the past 2 days...
Nothing has been done.
Suhani, what's there to eat?
I am very hungry.
What happened?
- Let me stay like this.
Everyone is looking.
- Let them.
What's embarrassing? I am your wife.
Are you embarrassed...
Be reasonable, let's go inside.
- Let your reasons be.
Can you not even ask me
what I've been through?
OK, I am sorry. I didn't know
what happened at the hospital,
I just thought...
Don't touch me.
- Are you an untouchable?
You could always sense
my mood on the phone.
Why are you so restless?
You always knew the minute
you saw me.
You used to call me twice a day
just to know how I was feeling.
Don't you remember?
- I remember.
In spite of living in the same city
and having a phone...
You used to send me telegrams
to cheer me up.
Where did all those things
got vanished?
I am still ready to do all that.
But, when will you grow up?
We aren't college students anymore.
We are responsible for each other.
Do people stop loving
after marriage?
Don't stare like that.
Did you even think of us or try to
find out if we are dead or alive?
Don't speak rudely, mother.
Not one day has passed...
when I've not missed you.
You could have come home also.
How could I have?
Don't you remember what you and dad
said when you threw me out.
Your father's tyranny will be
the end of us all.
Lying in the hospital...
- What's happened to dad?
I am not the doctor.
We've got a lot of tests done, but...
These tests are for jaundice.
Mom, I want to see dad.
If you come, he will be pleased.
We have come to call you.
But, don't tell him that we met.
Adi, Suhani is here.
Hi. What happened?
How come you didn't go to work?
Dad is in hospital...
can we go and meet him?
It was you who said that we will
not keep any links with anyone.
Now, what happened?
- Yes, but he is serious.
He's in the Railway Hospital.
- Who told you?
He's got jaundice.
He cannot be treated there.
But, who told you? - Mom and Dina.
I met them in the train.
They know where we live
and where I work.
But, they didn't think it necessary
to tell me.
It's not that.
Why do you think like that?
I still remember my promise.
But you are forgetting yours.
He spent his entire life's savings
to make me a doctor.
What good is my being a doctor if...a
Dr. Suhani, if your education is
compelling you, then you may go.
Neither am I a doctor nor
am I compelled in any way.
Why are you being indifferent?
Other than the two of you...
I have no one.
We are the only ones they have.
Suhani, I have not forgotten
his slap till today.
If you want to go, you may.
How's your father?
How do I know?.
Didn't you go?
How could I? I had promised.
Then, break the promise.
Let's go tomorrow.
What if he says something again?
When I've been slapped by him,
how does a little scolding matter?
Let's go tomorrow.
Behave yourself in front of dad.
And... - I'm wearing this for your dad.
Go fast - I am sorry. I am sorry.
- Take her there quickly.
What...? - Go home.?
Don't touch him.
Let his soul rest in peace.
No child would've given so much
pain to the parents.
Now, take your husband and
leave our house.
Mother...s
Daddy...
All my hopes are now pinned
on the Sintel project.
If we lose that then, we'll
have to close the shop.
With all the overheads...
Now, stop it please.
How long will you keep crying?
It's been so many days.
What should I do if
I feel like crying?
Had I not insisted on marrying,
all this would never have happened.
It was I who had insisted
on marrying secretly.
I was also so impatient.
If you are repenting it.
Why don't you leave me?
If I can live without my father,
I can live without you.
Leave me alone.
What should I say? - Just read what
is written. Come on try, please.
What if I get caught? Don't worry.
You just have to act a little.
Anyway, that's all you do
through out the day.
I'll slap you...
Hello! This is...
- Like a woman... shyly.
Dina Sharma.
Do you remember me?
Mr. Sharma's daughter... Dina?
Yes, Miss Dina! What a surprise!
How are you?
I am fine. I wanted to meet you once.
- Me? What for?
At 4 o'clock near the Kala Ghoda
parking lot...
Tomorrow.
Don't worry, I won't bite.
Can you connect me to Dina Sharma?
Miss Dina. Good morning,
this is Raghunath Pandit.
Maybe you didn't recognize me...
I recognize you very well.
What do you want from me?
I wanted to meet you.
Why? Was it not enough to
insult my family?
That's why... I mean... I want
to remove all doubts.
If you could meet me for 5 minutes...
Please... only for 5 minutes.
If you could meet me tomorrow at 4 P.M.
Near the Kala Ghoda parking lot,
I would be grateful.
Isn't that Raghu?
- It sure looks like him.
We were totally ruined after
that incident.
Dad passed away soon after.
But, why should it concern you... you...
I am sorry for what has happened.
But, it's unfair of you...
to blame me for all of it.
If that is your attitude...
why did you want to meet me?
Why did you call me here?
Excuse me, but it was you who
called me on the phone.
Otherwise, why would I have come?
The phone call was made by you.
I didn't even... do you think I had lost
it that I should have called you?
What do you think I am?
Looks like they are fighting.
Here is your coconut water.
I'm leaving.
Did you not call me... at the factory?
- Why should I?
You called me at the Bank.
I did speak to you and you did
ask me meet you here.
Maybe you are...
Oh God!
So this was your doing.
What do you think you are?
A matchmaker?
Do you want to start
a marriage bureau?
Actually... Your marriage broke up
because of us. So I felt that...
It's OK. Your intentions were good.
But, you didn't do well...
especially with Dina.
It's been 10 days since we
spoke to each other.
It's not unusual after marriage.
Look at Raj. Come.
We don't speak for months at end.
All our exchanges are
through servants.
I am beginning to feel that
Adi is tired of me.
Don't be stupid.
Everyone says that if Adi ever flirts...
with another girl,
He'll see you in her.
Is that any less worrisome?
How is it?
Looks like someone is very thirsty.
Why...
The other day when I was giving
you coconut water...
You were glaring at me.
Am I a matchmaker...?
I should start a marriage bureau.
I think after this success...
I should start one.
And when should we arrange for
the wedding bells to toll?
Raghu, will you come on
a white horse?
Or must I get a black train
booked for you?
The day after tomorrow,
they are coming home.
Then, you can book
your black trains.
What happened?
I wish Dad were still alive.
Have this coconut water and
stop the water from your eyes.
I have ordered food at home.
- What do you mean...?
Oh sorry! Those people didn't
have a place to party...
So, I called them here.
- I don't want to party.
Did you ask me? - I didn't check...
but Anju asked and I said yes.
Is Anju going to decide...
what is going to happen in my house?
You should ask me...
So many people and
so little common sense.
An open door opens like this
and not like this.
She'll just be here..
You were very scared of your parents
...how did they agree?
I had to smuggle her out...
- You are quite brave.
This is nothing. One day she took
Bhaskar to meet her parents.
You are quite an intelligent girl.
How did you ever get stuck
with this Bhaskar?
The same way I got stuck with her.
The minute I looked at her,
my mind started to wander.
You are a very
discouraging friend.
Get married first.
Then, you'll have to find out
the price of food grains.
Yes from Jeevan stores.
Suhani knows the rates quite well.
Remember...?
Men show their true colours
after marriage.
How's that?
Before marriage they are piling
on to you everywhere...
And after marriage they are
embarrassed to even hold you.
Does that really happen?
Yes. You are embarrassed
at your doing...
So the easy way out is a mangalsutra
to wear around the neck.
Before marriage every man
is special.
After marriage... he becomes
just another husband.
For me, Adi can never be ordinary.
I should have married you.
- What had to happen has happened.
You are tired of me now.
- What?
What were you saying?
Come on Suhani.
You know I was joking.
It didn't sound like a joke to me.
I've become stale.
Or have you started to
like someone else?
Stop this nonsense.
You never spoke like this
before marriage.
I am now.
Nothing has changed even now.
If you like someone else
you can go with her.
Now, where should I find
another destiny?
You were destined for me.
And now I have to break my head with
you throughout my life.
That's what you do best.
First, you taunt then you cry.
Do I trouble you so much?
What is my fault?
The fault is mine to have left
my parents for you.
Then, go back to them.
"A history of atrocities..."
"And yet, you claim authority"
"You take us by the hand
and hurt us"
"Good Heavens, no!"
"This is not done"
"A history of atrocities..."
"And it's blown out
of proportions"
"The lies in the world
now threaten my life"
"They're the ones who
inflict atrocities...
"And they're the ones who complain"
"Good Heavens, no!"
"This is not done"
"Friends..."
"How am I to spend a lifetime
misled by illusions?"
"If only I could take away
your illusions"
"Take away this affliction
of love too"
"Let that be... or else
how will you manage?"
"Your attitude, your involvement
shall lead us on"
"Life's a boat sailing
miles across the sea"
"We'll have to drown in it,
there's miles of sea ahead"
"A history of atrocities..."
"And the pot calling
the kettle black"
"The lies in the world
now threaten my life"
"They're the ones who inflict atrocities
and they're the ones who complain"
"Good Heavens, no!"
"This is not done"
I've been trying to find you for so long.
I searched everywhere for you.
Why? Is there something
very important?
Yes, it's important...
but now I am suddenly shy.
You... Dina...
I thought once things got
a little confirmed then...
You were hiding it from me.
Of course not. I wanted to meet
and tell you myself.
That's why, I'd stopped Aditya
from tell you anything.
Aditya... he knows about
two of you?
He's the one who brought
us together again. - Yes.
Dina, I've got to meet Aditya.
- Go and meet Aditya.
I have to go to Raghu's house.
- To meet your mother-in-law?
We've got the 90 million project
from Sintel software!
Hey, what are you watching?
Is this a Ramlila?
Hey you! Stop there.
Where are you going?
Sir, I have to go to the station.
Do I have to write it down for you?
Can't you hear me?
Sorry sir, Sorry.
You can't go from here.
There's been an accident.
Take a U-turn and go back.
- OK, sir,
Go on.
What are you doing?
Waiting for Suhani?
Like always.
If you'd married me, you wouldn't
have had to do all this.
If she doesn't come in
the next ten minutes...
We'll run away to a temple
and get married.
Let's go.
Is Suhani there?
- She has left already.
Did she say where she was going?
Are you sure she is not somewhere
in the hospital?
YASHWANT RAO I.A.S. RESIDENCE
What happened?
Who was driving? You?
What was the need to drive?
You don't even have a license.
Are you OK?
Did anyone else get hurt?
Did anyone?.
Tell me. Who was it?
- A girl.
How badly did she get hurt?
...Tell me...
Is she alive?
I don't know.
I got scared and ran away.
Good. It's all right. Did anyone
take her to the hospital?
Where did the accident happen?
Kennedy Bridge.
You relax. I'll go and
see what's happening.
Don't go.
- You go on inside.
Has an accident case from Kennedy
Bridge been reported today?
Yes, a girl has been admitted.
Is she your relative?
- What? Yes!
Inform Dr. Murthy and prepare
the O.T. You come with me.
Hurry up.
Doctor Khan, come to the
operation theatre. Quick.
Is she the one?
She is critical.
She has been hurt on her head.
Doctors can't operate on her until
someone takes her responsibility.
Give me the name.
- Yashwant Rao.
No, what's her name?
- Savitri.
Savitri. Savitri What?
- Savitri Rao.
How are you related to her?
Husband.
Oh Good. Come with me.
Some papers have to be signed.
Where are you coming from?
From the North.
Meaning? Are you coming from Kashmir?
No sir. North Bombay Society, Juhu.
And you...
- He is also... - Shut up!
What's your name?
- Aditya.
Where are you going?
My wife left home in the morning
and hasn't returned.
Have you lodged an FIR?
- Yes.
Have you checked the hospitals?
- What?
A girl met with an accident a little
distance from here.
Hospital...
Yes... Yes... I am speaking
from the hospital.
Because of the commotion I could
not report it earlier...
No, there is no need
to cover it up.
Let the law take its course.
I wanted... What...?
No, her relatives have not
been found yet...
Has an accident case of
a girl been reported?
When? - This evening...e
What's the name?
- Dr. Suhani. Suhani Sehgal.
There is no one by this name.
In an emergency case, they obviously
won't know the name.
Please check for a 22-23
year-old married woman.
Just a minute.
Mrs. Savitri Rao. Her husband is on
the phone over there.
His wife is in the trauma centre.
Is there any other?
- No.
Relax, Adi. I think we are
being too pessimistic.
Never mind. Let's go home.
Maybe she has reached home.
Inform me as soon as you
get some information.
Yes, I am at the Wadia hospital.
I'll talk to you later.
We cannot remove the clot
without a surgery.
Our area starts from this side
of the bridge...
If the blast is on that side...
Can't you see that I am
talking to someone?
I see that sir.
For the last half an hour...
You have been going from one side to
the other side of the bridge.
I'll call you back.
What is your problem?
Sir, it's been so long since
I lodged an FIR.
My wife is missing.
Have you found anything?
We'll tell you when we find out.
Now, go away.
Will the news travel to you?
Sir, at least make an attempt...
Make some enquiries.
You should know who she has
run away with.
Why are you wasting my time...?
How dare you assault a cop
inside a police station...?
How dare you talk about
my wife...?
Leave me. Let me go...
What if I don't leave it.
What can you do?
Even you'll be reported missing.
Sir, he's the son of
Barrister Seghal.
His wife has been missing
for so many hours...
I told you I'd take care of everything.
Why did you come here?
You are taking care... of me.
The surgery is over... but your wife
is still unconscious.
You'll have to wait.
I hope there is nothing to fear?
- She's still in coma...
We have located the FIR.
The girl's husband has lodged it.
His name is Aditya Sehgal.
It won't be difficult to trace.
You don't have to worry now.
Even he is tracing her frantically.
You both go home.
I'm here, isn't it?
No. We'll wait here. Once we have
handed this girl over...
Then, it's up to him.
What can the poor boy do
in this crisis?
Don't worry. Savitri didn't do
it deliberately.
It's an accident.
Whatever it is.
We'll wait here.
OK... I'll go and locate him then.
Is there a Aditya Sehgal among you?
- Yes. I am.
Aditya. Did you lodge an FIR
about your missing wife?
Yes... have you found anything?
- What was she wearing?
A light brown sari.
- Any watch or handbag?
Yes. A watch, a handbag, stethoscope.
I had lodged everything...
Come with me. - Where?
To your wife. Come on, sit inside.
Over there. She is in the ICU.
Suhani. Open your eyes.
You would talk throughout the day.
Now, why don't you speak?
Say something. Open your eyes.
Are you angry with me...
Please don't be...
Open your eyes.
Say something please...
Let us check...
That's the man whose car hit Suhani.
He's signed for the surgery as well.
How is she...?
You should pray... for yourself.
If anything happens to her...
I won't let you live in peace.
How did you hit her?
And why didn't you tell the police?
You were drinking and driving,
weren't you?
I won't let you get away.
It's not his fault.
Then, whose fault is it?
The one who is battling
for her life?
No harm will befall her. Before it does,
I will kill myself.
I hit her. It was my car.
Why should you be punished for that?
No harm will befall her.
There is a God above.
What we could do, we have done.
You can give us whatever punishment
you want to.
But, right now even we are praying
for your wife's recovery.
I know you are listening
to everything.
You are just pretending...
To trouble me... to fight with me.
Come now, get up. Right now.
Aren't you going to mark the
date on the calendar?
You didn't come home one day,
And everything is devastated...
How much I searched for you today...
I didn't search for you like this
even before marriage.
The truth is that today I have
understood our relationship.
For the first time I have
understood you. Found you.
Now, I can't lose you.
Till now I was only trying
to find myself.
Please come back...
Were you scared?
I just died.
What did you think?
That I'd let you flirt with
other women so easily?
What can you do for me?
Can you jump off a moving train?
SkyVision @ www.Funkyvilla.com Torrent Site
Never say this for fun also.