Subtitles synced by DISTEL.
Missings parts and songs synced
and translated by Bluerain_20.
Oh no!
You're out of tune.
Completely out of tune.
- What's up, Maestro? - A lifeless
voice can't sing in tune.
Sounds like she has a sore throat.
- What's wrong, Kiran?
- She needn't say. I know it all.
All these girls do nowadays
is to roam till late...
... at nights with friends.
She has shouted her voice hoarse.
And they'll eat whatever they like.
ls that a sign of love for music?
- That's going to get you nowhere.
- Please do not say so, maestro.
Tell us Kiran, d'you or don't you
want to master classical music?
You must devote yourself
completely to your lessons.
I'll be back after a few days.
Get over the sore throat by then.
Greetings, Sir.
- Does he have a problem with me?
- Never mind the daily dramatics.
Have you got the tickets
to the New Year's party?
I come before you, friends,
after giving my heart away,
with someone's face
before my eyes.
My beloved is the
killer of my heart.
I've become like
a vagabond for her.
She kissed me right
when she saw me,
but didn't look
back as she left.
And therefore, my
friends, I decided that...
I won't ever fall in love again.
Never again will I give
my heart to some girl.
She's given me such a
wound that it will never heal.
Now my heart will fear
every beautiful face.
I gave my soul and was wiped out.
Listen up, beauties,
this won't happen again!
Such a wound she's given me!
Juicy lips, cheeks that
beckon to the touch...
A sensuous gait,
that destroys a man.
Widened eyes... my heart races.
The ripeness of youth is
a fearsome force!
Deadly beauty,
poisonous coyness.
Oh my God, oh my God!
A beautiful body, a swaying
flower, but friends...
I gave my soul and was wiped out.
Listen up, beauties,
this won't happen again!
Such a wound she's given me!
Juicy lips, cheeks that
beckon to the touch...
A sensuous gait,
that destroys a man.
Widened eyes... my heart races.
The ripeness of youth is
a fearsome force!
Deadly beauty,
poisonous coyness.
Oh my God, oh my God!
If you asked me,
I would bring you the stars.
I would spread them at your feet.
Embracing you, I would
make your body blush.
Kissing your face, I'd
light you up like the sun.
I gave you my soul and was wiped out.
Who is going to love you so much?
You've given me such a
wound that it will never heal.
Now my heart will fear
every beautiful face.
Such a wound you have given me!
I come before you, friends,
after giving my heart away,
with someone's face
before my eyes.
No one else will be mine.
For this very reason, (my pain)
must somehow remain hidden.
A pack of biscuits and a bread.
Need anything more?
- No thanks. How much was that?
- Fifteen bucks.
Rohit Kumar, your neighbor upstairs,
screams his head off all day.
- Aren't your ears sore already?
- That's him rehearsing music.
And he loves music. Besides,
l am not irked to complain.
For God's sake!
How come you're so busy with your
accounts so early in the morning?
- Won't you sit down to a cuppa?
- Woe beside!
Rohit Kumar hasn't paid
me in 3 months now.
He gets me to make him new
dresses every now and then.
But just doesn't bother
to pay for the stitching.
He owes me a large sum too.
But I just can't complain.
Hey Kanhaiya! Come over
for a cup of tea.
Give it a rev.
It's all your fault.
You've given the house to a
tuppence worth of a singer on rent.
All you have for yourself
is a room in the backyard.
- Has he paid the rents yet? - He'll
pay up in due course. Fine fellow.
How are you, Rohit?
- Come over here, Qasim.
- ln a moment.
- I'm ravenous.
- What can I get you?
-2 fried eggs, buttered toasts, jam,
a special cup of tea. - Coming up.
Hello, Mr. Jamshed.
How d'you do?
- Forget niceties. Talk cash. - Some
bills are due for a couple of months.
Today's the first of the month.
I'll settle everything by the 30th.
Very well... er... what
did you say? By the 30th?
- Exactly. How many days between
the 30th and the first? - One day.
- There you are. - The number of
days between the 1st and the 30th...
- He's making a fool out of Jamshed.
- That's right.
Didn't you have a show last night?
How did it go?
- It was a riot! - Was it then?!
- The crowd went berserk as I sang.
And the girls were crazy about me.
There was this girl
who caught my eye.
She has beautiful eyes
and a pretty face.
- Fabulous! What happened later?
- She left after the program ended.
If she comes into my life, I'll
write the best songs on earth.
Dream you may.
But everyone cannot become Elvis.
Shut up Moolchand. You're a grocer.
What d'you know about music?
Someday Rohit Kumar will make the
greatest singer in our country.
No one even bothers to listen.
Look... it's Mehra. He's counting
the proceeds of the show last night.
- He made 50 to 60,000 last night.
- And we don't get a penny of it.
Happy New Year, Mr. Mehra.
What's so special about a New Year?
Just another day and another night.
Oh yes. But it was a grand
show last night, wasn't it?
- Well, average, I'd say.
- Average, d'you say? About that.
There! Look at the pile you made
last night. What are you up to?!
It's all because of me, Sir.
People come here to hear me sing.
- That's how you sake in the moolah.
- D'you take yourself for a star...
... just because I've put up
a couple of your portraits?
- You see, Sir. I am...
- You should be grateful to me!
Grateful for letting you sing
before such a large gathering!
Minstrels like you roam the
streets a dime-a-dozen.
And no one would even
care to give you tuppence.
You ingrate!
How dare you misbehave! You come
here to sing. Not to chase girls!
I'm not chasing her, Sir.
l was just...
- I'm responsible for the harangue.
- It's a part of my daily diet.
Now, what's it you were saying?
- I'd like to learn how to
sing from you. - From me?!
And, you wrote such a beautiful
song. I'm crazy about your song.
I can't think of anything else.
I couldn't sleep last night after
your show. I kept humming the tune.
- Neither did I sleep after
the show last night. - Why?
It is a new tune that
kept me up all the night.
Would you like to hear it?
The king fell in
love with the queen...
It was first love
at first sight.
The hearts of both were wounded...
by an arrowed glance,
that breached the hearts' walls.
The king fell in
love with the queen.
Such a beautiful song!
Songs like that are what I'd like
to sing. Not the classicals.
Please teach me how to
sing a song like that.
I'll work hard at it.
The king fell in
love with the queen.
It was first love
at first sight.
The hearts of both were wounded...
by an arrowed glance,
that breached the hearts' walls.
The king fell in
love with the queen...
Sometimes you meet
someone on the paths of love...
but it's not assured
that love will flourish.
Often the buds of desire...
are cut short before blooming.
Even so, who knows
why he did not agree...
His crazy heart
grew uncontrollably restless.
The king fell in
love with the queen.
He looked at the queen,
and met her gaze...
She looked away...
What else could she do?
She looked down...
and played with her bracelet.
The king cast such a spell...
that she eventually
reciprocated his love.
Why don't we get married, Kiran?
What?!
I've never thought about it.
- I've only think about one thing.
- What?
Music and my career. I want to make
the greatest singer of the land.
- That'll be difficult.
- Why?
Because that status has been booked
for me a long while ago.
What could be better for both of us?
We travel towards same goals. And
we could reach our goal together.
Tell me... will you marry me?
What brings you here?
- He's a famous singer. - I see.
So you are a singer, are you?
Actually, I'm a composer.
I write the songs I sing.
Classicals?
- Not classicals. I sing
lighter tunes. - How light?
- I don't think you understand.
- Please help me too.
I sing songs that strike a chord
in the heart.
And where do you sing such songs?
- Presently, I sing at a hotel.
- At a hotel?
One might as well sing at a hotel
as go around with a begging bowl.
As with wandering minstrels who
collect pence in tips if at all.
Enough. I have not come here
to discuss my careers.
So, what brings you here?
Excuse me, Kiran.
Stop, Rohit!
Listen to me...
I didn't invite Rohit so you
might insult him.
D'you take me for a fool? A look at
him and I know why you invited him.
Stop being foolish. Your marriage
has already been fixed.
- I'm in love with Rohit.
- Do you hear what she says?
You must consider the consequences.
This is not done.
The upbringing and education I've
given her all these years are a waste!
If you think so highly about my
upbringing and my education,...
... you should respect
my decisions too.
I have a feeling that he's a
cunning fellow. He's ensnaring you.
- You're still an innocent girl.
- I'm no innocent, mother.
And what does that make of you?
I'm an artist. And, he's an artist
too. You can't gauge our sentiments.
Don't I understand? An artist
my foot! A Bremen-town musician!
A good for nothing vagabond! And she
wants to marry him!
You'll get to know about
the realities in life in no time!
Don't you come back crying later on.
Our doors will have closed for you.
Just as well that you told me all
this. It'll help me take my decision.
I'm going to marry Rohit.
- I'll floor them at the audition
today. - May I accompany you?
It'll take me 2 minutes
to get dressed.
lsn't the plumber expected in today?
See you. Bye.
How are you going to climb four
stories in the condition you are?
But, this is your first recording.
And I wanted to be there with you.
I'm not recording for a film. Its
just a jingle for an advertisement.
When am I going to meet the right
people? When will I start working?
It's just a matter of a few more
months. What makes you so upright?
- Hello, Farida. Come in.
- What are you doing?
Nothing much. Just cooking.
- Like a cup of tea? - Why not?
- ls the tea brewed? - Yes.
I haven't seen you
around in 4 or 5 days.
- Have you been keeping well?
- Absolutely.
- What's the matter? You seem tense.
- Not at all. I'm perfectly fine.
How are your music
rehearsals going on?
l hardly find time outside household
chores. How am I to rehearse?
What of the career in music? Can you
immerse yourself so in the chores?
You must carve out some time
everyday for rehearsing.
Look at me... I must fetch Sonu
from school after I finish cooking.
I'll go and fetch Sonu... Yes. l
will. It doesn't really matter.
Will you please draw a bath for me?
Make it fast. I've to attend a party.
- What party? - Oh, there's
something I'd like you to know.
- I've dumped the job.
- Why?
l had enough of Mehra's abuses.
Besides, I want to move upwards.
- What's more, I met Gulbadan
Kumar today. - Gulbadan Kumar?!
Yes. He owns Prince Records. Its
really tough to get to meet him.
I walked into his office and sang
a few songs. He liked my voice.
He invited me to the party this
evening. Looks like I've made it.
- Just press these clothes for me,
will you? - I'm coming with you!
- What'll you do there? You'd get
bored. - No. I won't get bored.
- What about Sonu?
- Farida can put him to sleep.
All right. You can come along.
Get dressed in some good clothes.
Now. Take the clothes.
Press them quickly.
Congratulations, Mr. Gulbadan Kumar.
Ever since your company was formed...
-... music sales have grown manifold.
-It's the grace of The Divine Mother.
A double gold disc for the music
directors. Someday I'll get mine too.
l've recorded my voice on
a cassette... Rohit...!
l've recorded one of
my songs in a cassette.
- Will you please give it
to Gulbadan Kumar? - All right.
Hows the good lady? I greet you
in the name of The Divine Mother.
- Hello. - I'm Rohit Kumar.
- Of course, Mr. Rohit Kumar.
- Greetings! - Grand party.
- It's modest really.
- Have you listened to my cassette?
- Yes I did. - Did you like it?
- Very nice.
- Thank you, Sir. Thank you, Sir.
Glory be to The Divine Mother!
Congratulations, Mr. Gulbadan!
You're raking in gold discs.
Let's pose for a photograph.
- You're the biggest of them all.
- Not at all. - lsn't it, now?
It's the two of you, Messrs Amar &
Kaushik who are the most well known.
That's the magic of our music.
We've defined 6 super hit films.
- Our critics are now silenced.
- lndeed. lndeed, Mr. Gulbadan.
You must listen to the music
we've scored for our next film.
- The Divine Mother be praised. - We
recorded a song yesterday. Beautiful!
Which film is the song meant for?
Well... he's an upcoming artiste.
He's also a singer.
- Mr. Rahul Kumar.
- I'm Rohit Kumar, Sir.
Oh yes,... Mr. Rohit Kumar.
- Do you sing?
- Yes, Sir.
I see. For whom
have you sung till now?
- Nothing special yet. - Yes. Go on.
- I want to sing for you.- Of course.
- Don't forget to give my cassette.
- Oh yes. But, stop it now, will you?
- Yes... what is it?
- I'm not only a singer.
l've written a few songs too.
- And what are you?!
- A composer.
ln a country like ours, just
about anyone can turn a composer.
Call me up on Monday. If your
voice is worth it, you're made.
I'll come over on Monday
after giving you a call.
What more could you want?
Glory be to The Divine Mother.
- Mr. Gulbadan...
- Yes, Sir.
Why aren't you giving
him my cassette?
- I can't give the cassette now.
- Why?
- It was so difficult getting an
audition for myself. - So what?
How can I ask them to
audition my wife too?
They'll think I'm trying to
force my family down their throats.
- So, d'you feel that I'm imposing
myself upon you? - I never said that.
- That's what you meant! - I'm tired
and I don't want to get into a fight.
D'you mean to say that l
want to get into a fight?
Sonu is sleeping.
l'd only asked you to hand over
my cassette. Was it so difficult?
I haven't heard what you've recorded.
I don't even know what's in it.
I don't know if it's worth a hearing.
And, it was tough getting an audition.
Must I lose a chance by trying
to push your cassette?
An hour ago, you loved my voice.
Now, it isn't worth auditioning!
I don't mean that. One must practice
regularly to be able to sing properly.
Just another excuse! And I think l
understand you perfectly, Rohit.
You've been pursuing your career.
And all I get are flimsy excuses.
- Please don't scream.
- Why don't you say it plainly?
That I don't have the aesthetics.
That I should stop dreaming about...
...becoming a professional singer.
That's not what's going to be, Rohit.
I won't give up! And you for one,
cannot break my resolve! Get that?
I don't know why Rohit is doing
this. He mustn't do this to you.
- It's wrong on his part. - We've
finished our homework, Mother.
- May we go to play? - Make sure
you return soon. - All right.
You have the right to a career.
Why don't you discuss it with Rohit?
What are you doing here? I've been
looking for you so long.
- I had to discuss some
things with Farida. - What?
Besides Sonu is getting on my nerves.
Who is to take care of him?
I have to go to a rehearsal. Where
are my clothes? How about some food?
- I'm coming over. - And, where's
the file of my songs?
l've been looking for it all day.
I just can't find it.
l'd brought it down with me for my
practice session.
Why don't you just sit over here for
the rest of the day practicing!
- I said I'm coming. - Don't bother.
You can practice singing...
...for the rest of the day.
I'll feed myself at a restaurant.
- I'll look after the household too.
- Have I ever refused to do all that?
- What've you done? - Sorry, Mother.
- You've got my washing all dirty.
l've been at the laundry for 2 hours.
And I've asked you not to play here.
How many times have l
asked you not to play?!
What's up, Kiran? Why did you beat
him? What has he done?
He won't listen to me. And now,
he's got the laundry all dirty.
I'm sick and tired of chorus all day.
l've gone out of my mind.
We tread upon the same path, Kiran.
What could be better for both of us?
Open up, quickly.
Come on, hurry up.
Make sure to remember the day today.
We'll celebrate this day every year.
This is the day I've awaited forever.
The day on which my career commences!
Today was the day! Amar-Kaushik were
left speechless after I auditioned.
I'm singing the first song
for Pawan Chopra's new film.
I'm leaving, Rohit.
And they said that if this song
passes the muster while recording...
...I'll get to sing all the songs
for the film. I'm recording tomorrow.
- Want to come along?
- I said I'm leaving.
- Where are you going?
- Here are the keys to the house.
These are the rationing cards...and
here are the bills for the month.
l've paid all the bills.
You'll find the balance of the
money in the cupboard.
Here's the electricity bill. Make
sure you pay it up by the weekend.
I'm leaving you.
Wait a minute! What are you saying?
What's happened?
- Have I done anything wrong?
- No, you haven't. - What's it then?
- Tell me.
- Don't touch me!
- Just let me go. - But why are
you leaving? Say something!
Why don't you understand! It isn't
just an isolated something.
It might be my mistake too.
- Something is happening to me.
- What's this with you?
- I don't know! - It's nothing more
than a figment of your imagination.
-I must make a life for myself. -But
this and here, is what your life is!
Else, I'll go out of my mind.
So you want to walk out of this
marriage. But what of Sonu?
How can you walk out on him?
But, he's better off without me.
Oh God! I don't believe this! Kiran!
Why are you doing this to me?!
l've just got my golden chance. And
here you are...walking out on me!
I need you, Kiran. If you stand by
me, I can even reach for the stars.
But you had told me that we'd reach
out for the stars together.
D'you feel that I'm trying to stop
you from becoming a singer?
You might dream of becoming a singer.
But don't expect me to go around
singing false praises for you.
I lost my head. I agree that both
of us have made mistakes.
But that doesn't mean that you must
walk out of your home. lsn't that so?
We can always mend our ways.
Now, come in.
Now you're being stubborn. Just
like your parents.
-Don't drag my parents into this.
-Why not? You carry the same traits.
Now, are you going to stop
taunting my parents?!
Won't l! They haven't been able to
achieve anything in life.
And they're jealous of others.
- And d'you think I'm jealous of
your success? - Yes!
Thank you very much.
I won't ever forget that.
l'd rather suffer my traits than
your taunts for the rest of my life.
Where has Kiran gone?
- What I should be asking you?
- Why me?
Because she used to spend more than
half her working hours in your company.
And the two of you must've more than
discussed my weak points.
Forget all that. Kiran has left you.
- We must do something about it.
- Not ''we''. It's I who has to do.
And I'll do whatever must be done.
You must try to understand it now
or never. Kiran is very unhappy.
- And the fact is that...
- Fact remains that of the past 6 years...
... I've been trying heart and soul
to get a break...
... so that my career can take off;
so that my life shapes up!
After 6 long years, I get a break.
I'm slated to sing for Amar-Kaushik!
I took a cab home as soon as I got
to know; so that I could...
... share the greatest moment of
my life with her.
And she tells me that she's
walking out of my life.
- What does it mean?! - She couldn't
share the greatest moment of your life.
- It's your life, after all.
- You're fantastic!
That your husband deserted you
because you were unhappy...
... doesn't mean that every woman
is unhappy with her husband.
I haven't come here to discuss my
husband. I'm concerned about Kiran.
- You may keep your concern within
your confines. - I shall.
Before I leave, let me tell you that
you could never understand Kiran.
She is no petty woman to serve as
a part of your interior decor.
She had her own dreams. And it
takes courage for a woman to walk out.
Yes! And it takes more to walk out
on a helpless child. lsn't that so?
- Why are you sleeping here?
- Oh.. what? - And where's Mummy?
- Tell me... Where's Mummy?
- What's the time now?
The small hand is on 7.
And the big hand is on 3.
I'm going to be late
for the recording.
- Tell me, Daddy... where's Mummy?
- Wait a minute.
- You mother has gone to your aunt's.
- Which aunt?
-The one in Pune. -Aunt Ratna lives
there. - That's where she has gone.
- When is she going to come back?
- Very soon.. in 3 or 4 days.
Now make a move.
l've got to get ready.
- Who's going to get me ready
for school? - I will, son.
- And, who'll pack my school bag?
- I will.
- Who'll take me to school?
- What about my breakfast? - l...
what do you eat for breakfast?
An omelette of 2 eggs, toast with
butter and Bournvita.
A dash of coriander... and onions.
Ever had one of my omelets?
- No.
- Try it today. You'll love it.
- You're cutting them in such
large chunks! - That's just fine.
lsn't this fun! Yes, it's fun.
Now, take a look at this.. a circus
with one hand... two eggs in one hand!
Now take a look at how I break
both eggs using one hand.
The eggs had soft-shells.
But never mind.
This place is perfectly clean.
What are you doing?
I'm not going to eat that!
- It has shells in it. - A few
shells will make the omelette crisp.
- Here go the onions... and the
chilies. - Not that way! - How else?
Mummy used to flip the
ingredients first.
What Mummy doesn't know is that an
omelette is an omelette, flip or flap!
Eat it and you'll know. Later on,
I'll drop you at the school.
And afterwards, I'm off to record
my first song ever!
Your Daddy is going to
become a famous singer.
- What's up?
- The toast is burning!
Well, never mind that.
You don't know a thing!
Go on in... hurry.
Go inside.
- Who'll come to pick me up?
- I'll come.
Where are you going to
wait for me?
I'll wait for you under this tree,
okay? Now go on inside.
- What if you don't turn up?
- I said I'll come. And, I will.
- What if you're late? - I won't
be late. I'll be here on time.
- What if you're still late? - If
I am, you can wait under the tree.
Go on, now. Hurry.
- When does the school get over?
- No idea.
When does the junior school
get over?
- I'm that child's father.
- At 2 o'clock.
- I'm sorry to be late.
- ls this your idea of time?
You've turned a star even before
you've recorded a single song.
-I got stuck in the traffic. - Never
mind. Sit inside and get the lines.
We'll record the orchestra in the
meantime. Let's have another take.
- Give him his lines, will you?
- Come on for the break in your life.
- We can fit the 16 tracks on to 12.
- Very well. Let's try.
Let's have the rhythm.
Still waiting here? I'm afraid
we won't be recording you today.
- Sir...?
- lncrease the bass slightly.
- When will I record?
- After a couple of days perhaps.
Do keep calling to find out.
I'm late by only half-an-hour.
Must you be so upset?
- You said you'd be here on time.
- I did. But I was so busy.
- What if someone kidnapped me?
- But no one did?
What if someone did?
l've told ten times that
I'm sorry.
You must forgive
someone who apologizes.
Do you know the meaning
of the word ''sorry''?
What are you doing?
What's up?
This car run on batteries. It has a
horn. And, the headlights work too.
- So what?
- I'll forgive you if you buy me one.
What if I don't? Won't
you forgive me ever?
Had it been Mummy, she would've got
the car for me.
Ask your mother for one when she
comes back. Now, let's go. Come on.
Sunil, be quiet, please.
It's late. It's time to sleep.
Let's go to bed.
I already knew, already knew!
Look what you did!
Sit there!
Did not I tell you to be quiet?
I'm tired of telling you not
not to play on the table.
Well you can apologize.
After all, who gives you a bath?
You.
Who gives you food?
It's you.
Who takes you to school and picks you up?
You.
And who is buying you ice cream?
It's you.
And this is how you thank me for everything
I do for you? You spoil me all my work!
I already apologized.
It was the song I was composing.
And now it's spoiled!
I'll have to do it all over again.
I already apologized.
I know you're very angry.
But you do not have
to yell at me so much.
Get up, brush your teeth, put on
your pyjamas and go to bed.
- 250 grams of lentil... anything
else? - A packet of tea.
- The Red Label, or the Yellow?
- Yellow. - Not Yellow. The Red one.
- Why? - Because Mummy used to buy
the Red Label. - Give me red.
A pack of soap and coconut oil.
- Can I have a chocolate?
- Take these upstairs.
Forgive me for asking this... but l
heard something. ls it true?
I heard that your wife left your...
no, I mean to say that she didn't...
... care for you. She didn't care
for the child. Nor her status!
Let me have this package.
And I didn't like her either.
She used to have this temper.
Have I asked you what you liked
or disliked about my wife?
- No, I mean...
- Have I asked for your opinion?
I come here to buy groceries. Not
to listen to your useless banter.
- Do you understand?
- Understood. Here's your stuff.
That's worth 300. The balance last
month was 350, totaling 650 bucks.
- And I've stopped giving credit.
- I'm not asking for it.
Here's your money. 550.. and I'm
sending 100 bucks for you right away.
That's the credit.
- ls that all right, Mr. Manohar?
- Yes. Let's record it.
Thank you, Mr. Sharma for letting
my friend sing in the chorus.
- She'll even sing a lead part if
you let her do it. - Of course.
Shall we proceed, Mr. Manohar?
Take a look at this!
A letter from Mummy.
A letter from Mummy! Here!
- I see... it's addressed to you.
- Oh yes! It is.
Read it, quickly. And tell me when
Mummy is coming home.
- Read it aloud.
- Oh, yes.
''My dear Sunil...''
''You must be wondering where your
Mummy has gone all of a sudden.''
''Let me explain this... sometimes
your Daddy had to leave home.''
''And then, it was Mummy
who looked after you.''
''Sometimes, when mothers leave,
fathers have to look after children.''
''Your Mummy wants to make a
career for herself, Sunil.''
''That's why I had to
leave your home.''
''I may not live with you anymore.
But, you'll remain in my heart.''
''Don't ever think that
Mummy will forget you.''
''I remain your Mummy always.
And I'll love you always.''
''Take care of yourself. And, on
your way back from school everyday...''
That was marvelous. Ms. Vandana.
And you must concentrate, Rohit.
I want the right perspective
in your voice.
Don't sing in a stifled voice.
Open your voice up.
That's my file, Sir. It contains
the songs I have written.
Don't be afraid.
We won't steal your tunes.
No! I didn't mean that.
Let's proceed with another take.
Let's have a rehearsal without
the music accompaniment.
That's a lot of crap! Let's have
some real voice. Haven't you eaten?
- Go on... sing it.
- Yes, Sir.
Forget about turning a music
director and concentrate on singing.
- I'll ruin his happiness.
- Why! We have a composer!
- Go on.
- Yes, Sir.
Nonsense! Forget it. Please sing
his lines for him, Ms. Vandana.
- Well done, Ms. Vandana. Excellent.
- Did you get an idea of the tune?
- That's what I've been singing.
- Sing it properly! - Yes, Sir.
What are you doing! You're out
of tune! What are you up to?!
- Please let me finish my lines.
- Shut up!
- If you interrupt, you can't
appreciate the singing. - Shut up!
0-Please listen to me. -Bloody fool!
Shut up! Who d'you think you are?
Stay within your limits!
Else I'll throw you out of here.
And, I'll banish you forever
from filmdom.
Will a singer in a night club to
teach me how to compose music?!
- Yes. I can.
- What! What was it you said?!
Oh yes! I'll teach you how to score
music right away.
That is, if you may dare
to listen to me.
lsn't this how you've composed it?
lsn't that your song?
Now listen to this.
Please play along with me.
What are you up to, Sunil?
Be quiet and eat your food.
Pick up your spoon.
Go on. Eat.
It's yucky. It's bell plant and
it's very good for you. Go on, eat it.
-I don't like bell plants. -You do.
Aunt Farida has cooked it for you.
And you've eaten it earlier.
- What's all this black stuff
in this? - Onions. Now eat it.
-Onions give me stomachaches. -Not
at all. And now start with the bread.
- It's Yucky.
- You mustn't call food ''yucky''.
Don't spit on your plate.
Where are your manners?
Go on. Eat it now.
There... I've removed the onions.
There's this chocolate ice-cream
you've brought. It's in the fridge.
Yes I know about the ice cream.
But, you won't get any of it.
You must finish your food first.
Only afterwards you may eat it.
Sunil!... Where are you going?
Don't you open the fridge!
Now don't take the ice-cream out
of the fridge.
Can't you hear me? I'm getting
very angry with this now.
Don't take the ice cream.
I'm warning you, Sunil.
I'm warning you.
Don't you dare eat that ice cream.
Eat the ice-cream and you'll face
dire consequences. D'you understand?
Get up. Now!
And let go of the chair.
You unmannered boy!
And stop screaming.
- I want to got to Mummy!
- Enough of it.
No food for you. Nor any ice cream.
You can go to sleep hungry.
I won't talk to you ever again.
He's asleep.
Will you leave me and go away too?
- Never.
- But Mummy left me and went away.
- That's because I'm a bad boy.
- ls that what you think?
That isn't true. Mummy loves you.
She didn't leave because of you.
She left because
I couldn't understand her.
I wanted her to do what all other
mothers do all their lives...
... tending the family and doing
household chores.
But she wanted to do something else.
And she tried to reason with me.
But I was too involved
with my life and myself.
And do you know why she
stayed back so long with us?
That's because she loved you, son.
She didn't leave us because of you.
She left because of me.
Now, go to sleep.
Let's start a new life from
tomorrow... you and me.
I'm alone, you're alone.
When we're together,
then there is no sorrow.
You're my heart, you're my life.
Oh I love you daddy!
You are innocent,
you are mischievous...
But you love me daddy!
A little boy you are for sure...
but you're the leader of all.
And due to these mischiefs...
I'm loved by everyone!
This is said by
thousands of people...
But there is no one like you.
I'm alone, you're alone.
When we're together,
then there is no sorrow.
You're my heart, you're my life.
Oh I love you daddy!
You are innocent,
you are mischievous...
But you love me daddy!
Just imagine,
if tomorrow this entire world...
doesn't stand by my side.
Then who'll be the companion
of my journey?
It'll be me, daddy!
Everything seems
so beautiful today...
our world, our moments.
I'm alone, you're alone.
When we're together,
then there is no sorrow.
You're my heart, you're my life.
Oh I love you daddy!
You are innocent,
you are mischievous...
But you love me daddy!
- Let's have another ride. - No.
I'm tired. Go on. Play by yourself.
You've changed so completely, Rohit.
I only wish Kiran should've
seen you in these spirits.
- Don't talk about Kiran.
- Very well.
- Tell me the truth... don't you
ever think about her? - Not at all.
Look at me, Daddy!
- Don't do that, Sunil.
- No! It's my turn now!
- Don't you think about your husband?
- His case was quite different.
- He had started having an affair.
- Really? I had no idea. Who was it?
He had this girl in his office. And
my Romeo wanted to bring her home.
What nonsense!
Look at me now, Daddy!
I'm coming down standing up!
- No, Sonu. What are you up to?
Get down. - I'll get him down.
- What happened afterwards? - I told
him he was free to do what he liked.
But I wouldn't let go of the house.
It's for my children and me.
- No! Sonu!
- Watch your step, Sonu!
What's happened, Sonu?!
Take him to a hospital. Hurry!
Nothing's going to happen to you,
Sonu. You're going to be all right.
I'll treat you
to ice creams afterwards.
I'm Ravinder Kapoor. I'm the chief
assistant director in RP Films.
- I see. - I have come
here for a sound transfer.
I saw your friend all of a sudden.
She's very good.
My director wants a smart girl as he
is about to shoot an important scene.
The role is that of a friend
to the leading lady.
No. Not stand-by.
You don't know Mr. Kapoor.
That's right. Mr. Paresh Kapoor.
- You must've seen his film last
year. - Yes. - It was a super hit.
It's still raking in royalties.
- How many days is she to work
at it? - It's only a day's shoot.
- But...
- How much money will she make?
2000. And I'll make sure she
gets 100 bucks as conveyance.
- I'll speak to her about it.
- Please do try. I'll wait for you.
l've dumped Sunju.
He says that I'm selfish.
He asked me why I went to see
a film when he was sick.
I couldn't bore myself sitting
by him all evening; now could l?
Have I done anything wrong?
Tell me, Anjali... have
I done anything wrong?
You were supposed to
deliver your lines.
Don't you remember your lines?
Will she be able to
deliver the lines?
You wanted someone simple and
innocent. She'll deliver all right.
Didn't I tell you that I don't
know anything about acting?
All you have to do
is to my your lines.
Tell me, Anjali...
What have I done wrong?
You haven't done
the right thing, Deepa.
D'you remember how anxious he
was when you had fallen sick?
He kept by you and cared
for you like a man possessed.
And you can't even spare
an evening for him!
You call that boredom.
The truth is that you've
never even understood Sunju.
He loves you very much.
She's going on saying
whatever she wants to.
l'd told you earlier that l
know nothing about acting.
I tried it at my friend's instance.
I really want to become a singer.
- Very well... you may sing some.
- Sir...?!
- Please listen to the songs I've
scored. - I've helped you already.
I introduced you to Amar Kaushik.
And you've disgraced me.
- They started misbehaving with me.
- Will they really misbehave?
- You see, Mr.Gulbadan. - You see,
Mr. Rohit, I merely run...
.. a small-time music company. We
only publish records and cassettes.
I'm not a film producer.
Now, please excuse me.
- I'll be back in a minute.
- Please take your time.
One minute, Mr. Rohit.
I can help you sell your songs.
Amar Kaushik needs new tunes.
I'll get you 2000 for each tune.
- Here's my card. - So they get
the credit for my compositions.
Why bother about the credit?
You want me to give you a job so
you can walk out on me again.
That won't happen ever again. I beg
your pardon. Please give me a chance.
- lsn't that, Mrs. Kiran?
- Yes. She's Rohit Kumar's wife.
- She's made a heroine in films.
- She used to sing.
And now, she's up to
dancing in public.
Come quickly, Dad.
Take a look... over there.
It's Mummy's picture.
They put up the posters today.
I want to see Mummy's film. You'll
take me to see it, won't you?
You'll take me, won't you, Daddy?...
Won't you, Daddy? Please tell me.
How are we to see Mummy's film now?
It's a ''house-full'' show.
Let's go home.
I want to see Mummy's film! You'd
promised to show me Mummy's film.
I want to see Mummy's film at once!
Hurry up, Daddy.
How come you're here?
No one is allowed up here.
He wants to see how his Mummy's film
is projected. I spoke to the manager.
-ls he Ms. Kiran's son? -Yes. -Very
well. You can sit here and see it.
''Tell me... what can
you do for my sake''
''I can do just about
anything for your sake.''
''I'd get the sun, the moon
and the stars for you.''
''I'd bring the heavens and
earth together for your sake.''
- What's the matter, honey? - I'd
rather love a straightforward fellow.
''You needn't bring the sun, moon,
nor the stars into this.''
''You can take your rotten son back
to America with you.''
'' Before you leave, try some
delicious lndian cakes.''
Can you tell us how you are feeling
right now, Mrs. Kiran?
I'm happy to see that the audiences
have liked my performance.
- Would you like to work again with
Paresh Kapoor? - Yes, of course.
Any plans for the future?
What kind of films would you like?
- I haven't thought about it. - We
hear that you are Mrs. Kiran Kumar.
- It's said that you're married, and
that you have a son. Who said that?
Don't ask vulgar questions. And now
you've had enough. Please step aside.
Come along, Kiran. Let's go.
- Has Mummy forgotten me, Daddy?
- No.- Then why didn't she stop?
Why didn't she talk to me?
- Can I go to see her sometime?
- No. - Why not?
Did you see those stars?
They shine, merrily, but they are
far away from us.
Your Mummy is now like a star. You
can see her and long for her.
But you can't go anywhere near her.
Come on...Let's go home.
Then, my Mummy goes to a forest.
She comes across a
huge fellow in the forest.
My Mummy bashes him up.
- Go upstairs, Sunil.
- After a minute, please, Daddy.
Then the hero comes, and sings a
song with my Mummy.
-My mummy's very beautiful.-Really?
-She's more beautiful than yours.
Beautiful she is. But, she's more
stubborn than she's beautiful.
Why don't you go over to her, patch
up and bring her back?
If I go to her now, she'll think
that I've come because she's a star.
Forget her. ln any case, it was she
who left me. I didn't desert her.
- She can return if she wants to.
- And you're very stubborn too.
We've finished the cola.
Hey Moolchand!
- What's up? - 2 Colas please.
- I've closed for the day.
Down the shutter.
-Open up if you've closed down. - Am
I to stay open all night for you?
If you're so interested, you could
walk a block to fetch it.
- Why don't you fetch some for us?
- Am I your servant?
- Forget him. He's an illiterate.
- What?! An illiterate, am l?!
Did you call me an illiterate?
Oh yes. I am an illiterate. And l
know exactly what I am. Unlike you.
You sing in a rotten nightclubs and
think you're no less than Elvis.
He calls me an illiterate! And he
sits drinking in front of his son.
You couldn't even take care of your
wife. And he is lording it over me!
You bloody! What
did you say about my wife?!
- No! Don't!
- What did you say about my wife?!
I'll break your face! I will!
- Let go! And you! Get lost!
- Don't you dare touch me!- Get lost?
- Let's go! Just come back here...
and I'll show you! - Don't fight!
Go home, Moolchand!
And you're a strange fellow. Must
you pick up a fight with such a scum?
- Bad fellow! Come on, let's have
a drink. - No, he spoilt my mood.
Come home, Sunil.
What's it with you, now?
Hey! I just fell down.
Let's squat here for sometime.
- Why do you drink rum, Daddy?
- What did you know about rum?
I know everything.
Rum is an alcoholic drink.
One day, a drunk came
to the gates of our school.
The kids at school were
teasing him and poking fun at him.
And everyone threw stones at him.
I don't want anyone
to make fun of you.
Do you love me so much?
I love you very much too. I love
you more than anyone else on earth.
If you love me so much,
you must stop drinking.
From now on, I won't drink.
There's this fatso in our class.
Deven. He bullies everyone around.
He snatched Prakash's lunch box
away. I complained to the teacher.
Why complain? Box him in the
stomach. That'll do him right.
- Well, what will you do to him?
- I'll box him in the stomach.
Go on now.
I'll be back to take you home.
I was passing by when
I saw the two of you.
Sonu was looking quite cheerful.
I'd thought I'd
call you up sometime.
But I decided that it'd be better
if I met you personally.
How are you?
I'm fine, and I don't have much
to worry about. How have you been?
- Are you very forlorn, Daddy?
- No, I'm not. Why do you ask?
Nothing particularly. Are you
thinking about Mummy?
Go to sleep now.
My heart says, go, meet her!
But my feet stop as
they start to move forward.
Sometimes my heart
gets the better of me...
Sometimes I try to control it.
My heart says, go, meet him!
But my feet stop as
they start to move forward.
Sometimes my heart
gets the better of me...
Sometimes I try to control it.
My beloved, since
we have separated,
I have everything with
me in my life.
A lot of wealth...
A lot of fame.
But after losing you I feel that...
I don't have anything
if you're not here.
You don't know how many...
regrets I have in my heart.
Sometimes my heart
gets the better of me...
Sometimes I try to control it.
How beautiful were those days...
when we were together.
And I could embrace you.
It was just you in
my days and nights...
But you are so far
above me, my beloved...
That I can't even touch you.
It's impossible to reach you.
Just thinking about it
makes me so miserable.
Sometimes my heart
gets the better of me...
Sometimes I try to control it.
My heart says, go, meet him!
But my feet stop as
they start to move forward.
- Take a look at this!
- What's up? - Read it!
- Read..? -Read it..see who
wrote it! - One Pawan Malhotra.
- The film director! - Didn't he
direct CHAHAT?-That's him all right!
He has signed me up to score the
music for his forthcoming film.
- What are saying?! - Really?!
- Yes! And I can't believe it!
Pawan Malhotra patted
my shoulder and said...
''You're a very talented fellow!
How come I didn't meet you before?''
He liked my songs very much!
Thank God for that.
And congratulations!
Hey Moolchand!
Take a look at this!
Get that?!
All right. Understood.
So you've got money!
When are you going to pay me up?
I haven't yet received money.
I've just signed the contract.
I'll get the money soon. Let's
celebrate with tea for everyone.
- Very well..er..What do you mean?
- It's on me, of course.
-You should've said so. Come on in.
-I'll have a cup of tea too!
Are you going to become the
greatest music director now?
That I'll become. But, do you know
what I'm going to do before that?
- What? - Your birthday is coming up,
isn't it. - Oh yes.
- I'll get you a surprise gift
for your birthday. - Really?
- Yes. - What's it going to be?
- How can I tell you about it now?
I know what! lsn't it something
I showed you the other day?
ls it yellow in color?
The battery operated car!
- Where does Mr. Rohit Kumar live?
- I'm Rohit Kumar.
Ms. Kiran has sent this for you.
It's Mummy's car!
Hey folks! Come on quick! Take a
look at this. It's my Mummy's car!
What's it?
It's a letter from Kiran.
She wants to celebrate Sonu's
birthday. She has invited us over.
You'll go over, won't you?
You should go over.
Tell her that we will come.
But, there's no need to sent the car.
You mustn't be naughty, Sonu.
And you must speak to everyone
politely, understand?
- Are you listening to me?
- Yes. Okay.
If anyone offers you anything
to eat, don't be greedy.
Refuse it politely. But if you
must have it, say thanks afterwards.
Sonu has arrived.
- I hope we aren't late.
- No problem.
- I was worried that you wouldn't
come. - But, I have come.
Let me introduce you... my wife,
Lajwanti...and,...Mrs. Tolaram.
- Sorry for leaving you alone for a
while. - Only a while, wasn't it?
- I get childish when I'm with kids.
- You've always been childish.
Sonu is still cheating at
the game. He's just like you!
You're looking lovely.
Come over here for a moment, Kiran.
I'll be back in a moment.
Won't you meet others around?
We have other guests too.
Have you invited everyone to watch
you prancing with that fellow?
-I'll leave this party if you speak
so. - You must consider your status.
- You're a star. And, journalists
are attending. - Who invited them?
I wanted to celebrate a birthday.
You've made a circus out of it.
Don't teach me what to do
and what not to.
As of now, just stay away from him.
We have other guests here too.
- Happy tidings, Mr. Ramdayal.
- Thank you.
Happy tidings to you too.
- What's up? Any problem?
- Nothing at all.
They might not have taken
a liking to my presence.
- I should've sent Sonu here alone.
- But why? I wanted you to come too.
I wanted all of us to celebrate
Sonu's birthday together.
I've taken a lot of pains to organize
this party. And now, these people...
... they've spoilt my mood.
- I've asked you not to run around!
- Hey fatso! You won't catch me!
- Let me go! He'll catch me! Let him.
- I got caught because of you!
That's just as well. Now you can
sit with Mummy for a while.
My child!
- What's that mark? - I was playing
on the side. And I fell down.
-Oh no! -And it bled a lot. -Did
it take stitches? - Yes 8 stitches.
- How did it happen? - My mistake. l
wasn't careful. And he didn't listen.
It didn't hurt his eyes, thank God!
I could never have forgiven myself.
- And I didn't even cry.
- Really?
- Come on, Mummy. I want to see
your house. - Let's go.
- Come along too, will you?
- No. Just go on. - All right.
- See you later.
- Excuse us.
- Greetings.
- Have you had the cakes and other
goodies? - Yes I have, thank you.
- Had enough?
- Not yet. I'll have some more.
- Seen the villa?
- Yes. It's a huge one.
-It stretches right up to the beach.
-There's a swimming pool back there.
- I see! - It cost a million bucks.
- Fantastic.
- Are you still at song-and-dance
at the hotel? - Well, you see...
- Glory be to The Divine mother.
- Greetings, Mr.Gulbadan Kumar.
Greetings. Happy tidings
on your son's birthday.
I'm very upset with him, I am!
Tell me, is this any way to behave?!
You're the sole object of discussion
in the film business nowadays.
He has scored such lovely songs; and
he has put Amar Kaushik to shame!
Well, you've become
a very important person nowadays.
But you mustn't forget simple folks
like me. Do call up once in a while.
- Never mind that. But you must
get me the music rights. - Sure.
- Together, we'll make a stupendous
success out of it. - Surely.
Divine Mother be praised! A heroine
and a music director in the family!
No dearth of money! I suggest you
become a film producer. Say what?!
- Excuse me. - Oh yes.
- Be back soon.
- How many films have you signed?
- Just one till now.
You'll get many more, I'm sure.
But take care about signing films.
- What'd you like to have? Whisky
or rum? - I've stopped drinking.
May The Divine Mother bless you!
A Coca-cola for the gentleman, please.
Hello there! Nowadays, you don't
seem to care for us.
That isn't the case at all.
ln fact, we were discussing you.
After all, he has rising star with
him. Mr. Rohit Kumar!
The singer and composer.
A two-in-one!
Congratulations!
So even you've got a film!
What I don't understand is how he
bagged the film.
Because there still are people
who value caliber. Not names.
I see! But I think that behind
every successful man lies a woman.
But slightly different in this case;
..a successful woman behind the man!
- What do you mean? - Can a woman
who is beautiful and successful...
- ...not do as much for her husband?
- Surely she can do!
- What nonsense are you speaking?
- Do you think Pawan Malhotra has...
... signed you because he
likes your rotten songs?
- We were supposed to sign this film.
- You've got it because of your wife.
Don't believe it, d'you? Why! It's
commonplace. Come here, Mr. Tolaram.
- Come here, Mr. Tolaram. - Yes.
Come here. - What's up, gentlemen?
- Tell him... go on! Tell him how he
has landed this film. - Oh forget it!
- Go on, speak up. Tell him! - He
has scored some very good songs.
- To hell with the songs! You had
signed us. - Well yes, I did...
- On his wife's say-so, you threw us
out! Correct? - Nothing of the sort!
- She had merely...
- D'you hear that, Mister two-in-one?
It happens dear. Everything goes
in this business.
- People do use their good-looking
wives too. - Oh yes. They do.
Look...look at what's going on
over there. Go on... over there.
Someone bashes me up... and you're
trying to patch up! What's going on?
That's true! He couldn't cook
anything. Not even eggs!
Really?! How is it now? Nowadays
he has picked up a few things.
He makes a dish out of potatoes
now and then. Of potatoes?! Yes.
Sometimes, there are excess of
turmeric in it. But, I make do.
Oh hello, Rohit. Come in.
- Go downstairs, Sunil. - One minute
please, daddy, I want to tell mummy...
- I asked you to go downstairs!
- What's up, Rohit?
Wait for me downstairs.
Did you speak to Pawan Malhotra
about me?
Did you ask him to replace me with
Amar Kaushik as a music director?
- Why are you asking me this?
- Did you tell him, or, didn't you?
Give me an answer, Kiran.
Yes.
- Why?
- Because I wanted to help you.
I don't want your help!
I don't want anyone's help!
- Won't I succeed without your help?
- That's not the case, Rohit.
D'you want to prove that you're so
big that you can make anyone?
I've never thought of it that way,
Rohit. I did it because...
... I know that you can score
better music than those fellows.
That's what I wanted to prove
on my own.
And now, you've spoiled everything.
People will say that I've succeeded
because my wife helped me.
My success will never be mine!
- I can't do it! - Tell Pawan
Malhotra that I won't do this film!
Don't lose your head, Rohit.
Pawan Malhotra liked your music.
That's why he has signed you.
I haven't forced him to.
What does it matter if a few
people tell you a lot of nonsense?
I'm your wife.
If I don't help you, who else will?
I see! So can you walk out on me,
or come to my aid at your sweet will?
You don't want to help me. You just
want to show off your magnanimity.
You want to show me how
small I am, compared to you.
And you want to show your concern
for me though you live apart.
You've always thought ill of me.
You've always got me wrong.
Why must I try to understand
you in the first place?
I don't want to understand you.
Nor do I want to see you ever!
Don't ever try to meet me again!
Stop! Rohit!
- Don't step inside this house ever
again! - Listen to me! Please!
Come to your senses!
I already know why you
argued with me at the party.
She intends to start over
with that man again.
It took only a few minutes with him
to want to ruin everything again.
Don't ever think about it.
Do not think I'll allow it. I won't.
What's going on in this girl's head?
Leave her alone. She must
be tired. Let's go. - No!
I want to hear from her mouth that
she'll never see him again.
How did all this come here?
Look, Daddy! My birthday
presents! Mummy sent these over.
This is a military jeep. It turns
around whenever it collides.
Look! Here's a remote control car.
Why can't we live in
Mummy's house?
- Don't you like this house? - This
home is fine, but... - What of it?
But her house is so big...
and it's so nice.
She has 3 TV sets. We don't
have a single one.
What did Mummy tell you at
this party yesterday?
- She said that she loves me very
much. - What did you tell her?
That she's the best
Mummy on earth.
So now you want to live with
Mummy, do you?
- I'm asking you something.
- Do you know something?
Mummy is going to buy
the battery-operated car for me.
-Did you ask her for it?
-No, I just told her that I like it.
She said that she'd buy it for me.
Why did you have to ask her for it?
I was supposed to buy it for you.
- You haven't got it yet.
- But l was to get it for your birthday.
- And now, my birthday is gone.
- All right. I know that.
I'll get you that car today.
Understood? I'll get
it today! For you.
My car is coming today!
- How much does that car cost?
- 5000 Rupees. - 5000?! - Yes.
- It's a bit too much for that car.
- Fixed price. Take it or leave it.
- An advance of 5000 Rupees?!
- I need the money, Sir.
So you need all of 5000 Rupees!
D'you hear that, Mr. Godwill?
You may deduct a thousand rupees
every month out of my salary.
- lt'd be adjusted within 5 months.
- Will you be here for 5 months?
Seems like you've got a chance
to sing in some third rate film.
- And now, you're looking for chance
to give me the slip. - No, Sir.
That isn't the case at all!
I've forgotten these dreams.
The only person I have to
myself is my 6 year old son.
Yesterday was his birthday.
And I had promised him a gift.
A gift... worth 5000 bucks!
D'you hear that. Mr. Godwill?! I've
never given a single gift to my son.
And my good man wants to give a
gift worth 5000 bucks to his son!
You've spun a good spiel. But, I'm
not one to be taken in my your story.
- Please try to understand...- Don't
waste my time. And back to work!
Let's get working. We don't have
a circus happening here, do we?
- So you won't let me have the
money will you? - Not at all.
What are you doing?! I'll call
the police! Stop him, Godwill!
What hooliganism is this?
Put it down on my account.
Stop him!
Catch him!
Snatch the money from him!
Know something, aunt Farida? Daddy
is getting me a battery-powered car.
ls that so?
That's good news, I say.
- It's getting late. Time to have
dinner. - I won't eat now.
- I'll eat when Daddy comes home.
- No knowing when he'll return.
I must go home and get my
kids to do their homework.
- Go on... eat your dinner quickly.
- No. I won't eat now.
Very well. I'm leaving the food
here. Eat it when you feel hungry.
When did you return?
I didn't even get to know!
Where's the car, Daddy?
- Why haven't you eaten yet?
- I was waiting for you.
You mustn't stay awake so late.
I don't like this at all.
I was waiting so we
could eat together.
- What's happened, Daddy? - I lost
my son. I have lost. - Don't cry.
- Please don't cry, Daddy.
- My son asked me for only one thing.
And I couldn't get it for him.
This is the worst defeat in my life.
I don't want that car, Daddy.
Really... I don't want it.
Here... I have some money.
And I'm going to get more.
And I'm going to get
that car for you.
But, please stop
drinking, Daddy. Please.
I'll get that car for you, Sonu.
I will.
- Mr. Pawan Malhotra has summoned
me here. - Please follow me.
Please forgive me, Rohit. I've had
you summoned here using the alias.
Else, you wouldn't have come.
- I want to discuss something.
- ls anything worth discussing?
Please sit down, Rohit.
You had told me something the other
day. All I want to know is whether...
... it is your final decision.
- Why?
- Are you still firm about not
meeting me ever again? - Absolutely.
- ln that ease, I want my son.
- What was it you said?!
- I want Sonu to live with me.
- You want Sonu! lncredible!
How could you even think of it?
You left him when he needed you.
- D'you want me to... - You haven't
seen him in a year and a half.
You haven't even asked if he's dead
or alive. And now you want him!
-Sonu needs me. He'll be happy with
me. - And, isn't he happy with me?
Now wait a minute! D'you mean to
say that I can't keep him happy?
- I didn't say so. - D'you think you
can give him more happiness...
... because you're wealthy? - Please
don't shout, Rohit.- Why mustn't l!
- I'm his mother. And you can't deny
my right. - Neither can you mine!
I'm his father.
And he stays with me.
I'd even go to court to get Sonu.
Well, how do I play that?
Just like Daddy, don't l?
I'm sorry for having
touched the piano, Daddy.
ln terms of this notice,
Ms. Kiran seeks a divorce from you.
And, she wants that the child
be placed in her custody.
- All I want is my son. - I'll tell
you something before I take the case.
ln such cases, the decision
generally favors the mother.
I have been parenting him
for nearly two years now.
- She had abandoned the child.
- Yet, Ms. Kiran remains the mother.
Besides, she's a successful woman.
You don't have a job. That's worse.
You'd have to pay for court fees and
mine to the extent of 50 or 60,000.
That's irrespective of whether you
win or lose. D'you have the money?
- Yes. Please prepare the brief.
- Very well.
You may come here on Wednesday at
10 am. We'll discuss the case.
- Please bring 20,000 towards
expenses in advance - All right.
-I can pay 15,000 for all these
instruments.- 15000 only! How come?!
The piano is worth at least 20,000.
I'd bought it for 30,000.
I should get at least 40,000
for all the instruments.
This is business for me. I should
be able to earn a bit out of this.
- Well, give me at least 25,000.
- I can't pay more than 15,000.
- Very well, you may leave.
- You seem to be cross with me, Sir.
- We don't want to sell. Now, please
leave.- It's yours, do as you please.
- Please leave.
- Excuse me, gentleman.
What a waste of time!
Why did they call me at all?
Have you gone out of your mind?
Can a junk dealer appreciate these?
You're worrying for nothing. Sell
my furniture to raise the money.
No. You've already
done so much for me.
- I'll sell my songs.
- Sell your songs?!
- To whom?
- To Amar Kaushik.
You've really gone
out of your mind.
- He's willing to pay me 1000 for
every song. - Who gets the credit?
- They get the credits.
- You mustn't do such a thing.
These are fruits of your labor.
They're your hopes, your dreams.
How can you give that
away to someone?
Your songs are beautiful, Rohit.
You must get credit for these songs.
That's what I thought too.
I thought my songs were beautiful.
But, I've tried for so many years.
And, no one seems to like them.
And, at long last, I think
I have been entirely wrong.
- My songs might really be worthless.
- I don't agree to that.
-You're making a big mistake, Rohit.
- I may be. But, if in exchange...
... for these, I can have Sonu,
then these songs are priceless.
Else, these are no more than
scribbling on paper.
Why did you break my heart?
Why did we fall in love?
Why did you go away?
Away... away...
Why did you steal my heart?
If you wanted to break it.
Why did you fall in love with me?
If you wanted
to turn away from me.
Why did you break my heart?
Why did we fall in love?
Why did you go away?
Away... away...
You taught my heart how to beat.
You taught my heart
how to writhe in pain.
There were hidden
tears in my eyes.
But you taught them
how to brim over.
Why did you settle
into my heart?
If you just wanted
to toy with my affections.
Why did you fall in love with me?
If you wanted
to turn away from me.
Why did you steal my heart?
Whenever our gazes met...
I felt as if my heart
was on fire.
As if smoke was coming
out from my breaths.
I was not able to
live and neither die.
Why did you start a fire?
If you wanted to leave
without putting it out.
Why did you fall in love with me?
If you wanted
to turn away from me.
The filmfare award for the Best
music director, this year for...
... the song DlL MERA CHURAYA
KYON goes to Amar Kaushik.
Mr. Rohit Kumar's attorney
has sent me this letter today.
He has agreed
to divorce Ms. Kiran.
But he has refused the prayer to
place Ms. Kiran's son Sunil Kumar...
... under her custody. The case
therefore rests upon the contention...
... as to who may have custody of
the child. Before arguing the case...
-... I'll present some witnesses.
- This lawyer is a tough one.
I shall speak the truth, and
nothing but the truth.
Can you tell the court something
about your daughter, Mrs. Ramdayal?
My daughter is a simple girl, and
has all the qualities of a girl...
... who has had a respectable
upbringing. She's an obedient girl.
Why then, did she marry Rohit
Kumar against your wishes?
That's the only mistake she has
committed in all her life.
And, she's still suffering for
her mistake.
This man had treated her so cruelly
that she was forced to leave his...
... house at midnight. - Thank you
Mrs. Ramdayal. You may step down.
Can you tell the court about Rohit
Kumar's character, Mr. Ramdayal?
What can I say about a man who
has no character?
He's a scoundrel; and he's wayward.
You mustn't consider his appearance.
He inveigled my daughter using
those looks, and with his words.
- Really?! - He claimed to be
a singer of great caliber.
And he said that he was going to
become a famous music director.
He's still where he was.
And look at my daughter!
She came out, and now, she's so
successful. And we don't want...
... Sonu to live with him, because
the boy will turn wayward.
Has Rohit Kumar ever shied away
from fulfilling his responsibilities?
- No. - Has he ever tried
to shirk responsibility? - No.
- Has he been negligent towards his
son? - Never. ln fact, he spends...
... most of his time with his son.
He plays with the boy; amuses him;...
... reads stories to him and takes
him outdoors. Sunil is his very life.
I've seen very few fathers who would
do as much for their children.
Thank you very much, Mrs. Farida.
- For how many years have you known
Mrs. Kiran? - Some 7 years now.
Has Ms. Kiran ever told you
about her personal life?
Questions about Ms. Kiran's personal
life may be addressed to her only.
- Did she tell you anything about
her personal life. - Yes. - What?
- She was unhappy.
- With whom was she unhappy?
- She was unhappy about Rohit.
- Did Ms. Kiran ever tell you...
... that Rohit Kumar doesn't
care about his son at all?
Please reply, Ms. Farida.
I haven't yet heard you.
-Yes. But, that had happened before
Kiran left. - Maybe. But he...
...didn't care about his son at all.
Now, Ms. Farida, can you tell me...
...if you ever advised Ms. Kiran
to break away? - No. I did not.
3 days before she walked out,
did you not tell her that:...
''If you are so unhappy, it'd
be better for you to leave''?
Yes. But I never thought that she'd
really do something like that.
''If you are so unhappy, it'd be
better for you to leave Rohit''
Kiran was a good friend. And, I was
concerned about her. I still am.
- And whatever I told her...
- Was born out of your feeling that...
... had Kiran lived on with Rohit,
she would've gone mad or could've...
... had a nervous breakdown, or she
may have even been driven to suicide.
-But l... -D'you want an innocent
child to live with such a man!
You're making a big mistake, Kiran.
Rohit has changed completely.
He is no more what he used to be.
Listen to me, Kiran. Please!
Don't take Sonu away from Rohit.
He needs Sunil. Without him...
Please don't do this to him.
If you do not step down, it will be
regarded as a contempt of this court.
I can't quite understand how you're
going about this case, Mr. Bhatija.
At this rate, we're going to lose.
... out of the way, please.
Our witnesses are saying the truth.
And her lawyer is twisting facts.
D'you want me to tell lies too?
Must I stoop to Bhojwani's level?
D'you want me to raise a stink
over Ms. Kiran's personal life?
Am I to prove that she's deranged?
Must I accuse her of adultery?
- But that isn't true!
- Are you concerned about the truth?
Or, do you want your son? Tell me.
I'll handle the case accordingly.
I can present false witnesses as he
does. Do you want me to do that?
No. Do it honestly.
Look at her now. She has done well
for herself. She's the ideal woman.
My next witness is
Mr. Moolchand Gangar.
- Where did he transpire from?
- I have no idea.
- Who is he?
- The grocer in my neighborhood.
- We don't get along too well.
- You haven't told me about him.
- ls your shop located under
Rohit Kumar's residence? - Exactly.
- ln that case, you might be knowing
Rohit well. - Very well indeed.
- I've heard that he buys groceries
from your shop on credit. - Always.
- He might also be settling your
dues. - No. - Doesn't he?!
Why then do you still let him
enjoy your credit?
I allow credits to everyone.
You buy from me and you get credit.
Did you threaten to lodge a
complaint with the police, when...
... he had gotten drunk and
beaten you up?
If I told tales about your wife,
you would've bashed are up too.
Does it mean that you aren't
a good man?
It's not a question of being good or
bad. It's more a matter of intent.
- Now, did he pay you up after
the incident? - No, he didn't.
Now how does a man run his
household under the circumstances?
- How can such a person look after
his son? - You mean his son, Sunil?
- Yes. - He'd give his life for
Sunil. He loves his son very much.
He loves his son more than
I can ever love my son.
Love can't satiate hunger. And what
can one who has wrecked his home...
... provide for his son? - Rohit
Kumar has not wrecked his own family.
It's she... that woman sitting over
there? She has wrecked the family!
Please answer questions put to you.
Do not try to give a verdict.
Forgive me if I have erred. This is
my first ever appearance in court.
-I came here because he summoned me.
-You may leave now.
What you say is true. I've hated
Rohit Kumar for not repaying me.
I've even quarreled with him
for my money.
But my money isn't the bone of
contention. This is about his son.
You asked me what he'd do for his
son. Well, he has sold himself!
It might be easy for Ms. Kiran to
foot the bill for this lawsuit.
She's a famous heroine.
And she has loads of money.
But, it wasn't easy for Rohit.
Do you know what he did for his son?
He sold his life's savings...
his music... to Amar Kaushik.
They are now taking credit
for his music.
-Rohit Kumar must've told you that.
-No he didn't. But I know better.
I've heard all his songs so often,
it's still coming out of my ears.
The song ''RAJ A KO RANl SE
PYAR HO GAYA''... it's Rohit's.
I'm telling you the truth! The song
wasn't written by Amar Kaushik.
- Do you love your son?
- Yes. I love him dearly.
Why did you leave him?
He used to think that
I'll remain a failure.
It ruined my confidence.
I became fatalistic about
my failures.
I was confused, and I started
losing my confidence.
I felt stifled and confused.
I was scared. And I left my home.
Then, I'd thought it better
for Sunil's sake
not to take him along.
Why then do you seek custody of
your son now?
I know I had deserted him.
I can never forgive myself
for the mistake.
But, the situation has changed.
And, I am confident of myself.
I can look after Sonu very well.
After all I reared him for 5 years.
Must my child be taken away from me
because I've been away for 2 years?
He needs me now.
But I don't say that
he doesn't need his father.
But, he's still a child. He needs a
mother more than he needs a father.
And, I'm his mother.
I'm his mother!
You've spent nearly 6 years
with your husband.
- Has he ever manhandled you?
- No. He hasn't.
- Did he use abusive language?
- No.
- Has he ever ill-treated your son?
- Do you regard your husband
to be a drunkard? - No.
Has he ever had relations with other
women...in the nature of infidelity?
- No. - Then, the reason for your
desertion becomes amply clear.
With whom did you have the longest
lasting relationship before marriage?
- With my parents. - And you spent
some 22 years with them. - Yes.
But, you married Rohit Kumar
against their wishes. Right?
Yes. That's because I loved Rohit.
With whom, apart your parents have
you shared the longest relationship?
- With my son Sunil, I think.
- You spent 5 years with him.
And you've met him only
once afterwards!
Now consider your husband.
Don't you think you've shared a...
... very long relationship with him?
I didn't hear you, Ms. Kiran.
- Yes. - And how many years in
all, prior to your marriage...
... and afterwards have you shared
this relationship with him?
- Nearly 7 years. - 7 years!
Which means that you have failed...
...to sustain a relationship by
marriage, a social institution...
... that is held holy and of
irrevocable bondage in our culture!
- Please state your reply, Ms.Kiran.
- Tell us, Ms.Kiran...
D'you agree that you've failed
to sustain the relationship.
- No, I didn't fail. - Didn't you?!
Would you rate this as a success?
- Your marriage is on the rocks.
- We have failed each other.
Not ''both of us'', Ms.Kiran.
It's you. You have failed!
You walked out on your husband.
He didn't. You failed the relationship.
- It's the marriage which failed.
- Not the marriage. You failed!
You've failed to sustain the most
precious relationship of your life.
ls that true? Or, isn't it?
- Say it aloud. I didn't hear you.
ls it true? Or, isn't it? - Yes.
She walked out on her
parents after 22 years.
She walked out on
her husband for 7 years.
What guarantee that she won't desert
her child after another 2 or 3 years?
D'you think that your
case stands weakened now?
You haven't lost a single suit
till date, Mr. Bhojwani.
- But it seems that you're going to
lose this one.- No comments please.
Generally, It's the woman who is
favored in disputes like this.
That's because she's
a woman and a mother.
But presently, the questions
revolve around the child.
As I understand, this Court will
decide in the child's interest...
... about what's good for Sunil.
I've been looking after
him for nearly 2 years now.
I've learnt something.
And, I have understood much.
And slowly, I've understood
what it takes to be a good father.
It takes patience. One needs to
spend a lot of time with the child.
For hours, I've heard
him talk of strange fantasies.
I'd get tired of listening to him.
But, I'd go on listening despite.
One must reply to a thousand
questions he has to ask.
One must be there with him whenever
need be, so he might not feel lonely.
To do all that, one must love.
And I don't know where it's written
that a woman can love more than a man.
Must a mother always love
the child more than the father?
I do not say that the child
cannot have a better upbringing.
I've always tried my best.
Sometimes I'd scold him and he'd
go to bed with a heavy heart.
Up next morning, we'd have breakfast
together and we'd laugh and talk.
It was all as if
nothing had happened.
Later, I'd drop him to school.
And while returning from school...
...he would tell me about what
had happened all day in school.
We used to dine together. And
afterwards I'd tell him stories.
We've created a world for ourselves.
And it took a lot of love to do that.
If this is destroyed,
we can never build it again.
Don't do this, Kiran.
Please don't do this to me again.
You've told the court that it must
decide in the interest of your son.
Yes.
Did you work at the Copper Chimney
restaurant when you met Ms.Kiran?
- Yes,
- How much salary did you draw then?
3000 Rupees a month.
But, you were dismissed from the
job, weren't you?
I wasn't dismissed. I left that
job of my own volition.
You left the job! And I thought
that people take on...
... greater responsibilities after
marriage! - I wanted to rise in life.
- I wanted to become a successful
singer. - You must've received...
-.. several offers for singing.- l
did get an offer from Amar Kaushik.
From Amar Kaushik! Lovely! But
I don't think you have sung in...
-... any of his films. Or, have
you? - I had dropped the film.
-Left that too! Why? -Differences
had cropped up between us.
I see... differences!
And what did you do afterwards?
- I went back to the earlier job.
- At Copper Chimney? - Yes.
And how much salary
were you paid?
I didn't hear you, Mr. Rohit.
How much salary were you paid?
- 2500 rupees. - 2500?!
Down from 3000 to 2500!
You're the first person ever to
climb down the ladder to success.
And I do not think it to be
in your son's interest.
On September 13, you tried to rob
5000 rupees from the cashier.
No. I didn't try to rob.
I was asking for a loan.
You tried to take the money forcibly.
And when waiters in the restaurant...
... tried to apprehend you,
you fought with them physically.
I was merely taking a loan.
And I had intended to repay it.
Not only fisticuffs. Furniture was
broken and the restaurant losses.
For the crime, Mr. Rohit Kumar had
spend some time in a police-lockup.
- ls it so, or, isn't it?
- Why don't you try to understand?
Please reply to my question in the
affirmative or the negative.
I'm trying to give a reply. And l
can't do that in a mere ''yes'' or ''no''.
I was taking an advance. It was
to be deducted form my salary.
My son had asked for gift on his
birthday. And, I promised the gift.
Stop shouting! Else, this court
holds you for contempt.
Were you confined in the police
lock up, or, weren't you?
- Yes. I was confined.
- Good.
- Now, do you consider yourself to
be a responsible father? - Yes.
Was your son was about to lose an
eye because you were irresponsible?
- Was your son Sunil about to lose
an eye? - He was playing in the park.
- And he fell down. - He fell
down because you were careless!
- And he was about to lose on eye!
- It was an accident.
- It could've happened to anyone.
- Didn't you tell Ms.Kiran that he...
...fell down because
you were careless...
... and that he was
about to lose an eye?
Tell us, Mr. Rohit, is it true?
Or, isn't it?
-Yes. -Do you concede that your son
could've lost an eye for your fault?
Yes.
I had no idea that my lawyer would
drag that into the court.
He had asked me
a lot of question.
I had merely
answered his questions.
I know you aren't at fault. Please
believe me. I didn't do it willingly.
After hearing the depositors made
by witnesses, this court has decided...
... that the child Sunil Kumar be
placed under Mrs. Kiran's custody.
Vacations start from today.
It's a month long vacation!
We'll go to Matheran during
the vacation, won't we?
-Would you like an ice-cream?
-No. I want an ice-candy. -Come on.
Do you know something. Daddy?
All the kids in my class are going...
... to Simla on a school trip.
But, I'm not going with them.
I'll go to Matheran with you. We'll
have lots of fun out there, won't we?
We'll fly kites over there. And l
will carry the cricket kit with me too.
I want to tell you something.
This is a present from me.
It's a seasoned ball.
Do come over to play cricket.
We'll have a match.
Oh yes. You'll play for my team.
And we'll beat the grocer's team.
- Mr. Ramdayal called up to say
that the car is coming. - I see.
Carry the luggage down.
Let's go downstairs.
Don't cry, Sonu. Come on. You'll
enjoy yourself at Mummy's house.
You'll have lots
of toys over there.
And I'll come down
to see you too.
- Take him down, Farida. I'll be
with you in sometime. - Very well.
Where's your bat, Sunil?
Where's your bat?... He must've
forgotten it. I'll fetch it.
Come along, son.
Sonu has gone downstairs.
- I want to tell you something,
Rohit. - What?
This is Sonu's bat.
He forgot to take it.
I bought a full cricket
kit yesterday.
Why?! lsn't this bat
good for him anymore?
No. It's just that I remembered
that Sonu is fond of cricket.
Not only that. I've bought him
all the toys he could ever want.
I've made him a room that
looks just like the one here.
The same bed; a small table;
and a similar cupboard.
And I've painted the walls
the same shade of color.
All because I want to
make Sonu feel at home.
And then I realized that
this is his home.
A few articles can't make
a home for anyone.
Sonu stays here.
This is his home.
Over the past few days, our lives
and our sentiments were laid bare.
You must've been hurt.
I know that.
And today I know that nothing
matters more than the relationship.
I'm sorry for everything
that has happened.
You're staying here,
Sonu... with your father.
This is your home.
This is your home too.
Sync: DISTEL
@ www.subs.ro