Why did you run for the mail?
Who's going to write to you anyway?
Didn't you say you have
no one in the world?
You're an idiot!
These guys are my family!
- You're right.
- We share the bonds of love.
That you certainly do.
When these guys receive
their letters...
...some of them have tears in
their eyes, and yet others laugh.
l laugh and cry with them, too.
This is funny! ''Everything
else is okay'', she says.
What are you laughing for? ls it
a letter from your wife?
Yes, it is.
Let me read it out to you.
lt doesn't have all
the details, does it?
Oh come on! Not with me
here on the borders!
She says our uncle in Karnal is
dead... but everything is okay.
The cow had a calf which died;
but everything else is okay.
lt's four days since Munni has
been running a fever.
My son has fallen and broken his arm;
but everything else is all right!
My son is now 4 years old.
D'you know what toy he
has asked me to fetch?
He has asked me to bring an
enemy-tank when l go home...
...so we can both play together.
What does your son write?
His handwriting seems to be good.
He writes good things, too.
He writes that the people across
the border are just like us.
They dress like us and speak
a language similar to ours.
lf all this is true, why then
do they fight with us, he asks?
Return home at the earliest,
when the war is over.
l miss you very much.
''There has been no letter from you
ever since you have left''
''Are you angry with me?''
''Don't ever be angry, even if
the world is against me''
''Or l'd have had
enough of my life''
''l had been to your house.
Your mother is fine''
''She's lonely and keeps
waiting for you...''
''...making the wedding gear
for you all the time''
''l've told her that
her darling son...''
''...will come to my house,
when he wears the gear''
''Yours, Kamla''
''Dear son, the roof of
our house has been damaged''
''Every time we try to build it,
a storm knocks it off''
''lt's very difficult to
stay here when it snows''
''lf you could come at the earliest,
the house will have a new roof...''
''and we will have our son''
''Your mother wishes to see you
happily settled before she dies''
''You are undoubtedly doing your duty
in the service of the nation''
'' But you are also the only
support your parents have''
''Do write and tell us
when you're coming home''
What news, Bhairav Singh?
What is this?
Tears in a lion's eyes!
They are tears of joy.
Really? What's the
good news? Tell me!
lt's a letter from my wife.
l'm going to be a father.
Congratulations!
We're going to lay out
a feast today!
- Don't forget the porridge!
- Everyone gets booze from me!
Wait and watch! You're going
to have a baby-son!
There's a message
from the Command, sir!
Friends! The enemy has
launched an attack!
Have the village vacated.
The enemy has begun the attack.
We can't handle the post
and the civilians together.
l entrust this task to you because
you speak their language.
Undoubtedly, sir.
Rush to the border pillar...
...and keep me informed on
the enemy's movements.
Have the soldiers on alert and
ready the post for a battle.
Don't you worry, sir!
Come on. Let's march
to the pillar.
Move! The Commander wants
to meet you folks!
What mistake have we made, sir?
They won't even let me
bring my camel back!
What is the matter, sir?
What are your orders?
- Are all the villagers here?
- Yes, sir.
You know you're staying on the border
and since war has broken out...
...the enemy can attack
at any time.
So quickly take your children and
things, and leave the village.
- l want the village vacated.
- lt's a fight between the armies.
Why will they target us?
The enemy's bombs will not heed names
and things when they explode here.
Look after yourself,
Mr. Bhagiram...
Have the village vacated!
Quick!
They've blown up the barracks!
But they couldn't touch
the Goddess's temple.
Just you wait and watch!
We're going to win this war, sir!
Because the Goddess protects us!
Get out of the village!
Go on!
We've been asking you to do it!
Move it! Quick!
Get out! Hurry up!
Come on... Hurry up!
Mother!
They're not our tanks, sir! They're
coming from across the pillar!
A whole regiment of tanks from
Pakistan is headed for Longewala!
l see. Which is why they're
using artillery fire...
to drown the noise of the
advancing tanks.
Follow them like a shadow...
What treasure do you have in there
that you will risk your life?
- Go away...
- l can't go, sir!
My father gave me the Holy Quran
before he died, sir.
l've left it in there
by the oven, sir.
Here you are... now go away.
You went in there and
got the Quran for me, sir.
But you're a Hindu, aren't you?
Yes, l am.
Which itself explains my deed.
To render selfless service is what
Hinduism is all about.
This what the true Hindu has
been doing down the ages.
Go on now. Please!
Hurry up! Run away... Quick!
And there are people who
call the Hindus infidels!
Lay the anti-tank mines
all around!
Don't be scared, Gurmail!
Pick it up!
The anti-tank mine won't blow up
under a man's weight.
lt needs thousands of pounds to
explode, that the tanks have.
Now lay the mines! Quick!
There's an emergency call for you
from the Air Command.
They want you to call
back immediately.
The Pakistani air-force has
attacked our airbases...
...we need to give them
a fitting reply.
Our Prime Minister is likely to
declare an emergency anytime now.
As you've heard just now,
the war has broken out.
The enemy has commenced
attacks on our airbases.
We've got to give them a reply.
At the break of dawn tomorrow,...
...we will storm the
Rahim Yahya airbase.
They're heading for an attack
on our post, sir!
There's someone coming
this way, sir!
You will always find the black
sheep returning to you, sir.
You're the prodigal son...
You must not even be blamed.
You don't seem to have to
reached your home either.
l've returned from half-way
through the journey, sir.
l can leave my wife in
any state and condition...
...but l cannot desert
my company and my country.
l will obviously get leave after
we have won the war, sir.
Certainly.
Put me through to the C.O.
This is the Station Commander.
Who's that?
What is it, Major?
The Pakistani's have surrounded my
post Longewala from all sides, sir.
They can launch an
attack anytime now.
They have 40 tanks and
troops of a thousand men!
l have just 120 men...
...but unfortunately you cannot
get air support tonight!
Why not?
We have only hunter aircraft's.
They can't be used in night-combat!
But l will be there at
the break of dawn.
How will we hold fort
till dawn tomorrow?!
lt's hours away to sunrise.
- What's wrong, sir?
- Nothing, Harnam Singh.
The hour of our test has arrived!
Blow up every tank you see!
And let's pray for those brave 120
soldiers, who are confronting death!
Have the soldiers
fall in, Ratan Singh!
Tonight is the night when
we are being put to a test!
Because the air-force cannot arrive
to help us till dawn tomorrow.
And there's a lot of
time before daybreak.
Soldiers! There is the enemy!
We're just 120 men... and
they're a whole tank regiment!
We have been asked by the Command
to withdraw from our post.
But they have left the
final decision to me.
And l have decided that,
l, Major Kuldip Singh...
...will not desert my post!
l now leave your decision to you!
Anyone wishing to leave the post,
is free to do so!
Sir! You must listen to my decision
before anyone else's, sir!
Whether someone
stays here or not...
...l will not run away,
leaving my land to the enemy!
l'd rather die!
But l will not retrace my steps!
Bhairav Singh! Don't you ever
talk of dying again!
No dead man has ever
won a battle!
You win a war only by
finishing the enemy!
l didn't reach my house, although
l was given leave, sir.
l returned, only to be with my
company in its battle with the enemy.
Was it to be told that the Command
has asked me to withdraw?!
You might as well shoot me, sir!
But l will not obey this order!
l understand how you feel
at heart, Mathura Das!
But the Command must've thought of
something while issuing the order.
We're just a hundred and twenty;
and the enemy's troops number 2000!
So what's new, sir?
The Revered Tenth Guru
of Sikhism,...
...Sri Guru Gobind Singh
has proclaimed...
...l will set birds
against even the hawks!
Such will be the glory of Sikhs
in a victory of this kind!
When even birds can
take on hawks, sir...
...we're after all human!
We are not scared!
No one will leave!
Do l take it then that all of you
will face the enemy with me?
lndeed, sir!
Should anyone of you try to run away
after taking this decision...
...l will personally kill him!
God forbid, but if l happen
to waver in my step...
...and try to run away, you must
get together and gun me down!
That's an order from your
Commanding Officer!
Blessed is the one
who proclaims...
...in God lies true glory!
Victory to the path of righteousness
paved by the Gurus!
Soldiers! Back to your positions!
Listen carefully to what
l have to say.
The Command is not ignorant
of our weak position.
They want me to decide if we
are to fight or to withdraw.
You're forgetting, sir! l am
Major Vir Bhan's son!
l can't even think of retracting!
That's exactly what
l expected from you!
Come on, you swines!
No one will open fire
till l order it!
Let the creeps get a bit closer!
Or whom have we laid
the landmines for?
Victory to Mother lndia!
Hold it, soldier! Stay back!
The lndians seem to have
laid anti-tank mines for us.
No one will advance any further!
'' Blessed is the one who proclaims...
in the Lord's name is glory''
''Victory to the path of righteousness
paved by our Gurus!''
We seemed to have got
wrong information.
They have a battalion of 600 men.
Not a company of 120 soldiers!
The angels of your death
await you!
Either send your guys out...
...and surrender with your
hands on your head...
...or say your last prayer!
Save your measly band!
You can't escape!
You're Ghulam Dastagir, aren't you?
The infamous thug of Lahore?
Scum from the rotten gutters
of your city?!
Only time will tell if l say
my last prayers or you!
Should you set another foot forward
on your silly assignment...
...l will send you back to the
gutters you have come from!
What makes you shut up?
Give him a reply.
Mathura Das!
What the hell is wrong?
Come on! Steady...
- Bhagiram! lt's you!
- You're surprised, eh?!
You're handling a gun!
What will a soldier handle,
if not a gun?
But l've always seen a
ladle in your hands!
lt's thanks to the ladle that
you're such a strong man!
Now watch me work magic
with these guns!
l will bump off no less than a
couple of the enemy's soldiers!
Damn you...!
Now, buddy... who's going to
feed me if you kick the bucket?
Listen, buddy... l hope you remember
the inn we start after retirement?
We're going to be
equal partners.
- l have a condition.
- What is that?
- You will not eat at the inn.
- How can that be?
Then we can't have
an equal partnership.
l will have 90% of the holdings;
you will get just 10%
What for?
You're going to eat stuff
worth that much of money!
Damn it! The spring is broken!
You wanted a spring, Bhairav Singh.
Here it is.
Open fire! Go on!
This land is as much my mother
as it is yours, Bhairav Singh!
lf possible, please carry
a message to my wife.
Tell her that l am indeed guilty
and answerable to her.
l am repaying a debt to my motherland
in this birth of mine...
...l will repay her debt
when l am born again!
l will repay her debt
in my next birth!
Das! No...!
Bhairav Singh!
Go and take over the MMG's!
Take charge of the MMG's,
Bhairav Singh!
Take charge of the MMG's, l say!
Go and take charge of the MMG's!
l'll fix these guys now...!
We're returning to
the post, Gurnam!
l need covering fire!
Not one of them must escape!
Dharmveer is returning, sir.
He has asked for covering fire.
Officer Dharmveer is returning!
Give him some covering fire!
Blow them up!
Go and take charge of the
LMG in the next column!
Remember the great man, Dharmveer!
Remember the great
Major Vir Bhan!
lnvoke your father, my dear soldier!
''One Sikh shall take on a hundred
and twenty five thousand...''
''...and bring glory
to my revered Guru!''
Duck, soldiers!
Ratan Singh!
What the hell are you doing?
Bhagiram!
You won't have to cook for
10 extra guys anymore!
- Don't say that...
- You remember, don't you?
Ratan Singh... get up!
Don't leave me, my friend!
You're my partner!
You must start that inn, Bhagiram!
l'm game for the 10% share
in the profits!
But see that you pay the
profits to my parents.
They have no other support...
Ratan Singh!
They who can set birds
against the hawks, sir...
...will bring glory to
Guru Gobind Singh's name!
How could you do this?
You've left a friend?!
Why doesn't this
bloody night end?!
That MMG gun has
bothered us no end.
Blow it up with the tank.
Bhairav Singh!
Are you all right?
Watch out!
Beware!
Do not let them set foot
on my motherland!
Mother... here l come!
l'm coming!
Bhairav Singh! Come back here!
Mow him down!
Kill the swine!
Oh Mother... Goddess Shakti!
Goddess Mother...!
Goddess Shakti!
The infidel has an anti-tank mine
in his hands!
Drive the tank backwards!
Backwards, l say!
Drive it back... Quick!
Hurry up! Drive it back...
Assemble here, soldiers!
There is the enemy!
We must defeat them!
Go for them in full force!
Go for them in your senses!
Charge!
Hold your fire till
our soldiers return!
There's still life in Dharmveer!
Give him covering fire!
You asked me to invoke memories
of my father, sir!
To invoke memories of the
great Major Vir Bhan!
My father is here, sir...
to take me away.
lt'll soon be dawn!
You must live, Dharmveer!
Don't stop me, mother...
Please let me go!
Father is calling me over!
Let me go...
He's still alive, sir.
Please don't kill me, sir!
For God's sake!
For the sake of the God
you pray to!
ln the name of the Bhagwan
you worship!
Please don't kill me!
l have little kids back home!
What are your children's names?
Khalid... and Asma.
Nice names. Now tell me
the plans of your forces.
l'm an ordinary soldier, sir.
lt's the higher-ups
who plan strategy.
All they said was that we'd have
breakfast at Jaisalmer in lndia.
That we'd have lunch
at Jodhpur in lndia.
And that we'd have
dinner in Delhi.
l swear by Allah, sir! By the
Holy Quran! This is all l know!
Please don't kill me, sir!
l don't want to die!
We will not kill you!
You are a soldier of your nation,
just we are for our country!
We will treat you as a soldier
ought to treat another!
Give him some water.
ls it time yet?
There's still an hour
for sunrise, sir.
Listen, brave soldiers of Pakistan!
You will be conquerors
if you taste victory!
And you will be martyrs
should you die!
Do not bother about the
anti-tank mines!
Drive your tanks into their post!
Advance!
They said they'd have
breakfast in Jaisalmer!
But we're going to
feast on them today!
One Sikh is equal to a hundred and
twenty five thousand, said our Guru!
lt's time now to prove
His proclamation true!
'' Blessed is the one who
acknowledges the proclamation...''
''Glory be to the Lord's
path of righteousness!''
''We tread the path
shown by the Lord...''
''Victory to the Lord''
''What's the fun in being alone?
Be it you or me?''
Escape! The lndian aircraft's
have arrived!
ls that Base? Where the hell is
our rotten airforce?
The lndian air-force has made
life miserable for us!
They're hovering around us
like flies!
Most of our tanks have
already been destroyed!
Sir! We have won the battle!
The enemy is fleeing!
We have won the battle!
Sir...?!