Two minutes and 45 seconds.
You can save at least 15 seconds...
l sense a war; l've been
summoned to Head Quarters.
War can break out at any time.
and set-up a new air base there.
Victory to lndia!
The soldiers are here
for firing, sir!
Soldiers of the Punjab Regiment...
...the day we have
eagerly waited for, is here.
Orders have already arrived.
The Company will leave for Rajasthan
as an advanced force.
Every bullet you carry will
now bear the enemy's name!
So, let's see, soldiers...
how will you strike?
- This is Priti here, Papa.
- Yes, dear? How is everything?
- Nothing is right, Papa.
- Why? What's wrong, dear?
My husband is being sent
to the borders.
War is breaking out.
l'll die of the shock, Papa.
Could you have his transfer stalled?
You're politically well connected...
...you'll have to do
this much for me, Papa.
Stop worrying, dear.
- l'll have his transfer stalled.
- Very well.
Don't worry, dear. l've had
Kuldip's transfer suspended.
He will not go to war.
l'm having him sent to the
Head Quarters in Delhi.
l've heard all that
you had to say.
l understand what you
are getting at.
And now you'd better understand
what l'm about to say.
lf you really have
my transfer stalled...
...then l will leave
this daughter of yours...
...for whom you are doing all this.
Listen, son...
Get us some chairs.
What... was that you said to Papa?
Just what you heard me say.
You had sworn by our son that
you'd never leave me. Remember?
Yes, l had.
Will you break the oath then?
And what if something
happens to my son?
l don't care.
Don't forget the oath l took
when l joined the army.
l had pledged something when
l was born in lndia.
l had sworn by this soil...
...in which l have grown
from childhood to a man!
l had sworn by those
alps and peaks...
...which have been protecting my
motherland for over 5000 years!
l had sworn allegiance to 500
million of my countrymen...
...who are born of this soil
just as l have!
l can sacrifice my son
for them anytime.
Forgive me, Kuldip.
My love for you had
driven me to despair.
A life without you will be
worse than death.
lt was because of this that
l telephoned my father.
What if something happens
to you in the war?
Nothing will happen to me,
silly girl.
Your love Deepu's
will not let me die.
l'll return in one piece.
Watch out.
And that is a promise.
What makes you say that?
Your border outpost has been
kept ready by the BSF...
...and you only have
to take charge.
The tough job is left
to the Air Force.
We'll have to start from scratch.
And we don't even know how
much time we have.
Going by the situation in East
Pakistan, it's pretty certain...
...that they will start
trouble on the Western Front.
As you said, Pakistan will start
trouble in the Western Front...
...but we will be the ones
to ''finish'' it.
They will fire the first bullet;
we'll finish off with the last.
With the Air Force around, l don't
think you will need to open fire.
Victories and defeats in wars...
...are now determined by the
strength of the Air Force, Major.
But it's our soldiers who bare their
chests to the offenders' bullets.
after we clear the path for you;
we will first strike at their base!
There's no end to the debate
on the superiority...
...between the Army
and the Air Force.
All we must realize is that it
takes all hues to make a garden.
What's the fun in being alone...
Be it you or me?
Fantastic, Major! Very well said!
This is an emergency, Mathuradas!
All leaves have been cancelled!
But l've still sent your application
to the Brigade Headquarters.
l'll inform you of whatever
directions l receive.
That was Mathuradas; he
belongs to your company.
He was asking for leave in
an emergency situation.
Those who run homewards
at the sight of war...
...have no right to be in the army.
His wife is seriously ill
with cancer, he says.
You could relieve him forever, sir.
He could spend his life sitting
at his wife's bedside.
You will now go and take charge
of the outpost at Longewala...
...and relieve the BSF who are
presently holding fort.
120 men of your company
await you outside.
Will just a hundred and twenty men
protect the post at Longewala?!
600 soldiers will man
the post at Sangewala.
You send 600 men for Sangewala;
and l get just 120 !
lf the enemy decides to
break through a new opening...
...they will try Sangewala,
as they did in the war of '65.
Which means you expect them
to repeat their mistake!
Or they might just ask us which is
the safest way to enter the country!
The enemy will not obey us;
but you must.
Go and take over the post.
Strategies are planned at
the Headquarters, you know.
Not here in our offices.
Go and meet your men.
Attention, soldiers!
Don't move!
Hail lndia!
The soldiers are ready
here at the parade, sir!
Don't move, soldiers!
You didn't tell me we had a kid
among the 120 men, sir.
You're right, sir!
l am a kid.
My father was a kid, too,
when he joined the army.
But he was such a lovable kid...
...that God took him away
from us in the war of '65.
- What was your father's name?
- Major Vir Bhan.
Ask the soldiers to mount, subedar.
l knew Major Vir Bhan
very well.
l can't call him a friend,
because he was a senior to me.
But we were still very friendly.
- How is your mother?
- She's all right.
- Though she cannot see.
- Cannot see?
She has lost her eye-sight in
the tears she has shed.
We can't see anything around.
lt's a desert.
Don't crib! You have a runway!
You can...
Which are our neighboring villages?
''What's the fun in being alone?
Be it you or me''
Here's the army to
take over from us.
They're mostly Sikhs. Must be
a regiment from Punjab.
''Victory to Mother lndia''
- Where's your Commander?
- He's away on Patrol, sir.
Send word over wireless that we
have arrived to take charge.
Sir!
- There's a message, sir.
- What is it?
They want you at the post. The army
has arrived to take charge, sir.
Really? And here l was...
sleeping like a log.
How do you manage to sleep in the
sand through the night, sir?
We don't consider this land to be
our mother for nothing, Santram.
lt has a lot of compassion for us.
When it sees its children
going to sleep...
...it spreads out a protective
sheet of sand to cover us.
You have received the orders,
l believe?
This BSF company will move on
to the post at Gutaru.
You must know this region very well.
Mustn't you, Captain?
l know it as l know
my courtyard, sir.
Perhaps this is why my Headquarters
has directed me...
to join you with three of my men
in the battle here.
lt was a request from
the army headquarters.
Please ask them to light a lamp in
the Goddess's temple everyday, sir.
Do you see the Goddess's
temple there, sir?
My soldiers want you to light a
lamp for the Goddess everyday.
A lamp will be lit everyday
and prayers offered, too.
They believe that the Goddess will
protect this post, if you do that.
Make a point to remember
that, Kartar Singh.
Glory be to Mother lndia!
Move it... yes, from there.
Ask the soldiers to get their
fill of water from the well.
Get the water you want, soldiers!
- Get a bucket, feller!
- l'm dying of thirst!
- l'm longing to have a bath...
- Hold it, guys... Wait!
Wait, l say! Freeze!
Out of my way!
None of you will even
touch the water!
Let me first take the water
l need for cooking...
...you can drown in it
after that, for all l care!
- Are you issuing that order?
- Yes.
- Although l am very much here?
- Of course.
Do you know whom you
are talking to?
l know you're an officer...
a high-ranking one.
Your wish is my command, sir...
...but l will say this much.
Nourishment makes the soldier;
it's not the other way around.
No army in the world can ever
fight on an empty stomach!
You talk too much for a cook,
don't you?
l hope you don't
take offence, sir...
...Bhagiram cooks as lovingly
as the acid tongue he uses.
Many high-ranking officers take
everything he says jokingly.
And why not? lt's because of my food
that they've risen in the ranks!
Watch what happens when you
eat the food l cook, sir!
You will go places!
Let's go, buddy.
Here comes Subedar Ratan Singh
... to die here!
You've got just two
anti-tank guns!
Do the top-brass think the enemy
has only a couple of tanks?
Let them have a couple
of hundred, sir.
You don't need to worry, so long
as Ratan Singh is around!
Are you going to stop them
with your hands and feet?
lndeed, sir. l'd thrust my head
into their tanks, if need be...
...to silence them, sir.
You can't ever change, Ratan Singh.
You must be hungry as usual.
lsn't it?
l'm so terribly hungry, sir...
...l could grill the
enemy's tanks in my tandoor!
Go ahead then. Bhagiram is
waiting for you.
Greetings, Bhagiram!
Cursed luck, Bhagiram!
Did you curse your luck
when you saw me?
- Yes, l did.
- Why? Didn't you like my arrival?
My word! As if our friendship
has gone to the dogs!
l wonder what the lndian army
holds against me.
They send you behind me,
wherever l'm posted!
Don't blame the army,
if you take my opinion.
l suggest you meet
a wise astrologer.
You'd find him somewhere
among the bad stars.
The bad stars have no class.
This man is a demon-incarnate,
born to torment me!
ls this how you treat me for
our years of friendship?!
To hell with our friendship!
l just have to cook now!
You've been cooking for
a 120 soldiers, right?
Start cooking for
130 men from today.
- Where have 10 guys sprung from?
- Can't you see?!
- Here's one... two... three...
- Stop it, l say!
- Buddy boy!
- You're a pal!
- How far is the border from here?
- lt's just 16 kms., sir.
Are the villages around the border
friendly to us?
They used to be, sir.
Many moved across the border
during the war of 1965.
They're all related. And some of
them are informers, too, sir.
Start a full-scale checking of
the villages from tomorrow.
- Shall we use force, sir?
- Only if necessary.
These two happen to be
the narrow paths to the border.
They link us to Border
Post # 635 and 638.
l'd like to examine the paths
and the border-pillars.
Certainly, sir. You can see the
Pakistani bunkers from across them.
Prepare to leave for
the border early tomorrow.
There's pillar # 635, sir.
Don't remain standing, sir.
The enemy's snipers
fly around dangerously.
What madness is he up to?!
Please stop him!
That lndian officer seems
to be mad, doesn't he?
l could lay him flat,
if you wish, sir.
Hold it.
Madness and love have a
strange old relationship.
The Major seems to
love his country...
...as much as l love the
soil of these deserts.
ln which case, he's bound
to be given a medal someday.
My father was given one, too.
He was also a victim
of this madness.
He left behind a medal and
a blind mother for me.
May l ask you a question, sir?
Sure. Go ahead.
ls there no difference between
bravery and madness?
That which you consider madness is
a result of one's belief.
l strongly believe that my life and
death are in the Almighty's hands.
And my Almighty is with me...
not with the enemy!
Because l am always
in His protection.
These are the villages that
are most endangered, sir.
Because they use these
very paths for movement.
There are Pakistani's on
the wireless system, sir.
- On our frequency?!
- They want to talk to you, sir.
Yes? This is Kuldip Singh here.
We know you have arrived,
Kuldip Singh Chandpuri.
You're posted at Longewala with the
23rd Regiment of the Punjab, right?
We have been waiting for you.
Perhaps you are destined
to die in Longewale.
Run away from the post,
if you wish to escape death!
You can't escape us!
Should you die, your wife can
always get married again.
But what happens of your son?
All you can do is to
indulge in cheap talk!
Will you keep nagging us
like women?
Face me, if you're man enough...
...and you'll know whether l'm here
to die, or to wreak havoc on you!
Don't you guys dare to set foot
on our soil!
Longewala does not have space for
a graveyard for all of you!
As for my son... you're
a bunch of cheapsters!
Even my son could
put you to shame!
Let them advance, sir!
We will build a graveyard for
them, sir! We certainly will!
lt's the villagers who must've
passed on the information to them.
They keep going across
the border very often.
They've lit a fire
in the ruins, sir.
l wonder who they are and
what they are doing here.
- What is the matter, sir?
- Who are you?
We're travelling to Tanaud for a
visit to the Goddess's temple.
They're on their way to Tanaud,
to the Goddess's temple, sir.
- Where do you come from?
- From village Dongra, sir.
l thought we'd eat and rest and
give our camels a break, too, sir.
There's nothing on them.
Go ahead and eat.
D'you see the grass the
camels are feeding on, sir?
The grass is green.
Out here in the deserts, we don't
have green grass for miles.
Across the border in Pakistan,
however, they do have such grass.
He seems to have encountered death
for the first time, sir.
Ask him to get used to it!
This man can't be Major
Vir Bhan Singh's son!
Forget killing the enemy...
...he throws up at the
sight of their blood!
You can't win a war by being
martyred at the hands of the enemy!
Wars are won by slaying the enemy!
Shove that thing behind!
l remember a film l saw, Rafi, in
which the villain tells the hero...
...you mustn't mess around with guns;
they're not for kids!
What's up, lieutenant?
Why aren't you asleep?
Your father was martyred in
the war of '65, wasn't he?
Obviously. He was in the army.
Do you really hold the
lndian army responsible...
...for your father's death?
Yes!
Then why did you join the Force?
My father had invoked his love and
extracted a promise from me,...
...that l would join the army!
And why did he extract
the promise from you?
Because his love for the nation was
the biggest love he had ever known.
Which made him shackle his son
in this uniform!
l have been given a gun to shoot
down the soldier l encounter.
A soldier who is a son to some woman;
a soldier l've never met before.
A soldier who has done
no harm to me!
A soldier whom l do even know!
Why must l kill him? What for?
Because he will kill you,
if you don't kill him.
Who will trample upon your body to
tread on the soil of your motherland!
And this free land will once again
be shackled in chains of slavery!
We don't even cast a look at
the land the others possess.
But we're not such
worthless children...
...to watch silently, as they
eye our motherland!
Keep your eyes on the enemy!
Do not even blink!
Let's forget these serious things.
You're a young officer, Dharmveer...
Your mother must surely have
chosen a bride for you, right?
Did you see her, too?
Did you like her?
The beauty of it is that
she liked me.
This is the right mood!
How did it all happen?
Nothing much. l returned to my
village, after my commissioning.
Just when the bus ground
to a halt...
Auntie!
He's here, auntie! He has arrived!
He has arrived, auntie!
He's here at last!
- Really?
- l swear!
Mother!
Not there at my feet, son...
You must come close to my heart!
You ought to be in
my heart, my son!
l will bless you from the
bottom of my heart, son.
Greetings.
How have you been? ...and what's
this? You've started shaving!
My son has grown up!
However much l may grow,
l will always be your son, Mom.
You have weakened!
Doesn't the army feed you well?
He's just fine!
He hasn't weakened at all.
You won't understand this.
You can't see, what a mother
can feel with her hands.
Well, all right.
You can rest assured...
...that l won't cast
an evil eye on your son.
l've already got what l wanted.
What are you talking about?
l don't understand a word.
lt's good that you
don't understand.
Shall we move now?
- What are you doing?!
- lt's okay!
There you are, auntie!
My parents have arrived, too.
Congratulations! Dharmveer has
returned as an officer!
Bless you, son.
Heartiest congratulations, sister!
Thank God! Vir Bhan's family
is happy again.
God willing, Dharmveer must
get married soon, too.
l'll go and fetch some tea.
Try this one.
For all the mangoes l've had,
this one is incomparable!
lt has love in its juices!
... the idiot!
l must go and light the oven.
You must eat with us
before you leave, son.
Enjoy yourselves, kids.
l'll take a look at the fields.
What are you up to?!
- What have you done?!
- Why did you dirty my shirt?
You were so taken up
with the mango...
...couldn't you pay some
attention to me?
- Why? Don't you like mangoes?
- No! l don't!
- What do you like then?
- Must l tell you?
Mother!
Kammu! Come back here!
- Mother...!
- l'm coming after you!
Come back here, l say!
Are you back, son?
Yes, Mom. What are you making?
l'm weaving a bridal gear
for my son.
A bridal-gear for me?!
- For my marriage?
- You're the only one l have.
Have you found a
bride for me, too?
l don't need to. There's just
one girl whom we all like.
- Who's that?
- Who else, but the lovable Kammo!
No! Not that snob?!
She always has her nose up in
the air! l will not marry her!
- What are you saying?!
- Just what you've heard, Mom.
lmpossible! lt's Kammo
you must marry!
And l've made up my mind that she's
the one l will never marry! Never!
Why must you be so angry?!
What's wrong with her?
You just can't see
what's wrong with her!
The rustic idiot can't be wife
to an army officer!
Why are you flinging things around?
Why must you be so angry?
Won't l get angry? l insist
l don't want that girl!
But you're being stubborn that
l marry Kamla alone!
You can't do this, son.
Kamla and her parents have long
dreamt of getting her married to you.
But l can't ruin my life
for someone's dreams!
All right.
l won't insist. l'll beg her father's
forgiveness, with folded hands.
They've had the hope, ever
since you were little kids.
l'm not sure if he
will forgive me.
- Where are you off to, Mom?
- Leave me alone!
But l've only been joking!
- ls that the truth?
- Yes. l've been joking!
- Do you approve of Kamla then?
- Yes, l do.
May you live long, my son!
l'll have you both engaged
tomorrow itself.
l've heard it on the radio that
war is about to break out.
An emergency has been clamped...
...and the leave of army-men
has been cancelled.
They're being asked
to report for duty.
What's wrong, son? Why have
they stopped singing?
Continue singing!
You folks may please leave.
Why are you leaving?!
Dharam! Why are they leaving, son?
- Sit down here...
- Where is Kammo?
What's wrong? Tell me.
My leave has been cancelled, Mom.
l will have to return.
- Where to?
- War is about to break out.
Won't you wear the bridal gear
l've made, son?
lt's still not complete, mom.
First finish making it.
l will wear it after
l have returned.
No... l will not let you leave.
Don't be stubborn. You know l can't
stay back, even if l wish to.
No!
Please, son...
have mercy on your mother!
My eyes can't continue
to wait for you anymore.
Nor do l have the tears
l can shed for you.
Don't make it difficult for me, Mom.
l must leave.
- l will have to leave!
- No!
- l must leave!
l will have to leave!
No! l will not let you go away...
No. l won't let him leave...
l will stop him!
l won't let him go.
l won't let him go!
l will stop him.
Kammo? You?
You thought you'd leave
without informing anyone.
But l had already decided
that l would see you off.
So l can receive you again,
when you return.
Would you mind if l walked
with you to the bus-stand?
Let's go.
l will not let him go away!
l will stop him!
There's something l want
to tell you, Kammo.
Go ahead.
lf l don't return... you must
marry someone else.
You're laughing?!
l happened to remember something.
l saw a madman doing
strange things in Agra.
He used to look back...
shut his eyes...
look around himself...
angrily sit on the floor!
He'd then start throwing
blows around!
He'd turn this way and that...
...run some distance, look back
and lie down again!
He'd suddenly get up and
start running around!
D'you know what he
was trying to do?
He was trying to get
rid of his shadow!
l am your shadow, silly boy!
You can't get rid of me.
l must make a move.
Listen...
Look after yourself.
l didn't even have the courage to
look back at her from the bus.
Her eyes must surely have
followed the bus drive away...
You've heard my story. Won't you
tell me something about yourself?
Mine is the same old story
of the King and the Queen.
l'm a Rajput.
My forefathers once ruled
this part of the country.
l'm the company of
a blue-blooded man!
Love blossomed with youth and that
brought Phool Kanwar into my life.
She's the daughter of a princely
family from a neighboring village.
She became my bride.
l can never forget
that nuptial night.
Orders for you from the
Head Quarters, Sir.
There was my bride;
before my eyes.
And in my hand l held a
call from my motherland.
Very well. l will leave for
the border at daybreak.
Thank you very much.
Something wrong? What were the BSF
doing here at this hour?
They were here to congratulate me
on behalf of the battalion.
A congratulatory message
does not upset someone.
Haven't you heard of people being
helpless; that's how l look!
Don't you say a word
against my husband!
What happens, if we don't return?
Have faith, Bhairav Singh.
We will surely go back.
How else will God answer for the
loss of Phool Kanwar's husband...
...and for Kamla's youth?
Preparations are afoot here and
the lndians are bracing themselves.
This is a Pakistani informer
on the frequency, sir!
- On our frequency?!
- Yes, sir.
Their anti-tank guns are
positioned to the left.
Could you somehow
trace this swine?
l think he's in a radius of
10 kilometres to the west.
Let's go!
l don't know, sir!
Get the jeep.
That way, sir.
He must be holed up in
one of those houses.
There are about 120 soldiers in
this regiment of the lndian army.
He's dead!
Didn't you ask me to get
used to this, sir?
l've done it!
Hand over the body
to his family.
lf it remains unclaimed,
give it a decent burial.
- Who is this?
- Not ''is'' ; he used to be.
An informer of the enemy.
Who killed him, sir?
Kids grow up, as they play
with their toys, you know.
ls the border-pillar clear?
Everything is clear; we see no
movement of the enemy.
D'you think the Pakistanis are crazy
to break into this stretch of land?
They will go to Punjab or Kashmir,
where's there's greenery and joy.
A jackal goes berserk when its
death approaches, my friend.
But what will they find here?!
A god-forsaken desert
for miles together!
You end up eating half a kilo of
sand, even if you don't want to!
No matter how the land is!
lt belongs to us!
That's all very well. But what
does this land possess?
What does it breed?
Shrubs and scorpions?
You perhaps don't know...
this land breeds lions, too.
ln which case, lions from this
sand must be made of clay!
You're wrong! They'd any day
consign someone to the dust!
What are you getting at?
Had you not been in the army,
l'd have given you an explanation.
Really?
There! l'm no longer in uniform.
What do you wish to explain?
My hands speak better
than my mouth!
You have abused my motherland!
You have abused my mother!
He has abused my motherland, sir!
l consider this land
to be my mother, sir!
And the swine says it's a
barren piece of useless land!
He says it breeds only
shrubs and scorpions!
Tell me, sir! Won't children love
their mother, if she is ugly?
Do they have no
respect for her?
This man has dared
to abuse my mother!
Apologize to Bhairav Singh,
Mathura Das.
Embrace him as you would embrace
an errant brother, Bhairav.
Go on. Be a good boy.
Forgive me.
We're sick of waiting
for the enemy, sir.
Why haven't you married, sir?
l thought l'd always
be a free bird.
But l met a girl who refused
to bow to anyone.
You're an atheist, all right.
But why must you hate God?
l hate everything man has made
to suit his convenience.
The idea of God happens
to be one of them.
But there has to be a Supreme
Power to whom you bow.
No, sir. l bow to none.
Forget God. l'd make you bow
to a mere human being.
Will you really? Try it!
On the condition that
we will share the coffee!
You will stay at a particular place
for 5 minutes at eight tomorrow.
- l bow to none, she says!
- And what happened, sir?
That's no way of bringing
someone to his knees!
The fact remains! You did
bow to someone!
Death could scare anyone!
You could call God a scare, too!
l'm sure He won't mind!
Saying sorry won't help!
l won the bet, all right.
But my wings have been clipped!
l've decided to marry her.
You guys will have to dance when
you join my wedding procession!
My son!
l've brought your
bridal gear, son...
Mother!
The movement of our
troops has begun, sir.
l don't think we will have to wait
much longer for the enemy.
You know everything, sir. When do
you think we will see some action?
The bloody enemy neither fights
nor lets us remain in peace!
Patience, Gurnam! Be patient!
We're sick of being hold up
here for months, sir.
Why don't we simply
get it over with?
To hell with the enemy! Give us
the clearance to advance.
We can do nothing about that.
Just hold on to your position.
- Hail lndia, sir!
- Hail lndia!
ls everything all right?
Has my leave been
sanctioned, Subedar?
What's your problem that you're
dying to go home, Mathura Das?
My problem is that my wife
is dying of cancer.
There's no one to even give a
glass of water to my child!
We've been rotting here for months!
Without a godammed letter!
l can understand your
feelings, Mathura Das.
Here comes the mail, guys!
A letter from my beloved has come!
Come over, guys!
Here come the letters!
How about my letter?
Know what? My brother has passed
in the examinations.
- What is this?
- A letter, of course.
- You tell me.
- lt's a letter.
What a shame! Have you guys
seen me so happy recently?
- No, sir.
- My leave has been sanctioned!
l'm going home!
What's the time, Ram Singh?
- lt's a quarter to two.
- Time for the bus! Bye...
Jeet! l'm going home! Do you want me
to say something to your wife?
- Just that everything is all right.
- Very well.. Bye!
Manjeet! Let's shake, pal!
l've got my leave;
l'm going home!
lt's good that someone
is getting away.
Sit there with
long faces, you guys!
Here l go!
Sukhdev! l'm going home! Anything
to convey to your folks?
- Ask them to keep writing.
- Sure. l will do that!
So long! l'm leaving!
Mr. Ratan Singh!
My leave has been sanctioned!
That's good. You've got a
break then, haven't you?
Now go and look after
your wife.
Mr. Mathura Das! You are delighted
to be going home!
But the ugly manner in which you
have demonstrated your happiness...
...is totally unwarranted!
Your leave has been sanctioned
because you have a problem at home.
But who does not have
problems in the world?
ln fact, life itself
is a problem!
Now tell me!
Do you know of the hero in our midst
whose widowed mother cannot see...
...but whose son is lost here
in the sands of the desert?
D'you know of the hero whose
mother's mortal remains wait...
...for him to return victorious from
war and complete the rites?
One of these men has his father
fighting for his life.
A man who wards off his death
every day on the pretext...
...that the one to cremate him is
defending the borders of the nation!
lf each one of them were to make
excuses and go on leave...
...how will we win this war?!
Speak up!
Aren't you man enough?!
Before l declare you a traitor
and gun you down...
...just run away from here!
What he said is right.
Who will fight the enemy
The Major is like a coconut;
a hard exterior and soft within!
Why did you run for the mail?