What is love?
Love? ...Love is life.
Love? What is love?
Where does it happen? Why does
it happen? And how does it happen?
l believe that God predetermined
all our emotional relationships.
But then HE left it to
us to find each other.
HE made us all couples...
''and for every one of us,
there is a life companion.''
A soulmate? What nonsense! l
don't believe in all this...
''l'm absolutely sure that somewhere,
someone was made for me...''
and that someday l
shall certainly meet him.
''Okay, but will someone please tell me
how will l know who was made for me?''
''l mean, will she be wandering about
with a placard with my name on it?''
''When l see her, will
there be a clap of thunder...''
and a flash of lightning?
How will l recognise her?
''l don't know what others will do,
but l will recognise him.''
HE will speak to me...
''HE will give me a sign, and my
heart will realise that this is him.''
What is all this?
- This is love
Love!
''However far apart they may be...''
''Their paths will meet,
whatever happens,...''
''When two people are
made for each other''
''Made for each other''
The Heart ls Crazy
''Like the heart and its beat...
- Made for each other''
''Like the eye and its sight...
''Like the monsoon and the rain...
- Made for each other''
''Like man and woman...
''Made for each other''
''When God made a heart,...''
''HE split it in two...''
''and gave them two names...''
''Radha and Krishna''
''Now the hearts beat...''
''they part, and they unite...''
''for, they are made for each other''
''Made for each other''
''l don't know when...''
''like a silent thief...''
''the first look of love...''
''stole my heart away''
''ln love's very first
game of hide-n-seek...''
''l hid myself in the
shelter of his eyes''
''Now l'm frightened...''
''because like a silent thief,...''
''the first look of love...''
''stole my heart away''
''My hair disheveled, l
walk like l'm drunk''
''lf l am caught, l'll be questioned''
''Oh, how can l go home?''
''For, love's first sight...''
''slithered and sneaked in...''
''and stole my heart away''
''Jimmy, get Rahul.
- Rahul's not here.''
''lt's time for him to appear.
Find him, fast!''
Oh God! l'll be right back.
''Shruti, you found Rahul?
- No.''
''l don't know when...''
''like a silent thief...''
''the first glance of love...''
''took my heart away''
''Yes, very good. Keep it up, everyone''
Rahul! How often have l told you
that l get anxious when you're late...
l got this idea at the last minute.
And l thought that if l shoot out...
''of the stage, the audience will
freak out, and that's what happened.''
''What's the fuss all about?
- Look Rahul, l'm fed up...''
''with your last minute entries.
- Hey kid, l'm the director.''
''l do what l want. l can
change whomever l like, even you.''
''Yeah, but you'll never
get another dancer like me.''
lf l want l can get Shruti to dance.
- Shut up!
Nisha! Fight with him later. lt's
time to go on stage. Take the mike.
''What? Okay, let's get the lights.''
ldiot!
Thank you... thank you very much
l want to thank you all very much...
for making this dance show such
a big success. Thank you so much
''As you all know, this is
the last night of this show.''
''However, l promise you that
we'll be back in three months...''
''with a new story, new
songs and a new name... Maya.''
''Yes, 'Maya' is the name
of our new dance show.''
''Thank you very much everybody,
and good night to you.''
Cheers!
''Rahul, this new play 'Maya'...
what's it all about? Tell us.''
''Get up! Tell us about it.
- Okay, okay.''
l don't know.
- What?!
''lf you didn't know that, then
why did you tell everyone...''
that we'll do a new
show called 'Maya'...
''and that we'll do it in three months?
- Now look, even l don't know...''
who or what Maya is. But l do
know that in three months...
we'll do a show called 'Maya'.
Do you have in mind a
girl who's like Maya?
''Not in mind, as of now
l can just feel her.''
Nisha! l've got a girl in mind.
''Rahul! aren't you talking
about Pami, the Colonel's daughter?''
''Rahul, is Maya the
girl you are in love with?''
''No, l'm not in love with
anyone but lots of girls love me.''
But Maya is the kind of
girl that anyone would love.
Maya is the kind of girl for
whom you would leave even Soni.
''You dare not cheat on my sister!
- Ballu, shut up.''
What does she do?
- She invades my dreams.
ls Maya beautiful?
Very.
This Maya must do something...
''Maya dances,... but only for herself.''
''Excuse me, but she is a feeling,
a fantasy, beautiful,...''
and a dancer. But we've got
to find her in three months.
So who is she?
Maya is all these things
and yet she is only Maya.
We've gone around in circles
and we're back where we started.
Are you trying to make us look dumb?
l've done chores all my life!
But l'll decide this today!
''Good morning, aunty!
- Silly girl! Where were you?''
l was outside.
- Now you have to come with me.
l'm tired of the promises
your uncle makes everyday.
''So, today we're going to have a
fight and you have to take my side.''
Okay! Let's go.
''Bravo, bravo!''
''Bravo, bravo! What a performance!''
''Panditji,... excuse me, Panditji''
''Go on, Chandni.... er, Shanti''
Please allow us to have a teabreak.
Break whatever you want.
Please allow me to have a
word with your students.
By all means.
Watchman! Gardener!
''Shankar and Ramu, if you don't mind,
perhaps you'd all get back to work!''
Where are you going?
- Thank you.
Why are you driving away my audience?
- Please be quiet.
You gather the servants here so
they can't get on with their work!
l have to do it all by myself.
''As of today, no music recitals.
From today...''
only you will sing and only
you will listen. No audience.
Even in my own house my
songs aren't appreciated.
So how will others appreciate them?
''Because of your aunt's behavior,
l never became a great singer.''
''l know, l know...
Now have a cup of tea.''
''No, l don't want any tea.
- Oh come on, uncle.''
Have a cup of tea...
and sing a song for me.
Will you listen to my song?
- Of course.
Really?
- Certainly.
So let me have the tea!
Parcel for you.
lt's from Ajay!
Should be his cassette.
''Hear my song first.
- Later, uncle... please!''
See that? You have always
driven away my audience!
What are you dreaming about?
l was thinking how fast time flies.
lt seems like yesterday
that Mr. Khanna and Geeta...
had that accident and
Pooja came to our house.
''And now, it seems as if we
have no existence without her.''
And l have never seen such
close friends as Pooja and Ajay.
''Hey, fatty! How are you?''
''Shut up, l'm not fat.''
l've heard that nowadays you're
really packing your food away.
Don't do that or no
one will marry you!
ldiot! Don't worry about my marriage!
Who's going to marry you?
''By now, you must have finished
cursing me. So l'll proceed.''
''l'm having fun, as usual, and
work and girls are keeping me busy.''
Tell you what? l never
realised how handsome l am.
Don't make faces. lf you wish l
can fax you a list of my girlfriends.
''No, thank you.
- For your information...''
l've left Tina because she
doesn't like Hindi films.
Thank God. She was really stupid..
And now my heart is elsewhere...
- Who is she?
''Don't yell, l'm telling you.
She's called Dolly.''
There's no need to worry.
She really likes Hindi movies.
''Wow!
- Oh, l forgot.''
l may be coming to
Bombay for a few days.
When?!
- No need to stand. Sit down.
''lt's not fixed as yet. As soon
as l get to know, l'll tell you.''
''Okay, l'm off. Dolly is coming and
even though you haven't told me...''
l'll give her your love.
- There's no need.
''Okay, l won't... Hey! Here she comes!''
''Okay, l'm going. Give mum
and dad my love! Take care, bye''
''Hi! Hey Nisha, where've you put
that cassette you took from my car?''
You know there was a really
important track on it of our play.
Anything that goes into
your room vanishes forever.
Where the hell is the cassette?
- Rahul...
you have no manners. You must
knock before coming into a girl's room.
ls there a girl here?
''l am! Stop it, Rahul! l'm serious!''
''Look, don't talk to me in
this girly girly way. Please!''
You have also entered my
room when l had nothing on. So?
''That's different.
- Why? My honour's not honour, eh?''
''Shut up, Rahul...
- You shut up!''
''Go on now,... get my cassette.''
''First say sorry, then
you'll get the cassette.''
Must l say sorry ?!
- Yes.
Say sorry to you ?
''l'll fix you, Nisha!''
Don't play stupid games with me!
- You stupid!
''lf l catch you, you're dead!
- l'm not giving it to you!''
''Come on, give me back my cassette!''
Give it to me!
- l won't!
''Give it to me, l say!
- Okay, okay.''
Now say you're sorry!
- Sorry for what?
Sorry that you've wasted
my time and made me run.
''l'm not saying sorry.
- You won't, eh?''
l'm sorry!
- Say you'll never annoy me again!
l'll never annoy you.
- Say: Rahul is the best.
Never!
Rahul is the best. Okay?
- l know. Thank you very much.
''Rahul is the worst! Rahul
is a dog, Rahul is a monkey!''
Whatever happens l
shan't dance in your play!
So be it. There are
plenty of dancers like you!
There's no one who dances like me!
My wedding has been fixed.
- Wedding?!
l'm sorry.
''What's wrong with you, Anjali?
You're going to marry someone...''
you haven't chosen?
Someone you hardly know?!
l do know him. He's
the son of Mr. Kapoor.
l've known him for years.
- But you don't love him.
''Well, Pooja,... love
will happen in due course.''
''Love happen in due course?
What are you saying, Anjali?''
''We're not kids anymore, Pooja.''
lt's time we emerged
from our world of fantasies.
We are lndian girls.
The lovers of our dreams and
our husbands are not the same.
Someone else chooses
our husbands for us.
We learn to love them.
''This is the truth and the
sooner you realise it, the better.''
''Don't make this mistake, Anjali.''
''Someone, somewhere is made for
you and you should wait for him.''
Perhaps he is the one.
l believe that this is the
one who was made for me.
And l'm going to live
through with this belief.
And who knows? This
might happen to you.
Tomorrow you might marry a
man whom you merely know...
and slowly you might realise that
he was the one you were waiting for.
Nothing like this will happen to me.
l'll choose my husband myself.
''This is impossible, Rahul.
There can't be a girl like this.''
Meaning?
- lt's a meaningless character.
Maya exists only in your dreams.
Modern girls aren't like this.
What do you know? You're not a girl.
''Stop it, Rahul. l'm serious.
Modern girls...''
Maya is not one of these
modern girls. She's different.
She is my Maya.
''Your Maya, indeed! What
do you know about girls?''
You know only one. And that's me!
What do you mean? l don't
know anything about love...
and yet l make love stories.
What of it?
''Rahul, your Maya is really crazy.''
Don't you call my Maya crazy! And
you are the only one who feels this.
Nobody else is saying anything.
- Definitely!
''Rahul, l think Nisha is right.
- Thank you.''
l don't understand 'Maya' either.
Her character seems false.
Looking at it from a
psychological point of view...
l'm sure that you're on your own trip.
On a fantasy trip.
''l'm sorry, Maya is not in.''
Do you also want to say something?
- l think we need a lunchbreak.
Exactly! See?
- l don't know...
if such a girl exists or not...
and l don't want to know.
''Whether she is a lie, a
fantasy or mad or whatever...''
That is Maya.
''lf you cannot understand this,
l'm very sorry, l can't help it.''
But under no circumstances am l
going to change the character of Maya.
Excuse me.
- What's this!
l think Rahul's right.
You shut up. You are Rahul's yes-man.
- l was only saying that....
Okay... what were you saying?
Do you know of such a girl?
ls your Soni like this?
- No.
You figure the character of Maya?
Should we do this play ?
- Never.
''That's exactly what l've been saying!
- Right, but...''
Not again!
''That innocent face''
''The mischief in her eyes''
''Oh my!''
''That innocent beauty,
with mischief in her eyes...''
''stands afar shying away''
''Oh my!''
''For a fleeting moment she
shows herself and then turns away''
''lf you look with my eyes, friend,
you can see her''
''She's no ordinary girl,
she's a wonder''
''How else can l describe her?''
''Last night l dreamt of her...
her hair flowing wildly''
''When l woke up, l wished l
could go back to my dream''
''lf this how l feel
without meeting her,...''
''what will happen when l do?''
''Dark as the monsoon
clouds is the kohl in her eyes''
''Her gait has the grace
of the waves in the ocean''
''Wonder what HE used
to create her body''
''l wish she appears
before me out of nowhere''
''Rahul, how do you
like this? Hold this.''
Perhaps you haven't noticed
but everyone is staring at us.
So what? l don't care.
- But l'm looking funny.
Oh come on. How do
you like the orange?
Very nice...
- l'll be back in a moment.
Shopping?
- Yes.
Alone?
Very good! Never make the
mistake of going shopping with a girl.
''How d'you like it? Cool, isn't it?
- You like it?''
l like it very much.
- l love it! Let's go.
Once you've tried it on.
- Both of us like it... let's go.
To hell with Rahul!
So sweet!
- What did you say?
''Nothing, nothing at all. Off you go!''
Who is it?
- Aw... sorry!
Okay? Happy?
Why are you laughing? What's up?
- Where are your jeans?
l'm wearing it...
lt happens.
Who's there?
Crazy!
Happy birthday to you.
Everybody clap... Open the cake box.
How did this happen?
What happened and when did it happen?
How did this get swapped over?
l had ordered a chocolate cake.
You picked up someone else's parcel.
- l'm so stupid! l should've checked.
''l'm sorry, uncle.
- lt's all right, dear.''
Other people celebrate their
birthdays by cutting a cake.
l'll celebrate mine by
cutting sandwiches. No big deal.
Let me see who got my cake.
Who's this Pooja?
- l don't know.
And who's this uncle?
- Must be Pooja's uncle.
''First time l sent you out, and you
end up picking the wrong parcel.''
What have l done? l brought the
parcel the shopkeeper gave me.
But you should have checked.
- Excuse me...
''but it wasn't up to me to check.
Next time, do it yourself.''
l am hungry. This
cake looks really good.
Stop it. No one's eating this cake.
- Why not?
Because it belongs to someone else.
- They must be eating our sandwiches.
There's an address written here.
lt's nearby. Go and deliver it.
Are you mad?
''This is someone's birthday cake,
ordered with love.''
Someone's party will be ruined.
Go and give it back.
l'm not going.
Damn Rahul!
''Jimmy, let's go and give it
back and say 'Happy Birthday!'.''
So sweet!
- What did you say?
Nothing.
Yes?
''Good evening. Are you uncle?
- No, l'm aunty.''
''Actually, by mistake l
got your cake, aunty.''
The sandwich man!
- That's right.
Here's your cake...
wishing you a happy birthday.
Thank you and sorry.
Why sorry?
- Because l've eaten your sandwiches.
''That's all right. Actually, l ate
a bit of your cake on the way here.''
No wonder...!
''Okay, l'll be off Uncle.
- No. Come in and have some cake.''
No thanks. l'm in a hurry.
Some other time.
''Just a minute. Just
one minute, please.''
''Let the person who
bought this cake, thank you.''
''There's no need.
- No, no!''
''That poor man, whose
sandwiches you picked up by mistake...''
has brought the cake back.
- How sweet!
He's at the door. Go and thank him.
The cake has brought a
twinkle in my eyes...
and a musical rhythm to
the strings of my heart.
Strange man.
Why are you buying all these stuff?
''Oh, Anjali... Today is Valentine's Day''
What is this 'Valentine's day'?
- Don't you know?
The man you love most in the
world is called your Valentine.
''On this day, all lovers let
their hearts out to each other.''
This is all about love.
You won't understand.
Very funny! But whom are you
buying all these things for?
For myself.
- What?
''You see, l don't have a lover
who'd buy me all these lovely things.''
l'm doing this for my own pleasure.
- You've gone quite mad.
''Do you know, today isn't
an ordinary Valentine's Day.''
lt falls on the same day as the
full moon. Know what this means?
''l don't, but l'm sure
you're going to tell me.''
''lt means that, if you believe
that someone is made for you...''
''and you are waiting for
him with a true heart,...''
you will certainly meet him today.
- And you really believe this?
Of course. l'm absolutely sure...
that before midnight l
shall meet my soulmate.
Pooja! You're really mad!
- That l am.
''Damn Rahul! l'm going home. lf you
want to come with me, then come on.''
''Rahul, we all came together
and we'll all go together.''
''This is a very boring party. lf
you want to come, then come on.''
''Rahul, you don't get any better.''
''Look, how beautiful is the night...
and you're so unromantic.''
''Look, everyone's so much in love.''
You think that they're all in love?
Of course.
- Sit down.
''Tell me something, Nisha. You
think you know what love is?''
''Love is when you're so fond of
someone, that your heart tells you...''
you want to spend the whole
of your life in his arms.
That's what we call love.
- l see. You think the people here...
want to spend the rest of
their lives with each other?
l think so.
- Girls are so daft.
''Do you know, most of these
romances will be over before tomorrow?''
They'll fight over small things...
and will never see
each other after tonight.
''And next year, you will
see the same faces,...''
at the same places in different arms.
''Boys are also really stupid.
- l'm telling you the facts, Nisha.''
You must realise that you need
to know someone really well...
to spend your life together.
- That's right.
And in order to know someone well
you need to spend time together?
''True.
- ln today's times, who has the time?''
''Look; among all these party guests,
no one's known each other...''
for as long as we've known each other.
Does that mean that we can
spend a lifetime with each other?
Let me put it this way. Will you
be able to spend a lifetime with me?
''Here you are, Rahul. And
everyone wants you outside!''
Why?
- Everyone wants a song from you.
''Oh no...
- Oh, come on!''
''Tell me, will you be able
to spend a lifetime with me?''
''Yes Rahul, l can.''
l could spend my whole life with you.
''The moon whispered something...''
''which the night heard...''
''The moon whispered something,
which the night heard''
''Did you hear,...''
''lt said, fall in love''
''Fall in love''
''The moonlight came...''
''to my street and to
my house, to say...''
''fall in love''
''What can l say, what can l do?''
''This strange thing
that has happened to me''
''lt is a sign or did
my heart whisper...''
''fall in love''
''l can't explain, but l am
certain that there is someone''
''He is somewhere in my dreams,
but l cannot see him''
''l am here... he is somewhere there''
''But who is this who says...''
''Fall in love''
''l could die for him,
yet he is oblivious''
''But l can't complain. l
cannot call him unfaithful''
''l can hear him... even
though he is yet to speak''
''O my heart, be careful...''
''when you fall in love''
Hello?
- Are you mad?
Are you out of your mind? How
can you return just like that?
You said we had come together
and we'd all leave together.
Then you run away all on your own.
You know that we're all worried.
ldiot! Stupid! Fool!
Hello?
''This is not 6 7 1 1 2 3 7, is it?''
No.
- l thought so.
''l'm sorry, l thought
it was someone else.''
You're right. l am someone else.
l'm really sorry. Please excuse me.
''lt's okay.
- Thank you... hang on, one minute.''
''Don't hang up, please.
- Yes?''
The music you're playing...
''that's Pundit Shiv Kumar
Sharma's new album, isn't it?''
Yes.
- l thought so.
''You know, l wanted to buy it.
Where did you buy it from?''
From Rhythm House.
- l haven't been there.
D'you think they'd have it in stock?
- How would l know?
''l'm so stupid. How would you know?
You don't work there, right?''
l'm really sorry about all this.
lt's okay.
- Good night
Good night.
- l'm really very sorry
lt's okay.
- Happy Valentine.
Happy Valentine.
Nice voice.
''Ajay, you idiot!''
How dare you do this to me?
You scared the hell out of me!
Now l'm not going to give
up until l've got you. Stop!
How about it?
Cut it!
''Ballu! What are you up to?
- Why, what's wrong, Rahul?''
The spotlight should move from me to
Nisha after the drum roll. l told you
And l thought...
- Shut up.
''Come on, Nisha... do it again.
Let's take it from the top''
Rahul...
- Damn Rahul! What is it?
Please pack up early today.
- Why? What's special about today?
''Nothing. Come on.
- C'mon, let's take it from the top.''
''Rahul, you forgot?
Today is her birthday.''
Really? Why didn't someone tell me?
''Nisha, what's wrong with you?
Why didn't you tell me?''
''There are some things, Rahul,
which one knows without being told.''
Even then... you people
should have said something.
''Honestly, you guys are the limit...''
Rahul! Just relax!
- l'm very angry.
You've been forgetting all these
years. This is just another year.
Stop putting on an act and take
us all out to dinner. Come on.
''Come on guys, let's go.
- Nisha...''
What is it?
Happy birthday.
You remembered...?
Why didn't you say it?
There are some things which
one knows without being told.
''You idiot! Thank you.
- lt's okay, Nisha.''
Let's rehearse!
''Just joking. Come on, everybody.''
''Okay everybody, Tequila time!''
What are you guys drinking?
- Tequila.
l want some.
- This isn't for ladies. Have Pepsi.
''No, l want some.
- l told you! This is not for you!''
Today's my birthday.
- Happy birthday.
Thank you. l'll do as l please.
''Okay, suit yourself.
Give me another glass.''
So sweet.
- What...?
Nothing.
You're in love? Give over!
l know your kind of love.
lt changes every week.
''This is your kind of love, not mine.
- You mean, the marrying kind?''
Really? Who's the girl? Do l know her?
''Really well.
- Tell me who she is, please!''
Must l?
- Shoot!
Forget it.
That hurt!
Okay! One... two... three... go!
Didn't l tell you?
lt's not for ladies!
One more!
Damn you!
''Please, Ajay! Tell me who she is!''
Right then. We'll do this.
See that waiter?
Which one?
- The one serving water.
Keep looking at him. lf there's
still a glass of water on that tray...
by the time he gets to our
table then l'll tell you her name.
Promise?
- Promise.
Okay.
''Oh my God! Excuse me! A
glass of water, please!''
That's cheating. You can't do that.
Everything is fair in love and war.
Thank you!
- Everything is fair in love and war.
You idiot!
Nisha please... Nisha!
''Nisha, shut up!''
Shut up now... hush.
Don't say anything.
Say nothing at all...
''Take my shoes and give me money.
- Please... go to sleep, Nisha.''
Go to sleep. Good night.
''l'm afraid, Rahul.
Don't leave me l'm scared''
lt's really late. Now
quietly go to sleep! Good night!
First promise me
that you won't leave me.
''Okay, baby, l shan't leave you alone.''
''You won't leave me, even if l
ask for an ice-cream, will you?''
''No, l won't.''
''You won't leave me, even if l
don't dance well... will you?''
''No, l won't.''
''Not even if l call you names...
donkey, monkey... will you?''
''Of course, l won't.''
''You won't leave me, even if l tell
you that l love you... will you?''
''l love you, Rahul.''
''l really love you, Rahul.''
l love you.
There she is... still asleep!
''Come on, Pooja! lt's
seven in the morning!''
''The sun is up, Pooja.''
What the hell...!
You...? You idiot! ls this
the way to wake someone up?
''l'm so sorry, but seeing you fast
asleep, l just couldn't resist it!''
How could l miss out
on such an opportunity?
''You idiot! Stupid!
- l'm sorry... sorry, sorry''
''Listen, get ready quickly.
We've got to go to the airport.''
Airport? Are you going somewhere?
No. We are going somewhere.
''We? And where are we going?
- Well, that's a surprise.''
''lt's not far from lndia,
it's very near.''
We'll return by tonight's flight.
Get ready quickly!
l can't figure. What are you saying!
- Silly! lt's very simple.
l have to go on some business.
lt will take me just an hour...
just sign some
papers and then l am free.
''lf you come along, you'll see a
new city as well as do some shopping.''
And anyway l am leaving for London
tomorrow. That leaves only today...
which l want to spend
with you. So simple.
''But Ajay, l must find out if
it's okay with Uncle and Aunty.''
l've already got their approval.
lt's only you who has to decide!
''So fatty, are you coming or not?
- Of course, l'm coming!''
Then hurry up and get ready.
The flight is on time.
Wait a minute....
What's that under your eye?
Where...?
''Now wait, you fatty...!''
Never mind. l'll get you for this.
- Come and get me.
''You're going shopping,
aren't you? We'll see!''
''The heart is crazy, the heart is mad''
''The very first time lovers meet...''
''it sets their bodies on fire''
''Very slowly it teaches love...''
''it makes them laugh,
and it makes them cry''
''The heart is crazy, the heart is mad''
''lt keeps them awake all night...''
''it steals the sleep from their eyes''
''lt shows true and false dreams,...''
''it makes them laugh,
and it makes them cry''
''Those who follow the heart...''
''are known to be crazy''
''They discover their destination...''
''but cannot find the path''
''l don't need to see his face...''
''l don't need to know his name either''
''l don't need to think or worry...''
''because my heart will know him''
''We all listen to
what the heart says,...''
''the heart doesn't listen to anyone''
''l've given my life to him...''
''yet everyone knows, but he''
''So be it, give up these stories...''
''and all these signs of madness''
''All people's worries are...''
''all thanks to this crazy heart''
''Well, Ajay sahib,...
it's time for you to go.''
Now l have to go.
- Did you say something?
''Pooja, l want to tell you something.
- Tell me. What is it?''
This quick business trip of a
couple of days was all a pretence.
l came here for something else.
lt's been eight
years since l left lndia.
''l've earned enough of respect,
money ... life has been too hectic.''
l want to settle down now.
And whenever l close my eyes...
to think whom l would like to
spend the rest of my life with...
it is always your face that l see.
l don't know how or when my
feelings for you turned to love.
But l don't know
anything about your mind.
Or if there is anyone
in your life or not.
That is what l came here to find out.
l don't know what you think about me.
l don't even know if you would
want to spend your whole life with me.
But l know for sure that l
love you and l want to marry you.
l'm going towards the departure gate.
Once l've got there
l'll turn round and look.
''lf your answer is yes,
then you'll be standing here.''
And if you're not here
then l'll understand.
''And one more thing. Don't forget
that whatever your decision is,...''
''we were friends, we are friends,
and we'll always be friends. Okay?''
''And who knows, tomorrow
it may also happen to you.''
Perhaps you will marry a
man whom you only know ...
but whom you don't love.
Then you will realise
later that he was the man...
for whom you were waiting.
What? But why did you
keep standing there ?
Sometimes l'm so happy when
l make someone else happy...
that l can't think of anything else.
''You should have seen his face,
Anjali! He was so happy.''
l have never seen him
so happy ever before.
''And your happiness? You
don't love him, Pooja!''
Love? Love will happen in due course.
And we are lndian girls. We
can't choose our life partners.
Someone else chooses
our life partners for us.
We learn to love them.
lsn't that true ?
At last you have left your
girlish dreams and become a woman.
''No, Anjali. The girl
has become a woman,...''
but she has not given up her dreams.
''She believes in them completely,
even now.''
She is sure that Ajay is the one
for whom she was always waiting.
''Perhaps, it was HE who was
taking His time to show her.''
l'm certain that Ajay
will make you very happy.
l hope so.
''What happened, Nisha? Take
her to the doctor, hurry!''
''Slow down, Rahul. We're almost there.''
Get a stretcher.
''Hi, doctor...
- There's no need to worry.''
lt's a small fracture.
She'll go home in a week or so.
l told you Nisha would
start dancing again in a week.
''l'm talking about going home,
not dancing. She can't dance...''
for another three months.
- Three months...?
''Yes, Rahul. Her
heel is very delicate.''
lf she doesn't take care then
this fracture could recur...
and it could be more serious.
Does she know this. May l see her?
Of course. You don't
need my permission.
''Thank you, doctor. l'll see you guys.''
Whose going to get me a cup of tea ?
God! You won't learn to knock.
Don't give me a lecture. l have
something very important to discuss.
''Yes, tell me.
- Can you see me properly?''
''How many fingers?
- Stop it, Rahul.''
''Okay! See, your Doctor Kapoor
isn't up to much, in my opinion...''
Get a check-up with another doctor.
- Why?
This doctor was talking about
getting you discharged in a week.
''So what?
- No, it's not done.''
lt's been difficult getting
you admitted into a hospital.
You should spend at
least a month or two in here.
''And while you are away,
we'll also have some peace.''
''Rahul, l hate you! You're so horrible!''
You're always making fun of me.
l hate you. You're so bad!
''Nisha, behave yourself. Sorry,
nurse. She has gone mad with the pain.''
''But don't worry, l'll take
care of her. l'm a psychologist.''
Yes?
- l'm sorry.
For what?
l've put you to so much of trouble.
You've taken all the
money from the sponsor...
and how will you get
a dancer so quickly?
''And for three months, l....
- Now look...''
there's no need for you to worry.
Damn Rahul! Why do you think?
You're a good dancer?
ln this town there
are many such dancers.
''Sure, but you'll never get...
- A dancer like you, right?''
Right.
- Now you don't worry about this.
You have a nice rest and l'll
come see you in the evening.
l'll bring some food. We'll
eat together. lt's a deal.
Bye.
- Bye.
''l know. Chinese, right?
- Right.''
Not to worry. lt will all work out.
- How will it all work out?
We've taken money from the sponsors
and paid a deposit for the stadium.
''And most of all, where will we
get another dancer like Nisha?''
''Come on, if we try, don't you
think we can find one good dancer?''
There are plenty of dance schools.
One is close to our rehearsal hall.
''We'll find a dancer there tomorrow.
- Yes, yes!''
''You're right. How about that,
Rahul? Come on! Relax!''
Whatever happens will be for the
best. Let's go and have some cold beer.
''You go ahead. l'm not in the mood.
- Come on, buddy!''
''Lay off, he's tired.
Come on, let's go.''
Take care.
- Let's go.
Maya... l'll find her.
''Water, water...''
Excuse me...
The sandwich man!
Shanti... has a parcel
come here by mistake?
l haven't come for a parcel today.
- Then tell me what l can do for you.
l want to meet your daughter.
- l don't have a daughter.
No daughter?
- No.
''Then sir, this Miss
Pooja Malhotra...?''
Pooja is like my daughter.
But how do you know her?
l saw her last night.
- Night...?
Where?
- ln the dancing school.
She dances beautifully.
- And so?
''So, l wanted to meet her.
- What for?''
l want to ask her something.
- What do you want to ask her?
''Sort of, would she, with me...
- With you... what?''
lf she wanted to work with me.
- What work?
l do plays. l'm looking for a dancer
- You are doing a play.
Yes.
Are you a director?
- Yes. l am sorry.
l am sorry! Why
didn't you tell me before?
''l said so, when you asked me.
- l am sorry. Come on.''
''Actually, l am a singer.
- l see.''
l've done years of practice. Sit.
''As it happens with
many great artistes,...''
you really don't
meet many connoisseurs.
You've met me today. You
don't know how lucky you are!
''l know, sir, but l
have come to meet Pooja.''
''Now that you have met me,
you will meet Pooja, too!''
''l won't give you more than 75 bucks.
- 80 bucks, no less.''
Only last week l
bought it at that price.
This is the right price.
Taste it and see how sweet it is.
l will give you only seventy-five.
''Show me the watermelon.
- Here you are, sir.''
''Seventy-five is the right price.
How many do you want, Madam?''
Just one.
- Pack this for Madam.
But...
- Oh come on!
lt's your first sale in the day.
And you're haggling for 5 bucks!
Be a sport!
Hi.
- Hi.
Recognise me? We met last night
at your dancing school. Remember?
''Oh yes.
- l'm, Rahul''
You must've heard of me?
- No.
''Well, never mind. Actually
you are a pretty good dancer.''
''Actually, l'm doing some music
shows and l need a special dancer...''
for a special role. When l
saw you dancing yesterday...
l thought that you
would be ideal for this.
So what do you think?
Would you be interested?
''No, thanks.
- l've had it!''
''Sir, watermelon!
- Dammit! My career's at stake!''
''Excuse me, but perhaps
you misunderstand me.''
l'm talking to you
about no ordinary show.
lt's a very high-class show
with a very high-class audience...
and l am sure you will also enjoy
doing it. Why don't you try it once?
''Not for me, for the sake of art.''
Dancing is my hobby.
- That's really good.
But l am afraid of dancing on
stage in front of an audience.
Why are you afraid?
- l don't think l can do it.
l'm sorry.
- No... problem.
Excuse me... l'm sorry.
''You see, l'm really in difficulty.
Actually, my lead dancer...''
has fractured her foot. l've already
taken all the money for the show.
''lf we don't perform, l'll suffer
monetarily, l'll also lose face.''
''Come just once for a rehearsal,
and if you don't like it, it's fine.''
''But please, just once.
Please come to the rehearsal.''
l'm really very sorry. l can't do it.
''You'll have to take someone else.
- l beg of you, please!''
What are you up to?!
- You don't know me. l'm stubborn.
l'll not go until you agree.
Please come just once to a rehearsal.
''Everyone's looking at us.
- Please... please come, just once!''
l'll come.
- Promise?
Promise.
- When? What time ?
Two O'clock.
- Can you come at one ?
''Okay, l'll come at one.
- Thank you very much!''
''You know that we are neighbors,
don't you?''
l know.
- Thank you very much!
''Ma'am! You'll come, won't you Ma'am?''
''Yes, you will!''
Yes?
For you.
He's mad!
''Rahul, you said that girl
would come at one o'clock...''
lt's four now. l
don't think she'll come.
''So what should l do? So if she
doesn't come, won't we do our play?''
l was only...
- Go and get on with your own thing.
''Okay, relax.''
''Ballu, put the
spotlight on the entrance.''
Hi.
- Hi.
You must've heard of me?
''Cut it! No, no!''
''No Pooja, no! You are
not dancing with abandon.''
You are concentrating
more on the steps and music.
l don't want to see
how well you dance.
l have already seen that
and you are very good.
l want to see whether
you are Maya or not.
l want to see the extent of
Maya's love and abandonment.
l want to see what happens
when Maya dances wholeheartedly.
Right? We'll try it once more.
''All right, music!''
Cut it!
Why don't you understand
what l'm trying to tell you?
Forget that anyone's sitting here.
Forget that the music is playing.
Forget that this is a rehearsal.
Just think of Maya.
l don't want to see you dance.
l want to see your madness!
Maya's madness...
''l'm sorry, Pooja.
- Don't touch me.''
''l'm really sorry, Pooja. l was just...''
Never in my life has anyone
spoken to me in such a way.
''l know, Pooja... but l'm an idiot.
l don't know how to talk to girls.''
''l told you, l can't do it.''
But you're doing it really well.
l am going on about this Maya.
l don't understand this Maya.
- Never mind...
l don't want to do this.
- Don't worry if you don't understand.
We don't have to do this today.
We can do it tomorrow. Okay?
l don't want to do it
tomorrow either. - Okay.
''Maya, relax.
- My name is Pooja!''
''Of course, it's Pooja.''
''l'm sorry... sit down, please.''
''l'm really sorry... Pooja, if you
don't want to dance, then don't.''
But please stop crying.
Don't want water? No problem.
''You see Pooja, it's my way
to yell during rehearsals.''
l wasn't having a go at you.
l was only trying to
explain to you about Maya.
''Pooja, perhaps you
didn't understand Maya.''
Maya is the kind of girl
who lives in a dream world.
She believes that one day her dream
prince will come and carry her away.
Her friends have
always made fun of her...
but that did not shake her belief.
''And today, she has met
the man of her dreams...''
and she is dancing.
There is intense love in her dance
and madness and a certain arrogance.
''As if to say, ''l knew he would
come and now, see, he has come''
''My dream man has come''
Music!
Brilliant! Absolutely brilliant
''Nisha, l can't believe we got
such a good girl so quickly.''
''Had l not got the right girl for this
role, l'd have cancelled the play...''
''given back the money, and
willingly faced the music.''
But l was destined to meet Pooja.
''Her name is Pooja?
- No, it's Jeetendra.''
Of course it's Pooja.
ls she beautiful?
- Really beautiful.
Remember how l used to
describe Maya? She's just like her.
''That innocent face, those
dreamy eyes and that bashfulness.''
''She is too good,
Nisha, she is brilliant!''
ls she a good dancer?
- When she dances...
you can only keep
looking at her. l know that...
you will go crazy when you see her.
- l see.
But can she act?
''What? Of course, she can. lf
she can't act, what am l for?''
lf l can get you to act
l can get anyone to act.
Very funny.
''There's no water, no soft drink...
and you've called me for dinner.''
Wait a minute and l'll bring some.
ls she as good a dancer as me?
Are you crazy? There's no
dancer as good as you. Right.
Right.
ldiot. Can't even lie properly.
Torn!
The stitch...
''May l say something, Pooja?
- What?''
''When you laugh, you know...
- l know that l look good.''
When you laugh it starts to rain.
''With the gait of a horse,
with the majesty of an elephant''
''O King of the Rains,
where are you from?''
''l know a girl, when
she smiles,... it rains''
''l know a boy, when
he sings, it rains''
''The clouds have descended...''
''They have blocked our path''
''Tell us what your intentions are...''
''will you not let us go home?''
''There's rain ahead, a storm behind''
''The weather is treacherous...
Oh, where can we go?''
''The sky has lowered...''
''Everything has come to a standstill''
''How lovely is this season of shadows''
''Take it as the sign of the times''
''ln such a weather, say something...''
''...do something! Why
do you stand silent?''
The doctor has said clearly that
you can't go out of the house.
There's no need for you to
strain yourself trying to get up.
Now settle down quietly.
Whom are you phoning
the minute you've got here?
''Oh yes, he called to say
that he's at Soni's house.''
''At Soni's? Oh yes, today's
Soni and Jimmy's engagement.''
''Aunty, get my clothes out quickly.
l want to go there.''
''Look, l'll phone the doctor.
- Aunt, please!''
She just won't listen!
l hate these weddings. l don't
understand why people get married.
lf two people have decided to
spend their whole lives together...
why are the others making such a
fuss? Why are all they getting excited?
These days it has become fashionable
to have seven days of ceremonies...
''and merriment at weddings.
Forget it, buddy.''
''Get married, have a quiet
ceremony and then go home and sleep.''
l've even come to hate
the word 'marriage'.
''Excuse me, may l have another?''
But the one good thing is
that in all this fuss...
you get lots of goodies
to eat. Have you eaten?
Later.
- Let's sit.
l really love weddings.
''The different small ceremonies,
dancing, singing, and making merry...''
they're what l love.
- Very good.
l'm going to have all
of them at my wedding.
Are you getting married?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me?
When are you going to do it?
''Actually, nothing's
fixed yet. He works abroad.''
When he comes back then...
we'll fix a date when
we've found an auspicious time.
That's why l haven't
mentioned this to anyone.
l see. Congratulations.
Thanks.
''Rahul, when's your wedding with Nisha?''
Nisha and me? Have you gone mad?
The two of us are just good
friends and there's no chance of us...
''ever getting married and in any
case marriage and me, no thank you.''
''Actually, l don't believe at
all in these wedding ceremonies.''
l don't know how a person decides to
spend his whole life with another.
l fail to understand
and l'm certain...
There can't be a girl who
could spend her whole life with me!
You're mistaken in your thinking.
There is such a girl.
Where is she?
- Somewhere or the other.
Rubbish!
''l believe that in the beginning,
God made all the relationships.''
But then HE left it to
us to find each other.
HE created us all as couples.
For every one of there is a soulmate.
You just have to
wait till you meet her.
Do you think this is true?
This is the truest thing in my life.
True!
That means that you
have met your soulmate.
Yes. l have met him.
Something's amiss.
- What?
The ice cream's good. Have some.
- No.
Nisha! When were you
discharged from the hospital?
l ran away from hospital.
- Great! Jimmy and Soni...
will be delighted to see you.
- Where are they?
''Over there, go and meet them.
- Rahul is there, isn't he?''
Rahul's gone to drop Pooja home.
Thanks. See you tomorrow.
lt's that story you
told me at Soni's.
''That some special girl is
made for me... etc, etc...''
l've been thinking about that.
l didn't understand something.
- What?
How will l know who's made for me?
You have such faith in this
theory that you must know...
how l am going to
meet this girl also.
''l mean, will she be wandering
about with a board with my name on it?''
''Or, when l see her will there be a clap
of thunder and a bolt of lightning?''
Or will music start to play?
What will happen ?
''HE will tell you, HE
will give a sign...''
and your heart will
realise who the girl is.
l've even reasoned with her...
but she doesn't listen.
She does what she wants.
- Hi doctor.
''Rahul, it's good that you came.
This girl has worried me.''
Why? What happened?
- l told her clearly that...
''she needs to stay at home to rest.
But you see, she's packing her bags...''
and getting ready to go somewhere.
- Where to?
How would l know? l've tried my best
to explain. She doesn't listen to me.
''Well, only you can convince her.''
''Don't worry, she won't go anywhere.
l'll just go and twist her ear.''
Best of luck. See you.
- Bye
''What are you doing,
Nisha? Have you gone mad?''
''The doctor told you to rest, right?
By the way, where are you off to?''
l'm going to London.
- London?
''Well, Mum and Dad keep phoning
me asking me to go to see them.''
Months have gone by.
''l think l'll go to see them.
Besides, l want to run away from here.''
Want to run away...? From whom?
''From myself.
- What's all this nonsense, Nisha?''
''l've begun to get
scared of myself, Rahul.''
''l want to go, to avoid committing
mistakes, like l did one yesterday.''
''Nisha, you haven't
done anything of the sort.''
You only danced. Look here...
- Rahul...
now we should stop playing
hide and seek with each other.
We both know what the problem is.
What's the problem?
The problem is that l love
you and you don't love me.
''Look here, Nisha...
- l know...''
that you know how much l love you.
That night l wasn't so out of it...
that l couldn't hear
what my heart was saying.
''Actually, Rahul, we have
become such good friends...''
that we take each other for granted.
So l think that a bit of
space will give us time to think.
''But l am sure that when l'm not here,
you'll remember me often.''
Then perhaps you will
start caring for me.
''One thing is certain,
that an idiot like you...''
doesn't deserve a girl like me.
''And l don't why, but l
feel that when l come back,...''
you will be on your knees
begging me to get married to you.
And who knows at that point...
l may not want to marry you.
''Well, perhaps you
haven't seen your face...''
lt's better than yours.
Nisha...
you're really nice.
''l know. Come on now, l got say bye to
everyone before going to the airport.''
''Come on, Rahul, hurry up.''
We haven't been properly introduced.
Let's start from the beginning.
Hi! l'm Nisha.
l'm Pooja.
''Now that we are friends, will you
forgive me for what l did yesterday?''
Forgive you? For what?
''Pooja, what l did with
you yesterday, wasn't right.''
''Actually, ever since
this place was built,...''
l'm the only one who's
danced on this floor.
This floor has become my trademark.
So when l heard that someone
else was dancing in my place...
l felt bad.
''Without seeing you or
knowing you, l felt jealous.''
l shouldn't have felt that way.
''Had l been in your place, then
perhaps l'd have done the same.''
''Moreover, l really
enjoyed dancing with you.''
You were the one dancing.
l was doing something else.
l am really sorry.
- lt's okay
''Come on, Nisha, it's
time for your flight.''
l always told Rahul that there
could never be another dancer like me.
But l can't say that anymore.
And l'm sure that no one can perform
the role of Maya better than you.
''Not even me. All the best,
bye. See you.''
Bye.
Hi. l'm Rahul.
Perhaps you've heard of me?
l'm looking for a special
dancer for a special role.
l saw you dance yesterday and
felt you would be ideal for this.
''Check, check... 69...''
''Ballu, what are you doing?
Angle the spotlight properly.''
''Pooja, good, good. But...''
l think that you
aren't dancing freely.
l want to see how Maya
looks when she's happy.
l want to see the extent of
Maya's madness and love. Okay?
Do it again. Okay!
Quiet everybody. Take it from the top!
Music!
Cut it! Cut it!
''Haven't l told you to forget
that you are you, to forget that..''
people are sitting here. Forget that
there's a rehearsal going on here.
Pack up!
''One thing l don't understand, Pooja.''
''How l will know which girl
was made for me? l mean,...''
will she be wandering about
with a board with my name on it?
''When l see her, will there be a clap
of thunder and a flash of lightning?''
''Oh dear, what's happening?
l don't really know''
''l only hope this does
not turn into a romance''
''Oh dear, what's happening?
Nobody really knows''
''But if this is a romance,
then so be it''
''Take my hand in yours,
as long as you are here''
''Let us keep talking,
as long as we can''
''Let's sit here
looking at each other,...''
''as long as the night remains.''
''What name can l give
this season of my heart''
''Even the dewdrops seem to burn,
with the fever of my heart''
''Why do l feel as if
someone has caressed me''
''Please go away for a while,
so l can collect my feelings''
''And quieten the
violent beating of my heart''
''Let's slow down so that we
don't move ahead too fast''
''There is something
between us, don't deny it''
''And if something further
happens have faith in your feelings''
''For you should know, your
heart is not what it was''
''Oh dear, what's happening?
- l don't really know''
''l only hope this does not...
- turn into a romance''
''Oh dear, what's happening?
- Nobody really knows''
''But if this is a romance...
- then so be it''
l hope your uncle will be asleep
so l won't have to hear him sing.
Bye.
- Bye
''Rahul, l forgot to tell you...
- What?''
l can't attend rehearsal tomorrow.
- Why?
Tomorrow l'm going to Khandala.
- Khandala? Why ?
My teacher lives there.
- Which teacher?
My dance teacher. She
taught me everything l know.
Tomorrow it's her birthday.
''lf l say no, will you not go?''
''l shall go, but if you
say yes, l'll go happily.''
l'm joking. Go on. l'll
rehearse with someone else tomorrow.
Thanks. Bye.
- Bye.
l've had it.
Rahul...? What are you doing here?
l have a friend in Khandala.
He's been inviting me for ages...
but l've never had a chance to go.
And since we can't work without you...
l thought l'll meet him
and give you a ride too.
You've no one with you so l
thought it'll be company for you.
What are you staring at? Hurry up!
lf we go early we'll beat the traffic.
''Well, why are you smiling ?
- No reason.''
Let's go.
- Today l'm really missing my friend.
''Tommy, quiet! Quiet!''
They won't do anything.
l'll be right back. Stay here.
''Don't worry, they won't
bite you. l'll be back.''
Want some soft drink?
''Sandhya, what are you doing?
l'll give you a good slap.''
''Glutton, you have become
so fat, you can hardly move.''
No chocolates or ice creams
for you. Get it right this time.
Move the neck. Arms straight.
Why are you laughing?
Close your mouth.
lf anyone gets it wrong then
no one will watch TV tonight.
''Don't come begging me again,
Please Tai ! Please Tai !''
Look! Here comes your dear Pooja!
''Tai, how did you recognise me?
- There's no need to act smart.''
l recognise all the girls
from the sound of their steps.
Happy Birthday to you!
What's this? You've
brought me another ugly sari.
''Yes, l chose the ugliest
l could get my hands on.''
Where you are going?
The class isn't over yet.
Now l'm here... the class is over.
- You're spoiling them rotten.
They behave well all through
the year. And the day you come...
they start misbehaving.
- Sometimes one should be spoilt.
Tai! Wait!
Rahul is my friend.
- Your friend?
''Leave him, children.
- Go on, children... go inside!''
Why are you so frightened?
Happy Birthday!
What are you up to?!
- l'm trying to touch your feet.
''Do l look that old?
- No, but out of respect..''
Give me your hand...
- Pardon me?
Your hand.
Nice to meet you!
''Come on, you've caught a cold.
Come, let's go in.''
Save me from the dogs.
- They won't hurt you.
''Tai, who's he?''
l don't know but l
will have to find out.
''Pooja, you didn't tell
me what Rahul does.''
Rahul...he directs plays.
Nowadays l'm working with him.
l see.
l think that you
don't like Rahul specially.
''No, l like him very much.''
Very much?
''l mean, he's a good friend.''
Good friend? You
mean you don't love him.
''Tai, Rahul's just a friend.
A dear friend.''
l see... a dear friend.
lt's not like you think and in any
case l wanted to tell you something.
There's no need to tell me.
l understand everything.
''Stop it, Tai. Tai,
you've got it wrong.''
''Rahul, what's up?''
Nothing. Why are you standing
with the spoon? Come join us.
Stupid!
- Hey everybody!
''Come on everyone,
follow me... this way.''
''lf it's not love, then what is it?''
''Tai,... honestly!
- Look here, girl!''
l've known you since you
were twelve years old.
''What your heart doesn't
let you know, it tells me.''
The look in your eyes says
that you love this boy very much.
Now stop lying to me... okay?
''Just a dear friend''... big deal!
- Listen, Tai...''
''l don't remember when this happened''
''lt's become hard to hide
this secret from everyone''
''lf you say so, today
l'll ask God for something''
''Oh dear, what's happening to you?
- Beats me''
''l just hope this doesn't turn...
- lnto a romance''
''l see, so when is Ajay coming back?''
Nothing is definite but
he could come at any time.
l'll be right back.
''Pooja, give me your hand.
- Why?''
l won't hit you! Give me your hand.
What's this?
Listen carefully to what
l'm going to tell you.
Ever since you were a child...
you have always
considered others before yourself.
l have always been
overwhelmed by your behavior.
But today you have made me sad.
But l...
- Quiet!
Sometimes it's very
important to consider ourselves.
l see that you are
running away from your dreams.
You won't let them
come true. Don't do this.
Not everybody is fortunate to
have their dreams come true.
Don't do this.
''Tell you something, one
happens to fall in love many times.''
True love only happens once.
You are failing to
take the right step.
Lord Ganpati will help
you to do what is right.
HE will give you the
strength to fulfill your dreams.
''Keep lt with you,
always. l have faith in lt.''
''The Lord will set everything right.
- l love you, Tai.''
Stop it! l don't
make a habit of crying.
Why are you frightened?
- Pardon me?
Why are you frightened of
being in love? Tell her.
''Love and me? l was just...
- Okay, give me your hand.''
Nice to meet you.
- Take it!
''What's this?
- This is, in a way, my blessing.''
l'm very mean in this matter. l
don't give my blessing that easily.
But when l saw you l
thought that perhaps you need it.
This will help you to say
what you are unable to say...
Keep it very carefully.
You get it?
- Got.
''She is coming. lf you can't
say it, then l'll say it...''
l'll say it.
Definitely?
- Definitely.
Mark my words carefully.
Bye!
- Bye
''Bye!
- Goodbye, sister!''
''Excuse me, ladies and gentlemen...
May l have your attention, please?''
''Aunty, please... thank you.''
Since l am Jimmy's best man...
l have the right to make a speech...
and you all have to listen to it.
''Until today, l didn't understand
how two people can take a vow...''
to spend their entire
lives with each other.
l didn't believe in
these vows of marriage.
And seeing Jimmy and Soni together
only strengthened my conviction.
Because there can't be
anyone as innocent as Soni...
and there can't be a
scamp to beat Jimmy.
l used to worry that Soni
and Jimmy are too different...
to spend their lives together.
But today l realise that l was wrong.
l am a little ashamed to admit
that l have started believing in love.
''The kind of love in which
lips don't speak, eyes do.''
The kind of love that binds
two people together forever.
''And today, l keep
thinking of just one thing.''
l remember something a
very dear friend said:...
that God predetermined all
our emotional relationships...
but then HE left it to
us to find each other.
HE made us all couples and for
every one of us somewhere...
there is just one soulmate.
HE made Soni for Jimmy.
Today l thank God for
getting Jimmy and Soni together...
and l pray that HE may give
each one of us the ability...
to recognise our own soulmate.
Thanks.
''Rahul, you are strange.''
Soni and Jimmy have made their
farewells and you're still here.
''l don't like farewells.
- Okay, but drop me home, will you?''
My bangle?
''Rahul, have you seen my bangle?''
Damn! Now l am sure l won't find it.
lt was my favorite bangle.
''Mine, too.''
Rahul !
''Come on, give it to me.''
Come here and take it.
What childish behavior! Give it to me!
Come closer.
Here goes... happy?
''Closer...
- Rahul, stop it!''
Closer...
Closer still...
''How long shall we sit in silence?
We both want to say something''
''You say something, l'll
say something, my love''
''How long shall we sit in silence?
We both want to say something''
''You say something, l'll
say something, my love''
''We would rather have died than
reveal our secret, oh my love''
''You were a few steps away from me,
l was a few steps away from you''
''Yet we may as well have
been hundreds of miles apart''
''Step by step our wavering
hearts came together, my love''
''Come, you have won me over
and l am defeated by my heart''
''Today with great
difficulty my lips say 'love'''
''Now l'm madly in love...''
''don't ever leave me, my love''
''How long shall we sit in silence?
We both want to say something''
''You say something, l'll
say something, my love''
The set is ready.
''Good, well done. Call Pooja.''
Okay. Shruti Call Pooja.
''Pooja, we're ready.''
Are you angry with me?
- Not at all.
Then why aren't you speaking to me?
- l am speaking to you.
For three days l haven't seen
your face or heard your voice.
l was very busy.
l have been calling you everyday.
Why haven't you been answering ?
The phone has been out
of order for some time.
What is the problem?
Tell me. l want to know the
cause of your restlessness.
There's no problem.
- There is a problem.
Serious problem.
The fact is that we both
love each other very much.
We can't tell each other about it.
Today l've come here to tell you...
that l love you.
l love you very much.
And l know that you also love me.
''So then, say it once and that will
be the end of your restlessness.''
Everything will be all right.
l don't love you.
- You're lying.
l'm not lying.
- You aren't?
Look into my eyes and tell me
that we weren't made for each other.
We weren't.
''Tell me that when l go away from you,
that you don't turn to look at me.''
l don't.
''Tell me, when l touch
you nothing happens to you.''
Nothing.
- Tell me...
that you don't want to
come into my arms right now.
l don't.
Look into my eyes just once and
tell me that you don't love me.
l don't...
l don't!
Terrific performance! Very well done!
Nisha!
Hi.
- Great to see you back again.
But l am sure that when l'm not
here you'll remember me often...
''and when l get back, you will
be on your knees begging me...''
to marry you. And then
perhaps l may not want to.
''Well, l'll be off.''
l'm a little tired.
l'll see you all tomorrow.
What's up with Nisha?
- She's tired. She'll come tomorrow.
Don't get unnecessarily worried.
''l'm not a nice girl, Rahul.''
l'm bad. l'm really bad.
''No Nisha, you are my friend.''
And no friend of mine is bad.
''No, Rahul, you don't know
that l am not a nice girl.''
''Now you see, l love a boy
and have always loved him...''
and today l realised that he
doesn't love me. He loves someone else.
''l feel bad, l'm hurt...''
l'm upset. l feel jealous.
''Rahul, l shouldn't
feel like this. l am bad.''
''l am very bad. No, Nisha...''
''No, Rahul.''
''Actually, that boy
isn't just the one l love...''
but he's also my best friend.
''Today, for the first time,
l saw love in his eyes.''
''l couldn't put love
there in all these years,...''
but that other girl has.
Perhaps they are made for each other.
Perhaps l was never meant for him.
Perhaps her love for him is true.
''So you see, l should
be happy for my friend.''
l should revel in his happiness.
But l'm not happy... l'm not!
l'm very bad... really very bad.
''Nisha, you are not bad,
you are really nice.''
You know who is bad?
HE is bad...
THE ONE who plays
around with us humans...
''making A love B, while B loves C...''
and C loves D.... l
don't know why HE does this.
When HE makes one
person love another...
then HE ought to make sure that the
other one also loves her in return.
Right?
But that's not what HE does.
HE's really bad.
You're not bad. HE's bad.
You're right... lt's HE who's bad.
HE's bad!
YOU are bad. l am not. YOU are bad.
l haven't done anything wrong.
YOU are the one.
YOU are bad. YOU are bad.
''l'm sorry, Nisha.''
''Don't say sorry,
Rahul. Else, l'll cry.''
''l'm sorry, Nisha.''
''Don't say sorry, l'll cry.''
Ajay...
''when l was a little girl, you
used to tease me about my dreams.''
When l used to tell you that l am
looking for the one meant for me...
you would say that l am mad and silly.
You would smile and say
that when l grow up...
my dreams will vanish.
''But you know, l have grown up
and my dreams have not vanished.''
They have grown with me.
''That day, at the airport, when you
suddenly asked me to marry you...''
at first l didn't
realise what l should do.
''But then l thought, l was crazy...''
''you were my dearest friend,
and the one who knew me the most.''
Who could be better for me.
And l remained standing there.
You left and l made
you a part of my dreams.
l started believing that
you were the one made for me.
And then... and then l met Rahul.
Ajay! You're marrying Pooja?!
What are you saying?
But Pooja hasn't said
anything to me about it.
l had forbidden her from telling you.
l wanted to tell you myself.
l can hardly believe you! l am
so happy! When are you coming ?
l called just to tell you this.
l'm coming tomorrow.
Tomorrow...?
What can l tell you about Rahul?
Where do l start?
''Well, you should realise that
l've never met anyone like him.''
''Sometimes he's an angel,
sometimes a devil.''
Sometimes crazy...
and sometimes a genius.
Sometimes he scolds so harshly...
and sometimes he makes
funny faces to make me laugh.
At times he's more stubborn than a kid
and at times he's a beloved companion..
''ln three days? Oh no, l want time to
get things ready for a big wedding.''
''Ma, l don't have time. The company
is sending me to Japan for a year.''
You'll have to wait
for eight to ten months.
l can't wait that long.
''All right, you come here and
l'll start the preparations.''
''The dreams of your crazy
girl have come true, Ajay.''
She has found the
partner of her dreams...
and she wants your permission
to make all her dreams come true.
Can she make her dreams come true?
Ajay phoned just now.
He's told me everything.
''He's coming tomorrow, Pooja...''
...and he says to get the wedding
organised as quickly as possible.
You would tell me
your smallest secrets...
and you hid such a big one from me ?
Come here...
sit by my side.
''You know, Pooja, ever since
you came to this house,...''
''l've had a dream in which, one day,
you would become my daughter-in-law''
And l your mother.
''But l was apprehensive, l
didn't know how the two of you...''
would feel about each
other when you grew up.
Whether you would be friends
and care about each other or not.
''l also wanted that you should decide
if at all because you wanted it,...''
not for my sake.
l wanted you to choose Ajay
out of your own free will.
''You don't know how
happy l am, for l know...''
that there cannot be better
girl than you for my son.
Just watch. l'm going to
give you a grand wedding.
You have no idea how happy l am.
May you live long.
l want full lights and l want to see
M6 on both left and right of stage.
''Supandi, in a while l want
to hear the music tracks.''
''Soni, the elevation should
be three feet higher...''
or else the audience on stage
right will not know what is going on.
''When Ballu lights M6, one spot
light will filter here on this side...''
and the audience will get a
glimpse of the entry before it happens.
Hi Pooja.
l need to talk to you.
''The show opens in two days,
we'll talk later.''
Show me all the costumes of
act three. Go do some work.
''l have to talk to you.
- Pooja, just a minute.''
Okay... tell me what's the problem?
''Rahul, please try and
understand what l am about to tell you.''
''Rahul, Nisha is calling you.
The stadium has called.''
l forgot to talk to her. l'll
be right back. Where's Nisha?
Rahul please be serious...
Ajay...?
''My name is Ajay, but if you
like you can call me Rahul.''
Fatty! l love you!
l really missed you.
''Remember, l told you
that l'd come to get you ?''
Here l am. l came
here after meeting mom.
''She is so happy. Hey, l hope
you haven't changed your mind?''
''You're marrying me, aren't you?''
Have you told your friends?
- l was going to...
''Hear that! l'll have to do that, too?''
l'll tell them.
Ladies and gentlemen...
l'm sorry for the intrusion.
You don't know my name: it's Ajay.
l am Pooja's childhood friend.
And since she hasn't
found a worthy guy...
l took pity on her and l
am going to marry her.
Congratulations!
- Thank you very much.
''ln three days we are getting married
and you all must come, with family.''
''Pooja, you're weird. Why
didn't you tell us before?''
We had begun to feel
that you were our Maya.
We forgot you're Pooja and
you have your own private life...
...and your own relationships
and even prior commitments.
We are really stupid!
''Oh l forgot... Pooja, congratulations.''
Thanks.
- And this is...
''This is Rahul, our director.''
''Rahul, she likes your name a lot.
- She likes only the name...?''
''l hope so, man!
- Congratulations.''
''Thank you. Rahul, l have a request.
- Go on.''
May l take her away for an hour?
- Oh come on!
You are taking her
away forever from us.
''That will be in a
ceremonious way. Say what, Pooja?''
This is just a lunch date with Pooja.
Do l have your permission...?
My permission! Now l'll have to
get your permission to meet Pooja.
''Besides, now that you've come, Pooja
won't be happy here, will you Pooja?''
So go on. l'll get by without you.
''Are you sure?
- Yes, of course! Absolutely!''
You guys go and have
a good time. Go on.
We have his permission... let's go.
- Go on.
''Okay guys. Bye.
After three days, okay?''
''Ballu, show me the final mix.''
''Shruti, show me the sketches.''
''And Nisha, call up the
auditorium and tell them the sketches...''
will be with them by the evening.
ln two days we are going on stage...
Lights! why aren't you
showing me the lights.
There are just two days...
and you're taking it easy!
''Come on, the lights.''
''Shruti, show me the sketches,
Shruti, here, fast!''
Hurry up! We got to finish
the music rehearsals too!
This is our last meeting.
l'm getting married tomorrow.
l don't want to meet you
ever again after today.
Just think that l was
never a part of your life.
''As soon as l start to move,
track me with the spotlight...''
and the other will stay on Pooja.
''When l get right up to the audience,
then slowly dim the light.''
The show will be over... The End.
''That's it. Any questions? l
don't want any mistakes, okay?''
''Rajesh, everything all right?
- Yeah.''
''Okay then, tomorrow be
at the stadium on time.''
Pack up.
Something is bothering me.
- What?
l don't like the end of your story.
- Why?
This ending's too sad.
A love story should
always have a happy ending.
''The audience should
come out smiling, right?''
People like to live in a dream world.
''They have seen many dreams, now
let them see a little reality.''
Every love story is
like this in real life.
Full of sorrow and pain.
''No, Nisha, this ending
is absolutely right.''
There can't be another
end to this love story.
''l know a girl, when she smiles,...''
''it rains''
''l know a boy, when he sings...''
''Jimmy, just go and check
the next entry stage left.''
''The heart is crazy,
just refuses to listen.''
''Oh dear, what's happening?
l don't really know''
''l only hope this does
not turn into a romance''
''Oh dear, what's happening?
Nobody really knows''
''But if this is a romance,
then so be it''
Pooja's last entry is after this.
Get her ready and bring her here.
Don't worry. Nisha's getting her.
Thanks.
''Don't make this mistake, Pooja.''
Very few people are lucky
enough to love and to be loved.
''You can't break the tie,
which HE has ordained.''
You can't break it.
''l've spent my years giving
love the name of friendship,...''
now you are going to spend
the rest of your life...
giving friendship the name of love.
This is a betrayal! A betrayal of
love... a betrayal of friendship.
Don't do such a thing!
This is our last meeting.
l'm getting married tomorrow.
l don't want to meet you
ever again after today.
Just think that l was
never a part of your life.
l want to ask you
something before you go.
Did you ever love me...
even for a single
day or a single moment?
This line is not in the play.
- Raju!
Tell me just once...
have you ever really
loved me? Even for a moment?
What the hell is Rahul saying?!
l shan't go away until l
get an answer to my question.
l'm not going!
''Did you ever love me,
even for a single moment?''
No.
- What did you say?
l didn't hear that.
- No.
''Speak up, l couldn't hear.''
''No.
- Louder, louder..''
''No, l have never loved you.''
''Not for a day, not
for a moment. Never.''
That is all l wanted to hear.
''l'm Rahul,... you will
remember my name, won't you?''
What can l tell you about Rahul.
Where do l start from?
l have never met anyone like him.
''Sometimes he's an angel,
sometimes, a devil.''
''Sometimes he's crazy,
sometimes he is a genius.''
Sometimes he scolds very harshly
and sometimes he makes faces...
and makes me laugh.
Sometimes he is more
stubborn than a child is...
and sometimes he is
a beloved companion.
''What he is or is not, l
cannot really express in words...''
but l don't know why...
''When he looks at me,
l feel beautiful,...''
when he laughs l feel like dancing.
When he is upset l feel
like holding him in my arms.
When he loves me my
eyes fill with tears.
He has made me realise that l am
made for him... and he for me.
''l love him very much, not
for one day or one moment...''
but for my whole life.
''l love you, Rahul. l love you.''
''Now that l've seen them, l
believe that someone, somewhere...''
was made for me as well.
lsn't that true?
- Yes.
My name is Ajay. Yours?
l'm Nisha.
Are you married?
- What...?