Dehradun, a beautiful
paradise in the mountains...
...is situated far away from
hustle and bustle of humanity.
And in this paradise are
12 chosen school of India.
The very affluent
families of India...
...send their children here
for a good education.
Some own steel mills
and some, tea estates.
Every child is the
heir to millions.
Rajput School and College
is considered to be the best.
It excels in academics
and is the best at sports.
Similarly, Queens Junior
College is the best for girls.
The boys from all the
colleges are crazy about them.
There is a place called
Mallroad, is centrally located.
Here you find the shops
run by the locals.
The children of the poor locals
have an ordinary school.
The speciality of the boys here
is a poor academic record...
...and a good record
for bad behaviour.
The exams are
fast approaching...
...but the preparation at
Model College is different.
If they have any goal, it is the
girls from Queens college.
Like every year,
the exams are over.
There is going to be an Inter
College sports competition.
The entire colony is busy
discussing who will...
...be the winner of Inter
College cup, this year.
Squeeze it a little more.
Pass me the spanner.
- Ratan's cycle is ready?
- Just a while longer.
All right, I'll send Ratan over.
- Uncle, have some tea.
- No, I don't have the time.
Give me number 13.
Does Ratan have any chances
of winning the cycle race?
I don't know. But he is the
champion of our college.
- Hurry up. The boys are waiting.
- Yes, father.
Mr. Shakur, I am but a math
teacher at Model College.
Ask Mr. Ramlal about the probable
winners and losers in sports.
He is the coach.
Well, Mr. Ramlal, how are the
sports preparations getting on?
- Quite fine, Mr. Dube.
- Oh, really!
- Shakur, you'll take charge
for a few days. - Yes, sir.
Here is some money
for the expenses.
Why are you standing idle?
Don't you have to
train the Model boys?
Or... Have you given up
the idea of competing?
Since the time the Rajput boys
won the tournament last year...
...they seem to be walking
on air. The stupid...!
Criticism won't help. Our boys
will lag behind in every test.
That's not true, Mr. Dube.
I am not referring to Ratan but
to your younger son, Sanjay.
If he passes the exams this
year, I will distribute sweets.
I will do it... And plenty, too!
- Sanjaylal... I've found mine!
Only 2 marks! - Change it.
Pass it quickly... Have
you found yours?
- Hey! I've found mine.
- Let me have a look.
None of my sums are right.
Hurry up.
Hey, someone's here!
Who is there?
Thief! Stop him!
There he goes... Stop him!
Stop the thief!
Hey M ister, stop him!
- What were they doing?
- They were changing results.
- What happened?
- Everything's alright.
- Did Ratan tell father anything?
- No.
If father would have known,
that would be the end of me.
Once again I lied to uncle
Ramlal to protect Sanju.
I don't know why, but I believe
that I can do anything for him.
I am still unaware of
his feelings for me.
Ratan, you changed my marks
in math again, didn't you?
Yes, my dear.
I will fail and you will
be responsible for it.
Be grateful that I
did not tell father.
For then, you would have been
thrown out as you were, my dear.
Hey! I don't fear anyone.
Besides, why are
you patronising me?
- Do you know what your
problem is? - What?
You want to achieve success
without any hard work.
Don't you know
what integrity is?
Sure. You are the
epitome of integrity.
You are ' Mahatma Gandhi'...
you are 'Sarojini Naidu'.
Hold this.
Let me have a look. Wow!
Father was in great shape.
Hey, where did you find this?
In 1965 Model College beat
Rajput in the cycle race...
...for the first
and the last time.
My friends had brought me
home on their shoulders.
Neither have I, nor have the
rest of our locals forgotten it.
The same event will
take place tomorrow.
All eyes are on you, Ratan.
- Who are the brave boys?
- Rajputs!
- Who are the leaders?
At the Inter School
sports meet...
...Shekhar Malhotra,
the last year's...
...winner of Rajput College
is at the fourth position
Shekhar Malhotra is first,
Ratanlal Sharma is second.
And Randhir Thapar is
at the third position.
It appears that Sanjaylal
Sharma has sprained his ankle.
- What happened?
- I sprained my ankle, else...
Otherwise you would have come
first. What lame excuses!
Once again, Shekhar is first,
Ratanlal is second position.
Chances are that Rajput will
take championship once again.
Xavier's is leading at 245.
Rajput is second at 225.
- Model is third at 210.
- I sprained my ankle.
6 schools are participating
in this event.
The first baton has changed
hands at 100 metres.
Rajput College is in the
lead and Xavier's is next.
The baton has changed
hands again at 200 metres.
Model is at the second.
Whereas Rajput is still in the lead.
The third baton has been
passed to Shekhar Malhotra...
...and Ratanlal Sharma is
at his best to forge ahead.
And... What a wonderful
victory by Ratanlal Sharma.
And Model School gets
20 additional points.
That was wonderful, Mr. Ramlal.
The 100m hurdle
race has started.
And Ratanlal has displayed
a miracle once again.
But Rajput is still
at the same position.
According to
the score board...
...the Inter School
Championship is entirely...
...dependant on the
marathon cycle race.
It's tough competition between
Rajput, Xavier's and Model.
And now, whosoever
wins this cycle race...
...will be deserving of the
Inter School championship.
And the 50 km marathon
cycling has started.
The participants will leave the
stadium, on uneven terrain...
...to reach the highest
point and return.
We will be getting reports from
3 check points along the way.
'We will be successful'
' Model College'
The cyclists have
reached here...
...and they are proceeding at great
speed towards Baramulla Hills.
I, Rakesh Sharma from
Pillar Rock check point...
...welcome the
spectators at the stadium.
The cyclists will be
here at any moment now.
In first place, is Randhir
Thapar from Xavier's College.
In second place is
Vinay from Andrew's.
In third place is Shekhar
Malhotra from Rajput.
In fourth place is Ratanlal
Sharma from Model College.
And now the cyclists are
approaching the stadium.
At first place is Xavier's
followed by Lawrence...
Andrew's is third
and Peter's is fourth.
Next is Rajput
followed by Model.
The stadium has 5 tracks.
And Lawrence has
taken the lead.
Shekhar Malhotra
is trying his best.
And... he has
overtaken Peter's.
Ratanlal from Model
is just behind him.
They have forged
ahead of Andrews...
...and have now
crossed Lawrence, too.
They are in second place.
Now they have gone ahead of
Xavier's, taken the first place.
He missed by a hair's
breadth, Mr. Ramlal.
He would have defeated
Shekhar otherwise.
No, Dube I believe
in one motto alone...
..."He who wins
is the conqueror".
Rajput School is not
only famous for its...
A good education can be obtained
at any other place too.
The only difference is that
he boys of this school...
...are taught to be
leaders in every field.
The proof of this is the
Inter School Sports shield.
The person chosen as
the sports captain...
...this year is
the young man...
...who has taken
the responsibility...
...to win this shield.
He is Shekhar Malhotra.
I am sure that you will
win it the third time too...
...and set a new record.
- Who are the brave boys?
- Rajput!
- Who are the leaders?
- Sanju.
- Yes, father?
- Have you got your results?
- No, not yet.
You got your results
a fortnight ago.
It was under your pillow.
Leave alone lying, you have
no regrets about failing.
You still keep loitering with
your good-for-nothing friends.
If it was someone with dignity,
would have had sleepless nights.
He would have found
it difficult to swallow.
Shakur, let him go! He'll come
around when he's hungry.
Are you aware that Sanju,
Maksood and Ghanshyam...
...have failed again?
And now, these scoundrels...
...will be in your class.
Why do you associate
with those loafers?
Aren't there any nice
girls in your class?
They talk nonsense.
And they talk about high ideals!
Their language is horrible.
They abuse a lot and use
slang while speaking.
Wow!
What language!
- What do you want?
- I wanted the newspaper.
- Do you want the price
of gold? - Pardon me.
It is right there, take it.
...And bring me my wallet.
- Anjali, give me a napkin.
- I'm coming, father.
- Ratan.
- Yes, father.
Here's a new blazer for you.
You will be receiving
an award today...
...so don't wear the old one.
- Yes father.
- Take this money.
- That's not necessary.
Keep it, and don't forget to
pay respects to your mother.
I will.
Ratan, your new
blazer looks great.
- Isn't it good?
- Yes.
- Ratan, I want Rs. 50.
Do you want to buy books?
- Aren't you giving it to me?
- No.
Did you see that?
Ratan gets a new blazer...
...as well as money
and I don't get anything.
It happens
with me always.
Take a look at my shoes
...They're torn.
Sanju, do you need money?
- Do you have any?
- How much do you want?
- 40... 50.
- I'll get it.
You, idiot! You are taking
advantage of her feelings?
Don't talk nonsense!
She is my good friend...
...and cares about me.
Unlike you.
Ramlal's efforts are
the sole reason...
...behind the fine performance
by Pradip Kumar...
...Afzal Khan and
Ratanlal of our school.
And Ratanlal came second
in the marathon cycle race.
For this achievement,
he is awarded...
...the school champion badge.
This is your final year, Ratan.
This time you must come first.
I'll try my best.
"He is called as a
conqueror friends."
"He who knows how to
win a losing battle."
"The day we come into
the field euphoric."
"We will conquer
with a victory."
"He is called as a
conqueror friends."
"Why should we go
along with the world."
"Why should we bugger our
selves with excercise?"
"Why should we be scared of
parents or the teachers?"
"We are the
conquerors here."
"We can tackle
with everyone."
"Beware of us my friends."
"If they don't understand us."
"How does it matter to us?
"We know how to win
a losing battle."
"These lanes are ours
as well as the roads."
"Why should we feel scared?"
"Any one messing with us."
"Will get aside
feeling scared."
"We are the
conquerors here."
"We can tackle
with everyone."
"Don't mess
with us my dears."
"If they don't
understand us,"
"How does it matter to us."
"These beautiful
innocent angels."
"Are all crazy for wealth."
"When they realise the
value of true love."
"They will go
crazy about us."
"We are the
conquerors here."
"We can tackle
with everyone."
"We also are no less
than any princes."
"We know how to win
a losing battle."
Hey! ...Stupid...!
Take a look at that boy. He's
eating nuts like a monkey.
- He looks like one.
- Look at his antics.
- What will you have?
- A cheese sandwich.
2 cheese sandwiches.
...And make it snappy.
Sanju, make two milk shakes.
Ramu, make two cheese toasts.
Get up!
Look at him.
He is making a pass.
I have a good
mind to hit them.
Now watch the charm
of Shekhar Malhotra.
Who doesn't know the
inter college champion?
We visited Sidney point today.
It is a beautiful place.
- Will you come along
sometime? - Sure.
Chilled.
He's too proud of himself.
You've fetched the bottles but
forgotten the straws... Fool!
He's got the
intelligence of a child.
Ignore them.
They are jealous of you.
He panicked.
The Xavier's boys
are scoundrels.
Idiot!
What have you done!
How did this happen?
How did this happen?!
The boys from Xavier's
and Rajput had a scuffle...
...and they broke
the furniture.
By fighting over a couple of
girls from Queens college...
...you have maligned the
reputation of Rajput college.
If you have a tendency to
fight, like goons then...
...you should have
joined a sleazy college.
And you, Shekhar...
The captain of this college...
Weren't you ashamed of
quarreling at an ordinary cafe?
Sir, it was my fault.
It won't occur again.
If it occurs again,
you will be suspended.
You will not be permitted to
leave the hostel for two weeks.
Stop it, Sanju.
Did you speak to the
Principal of Rajput College?
Yes. Damage was
done to us but...
...they weren't
sufficiently punished.
Go and complain some more.
Why were you jealous?
Was it because a Rajput boy...
...easily charmed
a girl from Queens.
What nonsense! I don't care
about such cheap girls.
As if they care about you.
My dear brother, any
girl who could knock...
...Sanju out of his senses.
...has not stepped
on the earth as yet.
- Who is the new girl?
- She must be the spoiled...
...brat of a rich father.
Hey!
Are you blind?
He's gone.
Look at him.
They are asking for trouble.
2 chocolate milk shakes.
- How are you?
- Who are you?
I'm Ganshu. Have you forgotten?
We met in Delhi...
...at the market.
We were having snacks.
Don't you remember, Rina?
My name is not Rina, but Tina.
What will you have, Tina?
Or, will you have Chikoo?
It is great...
We won't do it again!
The old woman has a firm
hand. She has skinned me.
Aren't you new? I thought
I'd accompany you.
The boys in the blue blazers
are from Rajput college.
They come from
affluent families.
The boys in red blazers
are from Xavier's.
And those boys
in green blazers?
Don't even look at them.
They are from Model College.
They are trash.
We call them jerks.
Jerks?
Yes, dear.
They are jerks who look
like hungry wolves.
I have decided never
to make a pass...
...at any girl from
Queens college.
Hey... Who is she?
- Wow!
- O Lord!
Boys are dropping dead.
Should I call the ambulance?
Who is that boy with
the yellow headband?
He is J. K. Malhotra's son.
The owner of
Malhotra Steel M ills?
There is no girl worth knowing.
Neither is your Richa around.
- What did you do the last time?
- Nothing, just a kiss.
A good night kiss!
Your kiss is sufficient.
Who is that girl?
She must be new.
Seated beside her is
Ruksana, from Queens...
...who always says 'dear'.
She is impressed.
Hey! ...He's gone.
The idiot!
...He's gone to prey.
- Do you know me?
- Who doesn't?
Scoundrel!
Why are you laughing?
It angers me, that a rogue
is fooling a naive girl.
One ought to tell her that
Shekhar was dating Richa.
Don't worry, Sanju. I'll take her
aside and explain everything.
Even I can take her aside in
the corner if it is necessary.
Everyone has a corner
but no one has a girl friend.
- Hey... I'll beat you!
- Just you wait.
- What nonsense? - Will you
complain about this too?
I don't have the time for this
bickering. We are here to train.
Whose training? ...Are
these your champions?
And take a look at
this bag of bones.
Look Paunchy, there's
no need to be angry.
As for the cycle race, I'm
the champion around here.
No local boy can beat me!
And I shall win the
race this year too...
...and blacken the faces
of these scoundrels.
You're a scoundrel! Your entire
family is full of scoundrels!
I'll break your face.
- I'll break your face. - Why
are you fighting with them?
Hey fighter, pay
heed to your dad...
...or else you'll
be severely beaten.
Let's disperse.
Uncle, I've brought
a vegetable dish.
I have already eaten.
They will have it.
Sanju, will you have some?
I won't spare them.
Why are you kicking
up a storm?
Forget about
what happened.
How can I?
You are afraid of them.
They insulted father and you
kept mum! You are gutless.
I am not afraid of anyone.
Then, why did you keep mum?
Violence is not the solution.
Neither is submission.
Sanju is right. We ought
to give them a fit reply.
Today they were spared
because of father.
Next time I won't spare them.
What will you do?
You talk utter rubbish.
Shekhar is proud
and very ill-mannered.
Ratan will break his pride.
Ratan, I have decided to buy
an imported cycle for you.
But father, an imported
cycle costs...
...around 12 to
15 thousand rupees.
It's alright.
I'll save every penny...
...and I'll even
borrow if I have to.
Didn't he say that no
local boy could beat him?
This year, he will not win but
leave in defeat at your hands.
- Where did you go with Shekhar?
- Nowhere in particular.
- What did you do?
- We had a casual conversation.
Did anything interesting happen?
That will take place tomorrow.
But we're going to Sidney point
on a school picnic tomorrow.
- Is Shekhar coming there?
- Yes.
He said that he would fling
himself from Sidney point...
...if I'm not there.
- Deposit this Rs 1000 in
the bank. - Alright, father.
I'm off to Mr. Dube's place
and I'll have my meal there.
Ramu, return these empty crates
to the soft drink delivery man...
...and take delivery of
4 crates of soft drinks.
I'll settle the
accounts when I return.
Sanju, put this
bread in the oven.
Take this.
I'm going to the bank.
I'll go to the bank instead.
Father has directed
me to go to the bank.
- Do you need something?
- I need some bread?
Bread... Take a seat.
- No, it's alright.
- Please sit.
I'll bake some fresh
bread and get it for you.
Sanju, go to the bank.
I'll bake the bread.
No, you go to the bank and I'll
bake the bread for Kalpana.
Don't act smart.
Oh, all right...
But take my advice.
Grab her and give her a kiss.
Come on friends,
it's too hot out here.
"They spoke
with their eyes."
"And found life partners."
Oh... The bread!
Hey!
What are you doing?
This is Mr. Wadia's car.
If he comes to know...
...I'll be in trouble.
Damn, Wadia.
Just a moment. I'll go
and buy some flowers.
Hurry up!
Hey, what are you doing!
Where are you going?
Stop! Idiots!
"I don't care if people
call me a ruffian."
Stop!
What luck! They are three
and we are also three.
The one in the
centre is mine.
Ganshu, hop over to the store
and pick up three cigarettes.
The girls will be
impressed with our style.
You have brains!
- Get filter cigarettes.
- All right.
- Ghode, fetch some mint, too.
- Why?
When you approach them,
your breath will smell fresh.
Go.
Please stop!
Please don't be angry.
I've missed my school bus and
I have to get to Sidney point.
If I don't reach there, there
could be a great problem.
- I am Devika.
- And I am Sanjaylal.
Yes.
Instead of your picnic, come
along to Malroad for a coffee.
Some other time, perhaps.
You mentioned something
about a coffee.
There's a boy who
is running like crazy.
- Is he calling to you?
- No.
Devika, listen to me.
Sanjay considers himself
to be very smart.
I shall take the money for
the cigarettes from him.
Why did you have to get off?
I couldn't help it.
He asked me to fetch mint.
Shut up!
Don't you have any brains?
What?!!
Greetings, sir!
Greetings... So you know me, eh?
Who doesn't know you, sir!
You are the lord of this village.
Oh, all right!
Do you have matches?
Offer the matches to the lady.
- How are your cattle?
- It is all your grace, sir.
I hear that the produce is
not very good this year.
There's been no rain and
we have no money and...
Oh! Keep this.
Share it.
- Thank you, sir.
- You are welcome.
Thank you, madam.
Enjoy yourself... At last
your wish has been granted.
Come along.
- Hey! Is my Mercedes ready?
- No, sir.
Oh, no!
Where is your father?
He has gone to the police
station to file a report.
A thief stole one of our cars.
It was similar to yours.
It is a green maruti gypsy.
What a state this
country has come to!
Devika, I hate thieves.
It's a small place but
the coffee is great.
Hey!
Come here.
Fetch 2 cups of
special coffee and...
- What happened? - There's
a problem with the chair.
Hey! Change your chairs.
- What did he want?
- He's placed a tall order.
- Who will pay for it?
- No one.
Have some.
These pastries
are really good.
Look!
It's those jerks again.
Greetings, sir!
Greetings, madam!
Hello!
- We were passing through...
- So we decided to pay you a visit.
We were famished and...
all our money was stolen.
Serve them too.
Thank you, sir. We won't
forget your favour.
Let's make ourselves at home.
Hey, waiter!
Give us 3 menu cards.
Did you really come for coffee
or to make someone jealous?
Do you know Shekhar?
Yes, and I also know that he'd
called you to Sidney point today
Yesterday, I overheard Shekhar
talking to his friends.
He mentioned that it
took him a while...
...to woo Kamla,
Bimla and Richa.
But Devika readily
dropped into his lap.
He's a liar!
Richa is from Queens College,
but who are Kamla and Bimla?
They were from Sitaram college.
They returned home.
Why?
- They were cheated.
- What happened?
- How can I tell you?
- Please tell me.
This is what
happened to them.
That must be it.
I hear that it's
Shekhar's old habit.
I'll teach him a lesson
that he'll never forget.
I'll seek revenge on him
for insulting me today.
How?
Will you assist me?
- Shall I contact you at
Xavier's? - Yes... No!
I share my name with a
couple of scoundrels.
- Then? - There's
another number... 202.
Add my bill to my account.
Thank you, sir... Madam!
Waiter, fetch us 3 menus.
- Get lost!
- I'll pay you Rs 100.
She's walking on air since
the time she met Shekhar.
She'll come to her senses
when she becomes like this.
Is Shekhar really
like that, dear?
Who is Sanju?
I have befriended Sanju,
to seek revenge on Shekhar.
I don't want a
romantic involvement.
- So, Sanju is a nobody?
- He is not a nobody.
Any boy who gives a tip
of Rs 200 for a match...
...is surely somebody.
- Rs 100! Who gave
it to you? - Sanju.
- And Sanju took it back.
- Hey, give it back!
This belongs to father and
I have to return it to him.
Hey! What would happen
if I told Devika the truth?
She would have left.
I didn't want to befriend her.
I wanted to seek revenge on...
Shekhar, which I have done.
- 2 plates of 'samosas'
please. - Yes, sir.
It's blank.
Dear Ratan.
Why didn't you return the chit
that fell from Kalpana's books?
- It bore your name.
- My name? Where is it?
- The letter will cost Rs 20.
- What!
- All right. Give me Rs 10.
- I won't give a single penny.
All right. I'm off.
Come here.
Take this Rs 10.
This is your Diwali gift.
...and I'm not
interested in the letter.
Take this...
Don't hesitate.
I told you that I
didn't want it.
Read it. It might contain
something special.
Get lost.
Dear Ratan.
I don't know what
has come over me.
Tonight is 'diwali'.
All the boys and girls will
be gathered at the courtyard.
If you come holding a
red rose in your hand...
...I will assume
that you love me too.
With love from Kalpana.
Nazima, come here.
Give Kalpana this letter...
...and tell her that
it is from Ratan. - Okay
Kalpana, this is from Ratan.
Dear Kalpana, I don't know
what has come over me.
I dream of you always.
Tonight you will surely
come to the courtyard.
And if you carry a red rose...
...I will assume that
you love me too.
With love from Ratan.
All the boys here are crazy
about the girls from Queens.
And those girls don't even
given them a second glance.
Even we ought to do the same.
All boys are the same.
If you express your feelings
they don't care about you.
And if you play hard to get,
they come after you.
- Is that so? - Yes, of course.
Try it and see.
Who is your mule?
- Whose did you steal?
- Shut up...
Take this... Hey, look yonder.
Let's tease him.
Hey! Why are you holding a
red rose? Let me see.
Let us see.
- What a deep red colour!
- It's a rose.
Hey, look there! Kalpana
is also holding a red rose.
Is something going on?
He has improved.
I'll call Anjali over, surely
Kalpana will accompany her.
- Don't you want to speak to her?
- I don't want to speak to anyone.
Hang on!
It will be fun.
- Anjali, come here!
- Refuse.
- Tell him to get lost.
- Get lost!
Acting smart, eh?
Come here!
Hold your ground.
You come here, you pigeon.
Hey, why can't you listen?
"Those who are crazy after
the girls of this city."
"What can they know
about our elegance."
"You disloyal sweetheart."
"The one who
doesn't realize..."
"...Who I'm crazy about."
"What can she
understand about."
"...the style of
my amorousness."
"Understand me my love."
"There may be many beauties,
but we are no less."
"Have a proper look at us."
"Don't be so boastful
it can be that..."
"...ultimately you might
land up no where."
"Those who are crazy after
the girls of the city."
"- Come here.
- No no."
"Come here into my arms,
...don't go away."
"No... no."
"Many people
have gone crazy."
"Where can you
escape too."
"Hearing my plea...
with all style."
"Will come running
towards me."
"The one who
doesn't realize."
"Whom I'm crazy about."
"Those who are crazy after
the girls of this city."
"My disloyal sweetheart."
"Try and understand
sweetheart."
Tonight, Sanju sat beside me
long after everyone had left.
He seemed as though he
wanted to say something.
I thought I'd say it myself
that you are everything to me.
Numskull, how can
I explain to you?
Devika, please listen I have
nothing to do with Richa.
Infact, I was fooling her.
Like Kamla and Bimla?
Anyway, why did you call?
Devika, I'd like to meet
you alone some place.
- Like Kamla and Bimla?
- What!
Never mind that! I'm
coming to Malroad today.
- Where exactly?
- Ahead of Malroad there...
...is a road going uphill.
A tree bearing yellow flowers.
Wait for me at 5 p. M.
Beneath that tree.
Who are you calling now?
- Who is Sanjay?
- Hey! Give it to me.
- Yes, Devika. Go on.
- I have an appointment...
...with Shekhar at 5 this
evening. Could you come...
...to Malroad at 4 p. M?
You will have to come
there with some supplies.
Sure.
A long rope... 2 buckets.
And... what!
All right, I'll be there.
- What are you looking at?
- The necklace in the centre.
- Isn't it beautiful?
- Yes.
- It costs Rs 4000.
- So? I'll get it for you.
Why are you
sweet talking me?
Mr Thapar's car
is at your garage.
And I have to return it today.
I could take it to him and get
it back under some pretext.
And then we could go for
a drive in the evening.
Good idea.
But...
...what will we do if
Thapar keeps the car?
Wait and see.
I'll get around him.
- Add the fresh one too.
- All right. Here.
My stomach is hurting.
Shekhar, why have
you brought us along?
I'll look like a fool if I
stand alone beneath this tree.
Oh! So you want all of
us to look like fools, eh?
As you wish.
- Well?
- What?
- Take him somewhere.
- This fellow.
Go and obtain some relief.
There's someone with her.
I won't spare him.
Why are you hitting me?
Help!
We missed him!
- Where have you brought me?
- This is my house.
Is this your house?
I'll go and tell father
that I'm going out.
Sir, I have brought your
car from Girdhari Garage.
Give the keys and leave.
The engine is knocking. Shall
I take it back and repair it?
You bring back the car after 10
days and it's still not ready!
Commissioner, the
locals are thieves.
When they take the car to
the garage they keep it.
I know how to deal
with the likes of you.
Sandeep, take the keys
from him and throw him out.
Give the keys.
Sanjay, your house
is very impressive.
Was your father angry?
He was angry because I
was late for the party.
I tossed the car keys in anger,
I'll have to drop you in taxi.
Your father appears to
be very hot tempered.
So am I. Someday, I shall leave
this house and his wealth.
Devika, if I didn't have
any of this wealth...
...would you...
- What?
- Nothing.
Sanjay, I know what
you're trying to say.
- Would you believe me if I
told you something? - Go ahead.
Sanjay, when I first met you,
I didn't know who you were.
But it seemed as though I
had been waiting for you.
It is the truth, Sanjay.
I do not care for money.
Even if you don't have
anything in the future...
...you'll mean
the same to me.
This is my memento.
You might forget me...
...in the future, but I
shall never forget you.
I will have to solder it. It
will take 5 to 10 minutes.
- All right.
- I'll be back soon.
Give it to me.
- What happened? - I'm on fire.
The flame of love.
Why are you
being so dramatic?
- Is it gold?
- Yes.
Someone has given it to
me with trembling hands...
...and a throbbing heart.
- Who? - Devika.
- Never!!
Big brother, you are
the heavy muscular type.
A heavy model like you,
wouldn't understand love.
Stop your nonsense
and tell me this.
- Have you told her anything.
- No. Not as yet.
Therein lies the problem.
It's difficult to say anything.
It is not difficult. All you
need to do is take a decision.
- Have you come to a decision.
- Yes, of course.
- What will you say?
- What is there to say?
I'll hold her hand like this,
look into her eyes and say...
- Ganshu, Ghode,
listen to me. - Not now.
- It's something special.
- My father will kick my butt.
I've soldered it, but is it
okay if I fix it tomorrow?
All right, I'll come
for it tomorrow.
- Hi Anjali, I was on my
way to see you. - Really!
- Let's sit here.
- Anjali, come home soon.
Yes, father.
Ah, yes! I couldn't
bring the car back.
Thapar made mince
meat of me.
I knew that.
Anjali, I want to
tell you something.
- It's something special.
- Go on.
I don't know how to say it.
You might wonder...
...at the sudden
change in Sanju.
You won't laugh
at me, will you?
The fact is...
- Anjali, serve dinner.
- I'll be there.
Go on, Sanju.
No, not right now. We'll go
and speak in privacy tomorrow.
"Whether you say it or not
but I have already heard it."
"You have chosen me as
your soul mate in love."
"You have chosen and I
have already heard it,"
"the First euphoria
and the ecstasy."
"The love is afresh,
and so is the await."
"What should I do oh
my love lorn heart."
"Oh my love lorn heart
you only tell me."
"I'm flying high in
these euphoric winds."
"Or should I swing
with these clouds."
"Or should I get the sky
and the earth together."
"Tell me friends what to
do and what not to do."
"The first euphoria
and the ecstasy."
"He spoke to me in
such a manner that..."
"...he gave me the
colourfull dreams of love."
"As is I remain helpless."
"And he kisses me
with all his love."
"The first euphoria
and the ecstasy."
"The love is afresh
and so is the await."
Keep this as my memento.
You might forget me...
...in the future, but I
shall never forget you.
- Sanju.
- Yes, father.
- Deposit this Rs. 5000 in
the bank. - Yes, father.
What are you
looking at, Anjali?
- There was a lovely pearl
necklace here. - It is sold.
Ramlal's son Sanjay
bought it this morning.
- Do you wanting anything
else? - No, thank you.
- What happened?
- Sanju is crazy.
There was a necklace here.
I said that...
...I liked it so he
got it for me.
- So, what? - No,
it is very expensive.
And I don't want such
an expensive gift.
I'll get hold of Sanju
and have it returned.
Ratan, have you
seen Sanju?
I saw him heading
for sunset point.
Sanju, wake up!
- We have to go for practice.
- Let go off me! - Get up!
- Oh, all right.
- Come quickly.
Where are the rest?
Sanju is here too!
If he comes once, he takes
a break for several days.
- Have you taken the full round
today? - One hour 10 minutes.
If this was the race,
I would have won it.
You would have won it last year.
But, Shekhar forged ahead
It is the last few seconds that
decide the defeat and victory.
Whatever it may be,
everyone believes that...
...only you can defeat
Shekhar... It's true.
So much hope can make
a person nervous.
Especially father.
He keeps dreaming of...
...my victory and
Shekhar's defeat.
He wants to buy an
Italian cycle for me.
- It costs Rs. 20, 000.
- 20, 000!
I fear that if I don't win
father will heartbroken.
This training is very good.
We ought to take it too.
Okay! With such training,
you'll surely beat Shekhar.
We have seen nothing.
You may continue.
Sanju meets me very
rarely these days.
Perhaps he only remembers
me when he needs a car.
It hurts me, Sanju.
But I can still...
...do anything for you.
Don't ever forget me, Sanju.
Who is accompanying her?
What is she doing
with a boy from Model?
Do you know Devika?
She is from Queens College
and is of our class.
How dare a stupid localite of
Model College, befriend her?
- Are you Devika's father?
- M ind your language, bastard!
And I am not a bastard
but you are.
Come on, jerk!
What happened?
Sir, he is attempting to
ruin a respectable girl.
Which girl?
She is from Queens College
and she is my family friend.
- What nonsense!
- Shut up! - Get lost!
You are standing
upright now.
Let my boys
break your ribs.
Do you understand?
- What happened, Sanju?
- Quiet! You're spoiling him.
He must have
started the fight.
Don't interfere in my matters.
I don't need your sermon.
I'm glad to have found you.
I have something
important to discuss.
Let's go sit somewhere.
Not now as I have to
go for rehearsals.
Next Sunday there's
a dance competition.
...in which we're participating
with Rajput College.
Shekhar is also participating.
Right now, I want to
tell you about myself.
Devika, hurry up.
The bus is leaving.
I'm off now, we'll meet
at the dance competition.
- You are in the Xavier's
team, aren't you? - Yes.
At the Inter School
Dance Competition...
...after St. Peter's College,
...is Xavier's College
at number four.
"We are crazy for love,
we are love lorn."
"Our songs are
full of youth."
"Because of us
is this world."
"Where ever you see in
the darkness of the night."
"Or you search in
the morning light."
"We all are seen, no
one can be are equal."
"The world is
because of us."
Let's see how many points
the judges have given them.
After the spectacular
performance by Xavier's...
...the next college is Model.
Xavier's performed
well, didn't they?
Now, it is Model's turn.
"You are young, my friends.
Come on, don't feel depressed."
"Look at me!"
"Agreed that I have
no money now...
"...but that won't
be forever."
"Even my fate will
shine one day."
"Believe me, my friends."
"Manage with whatever you
earn through hard work."
"Don't eye what
others have."
"Fate will smile
on us too one day."
"The world will
envy us too."
"Agreed that I have
no money now...
"...but that won't be forever."
"Even my fate will
shine one day."
"Believe me,
my friends."
I have won a lottery!
"You are young, my friends.
Come on, don't feel depressed."
"Look at me!"
"Agreed that I have
no money now...
"...but that won't be forever."
"Even my fate will
shine one day."
"Believe me, my friends."
That was Model College.
I can hardly believe
that Model college...
...could give such
a lovely performance.
Now, it's our turn.
I believe, the judges are taking
some time to give the points.
And now for last
year's winning teams...
...Queens College
and Rajput College.
"My name is Fonseca."
You don't know me, baby."
"You cannot escape me, you
will have to come to me."
"My name is Monica. I won't be
intimidated by your threats."
"I will go where I please."
"I own a car
and a bungalow."
"Moreover, I will
even love you."
"All your big talks
are a sham."
"Your boots are borrowed,
your suit is hired."
"My name is Fonseca.
You don't know me, baby.
"You cannot escape me,
you will have to come to me."
"Sorry O dear, I did
not understand you."
"You are just the
right guy to marry."
"My dreams will all
come true now."
"We give a damn for
those who envy us."
"My name is Fonseca.
You don't know me, baby."
"You cannot escape me,
you will have to come to me."
Last year's winning teams,
Rajput and Queens college.
All the colleges have performed
well in today's competition.
The judges decision
is before me.
Let's see who
are the winners.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry that I couldn't
meet you after the dance.
Even if we had met, I would
have said the same thing.
You're absolutely
wonderful, Sanjay.
I didn't know that
you were so great.
You ought to get the first
prize for what you did.
I worked very hard...
...but I must have lacked
something to have missed it.
You didn't understand.
Anyway, forget it.
I'll be there at Malroadat
approximately 8 O'clock.
All right, I'll see
you at eight.
- Where are you coming from?
- The doctor's clinic.
- Why?
- I've got fever.
You ought to rest.
Why are you loitering around?
I'm on my way home.
Anjali, could I get a
car from your garage?
Where do you have to go?
Devika's coming to meet me today
and I'll have to drop her back.
- You can take it.
- Thank you!
Oh Anjali, sometimes I feel
as though I am in a dream.
Frankly, I'd never contemplated
that a rich girl like Devika...
...would fall in love with me.
- Sanju, may I say something?
- Sure.
Are you sure that
Devika really loves you?
I mean, some girls
mistake their feelings.
No, Anjali. It is not a case
of mistaken feelings.
Have you told her
all about yourself?
You mean, the fact
that I'm from Model?
She realised that on the day
of the dance competition.
And she is aware that no
wealthy boy studies at Model.
That is why she lost her
pallor when she saw you.
What!
The moment she realised you were
from Model and not Xavier's...
What nonsense! If that was the
case, why would she call me?
Why would she praise my dance
and come to meet me today?
All girls are not the same.
Devika is not a gold digger.
She likes me.
She loves Sanju.
Don't be naive, Sanju.
She doesn't love you.
Why are you talking nonsense?
Instead of being happy for me,
you're trying to create doubts.
I'm not creating doubts.
I'm trying to prevent you
from making a mistake.
I don't want you
to be deeply hurt.
Anjali, I don't like this
pointless talk from you.
If you don't approve the truth,
I'll never speak to you again.
I won't meet you either.
Neither do I want
to see you again.
Sanju, you shouldn't speak
to Anjali in this manner.
Why? What was wrong
with my statement?
Let it be.
Bye, Sanju.
It seems as though everyone
has gone crazy today.
Shakur, I'm going out and
I'll be back in a short while.
Hey! Who will serve at the
tables? Don't go anywhere.
Hey, waiter!
What will you have, Devika?
- What do you get here? - Nothing
special, it's a lousy cafe.
Now that we're here,
let's have some coffee...
...or the poor chap
will lose his tip.
Fetch us 2 cups of coffee.
And make sure that the
cups are washed and clean.
Chotu, give me
2 cups of coffee.
Did you see that? He
doesn't seem to be ashamed.
He is a perfect example of
a jerk from Model School.
- Is this Thapar's son?
- That's what he told me.
Why would Thapar's
son be at this joint?
Perhaps his father
threw him out...
...and so he has to
work at this lousy cafe.
Hey! There's no need
to stand around.
Fetch the bill when we
have finished our coffee.
You'll get paid for the coffee
as well as receive a tip.
Get lost!
Thapar's son!
You said that money
didn't matter to you.
You said that it
wouldn't matter...
...if I didn't have
anything in the future.
So it was a lie.
A person who has started
out with a lie...
...has no right to
call anyone else a liar.
I admit that I lied.
But I did it only to
disguise my poverty.
And you lied to
disguise your deceit.
Until yesterday I was Thapar's
son, so you approved of me.
And now that I am an ordinary
man's son, I disgust you.
That's because you
want a rich boyfriend.
If not Thapar's son, Malhotra's
son Shekhar will do...
...regardless of his bad
character. Isn't that right?
Yes, that's it.
- What is the matter, Devika?
- Nothing.
Hey Jerk, I've left you
Rs 10 at your cafe.
Take it from your
champion brother.
Why are you hiding
your face now?
She wouldn't even
care to spit on it.
Keep within the limits of your
status and you'll be happy.
Go and take
the 10 rupees.
Beat him!
Don't spare him!
Pick him up.
You woo a girl, eh?
You're Model's hero, eh?
You stupid localite! How dare
you woo a girl from Queens?
You've become too
big for your boots.
Didn't I tell you that I did not
want any tricks from you?
Bastard!
Don't spare him!
Break his bones!
Will you approach
a girl again?
What do you think of yourself,
you stupid localite.
Release him carefully.
Get lost!
Both of you go home.
Come along!
I've warned you not to
interfere with these boys.
You're still on
Devika's case.
Mark my words, this fight
will blow out of proportion.
And, if I hadn't arrived, they
would have broken all your bones.
Hey! I could have
handled them alone.
Who asked you to interfere? Don't
pretend to be a great saviour.
Oh! So you're very strong, eh?
Come on.
Ratan, I warn you.
Don't challenge me.
- Are you afraid?
- Hey!
I gave you Rs 5000 to
deposit at the bank...
...but this shows
only Rs 1000.
Father, you didn't
give me any money.
Ah yes!
I had given it to Sanju.
Sanju, I... What's this?
You've fought again!
I gave you Rs 5000 to
deposit at the bank.
But this shows
only Rs 1000.
How much did you deposit?
Why don't you answer?
Rs 1000.
1000? What about the
remaining Rs 4000?
I spent it.
Spent it! What did you spend
on? Why don't you tell me?
It wasn't a paltry sum that you
spent with no explanations!
Did you gamble?
Where is the Rs 4000?
Tell me!
I can't tell you, but I
will return the money.
I'm working day and night in
order to buy a cycle for Ratan.
And you blow it up
without a second thought.
Get out!
Get out! And don't
you dare to return!
Father, there's no need to go
to Delhi to buy a new cycle.
It will be an
unnecessary expense.
Besides, my old cycle
will suffice.
Don't worry about it.
- I'll be back by 11 p. M.
- All right, father.
Father, please forgive Sanju.
I'll reason with him.
It won't happen again.
Allow him to come home.
Let's go.
Sanju, father has gone to Delhi
and he will return at 11 p. M.
I apologised on your behalf
and he has forgiven you.
Come home now.
I know that you're angry with
me. I shouldn't have hit you.
Next time, I will ignore the fact
that you are my older brother.
And I don't need your pity.
Here's your blanket.
It wasn't me, but Anjali, who
covered you with this blanket.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
Yesterday, your fighter
and you were lucky...
...because I wasn't present.
What will you do today?
I'll give you the same treatment
that I gave your friends.
You will have to be
taught a lesson.
Let's see who teaches
whom a lesson?
- Ratan's met with an accident.
- What! How did it happen?
I don't know...
...but it seems that he fell
off the cliff with his cycle.
He has been taken to the
Government hospital... Hurry!
Doctor, I am Ratan's
younger brother.
What was... How is he?
What has happened to him?
- Where is your father?
- He has gone to Delhi.
- When will he return?
- Tonight.
Bring him along as
soon as he returns.
But, doctor... What's
happened to him?
The operation is badly needed.
I don't have the time to spare.
No one can
defeat Ratan now.
Call Ratan.
- Father...
- What is the matter?
I have forgiven you...
...but don't repeat
this mistake again.
Go... Go and fetch Ratan.
Ratan has met with an accident.
He is in the hospital.
The state in which
he was brought...
...required an
emergency operation.
He's still in coma.
I do not wish to
raise false hopes.
His condition
is very critical.
Be brave.
Yes.
Last night,
I fought with Ratan.
This morning he came to pacify
me, but I didn't respond.
If anything happens to him...
What will happen now?
How will father survive?
He means everything to father.
He... and you too.
"If ever you got annoyed
with me and went away..."
"...I had never expected
to miss you so much."
"I could never walk even
two steps without you."
"Yet in my innocence,
I always thought...
"...you will never leave me."
"I had never expected
to miss you so much."
"If ever you got annoyed
with me and went away...
Ratan has regained
consciousness.
I'm returning from the hospital.
He's fine. He even spoke to me.
The Lord has
answered our prayers!
What if he tells the police?
I warned you to tell the
principal, but you...
It would have been
better if he had died.
- Water...
- I'll get it.
If you tell anything to anyone,
the consequences won't be good.
What was he
doing here, so late?
Tell me.
You are keeping something
from me. What is the matter?
- Tell me.
- I'll tell you.
Sanju, do you think that
I'll be alright for the race?
Drink your medicine.
The race will take place
on the 24th of next month.
Even if I get a week's
practice, it will suffice.
Isn't that right?
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
There's still a month
and a half left.
Yes, there's a month
This time, I will defeat him.
Sanju, I will surely
defeat him this time.
I won't spare him.
I'll defeat him.
Come along, Sanju.
Hurry up, Ghode, let's go.
Shall we go?
Anjali, I will participate
in the cycle race this year.
- What! Are you serious?
- Yes.
I might not be able to
take Ratan's place...
...but it's the least
I can do for father.
Do your best, Sanju.
I'm with you all the way.
Idiot, you are taking advantage
of her feelings for you!
What is the matter?
Anjali, you might
consider it strange...
...but I'd like to tell you
what I have been feeling...
...these last few days.
What?
I have always considered
you as my closest friend.
But... I have grown
to love you now.
You'll be perfectly alright
in another 3 or 4 weeks.
Until then, take care that you
don't put too much weight...
...on this leg.
Don't be dejected.
It is destiny.
It doesn't matter that you can't
take part in the race tomorrow.
Without you, Shekhar's victory
will be meaningless anyway.
It is Ratan's cycle. Only a
little work remains to be done.
Tomorrow is the race...
...and Sanju wants to use
this cycle for the race.
What is the matter, Kalpana?
Aren't you aware
of Ratan's grief?
He had worked very hard to
participate in this race.
And now...
He is not in this race.
And Sanju is responsible
for all of it.
- Sanju!
- Yes.
If he hadn't messed
around with Shekhar...
...Shekhar and his
friends wouldn't...
What did they do?
Anjali, please don't
disclose this to anyone.
Ratan forbade me to do so.
Please, Anjali,
do it for my sake.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- What?
You know perfectly well.
Shekhar & his friends attempted
to kill you and you kept mum?!
Ratan, you aren't aware of what
father and I have been through.
We nearly lost you.
It's my fault.
You became the target for
Shekhar's enmity towards me.
- Where are you going?
- Let me go!
- Let go of the rod!
Leave it!
Do you want to know why I kept
mum? Listen carefully.
When I came to my senses,
I noticed that you had changed.
You had changed completely.
You had begun to realise
your responsibilities.
You learned to appreciate
me... and father.
You became closer to
us. I was very happy.
For your happiness, I couldn't
care if anything happened to me.
I have troubled
you so much.
And yet you have never
said anything to me.
Then leave
everything behind.
I have prepared the
new cycle for you.
Take it and try your best
at the race tomorrow.
The brave sportsmen have
set off for their destination.
A 50 km cycle race.
From the stadium
to Pykara junction.
...then a 20 km passage
through Baramulla Hills...
...to the highest point.
'We are as good
as anyone' - Model.
The cyclists are
passing through.
It remains to be seen...
...who crosses the dangerous
terrain of Baramulla.
"Baramulla Hills"
I'm Rakesh Sharma reporting
from check post 2 at Pillar Rock.
The first cyclists have
reached Pillar Rock.
In the lead is Shekhar
Malhotra from Rajput College.
In fifth place is Sanjaylal
Sharma from Model College.
Be careful,
or you might fall!
- Come along.
- The jerk is losing air.
I was bound by my
promise to Ratan...
...but I won't spare you now.
Because of you, my brother is not
participating in today's race.
I'll see how you are
able to finish this race.
Get lost, jerk! I'll see
how you try to stop me.
You hit my brother.
This is Ratan's reply.
You won't let me
finish the race, eh?
They've gone ahead!
Shekhar, you go ahead.
We'll take care of him.
Don't set him free.
Well...
The cyclists are returning
to Pykara junction.
Randhir Thapar from
Xavier's is in the lead.
Neville from Lawrence
is in second place.
At the eighth place is...
At the eighth place
is Shekhar Malhotra.
At ninth place is
D'mello of Peters.
At tenth place is Ajay
Parmar of Andrews.
And at eleventh place is
Sanjaylal Sharma from Model.
Xavier's is in the lead.
Lawrence is second.
Andrews is third.
Shekhar Malhotra has arrived.
And now, it is Sanjaylal
Sharma from Model.
Sanjaylal Sharma has
started his first lap.
He has now overtaken a
cyclist from Xavier's...
...to occupy the
10th position.
Moving at great speed, Shekhar
has come to the 5th position.
Shekhar Malhotra has
started his second lap.
Sanjaylal is
now at 7 th place.
Cyclists number 7 and 8
have taken a bad fall.
Shekhar Malhotra is
at the first position.
Sanjaylal Sharma is
at the second position.
He's approaching Shekhar.
He's come closer.
And that's the end
of the third lap.
A little bit more!
This is the fifth
and last lap!
The Championship
is only 200m away.
Mr Ramlal, even
I accept it today.
"He who wins is
the conqueror!"