Thanks to you, sir.
-Here he comes, the beggar!
-I've got the money.
-How much.
- Quite a lot.
And who'll pay the rest of it?
Look, if you don't pay me
all the money, by God...
I'll break your bones!
Remember that!
Okay.
Don't know where they come from
during business hours! Damn you.
Here, and stay away from
the police.Beat it!
Come on guys... Hey you!
Think it's free eh?
- Get going...go on
-Damn! Let me go!
Let go, I say, you old
swine! Bloody beggar...
What's going on? You bloody...
My God! Damn you...
You bastard! I'm Yashwant Lohar!
- Where's the chilly powder?
-In that red tin.
Okay.
Have you gone to sleep?
Don't sleep!
Yes?
Dead for the next 8 hours!
Sit. Careful...
- Take care.
-Don't worry about me.
Remember the dates.
...all the details.
Look into the eyes and talk.
Don't be afraid.
-It's okay, I understand.
-Look into the eyes and talk.
What excellent cards! Terriffic!
- What have I done?
-Nothing?
No!
That's why I'm letting you off
lightly.Else...I want no trouble.
Just because I'm an orphan,
just about anyone bullies me!
-I don't have parents, see...
-I also don't have parents.
I didn't play cards, but became
an inspector. Suspended, but still.
My wife's there. She's giving her
I.A.S. exam. She's also an orphan.
It's no crime to be one, but it is
a misfortune.Make it your strength.
Don't make noise that
you're an orphan!
Hi! At last you're here!
I was waiting for ages.
- Get off!
- Only till the next signal.
- This will not do!
- Will do, will do.Let's go.
- You own this, eh?
-No, you do!
You're a cop. Then where is your
uniform? Tell the truth now.
-Are you a constable or inspector?
- Get off!
- Why get offended?
- Off!
He's like a kid!
-So, Pawar?
- Want tea, sir?
-No.How are you?
-Fine.
- When will you re-join, sir?
- When the chap up there says so!
When did you start believing in him?
-Not that chap...
The chap who sits on my head! If I
shake my head then he'll know...
Sir, who ever picks a fight
with you, fights a losing battle!
-All well at home?
- Yes, sir.
How long will you pull on,
on half-pay?
My son will join the Academy
and be an offiicer, like you.
-Sign, sir.
-He'll be suspended.
His 1/2 pay will shatter your dreams.
You'll suffer in your old age.
- Think again.
-I have, sir.
What are you doing here
in a safari-suit?
What do you mean? I'm waiting
for you. Where the hell are you?
Then realised it's pay day, eh?
Might get some cash. Shameless!
- What are you looking at?
- You dream of cream like a cat!
-2 ice lollies, please.
-Right.
You'll give me money?
Can you afford it?
What money do you mean?
What money?
I've to give you my case,
plus money? Who are you?
-People know you because of me.
-How much you talk!
Now listen carefully. The
case is going in your favour.
-How do you know?
-My sources. I was told you were here.
Now don't do any dramatics!
One error and you'll be in trouble.
- They too yearn to provoke you!
-Let them, I'll... To hell with jobs.
To hell with you too! Selfish!
Eat one more.It may cool you.
Come home tonight. We'll eat
crabs made by my wife for you.
-Booze too!
-Sure.Booze too.
- ''Make friends...
- with a blind man...
And then be his guide-dog!
-A fag please.
-A fag too, eh?
-How much will you eat off me?
-I'm not living off a criminal.
-No, but a criminal lawyer!
- One ice lolly, and you make noise!
-How much?
-Forget it.
You're still on 1/2 pay!
Take the money please.
-How much do I owe you?
-I'll just check.
Rs. 970/-.
Give an envelop please.
Add the rest, to my credit.
So, Shaku, you'll soon
be leaving us, eh?
Here, take this. Not much,
but I've toiled for it.
Didn't take any dowry did you?
If any in-law trouble, call me.
- Okay then, bye.
-Have a soft-drink,
No, thanks.
-How much?
- Why here, sir?
Here, there.It's all the same.
I've to pay you.
-Rs. 500/-.
- 1/2 litre from tomorrow.
At least today, drink only this.
How's your mother?
This is for you, Yashwant.
- What is it?
- Wealth in form of paper.
- What shall I do with it?
-Nothing. That's what they want.
This is a reward to
do nothing.
- Take it.
- Who sent it?
Narcotics lobby.
They are those...
...who don't trouble anybody.
But if anybody troubles them...
...then they don't
spare him.Keep it.
-Keep it. We've also to earn.
- You're a pimp in an uniform!
Go give it to your wife.
She'll offer it to God, who'll bless.
- What!
-Shall I repeat myself?
If you form enmity with
outsiders we're with you.
But if you form enmity with one
of your kind, you'll repent it!
Go and dig up whatever you wish!
- Take off your shoes.
-Do you love me?
-Need you ask?
- Yes.
- Why?
Why do you love a man
who can't give you anything?
Agood house, food,
clothes, jewellery.
-I don't want all this.
-Neither do I.
Then why do people
try to bribe me?
- Take your shoes off!
- Why do they try to bribe me?
Why? Do they think I can
be bought like them?
- Why do they think that?
- Why do get so upset about it?
-It happens.
- Why?
Something wrong with my face?
Or do I have a body odour?
But that's natural.
This is not sweat, but blood which
drips as water from my body.
-Did you meet anyone again today?
- They can't stand one honest man.
That's because they fear you.
You make them realise...
...their pettiness. They want you
to stoop to their level and fall.
So why do you trouble yourself
over it by thinking?
You'll have to change yourself.
Don't try to change others.
When will you think
about me, and our home?
About our children
that will come later.
We want to give them everything
that we didn't get.Right?
You, your home, and kids...
That's what makes your world.
- You're right.I'm talking bullshit.
- You can't be wrong.
I am wrong.I say wrong things.
I think wrongly but bear it with me.
If you feel bad, beat me up.
But don't leave me.
On the ground floor of Tarapore
Towers, the men you want are hiding.
- Is this information authentic?
- 100%! Hurry, else they'll scram
Listen... whose letter is it?
- Where's the key?
-It's with the offiicer-in-charge.
Go get something.
Get something to break this!
Here, wear these.
This will protect only this part.
If you're hit here, you're dead!
- Who'll come with me?
- We will.
- What if you die?
-Prepared, sir.
Really?
Govt. will pay you Rs. 25,000/-
If you die on duty. Your wife
will get those Rs. 25,000/-.
Kids may beg all their lives.
Will do?
- Yes, sir.
- Good!
If I get killed, don't worry.
Just get them here, or in the head.
Got that? Give me that, will you?
Sorry, uncle.I didn't hit that.
Please give me the ball.
- What do you want to be when
you grow up?- Tendulkar.
Sachin can never be Gavaskar.
Gavaskar can't be Mushtaq Ali.
They've their own identity.
Try to do that.
That's fine.
But, my ball please.
My ball please.
Give me my ball.I didn't
hit it.He did.
I'm Inspector Yashwant Lohar.
Hands up! Don't move.
Kadam, if they try anything...
Shoot!
- Will this break our stumps?
- This kills men!
Forget the stumps!
Tiger calling control.
The 4 wanted criminals are hiding
in Tarapore Garden. There's firing.
Send additional force and
ammunition quickly.
You go there. That man's crazy.
If he shoots those men down...
- What will we tell their boss?
-Right, sir, I'll see to it.
-I'm sending you the force.
- Over, and out.
There's firing in Tarapore Towers.
All men are to go there.
Why has the firing stopped?
The back-door is covered.
Haven't gone upstairs, have they?
Cover me.
Go to the opposite building.
Close the lift.Don't move.
Shoot anybody who comes down.
Police, coming up.
This is InspectorJoshi here.
Put down your arms.
Surrender yourselves.
I promise you.
You'll not be deceived.
Put down your arms.
I promise you.
-Nobody will hurt you.
-Let's surrender.
-Shall we tell them?
- Yes.
We'll surrender.
We're ready to surrender.But...
But nobody should fire at us.
Stop firing!
- They are surrendering.
-Damn it!
That Lohar is still alive.
If he sees us, he'll kill us!
- We'll kill him before that.
- Yes, do that!
I'll lose my hold soon.
Please save me.
I'll surrender myself.
Look, I'll fall down.
What will you do staying alive?
Kill more policemen.
-No I won't.
-Rape some girl.
No...
-Again do drug traffiicking.
-No. Save me.
I'd have hauled you over, but
my arm is weak. You shot me.
That bullet is still in there.
Take your bullet back!
Get ready for an inquiry.
- Where's Inspector Lohar?
-My 2 constables are serious.
-See to them.I'm shot in my arm...
- Other docs are attending to them.
They're not in danger, are they?
Have their families been told?
You're taking so long!
-Finished?
-I've to put stitches. Don't move.
How many stitches will you put?
Am I a pyjama or something?
What are you doing here?
Nothing's wrong with me. Go!
Go and console the families
the injured constables.
Go! And shut the door!
- Who informed you?
-He's poor, but cannot be bought.
- Who is he? His name?
-I won't disclose it.
You should have transferred
this information.
Neither the case is yours, nor that
area is under your jurisdiction.
Wherever there's crime, that area
comes under my jurisdiction.
If a woman is raped in an area,
shall I keep quiet...
-...because that area is not mine?
-If the police have some rights...
...they come with some rules too.
You have misused those rights.
They were going to surrender.
Even then you shot them?
They killed my 2 men. That's not
murder.If I kill them, it's murder.
- You should've brought them to court.
-And what good would that do?
Same old story. Some pockets
emptied. Some pockets fiilled.
They'd be released on bail.
Then the F.T.R. would be ready.
Then the case will start, it'll
go on and on. Then elections!
The criminal will fight an
election from inside the jail.
His hoodlums force the nervous people
to vote, by scaring them more.
The criminal becomes an M.L.A.!
He's happy, and so are you.
- The circle is complete.
-Like some fine art...
...nowadays one attains one more
art. The art of idealism!
As long as you don't change
your ways, and yourself, I...
Neither I, nor my ways will change.
If you wish, change the vow, that...
...we take as commissioned offiicers.
Loyalty to the Indian constitution.
I'll try my best to protect
the freedom of my country.
Avoid communal disintegration.
Use my constitutional rights...
...by being unbiased and honest.
And apart from this...
...India is my country.
Dishonesty is my birthright.
All the corrupt are my brothers.
All the hoodlums here...
...the dacoits, the rapists are
my relations. To
serve them,
to prosper them is my greatest duty.
All my life I'll be loyal to them.
This Enquiry commission
has its importance too.
Enquiry Commission my foot.
Just say ''We don't need you''.
Why this farce?
To humiliate,
and break you from within.
They may hope that, getting scared
the man may join hands with them.
Let them try anything.And do
you know who's doing this?
A man who has not even passed
his school-leaving certifficate!
Four years back he was a vendor.
Today, he's a corporator!
See what he did? And how?
He threw a fat morsel to my
colleagues, who pawned their uniforms!
And what did they do?
They suspended me!
Because the power is on the other
side of the table, where they sit.
Not here where I stand.
Go! We don't need you.
You're an invalid!
That's power.
That's what I say! Why
don't we have this power?
Because over there, on that
chair none of us are there.
One of us should be there.
-How and who?
-Anyone.It could be anybody.
It could be you.Even her.
Learn more.Become able to occupy
the chair and then play the game.
There must be our
man there. Then play.
-I won't study.
- Why not?
If you want to become
somebody, you'll study.
-I...
- Yes?
-I won't study.
- You'll have to! Why won't you?
- What have you done?
- What you'd have, if you were attacked!
- Who is he?
-Must be one of your pimps!
Don't talk crap!
Take him away!
Get 5 people as witnesses too.
Call an ambulance too.
Useless bum!
Bloody bastard! Couldn't
even do a small job!
Good thing you bumped him off
like a street dog!
It's so very sad! But what
can one do with fate?
We've to shed tears no doubt.
But one has to live too.
Don't think you're all alone.
I'm there for you. Okay?
He was my boy from my ward.
His sacriffice will not go waste.
I'm very ashamed that a fellow
police offiicer did this.
Take it easy. You're so young yet.
You have a full life ahead.
But, it's all God's will.
He took him away.Never mind...
Everything will be fine. Your tears
will dry in a few days.
Don't feel lonely.I'm
always there for you.
Sit down now.
- Come on, Salim, surely not here?
- What can I do?
He was my man.
So she becomes mine too.
One has to take care of
one's possessions, isn't it?
Do you think what you
did was correct?
Yes.
What is your opinion about
the pact we signed in 1972...
...with our neighbouring country?
Does it still carry any weight?
Yes, very much. In fact, on the
strength of its compromises...
...the relations between
the two can improve.
Then where's the hitch?!
Here, and there too! Both, nations,
in a race to down trod the other...
...forgot, that because of
this attitude of theirs...
...the whole of S.Asia, is at
a great loss. I'll further say...
...if they want to avoid
self destruction,...
...the Simla Accord
is the only answer.
- What about Women's Liberation.
-Imported variety cannot work here.
-Did you come by train or plane?
- Train.
What was your bogie No.?
If I invite you out
to dinner tonight...
-...will your husband mind?
-He's like a son-in-law to you...
...so no question of him minding.
What was the no. of your bogie?
- You just said it was 527943
-Stupid questions get stupid answers.
- When will your wife return?
-In a couple of days.
-She'll be very sad.
- Yes, especially if I had died!
- What nonsense you blabber!
- You too think I talk nonsense, eh?
- Why have you come here?
- To hear your nonsense!
You were to rejoin tomorrow.
But you ended up with this trouble!
-How long shall I fight your cases?
-Had he killed me, you'd be free.
- Then you should've got him jailed.
-It was either him, or me!
It's a plot, I tell you.
The whole force is corrupted.
- You're also a part of it.
-And see what's happening!
- They are after my blood!
-It's a question of their survival.
A constable with 3 marriageable
daughters. How will he live on 1800/-?
He has just a stick as defence.
How will he take on a AK47?
He's not sure whether he'll return
home when he sets out on duty.
What compensation does he get
if he dies on duty?
25,000/- to 30,000/-?
-He too wants to live.
-So to do that, he'll take bribes...
...sell his integrity! Didn't he know
his pay when he joined the force?
This is like law of the jungle!
To avoid gangsters, go to the police.
To avoid police go to gangsters
To avoid both, go to politicians!
Because they all control each other.
He does as per the circumstances.
You've made foes in all the three.
No door is open to you!
What door?
They want to kill me in my own
house! Which door do you mean?
The gangsters', the corrupt offiicers,
or the damn politicians, who...
-...in broad daylight drink blood!
- Then rot here!
You invite trouble and then
dream of peace!
Sure.
If I die, how will it affect you?
You'll just miss a shoulder,
for your bier!
You preach me dishonesty, eh?
And you're a lawyer!
Did you read law, or did you
cheat and pass? Go and read.
Go and read all this.
Nobody can touch me! Now go!
Go! Else I'll kill you too.
Okay, kill me.But sign here first.
I don't have time!
Here! Sign down here.
You're like a dog's tail.
-Nothing can straighten it!
- Get lost! Give me a fag!
You won't improve will you?
It's impossible!
Can't you do such a small thing?
Why do I stuff you with money?
-Is he not in jail for murder now?
- Yes, but he should remain there.
- Get me?
- Trust me, sir.
He'll never breathe fresh air again.
Yashwant's lawyer is trying to
bail him out, and he may get it.
If this happens, I'll see
that you coffin is lowered!
The moment that man fell,
InspectorJoshi entered.
Then police came, and took me away.
Joshi was still upstairs.
When I left, that man a alive.
He was declared dead, later.
I didn't kill him.It's a plot.
-Now what?
-Bit complicated.
But I won't let him be sentenced.
-Don't talk shit!
Obliging me, eh?
Won't let me be punished...
-I'll go now.
-Eat with us.
No, I've to prepare things.
What is it? There's no case.
I'll be acquitted.
Look you're no ordinary woman.
You're a Deputy-Collector, okay?
My name is Salim Sheikh.
I'm a corporator.
I'm been friends with all the
Deputy-collectors posted here.
-So I thought I'd meet you too...
- What's your problem?
That all can be seen to later.
First, if I get to know you well.
-Just tell me your problem.
- You're offended.
We'll talk shop.My fiile is with you.
The name and number is...
You just sign it, and send it
to Mr.Kale.I'll be obliged.
I've seen that fiile.No hotel
can be built on that land.
What's the problem?Just think.
If a hotel is built...
...we'll be serving people like you
The nation will get foreign exchange.
There'll be rise in drug-pedalling,
smuggling, prostitution.
You'll have gambling-dens, and
thousands of fishermen will starve.
Under the name of foreign exchange
and tourism you'll prove patriotism.
-But you can go now.
- You forget the service I speak of.
And also that it takes years to
be promoted as a Collector!
If you have the right contacts
and the right helping hands...
...then this promotion
can be got very easily.
And that contact and those hands
are right before you.Believe me...
I'll serve you with all
my heart body and soul.
Take your heart, body
and soul elsewhere.
This is my offiice, not your den!
You're the power of this chair...
-... or shall I get you thrown out?
-I'm going...
But we'll meet again. God keep you.
She sounds like Yashwant.
What's wrong?
Where are you?
You're not with me.
You must've had a bad
first day at offiice.
Someone must've tried to bribe you.
Or some minister's note on table.
Somebody must have
ogled at you lustily.
This is common in
a government offiice.
But you'll have to work there.
Keep your hand on my head.
Now say I Ragini Lohar
will be honest in my work.
I'll use my powers for the
good of the people.
I'll never allow injustice
be done to an innocent.
My aim will be to improve the life
of the poor and the backward.
I'll never take any decision
under anybody's pressure.
Even if he is, my husband.
Inspector Lohar has 2 major
faults. His uncontrolled temper...
...and his habit to take bribes.
To lift his hands on others...
...is a habit with him.But,
he's also a very capable offiicer.
I sympathise with him greatly.
But when I reached there that day...
...I saw Lohar was beating
the man mercilessly.
I tried to intervene, but
Lohar didn't heed me.
He strangled the man and killed him.
You can step down now.
The picture is quite clear.
Besides being a government offiicer,
Lohar is also the husband of...
...our deputy collector.
He didn't even bother to think...
...that his actions could have
mar his wife's reputation...
-...and also hinder her work.
-If I'm a hindrance to my wife...
...if I'm marring her reputation,
I'm willing to divorce her right now!
My lawyer-friend here, will do
all that is legally needful.
Are you mad? This is no time
to talk nonsense.
Enough! Enough, I say!
- Why blame her?
-I'm not, ...
...but I've become
a hindrance to her.
-Have you gone crazy?
- Why do we marry?
To understand, each other, share
our joys and sorrows... enough!
...or to be a burden to each other?
- Get my divorce papers ready...
-Listen Yashwant...
-But I...
-But what? What is marriage?
What, is marriage? Tell me.
Ornaments? Good clothes?
A house? A car?
Luxurious life? She'll cook
for me, Bear me children.
What is sex? Ten minutes
we sleep together...
...the rest of the 24 hours,
we should respect each other.
We both should do something
that makes us proud of each other.
This court, as per the I.P.C.
sentences Yashwant Lohar...
...to 10 years of rigorous
imprisonment.
Take him away!
Why did you do that? You left me?
You gave me a divorce?
Made me a homeless? Why?
- What did I do?
-Nothing.
This separation is a facade.
Nobody can say now that my actions
cause you embarrassment.
Do your work.Nothing must
come in its way.Keep fighting.
Neither I'll lose, nor will you
get defeated! I will...
I'll always be with you.
A divorce cannot separate us.
This is, ''digging one's own grave''.
Got a long sentence.
Now he'll know! Lost his wife too!
Where will she go? I'll have
to make up for his absence.
Welcome, sir.I'm very
happy to see you here.
We're all one now. Same food,
clothes and under one roof too!
Now we're not different from you.
See this. This has
honesty and integrity.
My sweat too.
And this blood here...
is not your own.
It is sucked from those
poor, innocent souls.
You suck theirs for your own gains.
And I drink yours for their sake.
That's the difference
between you and I.
You can't sleep because you fear
death, while I sleep like a log.
That's the difference between us.
Your mother's heads hangs in shame.
My mother, if she comes to know,
will hold her head sky high.
That's where we differ!
I know I'm selling mirrors in
the city of the blind, but one day.
...I'll open your eyes and show
you your faces in those mirrors.
Understand? That's the difference!
I've to wait for so long
in this damn offiice?
-Has she forgotten?
-But sir...
What is it? It's half hour
and you didn't call me in.
You can see I'm talking to this
man. Wait outside, I'll call you.
Oh I see I thought you forgot me.
How can I forget you?
Well, carry on.
I live in a rented place with
my family for 15 years now.
But today my landlord is
threatening to kill me.
Because he wants to build a
factory on it illegally.
I've sent many applications
about it, but one clerk here...
...is demanding 500/- to
send the fiile ahead.
Rs. 500/-? Come with me.
Where are you going? You
really made me wait today.
If you, sign that fiile...
-...with your beautiful hands, then...
- You were always mannerless...
...but you're shameless even more.
I've told you before, I'll not sign.
- Can't you understand?
-I'll take care of Mr.Kale.
And your commission too!
Good evening, Madam.
- What's this?
-Mr.Kale sent it to you.
- You?
-Is your father home?
Come in please.
Welcome, Ms. Lohar.
- What impertinence is this?
- You should know.
You've sold yourself, you try
to pull me in too?
- You should be ashamed!
- Talk properly.I'm your senior.
Apet dog is better than a
senior like you.He'll starve...
...but he'll never eat from other
homes. You're dancing to the tune...
...of such a man, who can't even
put his thumb at the proper place.
-I'll suspend you!
- What else can you do.
If this is what you wanted, why
why did you study till the I.A.S.?
So that you could barter the rights
given to you by the Constitution?
You're insulting me in my house?
This may have adverse effects.
Do you know the difference
between good and bad?
Uprooting thousands of poor homes
you want to fiill your own.
This carpet, T.V.. video, furniture...
Imported Cars...
You think such things make a home?
Look! Look at these kids.
They make a house, a home.
What do you think?
You're making them happy? That they
can't live without these things?
Which you're collecting by selling
your loyalty? Have they harmed you?
By making them morally invalid,
you're being a foe to your own kids!
Ask them what they want?
this dishonest, luxurious life...
...or an honest father!
- Why are you standing around? Go!
- What she said was correct.
What! What did you say?
You're collecting all this money
for us. We'll live without it.
We'll work hard, and earn our living.
We love you very much.
We wish to respect
you all our lives.
If you get caught...No!
We don't want any of this.
- Then, what do you want?
-An honest father!
What? Sir, that girl
refused the money.
Damn him!
She's one in a hundred!
A small mosquito, can
make a man impotent.
One bed-bug can paralyse him!
Small things make man powerless.
Be a speck in the crowd at morn, and
get drunk and sire kids at night.
And then die again at dawn; Cos,
the soul and the man within is dead.
He has compromised with life.
A small thing, makes man powerless.
Bland food, coarse
clothes and silverware...
80 out of 100 are dishonest
yet my country is great!
The insect in a white cap,
declares, equality among people.
Is that why the big fish
is swallowing the small fries?
The curs that we elect, bite us,
to distribute our chunks between them!
The empty streets shudder at their
voices full of inhuman stink!
Babes born yesterday pant after
their first breath!
These bastards of the devil are
creating chaos! And we...
We the god-fearing beasts,
have made life, a 4-letter word!
What will the damn man do?
An insect has made him powerless!
Fall! Fall, you damned lot,...
but fall like that waterfall...
...which doesn't lose its hearty,
even after falling from a mountain.
And doesn't lose its after
falling low to the ground.
But who has the time to think?
Cos an insect, makes man impotent.
The war between Mandir-Masjid
left thousands dead...
Thousands more were sacrifficed
under pretence of duty and help.
He who killed King Bali and threw
Ravana in the jaws of death...
Erased sin with virtue...I seek
that Rama! But it seems...
...the Rama of modern times, has
an unending exile.No wonder.
For, one insect, makes man powerless!
Some time later, the devils will
come. They'll knock on my door.
They'll investigate my
burning and get fired up.
At that time, I'll not get scared.
I'll use my faith as a shield, and
the fire within me as a sword.
One of these days you'll jump
into that fire, for sure.
Abuse me today, sell me.
But what do I have to sell?
Just consolation of
my hot tears. But!
But I'll have my revenge! The
pause between my 2 last breaths...
...I'll give you free... free!
Sir... You have a visitor.
Don't salute me.Kick me.Right here.
Kick me.
I'm a prisoner.
Aprisoner of these insects!
I had forbidden you.
Why have you come?
To cry? To shed tears?
I can't bear it anymore.I won't
be able to go on with life.
I just want to live as your wife.
I want only you.Not this job.
The kinds of people...
Their way of talking.
Their lusty looks rip through
the clothes...
...and touch my body.
This rape by their eyes...
...I've to bear every day.
Not just once, but many times.
I feel as though...
...I'm standing naked in the bazaar.
I feel suffocated.
They should feel throttled
because of you!
They should've tears in their eyes.
If that's not happening
it's due to your weakness.
They'll not revere you, nor
stop eyeing you lustily.
The world is full of such lot.
What had I told you?
Look in their eyes and talk.
Build such a fire within you...
...that it reflects from your eyes
and makes them lower their own!
You vowed.If you break it, then
whether I'm here or not, is same.
I cannot accept a weak wife.
Your weakness is their victory.
You'll have to fight.
There's no other go.
What if they have an illegal power?
I do love you.
Love you very much.
And I always will as long
as you'll confront this.
Your name is Ragini Yashwant Lohar.
Instead of coming whining in here
again, better you consume poison!
I'll console myself that you just
weren't capable of bearing this load.
- What's going on?
-I'll just see.
What for?Just sit tight.
This is an every day farce.
To hell with them!
I'll set the bastard straight!
Hey you! Look what's going on.
Those bastards are after that
lone woman to rape her.
You bloody hooligans!
Wait!Just you wait! I'll show you.
You bastards. Come on...
I'll castrate you! Bloody men!
Bloody pimps!
Don't you have any sense?
Why are you out alone at night?
How did your husband allow
you out alone at night?
Come on now.Don't be scared.
You eunuchs! Why do you sit
inside and blow that horn?
Those bastards made you shit eh?
Couldn't shout even! Blows his horn.
-Is that you, sir?
- Yes, go on.
I'm Joshi speaking.
That Salim Sheikh...
He,...Mrs. Lohar who is
a deputy-collector...
Sheikh got his goons to attack her.
Make him understand.Is he mad?
This is not done in politics.
Not with violence.
That too on a woman? No...
The whole collectorate is
abuzz with this news.
- Get her security.
-I already have.
I've chosen an offiicer too.
They were together in college.
-His name?
-John Frank. College?
Right ho.
I'll do the confiirmation today.
Alright then.
Nothing...go.Later, may be.
May I come in?
You! Here? Where were
you all these days?
Come in. Sit down.
Sit down.
I've been assigned as your security
I'll investigate and arrange things.
In college you were very English.
You feared nothing, but Hindi!
And now, your Hindi...
It's unbelievable.
All those big, formal words...
Can't help it. This government
job is like that.Anyway you...
What will you have? Tea?
It's coffee without sugar!
Coffee, But bring sugar
and milk separately.
It's so nice to meet you again.
You haven't changed a bit.
You still can't.
Grow your moustaches longer.
You'll look a real policeman!
- Why are your hands so cold?
-Just like that?
-Are you married?
-I've to give a ''tipni''...
-I mean a...
- The same.
These windows will have to be shut.
That's it. They'll have to be shut!
I'll always owe you
one thing all my life.
I don't understand.
You had once paid my college-fees
and not told me about it.
If you hadn't done that I
might not have given that exam.
I can repay the money even today.
But that particular time...Never!
...I'm insulting you.
I haven't forgotten anything.
Neither have I, Ragini.
Yes, keep it.
Your share of sugar in my cup too.
And this is yours, without
sugar, as usual.
How could you do this, sir?
You gave her government security?
She, who insulted me, by slapping
me in front of the staff?
Forget it.
...you play your game, your way.
I play it, my way, Right?
If you ha any sense, you'd have
forgotten it by now. That's politics.
- Understand?
-But sir...This is like opposing me.
What can I do to her now?
since you've shown her support?
If you want to win the opposition,
then first, honour them.
Felicitate them.Everybody likes
to be honoured.Isn't that so?
You want to take revenge, right?
There are many ways to take it.
And she being a woman, will always
be aware of her reputation.Mar it!
Right,Joshi? What will you
gain by harming her physically?
- That too a beautiful body?
- Great! What a move, sir!
That's why I'm occupying
this chair.Now get going.
But forget that I told you anything.
- What about, sir?
Mr. Sheikh, why all this
razzle-dazzle?
The one who slapped you, insulted
me in my own house, is...
You haven't caught-on yet.
It's a political rule.
If you want to win the opposition,
then honour and felicitate them.
Everybody hungers after honour.
You're doing good work. You've
given the administration a face lift.
-I'm just doing my duty.
- Come, have something.
You too.
What are you doing there? Come here.
What lovely photographs. What poses!
You're in a hurry, aren't you?
Well, it's this way.
The society honours your post,
not you. So what is your duty?
To upkeep the respect and
the status of that post.Right?
And you... with your bodyguard?
If you do that...
...the govt. will fall in the eyes
of the public. What if I pose like...
- What are you doing?
-I was just explaining it to you.
In such a situation, anyone
would run away. Get it?
Look.I wanted to give you
one more chance, so I gave it.
If tomorrow you have any problem,
I'm always here for you.
You may go now.
The government lawyer has
tried to prove, that...
the deceased had gone to Lohar
to give him a bribe.
But Lohar demanded more
money and because of this...
...there was a tension between
them and exchange of blows.
And in a ffit of rage, Lohar,
with his own knife...
...murdered the deceased.But!
With all the statements given,
and presented proofs...
...and after considering
the conditions therein...
...this Court has come to
this decision, that Lohar...
...cannot be proved guilty of murder!
Thus, this Court finds the
accused Yashwant Lohar...
...not guilty with the
right of private defence.
Sir, he's free... acquitted!
-I've lost my sleep now.
- You'll never complete your sleep!
Go sleep.
We make laws, yes!
But we can't take them
in our own hands.
He's acquitted from this court.
Is this the only court around?
There are so many.
Go now. We'll do the needful.
I hope so, sir.
I'm very scared.He's a nut.
He may do anything.
-I know.Do you play chess?
-No.
I do.Let him make the 1st move.
We'll reciprocate to that.
-Madam?
- Yes?
Actually...I wanted to speak to you.
Can't you think of anything
else, but your duty?
And what's this ''Madam''...
Can't you call me just Ragini?
-Madam...
-Again? Okay, what is it?
''I'm really in a fiix.I don't
know how to tell you this.''
You're like fragrance...
How do I trap you?
How petty some people are!
They can think of
nothing, but body.
Even the animals are better.
When will they realise that under
this body, lies a heart too!
Congratulations, sir.
- Thank you.
When I came here, you said, we were
all alike.But now, we differ here.
Today I'm acquitted, with
my rank and dignity, intact.
I know sir. Those who love you
must be awaiting you outside.
They'll be very happy to see you free.
-How far will you come with me?
- Till outside.
Limit ends here.
You take care within,...
I'll take care outside.
That's my domain.
-I'm Inspector Lohar.
- To O.T.
I want this man's statement.
-He's critical, I can't
let you take any statement.
Try to get him round.
I must take his statement.
I'll leave my number with you.
- This is Dr. Godbole.
Yes Dr.?
That boy has survived.
- What! He survived?
-And give Yashwant a statement.
Really? He will, eh?
See? That boy will give a statement
to the cop! Think it over.
Who killed him?
Tell me! Who were
waiting for me outside?
Who were they? Who?
Who were they? Tell me.
Don't take law in your hands.
Come on.
Where had you been? You
made me wait for so long.
I awaited you for so long now.
Why had you separated from me?
Now I won't go away from you.
No, I won't go!
What's wrong?
That Deshmukh -master's daughter
because a widow today.
Her husband was killed
by some gangsters.
His bullet-riddled body...
...is lying in the hospital.
Why was he killed?
Because he saw the people
who riddled bullets at me.
They killed him...
Play with my body...go on.
This is yours. I'm not with you.
You can joy with me
for another 1/2 hour.
After 1/2 hour I've to go back.
I've to claim his body,
and get it cremated.
This is yours. Carry on.
This estate belongs to you!
I can understand your hunger.
Hunger for my body.
We get hungry for food...
We hunger for flesh too.
It's not easy to control
this hunger for 6 months.
But I'm not myself.My...
My senses are elsewhere.
In the hospital.
Do what you want to...
But I can't do anything.
Because I see before me...
...that young widow and their kid.
Come on in. Sit down.
I'll pour, sir.
-Be comfortable.
-I am, sir.
Lean back.Be at ease.
One must relax at times.
I'm retiring in November.
Just 6 months from now.
- You could get an extension.
-No.I don't feel like it.
And some people are waiting
for me to retire anyway!
In fact they're even trying
I don't get an extension.
Thank you.
You, sir?
I'm sending you to the
Anti-Narcotics Lobby.
I'll do what I can.But
even the C.M.'s involved.
I know. Go ahead and expose him.
Bare him in public. We'll see.
But remember, within 6 months.
After November, I won't be
able to do anything for you.
- Good you came.
- Why?
- Give us a tenner, please.
-Begging are you?
-No, just borrowing.
- What for?
- To eat.I haven't eaten anything.
- Can't your pop feed you?
He got paid yesterday, but he lost
it at cards. Drank hooch on credit.
He beat my mom black and blue.
Then he went for me.
I just turned and ran...
Please give me.
- Where is this den and who owns it?
- That Shetty will you play too?
Get lost. Go home.
Sir, sir.Lohar is here.
-Listen to me, sir.
-Scram, you...
Here. That's 5 thousand.Now deal.
- What's this, sir?
-Money. Can't you see? Deal, I say.
-I know, but...
-But? What?
You bleed them white, don't you.
And these shameless, give
then daily earnings to you.
They lose cash and booze on credit.
Then go home and beat up wives!
Kids beg on streets. A butcher's
better.He kills a goat...
...and sells openly. Come on,
deal! No.7.Now deal.
They come daily hoping that
they'll win today, tomorrow...
...else the day after. They lose
daily and you're always the winner.
One sided gamble.Not good.
Look at this gamble.A real gun.
5 bullets inside, one outside.
Go on try your luck.All is
yours. Win or service.
-I'll even stake my clothes.
-Spare me.
Spare me, eh! I'll try my luck first.
If I survive, I'll take everything.
This is gamble, understand?
Do you have the guts? Bastard!
-Enough. I'm on duty.
-Let me put a little.
I said enough!
Honestly! Scared of colour?
Always hollering...
- Come and play colour, darling...
-Buzz off.
-Showing off, eh?
-Put some on him too...
Even they can play, but you can't.
You're forgiven!
Take him to the police station.
I'll join you.
- The bastard!
- What was the name? Lohar?
Forget it.He made a mistake.
-Forgive him.
-Really?
He lifted his hand at me! Me!
Never mind.I'll have his job!
- Get my father on the line.
-Let it be, sir.
-Dial, I say.
-Had he known...
...who you are, he would've
never done this, would he?
-He'll be punished!
-He's a nut, sir.
He just re-joined and he struck
you. There goes his job again!
-How come he's in my chair?
- Why ask him?
- You come here. Come on...
- What?
Don't touch me.
I'm the C.M.'s son.
Don't, sir! He's the C.M.'s son.
So what if he's the C.M.'s brat?
He can't ''eve-Tease''girls.
-Look, don't come forward.
- What will you do?
Don't come near me, I say.
I shoot you. Shoot you!
This is due to your
cowardice.A brat...
...snatches a gun from you, and
you just stand there. Come here.
Come on.Kick him on
his arse! Come on.
Come on... kick him.
Go on, kick him!
Come on... kick!
kick him hard!
- What's this?
-He was caught eve-teasing.
But why hit him so much?
He was splattered with blood.
No.It's red powder.He's hurt
a bit, but he deserves it.
He went and sat in my chair
My staff was flattering him.
He was misbehaving.
Reciting fiilmi dialogues,
''I'll show you Inspector.''
''I'm the C.M.'s son!''
Does being the C.M.'s son, mean
he'll harass the girls?
I don't know all that, they think
I'm favouring you unduly,
True.
-And what about the job I gave you?
-I can't bear to see it.
I always told you to use your
temper as strength, not weakness.
Now go! The C.M. has called you.
-How come you're here?
- You called me to tell me...
...that you're not happy with my
work. Shall I tell you this?
I'm also not happy with your work
first repair the faults at home.
Then see to the state.
Make your son understand.
That you serve the people. When
you had begged for votes...
...they didn't know that the people
they're voting for today...
...their sons will eve-tease
their daughters tomorrow.
Hey! Calm down, will you?
Take him out, somebody.
-But why is he angry?
- What can one do?
This will always be hike this.
Let's get on with our work.
The Commissioner is in a meeting
He has sent you a photograph.
That man has come about a drug deal.
He'll leave in the morning.
If he can be caught, good.
Here, take this.
Show them the sample.
If they like it...
...send them the consignment.
People in ''224''are my guests.
Put their bill on my account.
- Who's the manager here?
- Your father, you bastard!
There's some news about
Inspector Lohar here, yet again.
Our correspondent's report
The bullying of Ins. Lohar...
...has reached its Zenith.
The public is fed of this.
He didn't even spare the son
of the C.M.! On ''Holi''day...
...the C.M.'s son was
enjoying himself with his friends.
Ins. Lohar deliberately beat
him up and jailed him.
Last night, he whipped a decent
man at a hotel.
People say he's a sadist who
gets pleasure in beating up people.
Please recall, that because
of such actions, Lohar...
...was suspended some time back,
But he still hasn't learnt his lesson.
- There's a saying in English...
-Nonsense! It's all bullshit!
They're hounding Yashwant.
They want to suspend him again.
-It's all a plot,
-If so,...
... then the C.M.,
won't let his son be beaten.
He was beaten because
of his own doing.
He was drunk and teasing the girls.
What else could Yashwant do?
And that drug-smuggler...
should he have let him escape?
-Normally one arrests and jails.
- This doesn't happen normally!
Normally police arrest just show
And a part of the stuff is caught.
Then in a 5 -star Hotel,
a sum is fiixed as a bribe.
Only what is caught is news. Not
what gets away. Yashwant's not so.
How long will I have to wait?
- What is it?
-My camera is stolen.
Is it stolen, or has
someone snatched it?
No, it;s stolen.
-Sit down.From where?
-I was covering a march.
Listen, you'll find Chikna Abdul
near Khyber.Bring him here.
- Where do you work?
-I'm a journalist.
- Where, I said.
-In ''Navbharat Times''.
- Your name?
-Deepak Sharma
- You wrote this?
- Yes, I did.
-Read it.
- Why? I've written it myself.
Do you know this man?
Ever met him?
No, I haven't.
Who'll play with fire?
- Why?
- Ofcourse, what else?
I hear he talks with his hands
Doesn't know laws and regulations.
This is democracy not dictatorship.
We all have our rights here.
Prove the crime.Let the court
punish him. Who's this guy to hit us?
See how decent you are
such a man should be suspended.
I'll write a lot more
about this man.
Next time you pen
print his photo too.
Let the public know
who this despot is!
- Greetings, sir.
-Ah Abdul! Come on in...
-Sit down.
-It's alright, sir.
-How are things? At home?
-All well, thanks.
-Had your lunch?
-No, sir,
You haven't, eh?
Here, take this.
- Take this. Have this biryani.
-I don't understand, sir.
Eat, I'll explain later.
Now eat.
Finished?
Here, drink this,
Do you know who he is?
He writes against injustice.
He's a big shot.
His camera is stolen.
In that march today.
Give it to him.
-I don't know about it, sir.
- Go on.
By God, sir, I don't...
I'll get it...
Take this away... Come on...
See? I fed him, gave him a drink.
Asked him properly, didn't admit.
A slap near the ear and he came
clean. That's why we have to hit.
If I feed everyone biryani, I'll
have to starve. Go, your bag's found.
Return, if you want photographs.
I'm Lohar. Unearth. What you want.
- Go and order one more biryani.
- Yes, sir.
He has crossed the limit now!
As long as he's alive,
I'll know no peace.
Go! But remember, after death,
he has to be shown as a martyr.
Your order will be carried out.
But you're forgetting politics?
- You're getting emotional.
-Right. When my son was hurt...
-...I had lost my head.
- The photos are ready and good.
-It's time the public saw them.
- You're right for the 1st time.
-She looks very decent.
-But nowadays one can't really say.
Here she comes.
I'm still alive.
I think, I understand.
I've some small needs. Some demands.
That someone love me.
Fight with me. Quarrel.
Get cross, and make up too.
I should need someone.
Someone could need me.
But this never happened.
Who was my mother?
Don't know.Father? Don't know.
When was I put in an orphanage
by a constable? Don't know.
I was cared for like a weed.
I grew up on punches, kicks...
...and food off other people's
plates. Why? I don't know.
How, and why did I educate
myself? Don't know.
Why I joined the police?
Don't know.I knew just one thing.
Every time, at every place...
I was not wanted.
Look at my colleagues in
the police department.
Because I'm a hurdle in
their black earnings.
They think I'm a traitor.
I don't ffit in their scheme.
Anyway, who are these people?
My wife.My own dear wife.
She too.
I married an orphan girl. Thought...
...two orphans will understand
each other better. That constable...
...give me a name in the orphanage.
That name, that borrowed name...
...I gave my wife. Gave her
my name, my love.
Name...Lohar.
Ragini Yashwant Lohar.
She's fed up of that name.
She's in search of another name now.
I'm going to kill them both!
-Anyway, your fees doctor.
- Where are you going now?
- You're mental state is bad.
- When was it fine?
Rs. 200 per session. That makes
it 400/-for 2 sessions.
It's quite possible.
Both are young...
...Good looking. Old friendship.
An old lost spark may have
been fanned again.
Then there's hunger.Mental or
physical hunger is hunger.
I also wasn't around.
Adjustment of our needs.
What can one do? We all
have our needs. Right?
Enough now! You've had
more than 1/2 bottle.
Have this. Come on...
Couldn't she wait for me
a bit longer?
I went in, and she let herself go.
I trusted a wrong woman.
Saw a handsome boy, and,
she fell for him! Bloody whore!
Doubt has made a home in your mind.
You doubt your wife?
You bloody... Get out!
That woman ruined and
sacrifficed her home life...
...because of your mistake.
And you doubt her?=
Shameless!
Get up! And get out.Don't
ever show your face again!
It was an inauspicious moment
when I became friends with you.
Shame on your life!
I spit on your kind!
Open the door.I'm hungry.
Don't feel lonely.
I'll always be there for you.
Let him click.Are you
scared of them?
How many photos will they print?
What will they prove?
That I'm a cheap woman.
We don't feel guilty about it.
I'm your friend. You're mine.
This too is a relation.
But a maligned one.
A much misunderstood one.
Why, I don't know.
But in whose eyes
will they malign me?
In the eyes of the world.
I don't fear them.
Yashwant has built a lot of
strength in me. They think...
...I'll fall in this eyes?
Forget it.
They don't know him.I do.
He trusts me so implicitly.
Anything else?
Being a senior police offiicer,
he married an orphan girl.
Gave her his name,
He never let me feel...
...that I was an orphan.He
educated me and made be able.
Who does so much for anyone?
Yes...
...we do live separately, no doubt,
but we still share same relationship.
My life starts on one word.
And ends on it too.
- You, and here?
-Surprised, are you?
No...
- Too much work, eh?
-No, just a little...
...Not ''a little'', but ''a lot''!
It's a conspiracy.
-By whom?
- The one who is against you and me.
A big conspiracy...
First they dumped this bastard in
water and then put you in his arms.
Then they took the photograph.
A very big conspiracy indeed!
Young...I'm also young.
Not as young as him.
He's much younger.
Just because he's young,
you slept with him. Whore!
For the first time...
...I felt I'm really an orphan.
Farce! I spoke the truth...
...and you found it so bitter.
Till now, you never looked
into my eyes and spoke.
Today, you hit me like this.
I can blow your brains
to pieces even now.
But first I'll kill
that bastard. Then...
I'll see how your face reacts.
And then later...
You never looked in my eyes...
and today you...
New sari, eh? You never
wore good clothes for me.
But for him...
New sari for him.
Open the door, go on...
An imported dog barks anyhow...
You always bark up a wrong tree!
Where did you get the photo?
Tell me.
Who ordered you to print it?
Tell me, where did you get it?
Who asked you to print it?
Name him.
It wasn't me.Inspector
Joshi asked me to.
Have you gone mad?
This is too much!
Get out of here!
I don't have a passport-size
photo with my wife.
You snapped her with that
bastard in the water...
You always drink foreign liquor.
I'm not even destined
to drink country hooch!
Sometimes my lawyer
friend, offers me some.
Today he threw me out without
dinner.He hit me like this...
Everything...
Everything is imported.
Don't you have anything
that's made-in-India?
I'm Yashwant Lohar.
Age, till my next breath.
I'm a policeman.It's
my religion and duty.
Parents, not known.I've such
a face that the goons think I'm...
-...a police and vise versa.
-He's mad, my dear.
-Don't talk to him. Go inside.
-He made me crazy.
And you drove him mad.
You must have hounded him...
...to bring this, bring that.
Your demands increased...
I just asked for children.
-Is Mr.Joshi there?
-He just left. Salim Sheikh.
Look.I've put the gun down.
We're not enemies! I pulled the
trigger by mistake.Habit, y'see.
You're the best of friends.
How's your wife?
No! I've got very high contacts.
I can feed you to your gills!
I'll feed you instead.Feed
poison to kids, eh?
Taste some yourself too.
-How much is this worth?
- 1,00,000/-.
Have some. Your father mustn't have
fed you such an expensive morsel.
-I'll die like this.
- You've lived too long anyway.
Let me show you
what you wish to rule.
I'll die, Yashwant.
There's still time...
Still time, Yashwant.
Still time...
-Still have time.
-But I don't have the time.
I've to sentence 2 more to death.
Joshi's waiting for you in hell.
Go, bribe him!
I want to confess.
I've sinned.
I loved a girl in college.
It was a one-way affair.
She didn't know I loved her.
I met her again after years.
But she was married by then.
I tried very hard, but I
couldn't forget I loved her.
I looked at a married
woman with lusty eyes.
Such a woman, who loves her
husband with all her heart.
I've wronged her, and her husband.
And I must be punished for it.
And they must get
life's choicest joys.
This is not your place. You should
be in the confession-box.
It's me.
I wish to speak to you.
Can you come here?
You're not saying anything.
I understand.
Please come here.I'll
be waiting for you.
Forgive me, dear.
I misbehaved with you yesterday.
I couldn't control myself
seeing that photograph.
Infact, I was scared that
I won't live without you.
I can't think of life,
without you in it.
I went to V.ikram.Drank booze.
He too hit me and threw me out!
If you leave me, I'll lose my power.
Won't be able to fight this world.
I have no one, but you.
-I won't live.
- Why are you lying?
You are a selfish man.
Rather, a devil!
Why, and how can I stay with you?
When I see your face...
...all those abuses ring in my ears.
You buried me yesterday. Your
apologies won't bring me back.
-Just this living corpse.Now...
-No.Don't say that.
I will never give you a chance
to complain again.Just for once...
Just this once...
Did you read? Sensational
news about you...
- What is it?
Why such a long face?
You really, have stirred
a hornets'nest! Listen...
The state C.M. had to resign
because of super-cop Lohar.
The C.M. was involved with the
narcotic lobby.Lohar exposed this.
The P.M. sacked the State
C.M. from his post yesterday.
A high-level inquiry will be held.
Centre has ordered the Commission...
...to change the present technique
to improve the image of the police.
The Commission said the corrupt
offiicers will be suspended soon...
...and he has suggested Lohar's
name, because of his great daring...
...and loyalty, for the
President's Medal.Remember...
...he played an important role in
exposing corruption in State Govt. ...
...and the nexus between the top
offiicers and anti-social activists.
To fulfiill this mission he had to
confront many hurdles. He faced...
...the wrath of the corrupt offiicers
from his own department. This often...
...led to his suspension.Even
then, he stuck to his duty...
Never discarded honesty. Thus
his name is suggested for the honour.
Why are you crying? You've
done a great thing.
What will I do with all this?
She has left me.
-I called her, but she didn't come.
- Who? Who didn't come?
Why do you want her now?
She's a whore, isn't she?
Where were you? Give us a treat.
But why this long face?
These red eyes. Boozed a lot, eh?
Smile, see this. Your photo.
Now you'll get an uniform.
That of an Inspector!
- Where are you going?
-My wife's offiice.
She works too?
Doesn't one pay suffiice? Don't you
earn ''extra''? Come, let's meet her.
Stop the car.
I want to talk to you.
Stop! I want to talk.
Stop the car. Stop it, I say!
Please forgive me.
I made a blunder.
Hit me if you wish, but don't
leave me.I've nothing but you.
From today, your wish
is my command.
I'll close my eyes and live.
Seal my lips;, Bow my head and live.
I just think of our house,
our kids and our comfort.
I'll give everything to my kids.
And for that I'll take bribe.
I'll become dishonest.
But please don't leave me.
If anybody's being murdered.
I'll keep quiet.
If any woman's being raped
I'll shut my eyes to it.
-I'll change with the times...
-Let go! He's taking my purse.
Want a paper?
There's his photo in it.
I'll have to fight another case
free of charge.Better I leave.
A very dangerous being.
But he's my friend.