Subtitle : By juleyano
http://juleyano.movies.
I never dreamed ...
I get ... that hath a
day Prime Minister.
Because I never had
intention to get involved on politics.
Nobody in my family had
to do with politics ever.
However, although I am happy ...
... That you may serve me
region as Prime Minister ...
Are also anxious ... ...
If I ever succeed ...
Ómplinesc my dreams.
To pass this test,
I need your help ...
As well as the supporters ...
in my party.
Glad to have him minister
Deputy Krishnakant with me ...
Whose expertise on policy ...
will have a tremendous value.
I promise not solve
immediately any problem.
Because, having regard to the manner on
On the situation deteriorated ...
It will take time ...
to save something.
Also, I can not promise ...
To assure the job ...
Youth on time.
I promise not
eradicate poverty.
But I can give the word of my ...
I'll eliminate crime ...
in this region.
This is my promise.
- No, sir! Please!
- Shut up! Not again "sir" ...
I did nothing, sir!
Please, believe me!
We'll show you after we get Ónauntru!
Œntotdeauna showing off
with your muscles, right?
This bandit of
Byculla, sir.
That's not true!
I did nothing!
Take it on imprisonment!
Van is here to lead him
John in court, sir.
- Where sheep are clothes?
- Here, sir.
You are personally responsible
On the condition where you are.
If you do not have
On future problems ...
The court will declare ...
what I said.
As Deva makes smuggling
drugs and gold!
And you yourself used to
to cover illegal activities.
These are words that
you tell them! Okay?
Œmbraca up!
Okay ... I'll give it
statement, sir.
But please bring me
here after the hearing.
Óndraznesc not to hang out!
P, not ol arrested on Deva
let me stay here.
After you give the statement ...
Deva ... will get behind bars
even on this imprisonment!
We want to talk about
witness that OL will bring.
He confessed that works
for Deva?
We can not say anything Ónca.
- The police somehow Deva themes ...
- You will find it on the ass, nd.
Truth you will Ónvatisa
Óndata the court verdict.
Will not last long on any case.
OSI give witness statement right now.
Mr. Kulkarni has not reached
Ónca on the court.
- I came Ónca?
- No, sir.
Then where the hell is it?
What Ont, MPLA here?
Why was I t, r, t here?
This is not good, Deva ...
Not sharp, Inspector!
Here there is a trial ...
And do not allow prisoners ...
screaming on the court!
But what I did?
But what have I done?
I have a Ónregistrare
your mistakes, Inspector!
Already six years of that, when ...
You were ... Ónsarcinat to
represent the law!
And on these six years ...
You killed mercilessly ... six people
On your Ónchisoarea!
Look, Deva ...
Let me go.
No, Kulkarni! I can not give you
allowed to get out of here.
I'm Onalta seat
judgment without Óndoiala.
But those people are
givers verdict.
Ónca verdict was not given Kulkarni.
He's guilty!
Not true, Deva ...
I have committed no crime.
I did not kill anyone!
So that, when someone close the
and he commence ...
On exposing atrocities give
Óndurate are those on your custody ...
This is why.. I
John will be sent on your cell imprisonment
You killed two of my men ...
P can forgive, not this one.
But the three men innocent
that you killed ...
... Had nothing to do
the crime world!
Killer NDU them, you
families thrown ...
On poverty and despair ...!
One of them was only
support for parents!
And poor worker on
you have Ómpuscat ...
Óntretinea a family ...
twelve people!
Ansari, kill all of you,
left on a baby three months ago!
You committed these crimes ...
... Just to decorate your uniform
On to your promotion!
No, Deva! Please do not!
You can not kill me so!
Our department will know how ...
I do this just for the sake
our department.
Did this revolver was given to
st, RPI evil in society.
But you only crimes he committed.
Do not do this, Deva!
This is the first time that, when this weapon
will be used for a noble purpose!
Listen, Deva!
What did you tell me?
I tell you I'm on exchange.
I regret for losing his job.
I was humiliated?
You, my brother own a position
Onalta hath a prestigious company ...
I ... how could I be the only
a worker at a mill?
For this we studied?
Well, Deva ... Admit that deserve
a better job.
But someone has to make some
things to and c, Stig existence!
No, Akash ... Can not work
just for that.
Can not work for others.
I do not like.
Talk about that, stigarea a
existing at that job, right?
On Look around you! So you live in a
job for which you get only 1300!
Deva! Why did you throw your shoe?
You can hurt! Listen, Deva!
Why did not you tell Óncaltarile
Your were broken?
At first paycheck, I'm gonna
buy a new pair.
Go ahead and wear them.
Or people will say ...
Brother of a man ...
important business ...
... Has nothing to Óncalta!
Dropped! He dropped and
his job!
Ónteleg not this guy wants!
- Forget it now ...
- What problem did you have there?
I did not like the service ...
I could not concentrate.
Here! He wants a job at
which can concentrate!
That Ont, MPLA after I
had influence on the game to talk to Surajmal....
After all weights taken ...
to convince him!
There are thousands of people who
standing in line for these jobs!
And this guy says
that the ministry did not caught!
I could not get used
never with such service.
I studied at, t much
for it?
- What Omi use university?
- What do you want then?
Have been lazy at home, p, not c, when
a job will find it for you?
Stop ...
Let him even man, nce on silence.
Shut up! Simply not
can have a job!
Or does not like, or
can not focus!
There's a limit of irresponsibility!
Here! You see what is arrogant?
No one wants to correct
On that Jaffa stupidity.
What has Ont, wrong? Why
celebrate with fireworks?
Do you know?
India lost the game!
I c, Stig 500 rupees
of this ONFR, angel!
For the country you live on that
Ll give me, NCAR ...
Not ashamed ... to the
ONFR celebrate, angel?
Guys, we have another
Gandhi, preacher!
Look ... out of here!
Go, right?
Let's go, bro!
Go!
You take Guddi home Akash ...
Come.
Well then ... you did
r, s my brother?
It was their mistake, Dad!
Became violent and then ...
Then he showed them
the bully is!
She jumped to her!
What is the difference between him
and those punks?
Yes, I beat! I would have broken
bones if he had not fled!
Deva! So talk to your father ...
Let me speak, mom!
C, when someone offends my brother ol ...
... You want me to stay away?
Who do you think you are to them
hit others?
And who's to create
problems? For us, no?
I do not want to worry you, Dad.
But I can not live
as a coward.
I can not Óntorc back
an injustice!
I insist that I made there
was what had to be done!
There was nothing wrong!
Œntotdeauna feel offended
whatever they do!
You can not like a t nar
sit passively, right?
What do you mean? I
I t was, nar?
This son of yours I was also
he t, nar?
Youth sheep give someone the right
Wear not civilized?
Come and give me m, NCAR.
C, when I was caught by those guys,
I was really afraid.
- Come on, Akash!
- There were 10 ...
... And had to protect him
and Guddi.
Guys like that are few tigers
of h, rtie: much ado about nothing.
Shoot them a punch
run away!
- Why r day?
- What did he say?
Ganfhi ... another preacher!
Gandhi, of course. You know what
great man was?
Titles!
Dad's at work.
Man, nec quickly something!
Brother ...
People are talking about ...
your exploits!
On the way you've beat
today ... it was amazing!
People will now Óntelege
My brother is a strong man!
Œnceteaza. If my father hears
Your praise ...
Big deal! Will certainly
then will sulk.
And I have to bring him a tray
with m, NCAR on camera!
Steel hear r, z, nd, right?
I do not think it is good to
certified by Deva at, t often.
I'm not saying it should
leave to make the head, but ...
Do you not love him?
This tray daughter
and your a go ...
Me ... e put on reality.
- What?
- It's true.
That I was not Ónseamna I
ignore mistakes.
One wrong step can make it on
a man regrets life.
I'm afraid of temperament
him on any case ...
Here! That's the signal for
Óncapat your son, nat come out on the street!
What's wrong with it on?
Why pl, NGI?
Do not tell us?
- Vilas today ...
- What did he do?
I cut way back.
C, when I asked to stap, NEASC,
I grabbed for me, never!
You Ónnebunit? Why did you have to
say that on his face?
Óntreb me what to do now?
What could I do, Mom?
- Come on!
- Brother ...
Deva! Wait!
Stop, Deva!
- Stop, Deva!
- May Ont, and listen to me, mother!
Stop it! Vilas steel will kill!
Wait, brother! Please!
It's a bill!
Remove the money, boys!
Stop, Deva ...
Stop it, son!
I cut way back, bro!
C, when I said to stap, NEASC,
I grabbed my mother!
On leave it alone, Deva!
A die!
Let l, ll say!
Leave it!
What did you do?
My son is a murderer!
You're a killer!
Why not have died at birth?
I am the father cursed ...
Get it here on this
and close the jerk he is!
Banish him forever!
I have such a son!
Get it here!
IMO feared this day!
But none of you will
could Óntelege why I acted like that!
You thought I was his enemy Deva!
I never suspected that
jerk grow!
Oen what's wrong
On his education?
Do not say that, sir ...
Vilas my brother.
To what do ...
I think it deserves ...
even more severe punishment.
Why only Deva? No
brother can not tolerate ...
What he did not Deva
something shameful, sir!
But that my brother!
What did my brother!
You gave both of the disease;
I never felt like a stranger here.
According to Article 307
Penal Code ...
Deva condemn the court ol ...
4 years of imprisonment.
Do not worry, okay? I'm going to
Make Dad to agree.
We appeal.
Just do not ...
Hey, Akash ...
What are you doing?
I want to crash?
Akash!
Apply double symbol
bride's forehead.
Not so funny, sir ...
Your son ... married
and do not you tell us anything?
In fact, it has happened
Both the fast ONC, T. ..
My son ...
Deepu ... hey! Wait!
Wait!
Now look ... I had to be
Ont, mple, was Ont, mplat already.
Deva turns the day
after four years.
Just keep your cool ...
I've been talking with him.
Brother!
Mom!
Be blessed, my son ~
You must change your life, son.
I still think Œnca
done wrong, mama?
See?
Has no opinion of
sorry for what he did!
I went to the police
and the court!
Even our relatives have been ...
My son came ... to imprisonment!
After we made the r, s family ...
Why has the nerve to Óntrebe ...
to hurt!
Please, sir ... forget the past.
To focus on the future.
Deva needs you now.
Your condition.
A man from the mistakes Ónvata
they do, Inder.
You can say, looking at him, that he regrets?
Yes, it's true that I do not regret anything.
That sense.
And I hate to get console
with a lie.
No need ... one family
should not tell him anything!
Family of c, shouted enough
from you.
Your parents are honored
because you have given life!
Now leave us alone on ... family
can not bear you anymore!
Why take things at, t
away? We Óntelege ...
- I'll talk to him
- Have patience, sir.
If you talk so, Deva
might Ónfuria and ...
How can you say that?
- Everyone knows that ...
- Dad is right, Mom.
That they are not willing to change me ...
It is my weakness ... or a
reflection of my stubbornness.
I am not allowed to do
else trouble for it!
Dad ... I'm sorry. I did not
offered no joy in life.
If I could ever
up to you ...
I have to believe that life ...
has reached my goal.
Listen! Stop it ...
Deva Do not let go!
Stop, Deva ...
Listen to me!
Listen to what I say, Deva!
If we leave ...
I no longer remains in this house.
Go with you!
Do not do this, Akash.
Family needs you.
Especially my father, who put
All hopes in you.
Do not disappoint.
Look who's here with me!
You have to sit there?
Do not hug me?
Let's see ...
Government money you made
a strong man!
Well ... You are a guest in this city
and the government visitor you?
I got a transfer here
After a lot of work!
There's nowhere that hometown!
You were moved here then?
Lord's assistant police!
I am delighted your progress, Inder.
In fact, we needed
years to be promoted.
But I am truly amazed
your progress!
Deva ours is a man
important now, is not it?
You bear all stand talking here?
But when you come
best.
Everyone at home will be
excited by your presence.
Now wait ...
You win money, Deva ...
But what about ...
emotional problems?
I mean, you found a girl?
- A girl?
- I mean your marriage.
Marriage? Do not see what state is it?
I have courage.
Very good, smart guy ...
I criticize me?
I'm gonna find myself a girl
that would be like ...
- Like what?
Where are we going?
You tell me?
Where the hell are we going?
Shut up and come with us.
Now look: I'm not
spoke back!
I was busy working for you!
Besides, not only
supporter of Prime Minister!
He has a few such people.
How many days hold in place a
Minister today ...
no one can tell!
These stories of cloak and dagger
that politicians will put them up to ...
CM ... support that it receives
from his friends ...
Your problems ... and not
is our job!
We've broken the deal, huh?
Police closed five
of our connections!
You promised not permit
three months ago?
What about this? And
do not the naive, right?
Watch what you say when
talk to me!
Hey, dude!
Have you ever used this voice
determined before being elected?
And what ways we
you give lessons?
And you're talking with two tongues!
I already borrowed 50 million
the contract that you promised us!
All that money went on
drain, right?
Such ups and downs are
a normal business Lal Singh.
In any case ...
We will not win anything ...
suspects the latter it on Krishnakant.
Honestly, Mr. Jindal, had all
ready for CM's removal last month.
We prepared 19 MLA
to support us!
Nobody could have guessed that things
the central government will get worse.
Did you read the interview Governor
in the morning paper?
This is nothing more than scam!
I understand that, sir Krishnakant.
I understand everything.
We lose business and you
're screwed in politics.
You know that two of MLA
that he thought loyal
I joined ... to CM?
- You're wrong, Mr. Jindal!
- Trust me ...
- Well, sir Krishnakant ...
Your company distinguished ... taught me
something about politics!
This is an example of manipulation
taking place right now ...
What happens, Mr. Jindl!
What's this?
We are with you, Krishnakant!
Swear that we will be
always with you!
Believe us, Mr. Jindal!
Hurry up! Find out who he was!
They are!
Ask her! As has been paid
to stop my car?
Who were those guys who
Shoot me?
Make a mistake.
I just ...
Girls like you would do anything
for a few rupees!
That's right ... you recognized
what they are!
Yes, looks like a cheap whore ...
Need to dress ...
way to earn a living!
But that's because they are
dancer at a club.
I have to wear it
for public sake!
I hope you do not have to tell you ...
That no girl ... do not
that of her own desire.
I did not intentionally hit the car!
Those men armed
wanted to kill me!
When I left after the
show, I saw killing someone!
Therefore follow me!
Well ...
No need to cry.
Go home lady, Mani.
No need. I'm going alone.
I do not want any favors.
Find out where he lives and that
's her problem.
Excuse me ...
Could somebody take me home?
To go.
You are not worthless!
You can not even get a girl?
I did my best, sir ...
Okay ... let me alone!
Are you married?
I see ... do not like men.
My daughter has the same problem.
I wonder what is in his head.
Mom!
What was that? Did you start
barfeste me again, huh?
- Not!
- So ... how's it going?
Did you take your medicine on time?
Course. And the doctor came
here to examine me.
I told him that he has no sense!
My cough does not heal!
You must have had another
sour-snack (m Indian NCAR)
No! I do not touch that!
You can not change, mom! You did not
doctor forbade me, NCAR spicy?
But I told him not to add
too many spices!
Ónsotitor bad aim ...
Which always gives head ... as if
would Óntelege all ...
The end ..., rsit by doing the same
mistake again!
- What you got for me?
- Apples and bananas.
And how ram us with lam, s?
You have that?
This is the first time that, when I looked!
Okay, I'll share with neighbor.
I gave once-sour snack.
The doctor forbade him something too!
And just as you're Óncrunti to me ...
Poor guy ... it took to get
On his wife every day!
's Fun here!
It's very nice!
I feel good here, mom ...
... But I had a
unpleasant experience last night.
Why? What has Ont, wrong?
You had a conflict with
new boss, right?
Not at all! Well ...
and an apple.
You did not say anything about
your new job!
Hope you do not do something illegal ...
You Óncredere on me, right?
Think I'd involved
ever on that?
No ... we all Óncrederea on you.
If I recover, I'm gonna
find a suitable husband.
If you g ndesti to someone, tell me.
I have someone on my mind ...
but it will take time.
OL must know.
I need to know ...
... What kind of person he is.
That's Deva sir.
He built an impressive reputation
On crime world, between a very short time.
Smuggle gold.
Although not a member Ónca
Drug mafia.
This is Jindal's owner ...
a large number of factories.
Smuggle narcotics.
Ties p, and not
international mafia.
This is Lal Singh, sir.
Owns a construction company.
The strength, came ...
Illegally occupy some ...
locations in the city.
With the help of officials ...
Raised new construction ...
illegal government land.
Already has that, few files on
police archives.
This is Khan, Mr. ... one
leaders of organized crime.
You could say his job
is to kill for money.
It is suspected for murder
multiple personalities.
Work for Jindal and Lal Singh.
Œmi Sorry, sir, the police ...
On ... I was able to gather much
evidence Ómpotriva these bandits.
But we are sure that if they
four are put under control ...
Crime will ...
disappear from the city.
Tell me something.
If the police know at, t
more about them ...
Why ... did nothing?
Is there a problem, sir.
Our judicial system.
Legal formalities sky
long time, sir.
And these people OSI
use financial strength ...
And ... to engage the
Best Lawyers.
The law simply does not
can keep up with them ...
And ... our positions are weakened.
But that's not the police Ónseamna
Óncrucisate arms should stay.
- Not at all, sir.
- The Department must Óntreprinda something.
We need special powers
for that, sir.
We need judges who
regardless of time,
Give us ... warrants
Ómpotriva these gangsters.
We need special powers ...
Them ... to arrest any, when
consider necessary ...
And then that, when necessary, to the
We confess the truth ...
... Should have permission to use
Their third degree measures Ómpotriva!
I know it's much truth
On what you say.
But who can guarantee ...
If police ...
receives such power ...
They will not abuse ...
their privileges?
If someone is caught
abuse, when these powers ...
No ... he will not be spared!
We must take
Ómpotriva's tough.
I liked the suggestion
you, Mr. Saxena.
We get you the knowledge
p my decision, not me, hold evening.
To go now ... and take
something to me, NCAR.
This is for you, Akash.
Seems expensive.
You write history with that
pen hath one day.
I'll do something at, t
important with this pen?
It would be good to keep it so.
It will be difficult to read history
that I write.
You're good at writing, Deva ...
Sherbet!
The table is ready, but never arrived Inder Ónca
But we keep flam, Nzi
's sake, right?
It was called just today. A policeman
OSI will owe Ont, i
So ...
C, t you provided Lal for
To clear the suburbs?
- Tell me!
- I've never been there, sir ...
In fact, I was away in Goa!
I know sheep criminals like you!
Do not touch it, sir ...
And we know the law.
I know what makes you
Both the arrogant!
You know you support
Your mentor, Lal Singh.
Which anyone can buy ...
Log you out ... and imprisonment!
But times have changed!
Time to get away
Lal's protection.
Because I have to destroy
people like Lal in this city!
Well ... Lal is the one who executes.
But you're up to it.
Looks like we'll give
some very good news.
Tell us ...
This is an excellent opportunity.
I think we will lose ground
from Kalina, Mr. Lal.
Because the trust Nanabhai
On land legally obtained ...
... To build a school there.
They and approval of the court.
I Ont, lnit with their lawyer and
I Óncercat to convince ...
Razg ... to, ndeasca.
But disagree.
Trust attorney's consent
tribunal. And ...
You ... you made, counselor?
I Óncercat all my
on state power, Mr. Lal, but ...
I have one billion online game ...
And you say ... "You Óncercat"!
What it is on this case?
What's your crime?
I killed someone.
I was a good idea
provoke him Lal Singh.
Is anyone there?
Help!
Help! Anybody here? Help!
Somebody help me!
Cry? Œnaintea statue justice?
Œncearca to Ónlaturi now ...
imprisonment will be first!
Help!
So that, when nobody
hath heard 9 to 5 ...
Who will hear ... after 5 o'clock?
Deva's judgment commence after 5.
You must be an animal
to kill someone, Dad.
I need to talk to you, Lal.
I have Ont, lnire important ...
not see?
All ONT, lnirile come only
after ONT, my lnirea, Lal.
Now look, Deva ...
I'm not here to kill you, Lal.
One of my boys could have
to do this very easily.
What do you want from me?
You put me, not the many lands ...
High.. and have many illegal constructions
Your greed has grown at, t more ...
ONC., t p, and not schools or cemeteries ...
Became your goals ...!
These are documents about
plot in Kalina.
You have to mix yourself
On that land issues.
Sign these documents ...
... And I leave you alone for five years on!
To save your five years of life,
for only a piece of pam, nt ...
... Not a bad deal, Lal.
Sign.
That lawyer that
You wanted to kill him ..
Ashok Pradhan ... ...
's ... My father.
If we do ever
such a mistake ...
I bring you ... hath such a state ...
On ... you to see your life
escape, NDU you through your fingers!
I can see by your heartbeat ...
Ll cherish life ... as much.
All home are scared, Deva.
I asked my father not to accept the case.
Are at, tea land which
Lal Singh asked me, did.
Courts can not do anything.
But Dad had ...
Not be ONT, MPLA nothing father.
Watch it on Lal Singh, even the most
evil criminals in the city ...
Óndrazni ... would not look at him.
I fear for you, Deva.
You made many enemies on the town.
I know Ómpotriva fight evil.
But police IB covers the villains!
Do not you worry about me.
I can not Óntelegi.
We are dealing only with villains!
- Anyway, how's work?
- I commence something new.
It's material
construction, OSI has av, nt now ...
In fact, negotiate with other
c tive builders.
I want to give it
and to commence a large scale.
No thanks ... I'm happy
as it is now.
I work from 9-6 ...
and then home.
Oen Besides, I would never succeed
I can handle a large!
Nobody can c, Stig
a dispute with you!
Yes that file dad. Contains
land in Kalina documents.
Hey, boy ... where's Mom?
Your mother?
He's gone.
He's gone! Where?
- Apollo Hospital!
- At the hospital?
- What place is it, son?
- It's a hospital, Mrs. ...
Just look hospitals?
Only the rich are treated here, lady!
That must cost a
lot of money, right?
Not much ... I just got
ten thousand rupees.
Ten thousand rupees! I
Teachings, rte head!
Go on your
you, lady!
- What did you say? My room?
- Even so.
- I have a room just for me?
- Of course.
Œnteleg! Go!
What large room!
Has TV! It works!
Course.
It's a TV in the colors!
I took a look!
- What is this device?
- An air conditioner, ma'am.
- What?
- An air conditioner.
Regulate temperature.
You are right!
Bed? E and this for me?
God ... no such beds?
Again my teachings, rte head!
- We go now, ma'am.
- Very good. Goodbye.
- What are you doing, Mom?
- My baby! Come here ...
May ONT and kiss you!
Come ... Hurry up!
You found a great job.
And Deva ... is really generous.
But seems innocent, huh?
Look ... you saw color TV?
And it's a machine that
will cool room!
And this bed ... is soft, right?
Deva'm very happy for you.
You'll quickly get back on your
the hospital, Mom.
You get treatment.
I do not care!
Who would want to Ónsanatoseasca
and go from here?!
I have to go. I'm gonna
ask the doctor ...
... Give me a drug
to keep me here!
So you only intend to use
My boss money, right?
I have to say about it!
I came to ONT, lnesc you.
For everything you did for my mother ...
I g ..., ndit we should
to thank you personally.
Very good ... says so.
What to say?
You already satisfied. More
Got anything else to say?
No, nothing else ...
Just ...
Does not look good c, when you're scared.
Look good c, when you're angry.
IMO mother said that
have a temper.
And them and is afraid of you.
And they? Is there anyone else
who is afraid of me?
Crazy girl ... she say anything stupid.
Why you Deva called
to the ONT, lnire, Mr. Jindal?
We are all times, problems ...
Oi ... and we let you stay with us
and sheep give all honor!
I agree, Mr. Jindal.
Deva could prove a
danger for us on the future.
Deva is the latest
On the world scene.
Not until you begin to
c, Stig important.
E t, and Óntreprinzator nar ...
More ..., s and
very ambitious.
From my experience ...
We should not Óndepartam ...
a man at, t capable.
Œmi sorry I Ont, rziat.
But I am surprised, why did you
Called to the ONT, meeting.
Obstacles on the path of our business
have become more numerous, Deva.
HotarÓ to what to do,
We have g ..., ndit to have
This Ont, meeting.
You must keep this clan.
And you're not a stranger.
Just because we belong
same clan ...
Can not g ..., NDI as,
Mr. Jindal.
G, thinking of is a funny thing;
can change on time.
The speed at which you create the ...
Stunned ... I.
You are cute, Mr. Jindal.
But I must inform you, gentlemen ...
I just ... like Ónvatat
to stay on his feet.
I commence to walk Ónca.
So ... just speed ahead.
You said something about some obstacles ...
What I'm saying is that you should
let some c, stiguri little ...
Create enemies ... hath us.
Only if we are united we are strong.
On exchange erodes enemy ...
Solid ... even the structure ...
P ..., not the total destruction!
We need to ensure that there
no cracks on our unit.
We need to gather all resources
Ómpotriva to fight their common enemy.
This enemy is the law.
We know that the new minister is
very honest man.
He's boundary, t to eliminate
crime in the city.
And the person you chose
This lead to fulfilled the plan ...
Inder Saxena ...'s.
I fumbled around in his past Saxena.
It's not even a person
our liking.
Œnainte to str, nga screw ...
I ... have to eliminate.
No, Mr. Jindal.
Killer NDU it on Saxena
We can not afford ... to challenge
Highly skilled police department.
It's a known fact that no
a police officer ...
... Can not stand too long
burden of truth and honesty.
C When Saxena will Óntelege this
work will transfer.
I think we should give them
Ónca three months.
After three months ...
If things do not happen ...
as planning ...
... You have to kill
Saxena you Ónsuti.
How can I promise that?
Time and death are things
no one can predict.
As you will live to see me
killer NDU him three months ...
Could anyone guarantee that?
Lord!
- How are you?
- I'm okay, son.
I would have been dead if I had
remained on the other hospital.
I got a new life here.
Why are you looking at me?
Œncerc to figure out who you are ...
Where did you east to
We get rid of our problems?
Someone not at, t much
even its people.
- What we do for you?
- What did you do?
Œmi ensure treatment ...
You engaged daughter.
By the way ... how do the work?
It's a bit immature ... forgive her if
says something stupid.
Has a sharp tongue that
grew up without her father.
Do not worry about it ...
take care of yourself.
Do what your doctor says ...
And to stay away from ...
m, NCAR spicy.
- I'll be back to see you.
- Very well, son.
Why should not worry on
about Guddi's marriage?
Can not sit with us
life.
I g, ndesc the condition
I grew up with it.
I was ready at any
to make it happy.
The idea for her to go ...
Be Ónconjurata of ...
unknown people ...
Location will Guddi
not new, Deva.
Groom that I chose for her
knows as well as we do.
Oen Besides, if he
Wear our bad sister ...
We show ... and us!
Who's that?
The remaining family members already
I took "interviews" ...
... And I have found to their liking.
However, if you insist ...
Guddi is the only sister I have!
I can sacrifice everything for
see it z, mbind!
I need a man capable
intelligent and good-hearted for her.
You have these qualities!
That's strange way of
to show your happiness!
I'm excited!
Are ONC, sang!
I was resolved one
biggest problems, Deva?
Dad's and he thanked
of this alliance.
in fact, he waits ...
C ... When we see the bride's sister.
Œmi sorry to say this
Hath such a moment ...
I have a problem ... but, my friend.
What is Inder?
Among the names of four
Gang leaders ...
... In town, on police files ...
One ... is the name of Deva.
- I know.
- Then you probably know as ...
Marriage ... it will enjoy
participation of many policemen.
My position on their face will ...
Please, my friend.
Please do not come to my wedding.
How about, Inder?
How could marry Guddi without
Deva's this? You know that, long t ...
Inder is right.
I would like the wedding
to suffer because of me ...
I will not take part.
Put double necklace
to g, bridal tulle.
Vermilonul apply now.
Stand up, we, doubt.
You have to say something?
Let me ONT and see my
sister on wedding dress ...
... To my happiness.
C, t've been waiting for this moment!
- Brother ...
- Watch out!
You pl, nge only to
Óncasa a beating from me!
Our sister is not nice, Akash?
It's not a doll?
What's wrong with you online?
Oen that Hal brought us life, Deva?
After childhood I had,
full of misery ...
C ... after those days, when we
fight and then we Ómpacam ...
Ómprejurarile us ...
now separated.
We are separated.
Guddi ... No pl, blood.
You will stay away from us, right?
You have to live on this city!
Oen Besides, I was never Óngadui
Your husband will be transferred here.
I have many links on the city.
Anyway ... let me know.
What wedding gift do you want?
I've already made a
but priceless.
Both the poor girls have tea
married today because of you ...
Their parents will bless me, nta.
What more beautiful gift I could ask for?
Take the Guddi home Akash.
Probably expect.
Now, son ... Take this money and
ASU me a 'bhel-pure ".
We are not allowed to bring
m, NCAR outside, lady.
But that will ram us only hath us!
Well ... you can keep the rest.
Not insist, madam.
Œmi may lose his job!
Gorgeous! Œti you lose your job
IMO if you buy a snack!
What kind of hospital is this?
Dying to have a snack ...
and no one cares!
Very well then ... leave.
Go save your job.
Aminabee, working at the dairy
slums and live on ...
Has a problem ... on her house.
Lady!
Deva! You have arrived, my son?
Yes ... what is it?
Look what people are saying
the slums!
Say I poisoned the kids!
I would do that?
We brought milk from dairy
to feed my children.
How could turn on poison?
- Where's the milk?
- There.
Is it Laptaria that the left hand switch
from Malad Railway.
From there we took milk /
Laptaria of it, nga passage
railway?
There's only one dairy ...
And that dairy belong, NDU's
Jindal's was imprisonment!
This is not milk ...
It's a narcotic.
Go ahead and call them.
They definitely come ...
just to carry your bier!
Move!
Drop your weapons!
Send away women
and children, Mani!
Hurry up, guys! Get out of here!
Hurry up, ma'am ...
Hurry up, guys! Take care
where you step!
I hope you're on all
mind, Deva!
You're a devil ...
Poison ... that would sell as
m, NCAR to c, Stig money!
Do not make the mistake of challenging myself, Deva!
Œti you put on life-threatening!
People are usually
cremated after death.
But if he Ont, MPLA
some children ...
You will be the first ...
incinerated alive!
Well, sir ... would not you
Óntorci home early today?
Watch the clock ... View
c, y much of NTO, rziat!
Œmi realize that, Shobha, but ...
You can not get away
what to do, right?
I had to keep store
Imprisonment for five days.
And Ónca have a lot to do.
But I promise to fix everything
On that, a few days!
Well ... Come home c, when you have time.
But Deepu and I have decided, t
we will have lunch with you today.
Now listen, Shobha ...
- There you go!
- My wife is sick, sir ...
And I have to rush ...
to get to the hospital.
But the work commence at 7 p.m. And they
need these materials on tonight.
Well, give me the keys to the van.
We do shipment on the way home.
There seems to be no one around.
But there's someone up there.
But we must do something ...
and Deva.
- But the minister is ...
- Quiet! We know everything!
I've already lost money.
Krishnakant simply not
State on the minister to bring him on his knees
And it's not our interest on him
May let live.
Œmi like this feature yours, Khan.
Attack the problem directly and
bluntly.
Minister does not want to quit.
So be isolated from his life.
We will plan the death of Minister ...
Deva ... but will be at the
to be blame.
Pick it up, Deva!
- Akash here!
- Akash! How are you?
I've been on this place go
some materials ...
I heard ... and speaking
assassination of Minister ...
Oi ... that will be put on C, rca's Deva!
What?!
There was some Jindal, who said ...
They will blame ... Deva's on!
Where are you calling, Akash?
Are hath a phone booth!
Ram and there, Akash. Coming.
Come quickly, Inder! I'm afraid!
Fri, Akash!
Very good ...
I'm waiting here!
Let me make a phone call, sir.
Yes ... let me talk to Rohit.
I will bring Ónghetata for
you usually on?
Give your mother on the phone.
I asked to wait there, no?
I waited there, Inder!
If you would have waited
Furthermore, I would have been killed!
Who? Who would you kill?
Those guys ... who spoke
Deva's murder!
Do something, or IMO Inder ...
will kill brother!
- You know that building?
- But you're by yourself, Inder!
Do not worry ... that, when I'm with you.
I'm a cop ... Come!
- Moving up?
- Yes.
This is ... this
belong, Inder!
Watch.
- Out there?
- Yes.
There's nobody here, Akash?
Ónselat not you, huh?
Not at all! This is where
had NTO meeting.
But Jindal said he will kill ol
Minister and will blame Deva!
Œnca're here, Akash.
This is the man, Inder!
This is Jindal!
If we had not found this
pen cap ...
I ... never knew who
of eavesdropping.
Catch this man!
That is exactly how
was me, not my brother.
M, not that your brother Deva
and plucked it from the root!
What do you mean, Inder?
I'm glad you're at, t
Smart Inder Saxena.
Œti we miss family
every happiness!
And do Ónceputul
throw, NDU your body ...
On his arms ... Deva!
Look, Deva ...
With salary this month ... I
I buy another Óncaltaminte!
Do not be dull, t!
Gandhi, preacher ...
You know what a man was?
I realize at, tea things
with this pen?
In this case, keep it
you and write with him.
Listen, Deva ...
No, son ... no pl, nge!
Take care of yourself, son.
Affliction may fall
on anyone, son ...
Do not spare anyone.
But should a Ónfrunti, son ...
Do not lose courage.
God will avenge
for what was Ont, mplat.
It was ur job, your would have them throw
Your brother's corpse on your lap.
But although I'm blind ... I see
As will be destroyed.
You're the one that will c, Stig, son.
Bless, Ntare at, tor
grateful people ...
Have a look ...
But what came Akash here?
That Óncerc to tell.
Why was he here in an hour at, t of t, rzie?
What do you mean?
Your time does not show
well, Lal
So why I brought
this soul Ónvatat here.
This is great Pandit
Badrinath Shastri.
It is a famous master
On astrology!
Has a PhD. About
influence the movement of Saturn!
Politicians and actors ...
Wearing amulets ... he offered.
Moreover, the film about Saturn
Script was written ...
All of this gentleman!
Now Leeladhar ...
Stop this madness!
Okay! Take my head if you want!
- But please wear it!
- What is it?
That? Here ...
An owl's claw.
- Claw an owl?
- Yes. And this gentleman ...
Spells ... he used to one
transform hath a defensive weapon!
This will occur trouble, sir!
- Wear it around on g, ment ...
- Get out of here!
Well ... did you carry on around
g ment if you want!
But should it keep on pocket ...
That's right ... just keep it
there. That's all!
There's no reason Óngrijorare now!
I took care of everything.
I Óngropat and a horseshoe of
horse on the doorstep.
We took precautions p, not
and on around the office.
The gods protect us now!
The priest recited spells 21,000!
Your enemies will not Óndrazni
not even close to you!
You know why I'm here.
Tell me ... who killed my brother?
Look, I do not know anything on Deva ...
Contact your brother's death.
I will torture you ...
p, IMO will not tell the truth!
Talk!
What's up, Deva?
Let me! My brother
was killed on his building!
Was building it!
Stap, Nestle yourself! What the hell are you doing?
Óntelegi not ... my brother was
killed on his building!
Lal Singh did not even
was on city time!
Akash's death not suicide
Inder! He was murdered!
Why clean stairs building
On that night?
What happened there?
If this is true on what you say,
I will not spare Akash's killer.
I pl, ns I
's death?
Akash not to sign anything for me?
Look, Deva ... methods
you use ...
is completely wrong!
Do not you realize that Lal Singh
you could even give on judgment?
As you can accuse
attempted murder?
I'm the one who has received a blow
the death of my brother.
For the law, the death of Akash
it's just another case ...
Which will receive a total ...
then the case will be imprisonment.
C When I find out who is responsible ...
I have to adjust accounts ...
for my brother's death ...
... On my way.
Wait.
I arrested this man ...
Who killed ... and one of
Our officers, Inspector Kulkarni.
I'm sure this man knows
More about Akash's death.
I had an injection which
On ten minutes ...
OL will say ... the whole truth.
We will tell you what to do ...
and for whom.
Get it here.
Deva ... not g, NDI as
police do nothing.
I put my life on game
I catch the killers of Akash.
Pig was killed!
No suicide ... were sacrificed
for STAP,'s null.
Do not see why the law is
On powerless against crime?
Is not that your department
have dedicated people like John.
You made several p, not now.
Have you fought p, and not death
then c, when they approached me.
- I want you all ...
- What should I do?
I want hotel and other interests,
manage it legally on ...
To be taken ... all of you.
To take over the business?
What Ónseamna this?
Óndepartezi you do not want us, right?
I do not want to riskier
lives for my sake.
Insult us say that when Deva.
Hotel and giving us
other business ...
Óncerci ... put a price on
our contribution, is not it?
- I mean, Rashid ...
- Rashid is right!
I swore to stand by each other and
the better, but worse, right?
How can you keep your worries
just for you?
You proved it today, Deva!
I was never "to" you ...
I just worked "for" you!
My head! My teachings, rte again!
I've had enough ...
Praise the Goddess!
Hey! Wait here!
You can not Ónauntru!
Do not get smart, right?
Why can not I go?
- What's this?
- Can not you see? It's a parrot!
- This has now allowed Ónauntru!
- But the lady sent for him!
Melt!
Is he here? My little parrot!
It's here on end, rsit!
My dear parrot!
What is your problem?
What harm could make
this parrot;?
- Œmi you lose your job, Ms ~
- But why worry OTI?
Monetary blame!
I got it!
Go Ónauntru, pee-pee ...
I have a new "home" for you!
And I Ónchiriat house
which you left it!
Bravo! ... but you gave it cheaper, right?
Not at all! You will receive on a regular basis
substantial rent
Make sure you give me all your money.
I pay taxes.
You sent for me, lady?
Here's a bill ...
... And bring me some rice!
I can get you something!
Not for me!
E parrot!
Tell the doctor that
I asked for this!
I fooled! Let m, ncam Ómpreuna!
Here you are! How OTI like
new home?
Look ... there's the TV!
And this machine ...
produce cool!
Perhaps you are tired of
old things, right?
So that, when open the windows
at our house ...
Swarms of t ..., Ntare Naval Ónauntru!
But you will not find even
one t, Ntare here!
Thanks to my daughter, Jaya,
have much luck.
He found a man who
is very generous!
Ómpreuna will rule the world with him!
Get to marry soon, God ...
Me to play with their children.
Welcome, Inder ... Log.
Let merchandise there.
These bags are 15 million
rupees cash ...
On gold bullion ... and € 20
millions were brought across the border.
Sit down.
I captured this merchandise hath a
Apartment in Dahisar, sir.
You made arrests?
The apartment is passed by name
a certain Hasmujk Patel, sir.
But there stood two men ...
Tenants ... for two months.
I told the owner and
other tenants ...
A business ... they dress.
But on the last two days ...
Their house was imprisonment ... and those
people disappeared.
He obviously knew the
Our operation.
These people may have
ties Deva or Jindal.
He can not, sir ...
secure connections there.
Deva has surely
to do with them.
C When you arrest ol Deva sir ...
I wish to be present.
Œntruc, t are convinced ...
Óndrazni ... no one will give him
Deva's way if you are present.
Continue your work, Inder.
I will find him, you nga
Oric, when you need it.
The Akash left him, nga us ...
I stay ... it's hard to on the house.
The mutual consolation.
But it's hard to answer the
Deepu's Óntrebarile.
Father and consoles all ...
I saw ... but pl, ng, when on his room.
Everyone loved him ...
I never hurt anyone.
I found this pen
l nga Akash's body.
He who has the cap ...
Akash's's killer.
I certainly found him hath day.
We have to find him, Guddi.
Why are all the lights off?
How you Óntorci at, t to t, rziu?
What's this? Drink alcohol?
How you Óntorci at, t
t, later, I Óntrebat!
I've been Ont, lnesc
my brother.
There I said it's not good
you NTO, lnesti with Deva?
- I warned you, did not you?
- Yes, but ...
This is the first time that ... When I
Ont, lnit, after the death of Akash ...
What am I to you now?
- What am I to you now?
- You are my husband.
In this case, you do what Oti says!
You do just what I say Oti!
Deva is a killer ... and I
I'm a police officer.
Not good for my wife
be related to a criminal.
Œntelegi this?
Please forgive me.
It will not Ont, MPLA.
Have to get used.
Have to get used to forget Deva.
For that, your years working with Deva?
- I'm four years.
- Œnteleg.
Good boy, I must admit ...
Has a large heart.
Probably has a business
important, right?
Yes ... business is good.
C, Stig than a month hath not,
one lakh or two?
2 lakhs? Playing with no less than
10 or 12 boxes on each month.
- Boxes?
- A box is ten million!
You mean ... 100 or 120
million on each month?
- Want a snack?
- No, lady!
- I will ask you to bring me yet!
- But I do not want, lady!
- How's my daughter?
- E skill.
- How does Deva about it?
- I love it.
An astrologer told him that he would
marry a rich man!
G, ndeste what you would do great couple!
A couple like that of the gods ...
Jaya Deva, you say?
Where's Deva now?
What is it?
It's something I have to tell you.
I gathered all the courage today ...
I tell you ... I love you.
Deva ... listen, Deva!
I liked that, when we
Ont, lnit first time ...
With c, t know you better ...
With at ..., t IMO stap, Nestle
more heart.
You know that life go, Jaya.
Do you know Ónseamna to dream about
life with me?
Police ... my enemies ... all me
can kill. Anything is possible!
I know that, Deva!
But I want to spend my life
with you at, t c, t will be.
- That's impossible.
- It is possible!
Anything is possible if you desire!
Once ... for once let love
lead your life, Deva.
I'm sure he will give a
new sense of your life.
Œnceteaza crap. Know
what is my life?
Do you know what my goals?
I would like to get involved
and lose my entire boundary, bad!
Then do not get involved!
Life and your goals are not
December, t hatred and violence!
All you did was to light
hatred torch on your heart!
Not able to love on
one ... absolutely anyone!
This money is not nothing Ónseamna
Now, Mr. Deva.
That Óntruc, t her illness
hath reached a stage ...
On all efforts ...
Doctors are useless.
What Ónseamna this?
It's hard to say c, t will live.
What's at, t serious?
He had this disease for some time.
Just as was
What has Ont, mplat, Deva?
Why are you angry?
It's something you want to tell me?
What did the doctor say?
I am dying?
But I knew it all the time.
True, Deva.
Although I knew the truth ...
I never left ...
m, hnirea overwhelm me.
Do you know why?
Jaya because I love very much.
He suffered greatly
after my husband died.
You begin to z, mbeasca of
again only after a long time.
Las When the fear of death
I see the way you ...
I could be missing ...
of all joys.
It's true that I was
fear of death, Deva.
But my fears were gone
after I Ont, lnit you.
Now I can go on alone.
Œmi you do another favor?
To see his daughter Wear When
double necklace ...
... Is what every mother dreams of.
You Ómplinesti me this dream?
- This is Inder, sir.
- Continue, Inder.
If you remember,
sir, I said ...
Ties with mafia ... c tive
very influential ministers.
- I'll be there. What place is this?
- Delta Tower. At 11 a.m.
Yes, Inder?
I got some crucial information
Contact Akash on his killers.
I come to Delta Tower ... at 11.15.
I'll be there.
Wait for me here.
Welcome, Mr. Prime Minister!
Jindal? You?
Inder was just middle
which I brought here.
In fact, I wanted to congratulate you ...
Honor ... for you.
- What do you mean?
- Detest ...
Gatherings and crowds ... not?
So I g ndit as
This place would be ideal ...
... For your death.
Come on, Bhola!
Go Deva ...
I'm gonna stop me!
Inder! Save it to Deva ...
Save it!
Come! Come!
Faster!
Come! Hurry up!
Drive the slums, Mani!
Send for a doctor, Mani ...
Hurry!
- What is it, Deva?
- I can not figure out!
Ónteleg you do not play with me!
- I want to talk Saxena!
- He's not here now.
- What's this?
- Inder called me, Haya.
And Jindal him to Ómpuscat the minister!
If I have left there,
would be killed.
Lu, when on account Ómprejurarile
I ran away on ...
Police will think ...
I'm Ómpuscat!
I can not Ónteleg ...
Inder ... why not get there?
There's a shadow on Óndoiala terms
they provide security department.
So that, when we can not
protect a person ...
What it definitely ...
We guarantee citizens?
Why can not Ónteleg is ...
Despite this ... as on a
able officer like you ...
How did ... Deva and his bandits
take him there the minister?
Unbelievable! I am very disappointed
the mistakes they've made!
C, when the minister has called you there ...
Why do not you ... Take
necessary precautions?
Why did you take with you
so few officers>
Minister haste me
talking on the phone ...
I determined to ...
run there immediately.
But that, when we got there,
I found Deva ...
... Go, NDU it back on the minister!
It was hard for us to ochim it ...
So ... I have hit
the minister on the shooting!
Know the relationship between you and Deva.
Oen Despite this, we
Óncrederea all on you.
I will endeavor to
Óncrederea reward, sir.
Oen For me, Deva
just a killer, sir.
OEL want to Deva ... dead or alive.
I put on alert all
14 areas, sir.
Our people search through all
town to find it.
I put 250 officers
On this operation ...
And every out of town ...
was imprisonment.
'll Catch on clean steel, when the Deva.
A special announcement.
The Prime Minister was Ómpuscat On
This morning at 11 a.m.
A criminal ... named Deva.
Minister guards fought back ...
But despite all efforts ... on ...
Deva escaped Ómpreuna ...
Prime Minister.
Minister for assault and kidnapping ...
Why these actions ... ...
Ónca be explained ...
by the police.
I did not say they do not know
nothing about Deva?
Why do not you think?
I really do not know where Deva!
Everyone remember to commence
then c, when coming here.
But gradually the truth
comes out.
What? What do you mean?
It's not fair to harass me
as you do!
You can not harass a citizen
guilty on like this!
I'm a lawyer ...
I know the law!
Your son, murderer,
running from the law ...
And you have the nerve to ...
I Ónveti law?
You should not have to do that,
Officer.
My tears Ónseamna
much for my son ...
If you find it, you doborÓ
c,'re a man like you ...
For every tear ...
I paid it!
Are you happy?
I told you he does not know anything.
But you have to do that.
Forgive him, Father ... Please forgive him!
I am an honest man, Inder ...
I did not tell a lie
life!
Nobody in my house
Deva knows where!
- I know that, Dad ...
- They do not know anything!
You look on TV.
What show?
Anyone who provides information about
you will be rewarded.
- Do you reward?
- No.
Ónca police state was not on him
find the Deva.
I pulled the bullets from
his body, lady.
But his condition
deteriorates rapidly.
I gotta go to the hospital ...
If not, you can die!
I told you already that
we can not go to a hospital.
Very well!
Do what you want!
But I can not stay here!
I want to go now!
Only Óncearca to remember
who you're dealing with!
I explain just once ...
I want him to live ...
... Not to save my skin,
because he knows the truth.
But he's a good man!
Got anything else to say?
What I c, Stig? What I c, Stig
in this farce?
Lal Oen, we lost a
friend who was like a brother to me.
And you still have not been able to on
Deva do anything on now!
All this ... just for you
did you get there on time!
And that, when you arrived, officers
those t, mpiti Ónsoteau you.
Because of your
Deva escaped!
If you had killed Deva
there, on the spot ...
Received much praise ... you.
You have occurred on the first
page of newspapers ...
Assassin to kill ...!
I'm the one who fired on the minister.
If he survives attack
and confess ...
If you have the slightest problem,
You can be sure, Inder Saxena ...
Mr. Jindal! You have not complied
Óntelegere your side!
You must kill
Minister. But you missed!
Do not yell at me, Inder Saxena!
You're not important enough
to raise your voice at me!
You can yell at subordinates
On your desk!
It has nothing to do
with my position.
All I'm saying is that,
whatever the ONT, mplat ...
Why Inder spoke with Jindal?
Your clothes, ma'am.
- What ...
- Take the money.
But I rest.
- You can pay me m holds.
- I'll get it right now.
- It's on my pay right ... I, hold.
- I get it hath a moment, madam.
What's this?
Inder gets sloppy.
"I found this pen
l nga Akash's body. "
"Who has the cap ..."
"Is Akash's killer:.
What Ónseamna as Inder ...
Brother! Here's Guddi!
Yes, Guddi? What is it?
Listen, do you?
Yes, you heard right. Continue ...
- You know, brother!
- What should you know?
I need to know ...
Yeah, bro ... Listen, do you?
Yes! Continue!
I need to know who
Akash killed him!
Who was?
Brother ...
Gorgeous!
For the first time, see c, t
OSI sister loves his brother more ...
I saw her today for the first time!
What were you about to say?
Me I killed Akash?
You were about to tell
my name is not it?
Yes ... I killed myself Akash.
But do not be surprised.
Œti remember, right ...
Deva ... what your brother did to
arm pulled my brother Vilas?
You just saw arm ripped ...
On while I ... I saw
p suffering, not death!
What shocking betrayal!
Our relationship, love and dance,
Our marriage ... it was just that?
You did something despicable, Inder!
You killed my brother!
God will not
forgive me for that!
God can not hear
from such a distance ...
Well ... not stand hearing.
You will have to go on
heaven to talk to him.
My wife ... yet
I figure on exposed!
Why are all these
cops here?
What's up, Deva?
Wait here ... I'll go check.
Take the car out!
"In God ... stay Truth"
"He talks about you
the neighborhood. "
"The way you've put on the run
those guys ... was superb. "
"Everyone knows now that
My brother is a hero. "
"More ONT and let me me
sister concern ... "
"... On the wedding dress."
"Listen, do you?"
"We need to know who
Akash killed him. "
I came to the remains
pam, ntesti of my daughter.
But her brother has already taken.
- Who? Deva?
- Yes ... that's his name.
Now remember on the
whose remains you brought.
Why was enhanced
security, Shinde?
- Order the head, sir.
- Why?
It's about me
lightning strike?
Go!
Œmbunatatirea security, between really!
- Hi, Mr. Jindal!
- Yes, Inder?
I Ónteles, on end, rsit.
We Óntrebam the
Guddi had found ...
... That I could have
Exposed on Akash's killer?
What was it?
She had found cover
Akash's pen ...
Same ... and gave
Deva's phone!
Poor soul! Brother
they died without Óndoiala ...
And sister ... she was murdered!
Even after death, she ...
Gave us last ... evidence
On this crime.
Akash's deaths and Guddi
will ram us a mystery!
To tell you the truth, Mr. Jindal ...
Even c ... When I saw
My brother's corpse, Vilas ...
On fire ... was a heart
which was extinguished.
What repulsive show that, when
are exposed, Inder!
Deva! Do not touch me, Deva!
For the sake of your father!
For your mother!
I'm your sister's husband!
Here's my book!
It's a ten leaf!
Give me peace on!
Ónca pig is on life!
I'll kill him!
You must kill the bastard!
Let me! I'm going to make pieces!
He used to talk too much!
But Deva took him on Home
beat him like a c holds!
C, when they could not protect him
Ónsusi, how will we defend ourselves?
He used to boast as if
On police had Óntreaga pocket.
But no matter ... I hope Jindal
drew a lesson from this.
Well ... you got to Jindal?
Yes, sir ...
- Give me the boss on the phone.
- Not at home, sir.
It's not home? Where is it?
- He went to the police station.
- For what?
I do not know. But he went
after he called Mr Inder.
That's the limit!
Must there,
console, NDU it on Inder!
This man has lost his mind!
Give me drink.
Why tremble, Khan?
Œti like to play with death, right?
Not me, Deva!
You killed c tive people
city ​​street.
How can you die hath
these four walls?
Run, if you're afraid ...
Run if you can save
from death!
Run! Run, Khan!
Run!
Move!
Get out of my way!
Help! Out of ...
Help!
Move!
Help! Move!
Save me! Belong to religion
Your ... Are Bashar Khan!
That man will kill me!
I will kill you!
Save me, please!
Bashar Khan?
Bashar Khan are not the same ...
Blind woman ... who put that
Me and toddlers ...
To Ómpacheteze milk ...
poisoned for you?
You are responsible for the death
of many innocent!
After you have destroyed joys
and peace to these people ...
Now pretend ...
're one of them?
Oei pray for your life?
No! Do not make the mistake of her
give shelter this bastard!
This man is a murderer ...
And a criminal ... not
religion ... no faith!
These demons have deleted
pam on the face of the earth!
God Œnsusi decided t it!
This is also your court, Deva!
Go and do right ...
Just do right, Deva!
Someone sent a corpse
for you, sir.
It's a call for you, Mr. Jindal.
You hid on
behind police Jindal?
Inder probably has c, initial and
Ónsusi him on guard around you, right?
But that's a good thing.
In it, nga your death ...
Police Department will ...
get rid of their garbage.
That looks good
body, Jindal.
It's the same Khan ...
That kills people ...
to your order.
This is the fate that
you will have, doubt.
Look, lady ... even
Óncercati to Óntelegeti!
There is no Ómbunatatire
On his condition!
From injuries, poisons
to rasp, ndeste everywhere.
Need to clean wounds.
I have to go to the hospital to
taking medicines and some tools.
Let me go ...
Œncercati to Óntelegeti will tell!
Very well. But people
Ónsoti my will.
Come Ónauntru ... wait here.
I want all of them
and drugs ...
Ómpachetate on ... two minutes.
- Right, Doc.
- I.
- Here is Dr. Rane ...
Apollo Hospital ... from.
I know where I hid
Deva the minister.
It's near the old fort
L-nga Malvani village.
Minister's critical condition.
Victim to a hospital immediately.
Of course, it can be saved.
And he wants to Deva
And save lives!
I have bad news and
good news, Jindal.
That you want to hear more ONT and?
Good ones.
I found Deva's hideout.
But the minister's Ónca on life ...
Deva ... and wants to save him.
Where's Deva? Tell me ...
Where's Deva?
It is important to him Ont, lnesc!
Where is it?!
Listen, people of Devpura ...
Ónconjurat police ...
Óntreaga colony!
If any of you Óncerca
to sheep ram, not loyal to Deva ...
Or if any will Óncerca ...
During the operation on a ...
Will be delivered on ... hell!
Las bastard!
Oen hide the hole, rat?
You have to go out now ...
... Or I'll dig your grave, word
even there?
Wine fucking pig!
Œndrazniti to arrest Deva?
Inspect every home! Kill it
the Minister as soon as you find.
Who's that?
Who Óndrazneste to touch Deva?
None of you can
to catch the Deva!
Deva! Where are you?
Deva must escape!
Hurry up! Come!
Hurry, Mani! Move!
Start the car ... Hurry!
Close the door.
Move! Repde!
Do not let it get away!
Get out, Deva!
Get out and Ónfrunta me!
Here I am! And you
where are you hiding?
Oen what hole are you?
Come out.
Kill him! Kill him!
Kill him!
To kill a beast ...
Must be a beast ... Deva.
My son!
Deva is innocent ...
Jindal was he who pulled on me.
It was Saxena who called me
and I called the Delta Tower ...
... Alone.
But I found Saxena
c, when I got there.
Jindal was there on exchange.
This court ol Deva condemn the ...
Subtitle : By juleyano
http://juleyano.movies.