India, an ancient land...
whose history is woven
with the most amazing stories.
Let me tell you one such story...
about a group of great sages...
who meditated deeply in the Himalayas...
for which they received a Boon.
A divine Light (Brahm-Shakti)!
As that Light met the mountain...
Weapons of Power (Astras) were born.
Bearing the power of fire-
the Fire Stone (Agnyastra)!
The Water Stone (Jalāstra)!
And the Air Stone (Pawanāstra)!
Astras that contained the powers of
different animals and plants.
The sages had achieved what they desired.
But then, a cry arose from the Universe.
You see...
within the Light...
another Astra (weapon) was being born.
An Astra like Lord Shiva's Third Eye.
It could Create...
but also, Destroy.
The sages realised that this Great Astra
would have to be controlled.
Eventually, with great struggle and sacrifice...
the sages calmed the Light.
Then, at the peak of the mountain appeared...
the most powerful of all...
the Lord of all the Astras...
BRAHMĀSTRA!
The sages knelt before the Brahmāstra...
and they called themselves...
The Brahmānsh!
Passing the Astras down generation to generation,
the Brahmānsh existed secretly in society...
protecting the Astras, and using
their Energies for the greater good.
Time moved forward...
each Age came and went by...
the world kept changing...
and with that change,
the world forgot about the Astras.
Now, let us jump ahead to modern India...
and meet a young man,
who doesn't know yet...
that the Fire which sleeps within him...
is going to Light up this World of Astras.
Today, on the Festival of Dussehra (Good vs Evil)...
a new Battle for the Brahmāstra is beginning...
and this young hero's destiny
is going to lead him into it!
His name is...
Shiva.
I'll take that.
Well done, young cheetah...
you surprised me.
I'm Mohan.
And you?
Shut up and give me the Piece, calmly.
What fun's a hunt...
without a little chaos?
Now don't go trying to be a Hero, Scientist!
Another hunter...
and yet again, I didn't see you coming.
You know...
I really must be getting old.
No, wait.
Here you go, baby...
enjoy!
Not bad, huh?
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch!
Aye you, hunter Number Two!
You're no cheetah...
you're a bloody elephant!
Don't break everything, you brute!
Actually, you're no elephant...
elephants are wonderful.
You're a Hippo!
ZOR (Force) of a Hippo is in you.
Aye... ZOR (Force)!
That's a great name for you.
- Write it down or you'll forget it,
you stupid Hippo.
Come on, man!
Why so angry?
I can't find the Piece.
But he threw it right here.
Yeah, but it has disappeared!
Come let's give you a name, too!
You are in too much of a hurry,
hunting fast-fast-fast-fast!
Your name should be...
- RAFTAAR (Speed)!
- Where is the Piece, Scientist?
Tell us and we will spare your life!
Raftaar... Zor!
Hippo... Cheetah!
A solid team of hunters, you two!
But...
the animal you have come here to hunt...
is the jungle's...
most clever beast.
What's happening to him?
- He's got some new power!
- Can you guess which one?
THE MONKEY!
That Anklet!
Bye, friends!
- Come on, Raftaar... your turn!
- Come on!
Not bad, cheets!
Okay, okay... wait, wait!
You guys know right,
that you can't possibly catch me?!
Enough of this game.
Now, I must fulfil my duty...
to the Brahmānsh!
So, bye!
Not even your Anklet
can carry you that high...
Monkey!
Zor, you still don't get it...
This is not an Anklet...
This is the...
STOP HIM!
Vānarāstra! (Super Monkey Weapon)
Damn, we lost him!
Fire...?
You can outrun Raftaar's speed...
overpower Zor's strength...
but you cannot escape
the obsession of JUNOON (Passion)!
Hello, Mr. Scientist.
Hunter...
you're the real Hunter.
Who are you?
But I already told you...
Junoon (Passion).
And now...
our Piece!
What are you going to do, Junoon?
Do you even realise the power in this Astra?
I understand this great Astra far
more deeply than you, Mr. Scientist.
It is my sole purpose.
You bring Darkness with you Junoon.
But, the Light is coming...
and in every Battle of the Brahmāstra...
the winner will always be...
the Light!
Hey, buddy?
- Hail Goddess Durga!
- Shiva...
- Hail Lord Ram!
Aye, Shiva!
- Aye, what happened?!
- What a show we put up today!
We could play any world-class club.
- Swallow these big dreams
with these cheap snacks.
- What a cool AV you made, man.
- Like an inferno!
- Today was truly fun, man.
Mad party!
Ya but that Ravana Statue blast was freaky!
Maybe there was too much gunpowder in it?
This was supposed to
be a Dussehra celebration...
but it was more like Diwali.
(Festival of Lights and Fireworks)
Fire is a messed up thing.
Ohohoho... Mr. Shiva.
Good Morning, Mr. Shiva!
How are you?
Buddy!
How come you fainted like that, man?
I just overdid that Dance number!
From now on, I'll just make people dance...
and control my dance moves.
Bro...
You're okay, right?
Yeah, I'm fine buddy. Let's go!
It's freakin' late guys!
- And we have that event tomorrow.
- Correct. Come on!
Sup bro?
Another penny for your thoughts?
Dude, there was this girl and...
she stole my heart!
Get lost!
She stole my heart
Breaking news!
Our friend sees a girl and faints.
But, but... what a girl?!
Whoever she was... she's gone!
You're never gonna find her again!
I'll find her.
- Eh Shiva! Come on, let's go!
- I'll find her!
Time's up! Pack up, gangsters!
Come on, come on!
- Aye, Shiva.
- What are you doing, man?
Shiva, what are you doing, man? Let's go!
- Aye, Shiva!
- Tiger, come on!
- Where's he going?
Aye, Shiva!
Aye, Shiva! Wait!
Where are you going, man?
- Aye, lift! Wait!
Excuse me! Can we get a lift please?
This place is packed!
Excuse me, Madam!
Hi!
Who are you?
WHAT are you?
Say it.
Say what?
Whatever’s on your mind.
I really like you.
Click!
Click?
Click means...
I'll always remember this moment.
What will you remember?
That I met a monkey...
and then he fell off the elevator!
Sorry.
Can this monkey have your phone number?
- Okay then!
And you, my Juliet from London.
- You please relax!
- Shaina didi.
Dude, you never who's a stalker!
We're taking you to
Putlu's Diwali party, Isha Di.
Isha...
So, Mr. Monkey...
will you come with us?
For Putlu's party?
Isha, I really want to come with you...
but I have to be somewhere else.
Like now... before midnight!
Why?
Do you transform into a beast at midnight?
Sorry for the disturbing.
But off we must be going!
Bro... time's up!
Sorry, Isha.
I made a promise to someone else...
to be at a Party!
I have to go.
Okay...
go then!
Hey... you didn't give
me your number, Isha!
And you didn't invite me to your party.
- Meaning?
- What are you doing, man!
- Yeah, yeah... Relax!
Will you come out?
Just for a minute?
Isha?
- Okay. Shaina didi come.
- What the hell?
What the hell is going on?
Have you gone mad, Isha?
The elevator is gone!
We'll have to walk down now!
Shut up, Sunny!
- Guys?
- Hail Goddess Durga!
Guys, what the hell is going on over there?
Shaina didi, wait!
Isha...
what you said earlier, what did you mean?
I'm just saying...
I invited you with my cousins to our party.
Hmm...
But you didn't invite me to your party.
And that's fine.
Now go!
- Come on, Shiva!
Shiva.
Aye, boy! What are you doing?
I'm jumping off this building
to win your love, baby!
Aye!
- Oh my god dude!
- That was awesome!
I didn't ask you to come
with me for a reason.
What?
Say it!
You're wealthy.
You're obviously wealthy, right?
And where I'm going, where I'm from...
that's anything but wealthy.
You wouldn't be comfortable there, Miss.
So?
Are you ashamed of where you come from?
You didn't ask me to come along because...
actually you won't be comfortable.
It makes no difference to me.
Sure I'm rich... but I'm not shallow.
- Shaina didi.
- Mad skills bro, mad skills.
Take that! Gucci-Prada!
- Shaina didi-
- So then prove it!
And come for my party.
- We're not coming anywhere, okay!
I know you want to come.
No we don't want to go with you,
and neither does she!
Isha, tell him!
I don't know...
it could be fun.
Thousand percent! Let's go!
- Don't go anywhere, Didi!
- Bloody English medium...
I'm taking you to this season's
best Diwali party!
Let my brother go!
Can you jump?
There is no need,
we have a car you know!
Isha! Yo!
- Isha, listen to me!
Isha...
can you trust me?
- Isha, this is a really bad idea!
- Isha, stop!
Isha! Oh my god!
- NO!
- Oh! She did it!
- Too good!
Come on, jump!
- Jump!
- Jump, jump!
You okay?
I survived?
Now?
Now we have to run, let's go.
Okay...
let's go!
- Oh, we aren't there yet?
- Let's go!
Now we have to run.
I know...
Then stop staring at me.
- Baby, get on that snake ladder!
Aye, red shirt!
- I have a name, madam! Tiger!
- Arrey, it's dangerous ya!
- C'mon Sunny, carefully but come.
- It's going to be midnight soon guys!
So, what happens at midnight?
Birthday!
Whose?
Girlfriend.
Oh!
Then we definitely can't be late.
- Come on, you posh people, hurry up!
I'm scared, Didi!
Sunny, don't kill my vibe!
There!
- Isha...
- Yes?
So, I don't actually have a girlfriend.
Okay!
And you?
I don't have a girlfriend, either!
- You're late, Shiva dada!
- Shut up, shorty. It's not 12 yet!
Someone's won a big hand this Diwali.
Hi babes.
Hi handsome.
Move move, hero!
- 10...
- 9...
- 8...
- 7...
6...
5...
- 4...
- 3...
- 2...
- 1!
You were born in the zoo...
with lions and tigers...
and monkeys like you...
Happy Birthday to you!
Isha...
I'm at a Diwali party for kids...
who would've thought.
Why are there so many random kids here?
You idiot, this is an orphanage.
Come, babes.
Huh?
I thought you wouldn't be able
to leave your DJ show.
To see this smile, I'd leave any show!
- You're the best, Dada.
- And you're not so bad yourself!
Aye Shiva, let's dance!
Yes! Let's dance, Shiva dada!
Dance dance dance!
Show us that step of yours!
Are you serious?
- Kids, custard?
- Leave it man!
- Want some custard?
- No man, I'm lactose intolerant.
- What's that?
- I can't digest milk.
What did your mother feed you then, juice?
Aye! He never drank his mother's milk!
Aye, half-pint!
Who do you think you are?
I'll give you one tight one?
- Wait, I'm climbing up!
Leave some custard for the kids too!
Kids! Time to burst crackers, come on!!
- Shiva, coming?
- No!
He's not coming anywhere...
he's got a firecracker of his own tonight!
Gannu, you little swine!
Be careful out there.
Say it.
Whatever's on your mind, just say it.
Who are you?
Tell me, Mr. India...
these kids?
They're MY kids.
You take care of them?
And they take care of me.
I never want them to feel
they don't have family.
And you?
And I...
I'm also one of them.
I was born here.
So, Shiva...
you know nothing about
your mother or father?
My father is a riddle.
He was the real Mr. India (Vanishing Hero)!
He'd disappeared before I was born.
Actually, this joke always kind of stings.
In our society, a man's identity
comes from his father.
No father. No family name!
That's why I'm just...
SHIVA!
Nothing before. Nothing after.
I'm thinking that whoever I marry,
I'll just take her family name.
By the way, what's your last name?
So this is my cave.
And what about your mother, Shiva?
My mother?
In my mind...
she's a Goddess.
Like all mothers are!
What happened to her?
I lost her.
When I was about a year old.
My landlady tells me she used to live
with me in this very room.
When I started earning money,
I rented this room back from her.
Living here, somehow makes me
feel closer to my mother.
This conch shell was my mother's.
And it is all that she left behind for me.
So I made it the main
attraction of my Temple.
What happened to her?
Please don’t ask!
If YOU ask, I’ll have to tell you.
And you've already learnt
too much about me!
Your life must have been so hard?
No not really.
I mean, there have been hard times...
but life has always been beautiful.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
Should I get you more custard?
I'm sorry.
I know that I'm an unwealthy
orphan chap...
but truly, my life is good.
Totally first class!
But that's the thing...
despite everything, you're still first-class.
You had nothing, Shiva.
Not even your parents!
But instead of complaining about life...
you love it!
Your attitude is so nice, Shiva.
How?
Should I tell you?
Now that I've made you cry,
let me cheer you up a bit.
I live by a very simple theory.
When life gets a bit Dark...
then, ladies and gentlemen...
find the Light.
Light?
Explain?
Light can't be explained...
it can only be felt.
Still, for you...
I’ll try, Isha Madam.
Light - is what protects us
when faced with any darkness.
It is that special power...
which brings meaning to our lives.
And where do you find this Light?
In Goddess Durga.
In the smiles of my kids.
In music.
Sometimes I even find it
in my Landlady's custard.
If you look with a pure heart,
you can find the Light everywhere.
So, ladies and gentlemen...
keep searching for the Light.
Because whenever you find it...
It will remind you...
that life is beautiful.
Understood.
Light.
Like tonight...
I found you, Isha...
and I found the Light.
What happened, Shiva?
Shiva, are you okay?
Can I get you something?
Isha! Please!
- Fire!
- Shiva, you-
What's happening, Shiva?
I'm not understanding this!
- Shiva!
- I'm sorry I'm-
I've got to go!
Shiva?
- Seven days!
- It has taken me seven days to break you.
- But now you are fully under
our control, Mr. Scientist.
- I SUMMON THE VASH MUKUT (Crown of Control)!
- A Great power...
- Darkness.
- Surrender to it!
- And show me...
- you are the Protector of the First Piece.
- Who keeps the Second?
- Three Pieces...
- The Second Piece?
- Is it with the Artist?
- Show me.
- Varanasi...
- Kashi...
- Your friend!
- The Artist...
- Is the Keeper of the Second Piece.
- My friend...
- Artist...
- ANISH SHETTY!
Let me help you, Shiva.
Let it be!
There's-
There's nothing you can do!
Please!
- Now...
- The Third Piece!
- Show us, Scientist.
The Third Piece...
- The Third Piece.
- Where?
- The third piece of the Brahmāstra...
- Is it with the Guru?
- Guru...
- Guruji...
- The Brahmānsh's Guru...
- Who is it now?
- Who?
- And where is he?
- The Ashram...
- Where is the Ashram?
- Ashram!
- Ashram... where?
Ashram...
- Who is the Guru?
- Where is the Ashram!
- Enough...
- Enough.
Enough.
- The Brahmānsh's Guru.
- Who is it now?
- And where is he?
- Where is the Ashram?
- Who's the Guru?
- The Ashram...
- where?
- Enough!
- Who is the Guru?
- Where is the Ashram!
- ENOUGH!
ENOUGH!
I will tell you nothing else.
You've lost, Scientist.
Just accept defeat.
Far greater than your passion, Junoon...
is my duty.
Aye!!
Oh and...
I never lose.
Have you started doing drugs, Shiva?
Don't lecture me, uncle...
it's not like I slept in your house!
- This isn't your father's building!
- Ya, so what?
It's mine!
Isha...
- What happened?
I don't know what happened...
the whole night got ruined.
- Take care of yourself, Shiva.
Have you completely lost it?
Where did you disappear?
She waited for two hours for you,
before leaving.
Where do I find her now?
Yeah exactly...
because she actually lives in London!
But she's staying at
her grandfather's house here.
Not just a house... it's a palace!
They're real big-shots.
Ya totally out of your league, Shiva!
How do you'll know all this?
I know everything!
Aye, Shorty...
I'm going to hang you
upside down and whack you!
- Relax, Dada...
she's our Facebook friend now.
The festival (pandal) you played at
the other day belongs to her family!
There's another celebration
there today, too.
Chant the Name of Goddess Kali!
Maa! (For Goddess Kali)
- You are fully under
our control, Mr. Scientist.
- Great power...
- Anish Shetty.
- Your friend... Artist?
- The Three Pieces...
- Who keeps the Second?
- Varanasi...
- The Third Piece...
- Kashi...
- Your friend... Artist?
- The Ashram...
- Guruji!
- The Brahmānsh's Guru...
- who is it now?
ENOUGH!
Help me, Maa.
Does this laptop have internet?
This whole place has Wi-Fi.
You can WhatsApp God if you want to!
Move!
Hey, you can't really do that!
I was just joking, man!
One minute!
- Let me be, please.
I'll lose my job!
Let me finish my work!
The suicide of famous Scientist
Mohan Bhargav has shocked the nation!
Last night, Scientist Mohan Bhargav...
jumped off the balcony of
his penthouse and took his own life.
Social media is abuzz with famous personalities
and politicians expressing their grief.
Who is playing this News so loudly?
Hey, did you know this man?
Delhi Police is investigating
this case deeply.
We will continue to update you
on this shocking incident.
But on the happy occasion of Diwali,
for a Scientist of this stature...
to commit suicide is
a huge blow for the nation-
Everyone! Please go ahead
and take a 10 minute break...
- we're all set for the celebration tonight.
Let me look around calmly to see
if everything's up to Grandpa's standards.
Please go take a snack break.
Madam, I ate before I got here.
So now eat a little more. Please!
- Okay.
This Scientist who was on the News...
is famous?
SpaceHind is one of
the country's biggest companies.
Shiva!
What is going on with you?
Isha, my life has certain mysteries...
which are very strange.
Shiva...
can you trust me?
This Scientist's death
that's on the News...
I saw a live broadcast of this.
In a dream but...
it was more than a dream!
What?
Yes, Isha...
that's what was happening to me last night
when I was getting those electric shocks!
- Shiva, you-
- Ya sure Laugh!
I feel like laughing at myself too,
for having fully lost the bloody plot!
That wasn't a suicide, Isha...
it was murder.
That Scientist was trying to
save himself from those three killers.
Something extraordinary
is going on in this world, Isha...
something beyond the
understanding of normal people...
There are ancient Weapons of Light.
Astras.
That Scientist is a part of something
called the Brahmānsh... was.
There's some Guru...
and now...
Now what?
Now those killers are
looking for someone else...
in Varanasi.
I've seen him, too...
Anish...
Anish Shetty!
But... why are YOU seeing all of this?
Who are you, Shiva?
What did you say?
Anish Shetty?
I've definitely heard that name.
Anish... Shetty...
That's him!
I couldn't remember clearly...
but he's a famous guy, too.
Artist, architect...
and the News says he's
working on a Heritage Site...
in Varanasi!
Isn't this what you saw?
What the-
So this man is real, too?
What is all this weird stuff,
that's happening to you?
Forget about me, what's going to
happen to this Artist now?
Shiva, you should report
all this to the police!
What do I say...
that I see stuff in my head?
Who will believe me?
I do...
I believe... you.
I feel like you'll never lie to me.
Isha, I left you alone
and ran off yesterday...
I'm sorry.
Forgiven.
But on one condition only...
promise me, you won't keep
any more secrets from me.
- Hail Goddess Kali!
- Who the heck?!
That's my grandpa!
He used to be a priest.
- Hail Goddess Kali!
- Don't worry, he'll go back to sleep.
Grandpa!
Sleep!
What are you thinking now, hero?
I'm going to Varanasi.
What?
This Artist needs to be saved...
this is now my responsibility.
Are you serious?
But Shiva, you could be in danger there!
Goddess Kali's blessings are now with me.
It's the season of Diwali
(The festival of Lights)!
Whatever comes...
I'll face it.
Maybe I should come
along with you to Varanasi.
Come on.
I'm serious... I'll come.
Actually...
I am coming... with you.
Don't be ridiculous.
You can't just come to Varanasi.
Shiva...
I'm coming.
- But Isha, it could be dangerous there-
- The flowers have arrived!
- Namaste.
Shiva...
everything that is
happening in your life...
it feels like destiny has something
very special planned for you.
And for us to have met like this...
that's destiny too, isn't it?
Maybe... we've met so that I can help you.
But Isha, out there I don't know
what could happe-
Isha!
Do you know the meaning of 'Isha'?
Parvati (Lord Shiva's Wife).
And without Parvati... Shiva is incomplete.
Okay?
Shiva, is your hand alright?!
Isha, I don't burn in fire.
I have a strange connection with fire.
Fire doesn't burn me.
Isha I know you're sca-
Why did you hide this from me?!
Isha...
Isha, please!
WHO ARE YOU?
- What other secrets are you still hiding?!
- This is the last one...
I swear... and the biggest.
I was just a kid when I found out...
that I was different somehow
because fire didn't burn me!
This Thing was so freaky that
I never told anyone...
and I just buried it deep within myself.
Isha...
my room...
there was a fire there... in which my-
I didn't burn but everything was destroyed!
But Shiva this...
this fire on the water,
coming towards you...
what is all this?
I have no idea, Isha. No idea!
This thing in me is growing...
my connection with fire,
is waking up suddenly!
- Since when?!
- Since a few days now, ever since-
I'm sorry I-
I'm sorry I scared you.
I could never be scared of you.
Please don't ever cry because of me.
Then don't keep things from me!
Just tell me everything, Shiv-
I love you.
I've been in love with you
since the moment I saw you.
I don't know how I know this...
but I just know that
I will love you forever.
Thank you!
Shiva...
Isha...
they are those three killers!
- Raftaar, Zor and Junoon.
We have to get to the Artist before them.
Let's go!
How are we going to find him in this chaos?
I don't even see your killers anywhere.
- They're not MY killers!
- Sorry!
Isha... up there!
- Raftaar!
How did he get up there?
He has the... Scientist's Anklet.
The Vānarāstra!
Why is he looking at us?
He's not looking at us.
Shiva...
Artist!
We have to get him out of here quietly.
How?
Where the hell is he going?
Shiva!
Did you see him jump?
He's like a circus monkey!
Don't get too excited now. Focus!
Where's he going off alone?
He's safer around the crowds!
Your other two killers
could be anywhere, Shiva.
- They're not MY killers, Isha!
- Sorry!
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Shiva, go! I have a plan!
You just come with me, Isha!
Shiva, they don't
recognize us so we're safe!
You just get to the Artist.
Go!
- I've got some personal work to do...
so I'll be in my office.
But I'm very happy.
Everything is going off well.
- Sir, it's all because of your hard work!
- Go enjoy the festival.
- Thank you sir!
- Sir!
- Not now, please.
Can I-
- What's wrong?
Excuse me!
Where is the main fair here?
- Where I can get some snacks?
- I don't know!
Oh no!
My battery just died!
May I borrow your phone please?
My sister is here somewhere
and I need to find her.
Please give it...
outgoing calls are really cheap these days!
Madam, ask someone else.
I'm in a hurry.
I was just asking for some help...
not like I asked for your kidney... cheapo!
I know you're a member of the Brahmānsh.
There's no time to explain everything,
but your life is in danger.
You have to get out of here, Sir
and I've come to help you.
Shiva, I'm fine!
What a gangster you are!
Where are you?
Look outside the room you're in...
you'll see an under construction area.
- I'm there, on the floor below you!
Okay listen, I'm getting out of here...
you get the Artist quickly
and meet me at the main gate.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
- Found your phone?
You shouldn't have gotten mixed up in this.
Who are you?
And where is Anish?
Shiva!
I heard your entire conversation...
I know you know where Anish is.
- SHIVA!
- Where is Anish?
Tell me or else...
Shiva!
Raftaar, no!
Come on... let's go!
How many are they?
- This way, Sir.
- Let's go!
Hey... keys!
- Drive!
He's in really bad shape.
We have to take him to the hospital.
No!
You two can get off,
I'll handle things from here.
You've been shot, Sir!
Do you want to die?
Shiva!
I just need to get there.
Where, Sir?
The Ashram?!
Where the Brahmānsh's Guru lives?
The Brahmānsh has remained
a secret... always.
But those three know everything!
And so do you two... how?
Sir, Shiva's right!
We have to take you to the hospital.
"Sahasra Nandim Samarthyam"
(Sanskrit Chants)
"O Nandi Astram"
Nandi Astra! (Nandi is the Sacred Bull)
I'm okay.
Just tell us the address of the Ashram.
I can't.
You have to!
Because getting you to
the Ashram is my responsibility!
OUR responsibility.
Sir!
Punch in the address here
or we'll take you straight to the hospital!
- Here...
- Sir, this says we're 20 hours away...
- where are we going?
- To the birthplace of Indian History...
- the Himalayas!
If you two are done with this
Lovers Point Sunrise, should we get going?
Sir, we were waiting for you to wake up.
She thought maybe you've popped it!
You look much better, Sir.
Let me see.
Your wound has healed completely.
My partner is taking care of me.
Nandi Astra!
Which has the power
of a thousand bulls in it.
"Sahasra Nandim Samarthyam"
Sir...
is there an Astra...
which is in pieces?
Triangle type...
but if you join it, it becomes round.
Like a pizza!
Uh...
Brahmāstra!
Brahmāstra?
Who are you, Shiva?
How do you know all of this?
Sir, what is the Brahmāstra?
"Sarva Astra Pradhānam"
"Srishti Vijayeta Karākam"
Our pride!
Our honor!
The Heart of the Brahmānsh!
That has the power of
the entire Universe within it!
The Lord of all the Astras-
Brahmāstra!
Yes, sir. Exactly!
Those killers are after this Brahmāstra!
We need to get to the Ashram.
So... you have a piece
of the Brahmāstra, right?
Can we see it?
What's wrong with you?
Shiva!
Sir, he's getting those Visions again!
Let it happen, Isha...
I want to see!
Stone... that stone is waking up!
Who?
Who is that?
Me?
You?
Us!
Here?!
They're watching us!
Sir...
the killers are in that truck!
Run!
Isha...
they can't get their hands on this Piece.
Get this to the Guru, whatever it takes... go!
Sir, please get into the car!
- Then who will stop them?
No way! We can't leave you alone, please!
To protect the Brahmāstra
is my duty, Shiva.
Don't deny me this chance
to fulfil that duty.
Please.
Go!
- Give the Guru my regards.
- May the Light of the Brahmāstra...
- always watch over you both!
He wants to fight.
What happened, Shiva?
"Sahasra Nandim Samarthyam"
"O Nandi Astram!"
Crush him so hard...
"Khand Khand Kuru"
That the pieces of the Brahmāstra
are lost within pieces of him!
"Mam Sahayakam"
Drive!
SHIVA!
Shiva, we're going to crash!
What are you doing?
- Stop the car!
- SHIVA!
What did you see, Shiva?
Energy.
And Sir...
No!
Shiva?
NO!
Get up.
- Get up.
Fight.
Stand up.
- Fight back, Sir!
- Kavachāstra (Magic Armour)... Protect!
What happened?
He's gone...
so are the two killers!
Just breathe, Shiva.
I'll drive... okay?
Two killers so then...
the third?
Go go go!
Go go go! Faster!
Faster!
Where'd he go?
Shiva!
- Let go! Let go of me!
- Shiva!
Shiva!
Isha, I won't let anything happen to you!
- Let go!
- Shiva!
- Let go of me!
No!
Shiva!
It's not far now.
There is a dirt road ahead.
Shiva!
He's got a gun, Shiva!
Shiva, look out!
He's just not dying!
- C'mon, Isha!
I do too...
What?
You said...
you love me.
I do too.
Say it.
I love you, Shiva.
I love you, Isha!
No!
The Brahmāstra belongs to Him!
NO!
Shiva!
- Shiva...
Guruji, Shiva's in pain.
The whole day has gone by,
why is he still asleep?
He's sleeping...
because within him
a Great Power is waking up.
Master of Astras.
O Supreme One.
We have lost one of our Comrades.
The Guru's identity...
- and the location of his Ashram,
are still unknown to me.
There is something else...
there is a boy,
who is interfering in our cause.
We will find out more about him.
I will resume my mission
for the last Two Pieces...
I will keep fighting...
but I need your Power!
Help me!
So that I can fulfil my life's purpose...
and bring you back to life!
Help me!
So that I can attain
the Brahmāstra for you!
HAIL BRAHMĀSTRA!
In my time...
there has been only one Emergency
Meeting of the Brahmānsh High Council.
Today is the second!
The Brahmānsh is in danger.
Two of our senior members,
Mohan and Anish have passed away.
But these were no ordinary deaths...
they were murdered.
What?
Those Assassins have
stolen the Vānarāstra...
and the Nandi Astra.
And also... one piece of the Brahmāstra.
But who are these assassins?
And how do they know about us, Raghu?
We have no information at this time...
but the position of the stars tells us...
there is some great secret...
behind these events.
- So what do we do now, Guruji?
Now we must-
Now we must search for answers.
Stay alert...
and warn all our members.
- Let us say a Prayer before we depart.
- Where are you taking me?
- Who goes boating on a mountain?
You just come here.
If this is the reaction
I get for fainting...
I should do it more often.
I thought it was all over at the gate.
You saved us, Shiva! Thank God!
Enough of this drama.
Let’s get out of here, Isha.
I know it's a viewpoint,
but is the PDA necessary?
They've made our viewpoint
a lover's point.
- Awake all of 5 minutes, and already at it!
- Move, Romeo!
- Mom's calling...
- Are you planning to talk to her from my lap?
Bro, we only get phone network on the boat.
By the way, I'm Sher!
Guys, this is Shiva...
and Shiva, this is Raveena,
Rani and this is little Tensing!
- Who are these people?
- Us?
We're the Avengers of this Institute!
They're new members of the Brahmānsh...
here to learn under the Guru.
If we're done with the small talk,
go meet the Guru.
He's expecting you.
Namaste, Sir.
Sir, if I can be honest...
when I heard ‘Guru', I imagined someone
in long robes with tangled hair!
But you're a total rockstar!
A man's identity is not known
by his outward appearance...
but by the Energy inside him!
Like you... on the outside,
you're an ordinary young man...
but inside of you, hides a powerful warrior!
Warrior?
Me?!
Stop mocking me, Sir!
Outside... those Senior Citizens of yours...
they are Warriors!
Shiva?
- Sir, may I?
- Yes.
But the Astras they all had...
My mind is blown, Sir!
Anything could be an Astra here...
like this knife.
Used to cut fruits or slay demons?
Hmm...
Astra...
like you, Shiva!
We, the Brahmānsh...
protect powerful Astras...
- but you are an Astra yourself.
Agnyastra (Fire Astra)!
According to Isha, if I ask you to...
you can't even light
a candle with your Fire...
and yet yesterday at my gate,
you burnt that Assassin to ashes!
Now, if I tell you that
this is just the start.
That one day...
with just a small flame, you can burn
a whole building to the ground.
What will you say?
I'd tell you to lay off the drugs, Sir!
Join the Brahmānsh, Shiva...
and I'll transform you...
from a DJ into a Dragon!
- You were right.
This is an Astra.
My...
Prabhāstra (Sword of Light)!
- Comes in very handy...
Just like...
a pocket-knife.
Sir, you're offering a membership
to the Brahmānsh...
like it's a Diwali Shopping Sale,
that one obviously says Yes to!
But I've got to break your heart
because my answer is...
no!
I see.
Sir, you're right.
I do have a weird connection with Fire.
But this Fire Power...
I don't want it.
- But why, Shiva?
- Because you're in my life, Isha.
And THIS Power between us...
is enough for me.
What did you call me, Sir?
An ordinary man.
There's Power in leading
an ordinary life too... Light in it!
And this Battle of yours...
It's Dark, Sir.
I don't want to get stuck in it.
But you are already stuck, Shiva...
in our DARK Battle.
Have you ever wondered about your visions.
Why ONLY you get them?
Why did your life bring you here?
Why you were given this Boon of Fire?
Because the Brahmānsh is in your destiny.
In this, there is no doubt.
And you have no choice!
You're crossing a line, Sir.
Any person, at any given moment...
always has a choice in
what they do with their lives.
And this Battle for the Brahmāstra...
is not mine, and I won't fight it!
That's my final choice!
- Shiva...
- Let's go!
The Battle for the Brahmāstra
was your Parents' Battle!
Your parents were...
Warriors of the Brahmānsh!
What?!
Everything is connected, Shiva...
you are not understanding, Shiva.
You are connected to us
because your Parents were connected to us!
The Brahmānsh is in your blood!
And if you leave today,
you will never learn anything about them!
You will remain an Orphan forever!
That's the choice you are making!
Remember that!
You tell me clearly everything
you know about my parents!
I won't tell you anything!
I won't tell you until you become worthy
of hearing their story.
And there's only one way to do that.
What?
Stay here, Shiva.
Stay here.
And ignite your inner Fire!
You're blackmailing me, Sir!
I will do anything
to protect the Brahmāstra!
I have only one connection
to the intentions of these Assassins...
You!
So you have to stay here.
And I can see in your eyes...
that your choice is changing!
Isha will have to leave...
with the Senior Citizens of the Brahmānsh.
She'll be back in a few days
with your things.
You'll have very little time
so say your goodbyes.
Guruji has me trapped.
Well, that's why he's the Guru!
I'll finally learn
about my parents here, Isha.
Will you be okay without me?
No.
But at least you'll be safe,
away from me.
Why didn't you tell me?
I knew you'd feel bad.
Got yourself burnt by my love.
Since a while.
Fire destroys everything, Isha.
It also illuminates everything.
My Warrior of Light!
Tell me again about your visions?
For the last time, Raghu Sir.
There's a killer, Zor.
- And another... Junoon.
And they want The Brahmāstra!
But we don't know why?
Oh, and... Junoon has a stone.
Like coal...
broken...
- and that stone has power.
Can you remember anything else?
There's one more thing...
it's not really clear in my visions, but...
I think Junoon has a Guru, too!
Anything else?
Nothing else, Sir!
It's hard enough to
remember even this much.
Come on, Santha...
let's end today's investigation.
Please also note in my statement...
that Junoon is looking for you
and she's deadly!
So please be careful!
Even if Junoon finds us,
she doesn't know...
that I have a new Astra...
who's far more deadly than her.
Agnyastra (A Fire Stone)!
But at the moment... he's OFF!
So Dragon...
Time to come ON!
What does that mean?
Here.
This is the Āyur-Mudrika (Ring of Healing).
It can heal these dying plants.
Try it!
Nag-Dhanush (Snake Bow) - Awaken!
Rani, you try.
Woah... It came ON!
Gajāstra (Elephant Shield) - Protect!
For any Astra to come ON...
first, the wielder needs to come ON...
from within!
That went way over my head, Sir.
So, Dragon...
You have to switch from OFF to ON.
How?
Simple.
By finding your button.
- Button?
- Yes!
- Is he high?
- Come on, Shiva.
Increase this fire.
So what's your button, Sir?
- Come, Tensing!
Activate the Pawanāstra (Air Stone)!
It's just not happening, Sir.
Amrita...
Dev...
Isha...
- Isha...
Tell me where the Ashram is...
and I'll spare your life!
I'm not afraid of you...
Zor!
Nandi Astra!
ISHA!
- Shiva!
Isha, are you okay?
Shiva, how did you know?
Are you okay or not?!
I'm a bit hurt...
- but... I'm okay, Shiva!
- I'm fine... I'm okay.
Thank God you're okay, Isha!
- Shiva!
Thank God you're okay!
Aye, Shiva...
- I'm okay.
I love you.
I love you, Isha!
I love you, Shiva!
Hello?
Shiva?
Hello, Isha?
Your voice is breaking... hello?
- Isha!
- I've spoken to my people...
Isha is fine.
She's coming here.
Shiva, tell me what's on your mind...
what's the problem?
Isha...
how do I explain?
Look, Shiva...
most people fall in love...
but very few people fall so deeply in love.
I love Isha very deeply, Sir.
But...
Isha is my button!
If you knew this, why didn't you tell me?
Because when this button is ON...
You become the Agnyastra (Fire Astra)!
And fire destroys everything, Sir.
Why are you fighting your fire?
Fire took my mother from me, Sir.
You say you knew her, right?
She was burnt to ashes by fire.
Those memories will always haunt me...
those nightmares will never stop.
You say I'm the Agnyastra.
Could it be that...
my fire took my mother's life?
And that's why...
you hate fire.
No sir...
I'm scared of it...
very scared of fire...
and that's why I always run from it.
That’s how life is, Shiva...
it doesn’t work around our fears...
it brings our fears to us!
And so life...
brought Isha to you!
Isha.
Sir...
my life has been beautiful...
but it's been lonely.
Maybe if I had my mother...
it would have been different.
Now I have Isha...
and I'm not alone.
Before her, I was incomplete...
now, I'm whole.
Look...
the Power of Love!
A Power that...
like my mother...
could burn Isha.
And look...
the Strength of Fear.
I understand your situation, Shiva.
Isha is love.
Love connects you to fire.
But fire...
is your biggest fear!
What will you choose?
Love?
Or Fear?
I've already chosen love, Sir.
Then you must accept your fear!
And give your fear...
Love.
Isha is just the path...
but your button...
is Love.
Shiva, I don't know
what happened to your mother.
But I do know that...
the Fire of Love cannot destroy anything.
A fire like that...
can light up the whole world!
And no one has the right
to cage something so pure, Shiva.
Respect it...
be grateful for it...
because love...
Is the most powerful thing in this world!
Wow!
Fantastic!
I can't make fire without a flame, Sir.
The right time comes at it's own time.
Sir, when will the time be right...
for you to tell me my parents story?
I've been carrying around this question
my whole life, Sir.
Ashram!
- Guruji, what happened there?
He was looking for the Ashram.
We should search this area carefully.
Sir, that was one of Junoon's men.
His pendant...
I've seen it.
Sir...?
That Black Pendant...
had glimmers of the Agnyastra in it.
Agnyastra?
Shiva, it is time to tell you the story!
Come.
- Māyāstra (Astra of Concealment)
- which reveals its true form,
only with its master's blood.
- This story begins with...
the Lord of all the Astras.
Is this...?
A piece of the Brahmāstra!
Didn't I bring this piece from the Artist?
The Second Piece.
- Three Pieces...
- you all know that...
there are three pieces of the Brahmāstra...
- But...
about thirty years ago...
when I was just a young student
of the Brahmānsh.
- The Headquarters of the Brahmānsh...
was in the seas, on an island.
- Back then, the Brahmāstra
wasn't in three pieces.
- It was whole.
- And...
He was there, too...
a young warrior...
Dev!
- Dev was very powerful.
Different from everyone.
- He had a fierce obsession
with all the Astras.
- He could make the impossible, possible.
- He mastered not one... but many Astras.
- But the Astra he became
the King of was...
The Agnyastra (Fire Astra)!
- When Dev unleashed
the power of the Agnyastra...
- all the other magic of the Brahmānsh
paled in front of his Fire.
People used to call him...
Agni Dev (Fire Lord).
- He was already Jal Dev (Water Lord).
Kavach (Armour) and Gyaan (Knowledge) Dev!
- but eventually he wanted to be...
- Brahm-Dev!
Meaning he wanted...
the Brahmāstra!
- Keeping the Brahmāstra calm
is the duty of the Brahmānsh.
- Dev didn't care about this.
- He defeated the Council members...
- and stole the Brahmāstra.
- And then...
for the first time in this age...
the Brahmāstra woke up.
- Then...
- appeared an extraordinary
and terrible sight.
- The earth, the ocean...
- and the heavens came alive.
- That day I understood...
- what Brahmāstra truly is!
- Dev would have willingly destroyed
the world with his greed for the Brahmāstra.
This village looks empty.
Did Dev succeed?
Sir?
Did Dev win?
No, Son...
we haven't gotten to the real Battle yet!
This story has another player.
- Our Ace of Spades!
- Who fought Dev in the Last Battle
for the Brahmāstra...
- and by breaking the Brahmāstra
into three pieces...
defeated Dev and destroyed Dev's fire!
Who was he?
She.
- A beautiful...
- and pure Energy!
Amrita.
I've seen her name on your boat.
Not mine...
- Amrita's boat.
- Which was the only survivor
of that Battle.
- The boat returned to us
with the pieces of the Brahmāstra...
- but there were only two.
But the Brahmāstra is in three pieces?
In the Last Battle for the Brahmāstra...
that Third Piece was lost!
- WHAT?!
You mean the Brahmāstra is incomplete?
What happened to Dev and Amrita?
The island where all this took place,
was swallowed by the ocean...
And with that, the two of them, too.
- That's what we all believe...
- but don't truly know.
Sir...
you were going to tell me
the story of my parents.
But this story is about
Dev and Amrita's battle!
So...
then... how?
Before the Battle, what was
Dev and Amrita's relationship?
One of Love.
Yes, Shiva.
The last battle for the Brahmāstra...
- is also the story of two lovers.
Dev fought for his passion...
- and Amrita, for her duty.
But by the time the Battle happened...
Amrita was pregnant.
- Thirty years passed...
- then...
- suddenly, you appeared before me.
- And I saw a reflection
of Dev's fire in yours...
- and in you, a glimmer of Dev!
Is it possible that in that Battle...
Amrita... survived, somehow.
- And Amrita's child was born.
- And that child...
Is me?
Sir, you don't have any proof of all this?
Everything is connected, Shiva.
Everything-
By fire!
Yes, Shiva...
we'll talk about this later now.
Guruji!
- I found this!
That man was from this village then!
But where have all the villagers gone?
Let's go!
- The Black pendant had glimmers
of the Agnyastra in it.
Shiva.
Let's go.
- Dev...
- Amrita...
- Dev's fire...
- My fire...
- Agnyastra...
Shiva!
- The ocean swallowed the island.
- But in the end he wanted to be...
Come on, Shiva!
- Brahm-Dev!
- Who?
- But in the end he wanted to be...
- Brahm-Dev!
- Who?
- Welcome!
Welcome to our Army!
Junoon.
- You are not farmers any more...
- but soldiers of a great cause.
- What we are seeking,
is what you all must seek now!
And for that end, we must find
the headquarters of the Brahmānsh first!
Some strong power resides...
in that pendant.
How is the hunt for the Ashram progressing?
These Himalayan ranges have many towns,
many villages, and many houses.
It's only been a few days.
We need more time.
Seven days!
I give you all seven days.
- We will attack as soon as
we find the Ashram.
And remember...
this power you are
all feeling within you...
it is the greatest power of all.
And it has only one purpose...
BRAHMĀSTRA!
- Who?
Something's happened to her.
Shiva!
- She knows we're here!
Guruji!
Move back!
The headquarters of the Brahmānsh
is no longer secure.
We have to leave from here
before they find us.
I'll make some arrangements.
- I made a mistake...
- While I was thinking about
our next move...
- their power grew too strong.
Namaste!
Weren't you hurt?
All better, thanks to Dr. Rani.
Just making sure you guys
have no trouble cuddling at night...
So, Guruji asked me to bring anything
that's related to your mother.
Has he told you anything
about your mother, Shiva?
- I've told him everything, Isha.
And the proof of my story...
is in Shiva's hands.
How?
My friend, Amrita...
had to break the Brahmāstra
in order to stop Dev...
- and since that day we have believed...
that the third piece of the Brahmāstra...
is lost.
But you think,
the Third Piece was not lost...
- it survived.
- And Amrita kept that Piece with her!
This conch...
- isn't just a conch is it, Guruji?
Māyāstra...
- which reveals its true form,
only with its master's blood.
And if Amrita and Shiva
have the same blood...
- Shiva should be the master
of this Astra, too.
- Brahmāstra...
The Third Piece...
and my proof...
that you are Amrita's son...
- Shiva!
Not just Amrita's son, right?
My father, Dev...
What about Dev, Sir?
What do you think?
In the Last Battle for the Brahmāstra,
my mother was not the only survivor...
Dev survived, too.
- What?
And even today, the force
that still wants the Brahmāstra...
is Dev.
- How do you know this, Shiva?
- I just know.
When I wore the pendant,
I saw a body...
surrounded by Astras.
That is Dev.
Junoon's Guru... is Dev.
The broken stone Junoon wears...
is the Agnyastra-
which is still connected to Dev...
and also to me.
Junoon...
Zor...
That whole Army is Dev's army.
From the start,
the presence in my visions...
that's Dev!
He's not fully alive yet...
but not quite dead either.
He's just...
there.
- I don't understand any of this.
I'm so confused.
But how did Dev survive all this time?
- And how did he find Junoon?
- Yeah, how?
How did he build this army?
And Amrita? Why didn't she return
to the Brahmānsh after the Battle?
- And why did she keep the Third Piece?
- Yes, why?
This Case is still full of questions...
that we don't have answers for.
Aye, Shiva...
are you okay?
- Isha...
- in all of this mess,
I forgot my own theory...
- when life gets a bit Dark...
- then Shiva... find the Light.
- Of course, my parent's story
is still shrouded in shadows.
- But for me, there is Light in the fact
that I finally know who they were.
I will pray for the safety of
all the Astras.
- And with that, I know who I am.
- This fight is now my fight.
- And this is now my duty!
Rani tells me you're making
some really cool fireworks these days...
but for that you need
to be ON or something.
Now watch...
Fire Show for you!
Guruji!
Isha!
- Sher...
- Guruji...
The ropes that bind us all, Shiva...
have incredible power in them.
Only your power can break them now.
Junoon has joined Two
of the Pieces, Guruji.
She has taken Rani.
And she'll keep torturing her until-
She gets the Third Piece!
Which is with us.
We'll give her the Third Piece...
and save Rani.
But remember, Shiva...
If all Three Pieces come together...
the world will be destroyed!
Have faith in me, Guruji.
Junoon doesn't know
that you have a new Astra...
that will destroy her!
- My...
Agnyastra!
- Go, Shiva!
Unleash your fire!
Zor!
Take me to Junoon.
- We have what she wants.
Thank you.
You finally led us to the Brahmāstra!
The moment you wore that Black Pendant...
we controlled your mind long enough
to get what we needed!
Your mind is also in
someone else's control, Junoon.
And it's not you...
but Him I want to speak to... Dev!
Brahm-Dev!
Speak his name with respect!
Catch!
Shiva!
Are we safe, Shiva?
Isha, why aren't they burning?!
Because they're wearing
those black pendants.
Which have the power
of the Agnyastra!
Dev is protecting them!
And I'm protecting you.
Don't be scared!
She's going to do something!
A different Power?
Water?
Rain...
Isha, Lighter!
Don't let the flame go out!
You have the power
of the Agnyastra in you!
- How?
You should join us.
Brahm-Dev has power
you can't even imagine.
I don't want the Power of Darkness...
because I believe only
in the Power of the Light.
The games end now.
The game is just beginning!
Destroy them!
Isha!
Don't move.
I'm going to distract them from you.
Shiva!
- If all Three Pieces come together...
- the world will be destroyed!
Isha!
Burst!
Stop firing!
He must have no fire!
Come on, Rani! We have to go!
Shiva!
Go, Isha! Get out of here!
Take the Brahmāstra piece and kill him.
Raveena, catch!
Guruji!
- SHIVA!
Tenzu, stay hidden!
Tenzu...
Enough, Junoon!
Give up this obsession,
or you'll lose your life!
My life isn't yours to take!
Because it's not even my own.
And until I've fulfilled my mission...
He won't let me die.
My Lord is resting...
but you are just a small ember
in front of His Fire!
Awaken!
Come to me, Brahm-Dev!
- Show your Power!
Set this sleeping Agnyastra ablaze,
Brahm-Dev!
- Remember...
- Warrior of Light...
- there is only one master of Fire!
- Brahm-Dev!
Tenzu...
Run!
If you come any closer,
I'll throw the Brahmāstra in the valley!
And the Brahmāstra will be lost again.
Tenzu, go...
and don't turn back... okay?
Now, take the Agnyastra off
and put it on the ground.
- Or I'll throw this!
- She won't be able to
throw the Brahmāstra!
BRAHMĀSTRA IS MINE!
Don't come any closer,
or I'll really throw it!
Junoon, I'm going to throw it!
You won't go through with it.
You're weak and for your weakness,
you will pay the price!
Yes!
Tenzing!
Hail Brahm-Dev!
"Sarva Astra Pradhānam"
"Srishti Vijayeta Kārakam"
"Trikhandam Sanyogam"
"Tatha Prakatam Brahmāstram!"
It's the Beginning of the End!
No! Run!
Isha!
- Shiva!
- Guruji!
Guruji!
Shiva!
You'll die, Shiva!
Without her I don't want to live!
Shiva...
Shiva!
Shiva, don't!
What have you done?
You could have saved your own life!
But... YOU are my life!
Everything is ending!
We will never end, Isha!
Light...
The Light is coming, Shiva!
From our beginning...
the Light has been here Isha... in you!
When we die,
you find me on the other side.
We are not going to die, Isha.
And if death must come...
it will have to take me first!
I love you, Isha!
SHIVA!
And then I witnessed the greatest miracle
I had ever seen.
The Light of the Brahmāstra
was controlled by Shiva's Fire!
Shiva was ready to
give up his life for Isha...
And with that act, he showed he was
capable of the highest form of Love...
sacrifice.
With that sacrifice...
Shiva finally created Fire
from within himself...
a Fire of Love...
Which calmed the most powerful Astra
in the Universe.
And I understood,
that in this whole world...
there is no greater weapon than Love.
Click.
That night we witnessed
the birth of a divine Hero.
Now, he needed no source to create Fire.
The Darkest night was ending...
The Light was here.
We had won the battle.
But the war...
still remains.
Hail Brahm-Dev!