THE THIRSTY ONE
These smiling flowers
These fragrant gardens
These paths dipped in color and light
Drinking the nectar of flowers, the bees sway
What can I give to you, O splendid nature?
All that I have is a few tears, a few sighs
I told you to keep the papers in order.
Has a ghost stolen that manuscript?
- Where is the paper? - I... I...
- Good morning. - Good morning.
- Did you hear something?
- He wished you good morning.
Fool! Where is that manuscript?
Have you looked at my things?
Wings?
Wings.
God forbid! This is a publishing house,
not a birdhouse!
Things. Have you read the poems I left?
I have.
Did you like them? You'll publish them?
Why? Am I crazy?
Call that poetry? It's a crusade
against hunger and unemployment.
Sir, poetry deals with delicacies.
Write poems about flowers and songbirds.
You're incomparable, sir!
Write about wine and the carafe...
the delicate neck of the carafe,
the curve of a woman's eyebrow.
Be quiet! Are you a poet or a barber?
Have you studied poets like Mir and Momin?
Have you?
Josh and Faiz, too. Beyond your
comprehension. Return my poems.
They must be somewhere. We'll find them later.
You're making a mess of my papers.
Are you mad?
What is this? Oh no.
...
So that's where my poems were.
Who are you to throw them away?
Should I make a paper hat of them?
Don't insult them by wearing them
on a hollow head.
- So my head is hollow? - Yes.
How about yours?
If you're a poet, I'm a donkey!
Obviously, but it's nice to hear you admit it.
Are you weighing vegetables or gold?
Add another eggplant.
Come on.
Grandma, there's Uncle Vijay
Vijay. Here's you money.
- Uncle. - Vijay.
Vijay.
Grandma, hurry up.
I've caught Uncle.
I'm not your enemy. Why run from your mother?
- Mom I...
- Son, where have you been all these days?
You lost your father.
I can't bear to see you suffer.
I'm well, mother.
Of course! Just look at the state you're in.
Come home. I've hidden away
some special food for you.
Come my son.
You've found him?
Yes.
Come my son.
Vijay had such a promising future.
Look at him now.
I hear poetry has obsessed him.
Take no notice of them. Eat.
So your poet is back?
Every literate donkey thinks he's a poet.
Brother.
Where else can he go? Who will feed him?
Don't listen to him. Eat.
See, brother? We earn and mother
feeds delicacies to her darling son.
His lack of shame amazes me.
If he had any self-respect,
he'd starve rather than eat here.
Shut up, you two!
I won't hear a word said against him.
He's back after so long, thirsty
and hungry, and you begrudge him.
He's hale and hearty. Why doesn't
he earn his keep? Depending on us.
He's your brother. After father
died you should look after him.
Father has gone and with him his duty.
It wasn't our wish that our parents
produced such a good-for-nothing.
...
What?
That I should have to hear this.
It was my misfortune to give birth to you two.
You won't let me work as a maid
because of your "prestige."
I would do that to feed my son.
...
Sister-in-law, where are my poems?
Address me, not the women.
I sold them as waste paper for ten annas.
Ten annas? You sold my poems as waste paper?
Uncouth fools like you know no better.
You call me uncouth?
Did you hear that, brother?
How dare you? I got rid of your papers,
now I'll get rid of you!
Out! Useless!
Where will you go on an empty stomach?
Who will look after you?
Take me with you. I don't want to
stay in this house another minute
Don't worry, mother. I'll do my best.
I'll take you away from here as soon as I can.
Vijay, let me get on with my work
instead of searching waste paper.
There was an important file
among that waste paper.
A file? Handwritten papers?
- Where are they? - A woman bought them.
What?
They caught her eye, she read some,
then she took them away.
Who is she? Where does she live?
How do I know? She wasn't a local person.
Vijay, if she comes again, I'll ask.
Come in. Were your brothers
as affectionate as ever?
Hungry? You'll end up starving to death.
As for me, I got 200 rupees
from a rich man today.
How?
He ran over an old woman's leg,
but I gave false witness for him.
Shyam, remember how you found
a lamed sparrow as a kid?
You cared for it until it was better.
I was only a kid then.
But you're still the kid.
...
Do not complain if I look at you
with impudence.
There!
You looked at me again with such longing.
- You looked at me again... - Listen.
I say...
Who knows what you said?
Who knows what I heard?
Something stirred in my heart
Who knows what you said?
Who knows what I heard?
Something stirred in my heart
Who knows what you said?
...
I heard a ringing sound
I felt a tingling sensation
Slumbering dreams reawakened
Something stirred in my heart
Who knows what you said?
Who knows what I heard?
Something stirred in my heart
Who knows what you said?
...
My lowered eyes looked up again
My faltering feet are steady now
There is new life in my step
Something stirred in my heart
Who knows what you said?
Who knows what I heard?
Something stirred in my heart
Who knows what you said?
...
My hair floats around my shoulders...
filled with sweet fragrance
Secret longings unravel
Something stirred in my heart
Who knows what you said?
Who knows what I heard?
Something stirred in my heart
Who knows what you said?
Who knows what I heard?
Something stirred in my heart
Who knows what you said?
...
- Listen. - Yes?
- That song you were singing...
- Did you like it?
Where did you get it?
It's mine.
...
- It isn't yours. - Then why ask, if you know?
Because I want...
What do you want?
The file with that song in it.
Is that all?
I don't like absurd jokes.
Do you like me?
...
No.
Then why are you following me?
If you have that file, it's precious
to me. Whenever I have money...
You've followed me empty-handed?
You think this is your family home?
Get out!
Please understand.
I only want that file.
- Remove your hand. - It's very important.
Get out!
Must I kick you out?
Stop shouting, silly.
Your new customer will run away.
A pauper! I lured him here,
but he hasn't a penny.
Juhi, it was him.
Gulabo, what's come over you?
Where are you running?
I must apologize to him.
I treated him very badly.
Stop talking in riddles.
Speak in plain language.
What's all this about?
The man who followed me is a poet.
The poet whose poems I bought as waste paper.
Look: the same writing, the same paper.
And I threw him out as a pauper
He is a pauper
If you hadn't thrown him out,
would you prefer hugging him?
Our profession has its standards
Let's go back upstairs
...
It's fun
Hello
They are very bad boys
Vijay, have you written any poems
in the holidays?
A few
Create something extempore,
then we'll consider you a poet
Extempore?
- Shall I?
- Yes
Shall I? On what subject?
Which subject?
Who is she?
Who cares? There's your subject:
a poem about her
When I walk, even my shadow
lags behind
When you walk...
the earth and the sky keep pace
When I stop, a lonely evening
falls upon me
When you stop, spring and
moonlight stop too
...
Learning your poetry lesson, Vijay?
Yes sir. I mean no sir
Sit down
- Mr. David
- Present sir
- Miss Shobha
Miss Pushpalata
Present sir. I am here
Oh, sorry
...
Miss Sinha. Miss Sinha
Present sir
...
Life may present us with many
trials, but we will never part
...
Never break our vow of love,
even if Judgement Day is upon us
Life may present us with many
trials, but we will never part
Never break our vow of love,
even if Judgement Day is upon us
We leave the world behind,
advancing step by step
Who knows how long we will travel
together as carefree as we are?
...
Coolie!
I want a coolie!
At your service
What?
God! What has the world come to?
Educated people working as coolies
Fine
Here you money
...
Have you brought money today?
No credit
...
It's counterfeit
What?
I suppose you've got nothing else?
So that's your game!
You brought the counterfeit
money on purpose.
Who'll pay for the food
you've eaten?
Pay up, or I'll have your shirt
Take the plate away
Put it back
Take your money
Keep the change; go to a barber.
He'll make you look more like a human
Move it!
Why don't you eat?
- I'm not hungry
- Yes, you are
You've no right to pity me
I'm sorry... don't let my anger
offend you
You have every right to be angry
I treated you very badly
the other day
I've nothing against you
Then please eat... for my sake
For your sake?
You hardly know me
I know you very well
How?
Through your poems and songs
I know your thoughts and feelings
What else is there?
I can't understand you
The other day, Miss...
Why do you address me so politely?
It seems strange
Why?
Until today, I have only heard
people rebuke me
Their crude remarks...
their taunts...
their abuse, their dirty jokes
But you show me so much respect
Massage, oil massage,
head massage
If your head reels with pain,
or your heart sinks in gloom
Don't fret, leave it to me,
I'll make things right soon
Massage, oil massage
If your head reels with pain,
or your heart sinks in gloom
Don't fret, leave it to me,
I'll make things right soon
...
The oil I use has perfume,
curing baldness and dandruff
Once my hands begin to whirl,
your fate won't look so rough
The oil I use has perfume,
curing baldness and dandruff
Once my hands begin to whirl,
your fate won't look so rough
Listen to me, my son.
This oil has great healing powers
It cures a thousand ailments,
so why not give it a try?
If your head reels with pain,
or your heart sinks in gloom
Don't fret, leave it to me,
I'll make things right soon
...
Suffering a lovers' tiff?
Is your business in the throes?
A single touch of this strong hand
will dissipate all woes
Suffering a lovers' tiff?
Is your business in the throes?
A single touch of this strong hand
will dissipate all woes
Listen to me, mister.
This oil has great healing powers
It cures a thousand ailments,
so why not give it a try?
If your head reels with pain,
or your heart sinks in gloom
Don't fret, leave it to me,
I'll make things right soon
...
Be you a servant, be you a master.
Be you a leader, or one of the led
Come to me, as everyone does;
king or soldier, bow your head
Be you a servant, be you a master.
Be you a leader, or one of the led
Come to me, as everyone does;
king or soldier, bow your head
Listen to me, mister.
This oil has great healing powers
It cures a thousand ailments,
so why not give it a try?
If your head reels with pain,
or your heart sinks in gloom
Don't fret, leave it to me,
I'll make things right soon
Mr Vijay, come here!
A great poet. I was singing
one of his songs
Business has doubled since
I've been singing your song
- Really?
- Yes
Don't go
- I'll just finish him off
- What?
Stay put
Mr Vijay, I'll give you a special
massage, completely free
No, Sattar. The present times
have battered me quite enough
It's amazing how you still manage
to smile, despite the battering
I've seen only two blissfully
unaware creatures
A donkey in the noon sun
and a starving poet
True. The heat may come from
the glitter of gold or the sun
Only donkeys relish it
- What did you say?
- Still! We're discussing donkeys
...
Here I am
- Juhi, weren't you waiting for me?
- I'm waiting for a man with a car
With a car? Not a masseur?
- No!
- No?
- May Allah puncture his tyres
- May He puncture your head
My?
- Juhi, are you cross with me?
- Out with it
You get upset when I speak of
the man with the car
Have you no consideration for
the heart you've punctured?
- Get it patched up
- I have no wife to patch it
- What do I care about it?
- Let's get married
Get lost, you idiot!
Did You hear? You gave me
the gift of massaging
If I had the gift of cheating,
I'd be the one driving her around
I'm done for! What hit me?
A coconut? I get it.
I won't say another word
Phullu! Stop! Brother, don't
let him escape. Stop him
If you let him go,
I'll have to chase him for a mile
I'm half my size,
thanks to chasing these boys
Hello, Pushpa
Vijay? I didn't recognize you
You were smartly dressed at college.
Whose "love" brought you to this?
Someone who won't let me go.
- Who?
- Unemployment
Are these children yours?
And their father's.
They're Gullu and Phullu
Their father's name
rhymes with theirs
- Rhymes with theirs?
- Yes
There's a gathering at our old
college tonight
All our classmates will be there.
You must come
Gullu, wait
Now for another mile race
I'll leave. Gullu!
What are you doing here?
Come on
You must come tonight.
Don't forget
Gullu, wait.
Leaving the world behind,
advancing step by step
Who knows where we're heading,
as carefree as we are
Leaving the world behind,
advancing step by step
Where is Bhattacharya?
He was going to recite next
Oh, God! Yes!
Leaving the world behind,
advancing step by step
Vijay, why stand here, peeping in?
Come inside
No, Pushpa. My clothes...
Clothes? You're covered from
head to foot. Come along
Move a side
Come
Ladies and gentlemen
Mr Bhattacharya isn't here.
Well, we're delighted...
...
we're delighted that
Vijay is here...
and I request him to
recite one of his poems
Come Mr. Vijay. Come
Don't be formal
Start, Vijay
I am weary...
I am weary of the struggle of life
The weariness of my heart
may spurn the world
Why such a sad song on this occasion?
Recite a happy verse
Afflicted by grief,
how do I find a song of joy?
How do I find a song of joy?
I can only return to this life
what it has given to me
The desires of the heart
are stirred once again
I confess that I have been
crushed by life's sorrows
There! Today I break...
There! Today I break
all ties with hope
There! Never shall I voice
a complaint again
Are you an ex-student?
- Yes
- I see
Do you work?
I spend my time looking for work
Your poems are good
Thanks
My card. Come to my office
tomorrow morning
Modern Publishing House.
- Yourself?
- I am the owner
- Greetings, Mr. Ghosh!
- Have a seat
Here are my poems
- When were you at college?
- From '48 to '52
Shall I read the poems aloud,
or will you read them?
1952.
I married in 1952
Did you study science or arts?
Arts
May I recite the poems?
You're sure you left college in '52,
or was it before?
In '52
In '52. Mr. Ghosh, my poems?
Will you work in my office?
Work here?
I thought you called me about
publishing my poems
There's plenty of time
to publish your poems
I must find out more about you
About me?
Yes
Mr Chatterji, this is your
new assistant
You can start tomorrow
- Farewell!
...
Hello, Meena
Vijay
What if my heart were to
dwell in your eyes?
What if I close my eyes
and punish your heart?
What if my heart were to
dwell in your eyes?
What if I close my eyes
and punish your heart?
What if my heart were to
dwell in your eyes?
...
I will weave flowers of love
in your hair
What if I were to shake
the flowers to the ground?
I will weave flowers of love
in your hair
What if I were to shake
the flowers to the ground?
What if my heart were to
dwell in your eyes?
...
I will bring you into my dreams
and tease you
What if I were to rob your eyes
of sleep?
I will bring you into my dreams
and tease you
What if I were to rob your eyes
of sleep?
What if my heart were to
dwell in your eyes?
...
I will lay my heart at your feet,
swooning
What if I still won't comfort you
in any way?
I will lay my heart at your feet,
swooning
What if I still won't comfort you
in any way?
What if my heart were to
dwell in your eyes?
What if I close my eyes
and punish your heart?
What if my heart were to
dwell in your eyes?
- How have you been?
- I'm alive
- I would love to see you happy
- Thank you
Don't worry, I have learnt
how to be happy
Has another girl been teaching you?
Another girl? One was enough
for a lifetime
I don't want such suffering again
You mean you have erased
your first love?
I should have
...
I completely forgot...
I was going up
Lady, won't you let us close?
Three hours you've waited
Who for?
Does Mr Vijay come here often?
He did, but not lately.
Any message for him?
Why whisper sweetly to the boy?
I am here, too
Have you found them?
What do you think?
Vijay calls them his poetry
I've read them, they're fine poems
OK
Why not publish a few?
- Are you mad?
- What?
You should know we publish famous
poets, not the trash of novices
Fill the blank space with
a soap advertisement
Yes, Vijay?
What do you want?
Yes. This trash of a novice...
may I take it away?
Sure
- Vijay
- Yes
Are you free tomorrow evening?
Yes
Come and lend a hand at
a party in my house
I'll be there
...
- Did you see that, Juhi?
- What?
What I am observing
What do you see?
You see but you refuse to
All I see if your silly face
Really?
Keep looking!
- Did your heart miss a beat?
- Yes
Let it race a little more
- My heart is getting confused
- Confused? Or stirred?
No way!
No?
Juhi, be cross with me
as much as you like...
but who will care for you
in your old age?
God will
Don't talk of Him, or a coconut
will fall on your head
If you want a secure future,
listen to me
If I listen to you,
I'll starve to death
You barely feed yourself,
how can you feed me?
You can have my share
My hunger will be satisfied
just by seeing you in my home
- Really, Sattar?
- Abdul Sattar
Abdul Sattar, do you love me
that much?
When do we marry?
Stop, you idiot!
Did You hear that? No, nothing
No coconut
Where is your husband?
He's unwell. He wanted me to take
him to hospital, but I put it off
How could I miss such a party?
...
Thank you. How kind of you
Haven't you brought your son?
No
Vijay
How did you find my address?
Your address? Do you live here?
Yes. Let's go outside
Mr Ghosh told me to come
Do you know him?
I work for him. And you?
I am his...
Who is the most talented poet here?
All are good, but the man
in the black jacket...
Don't tell him about us.
Understand?
He's considered to be
the greatest of poets
Excuse me
I disagree
Poetry about the nation's progress
is better than empty love poems
Gentlemen, stop this argument for
once; the drinks are here
Don't bother, dear.
What are servants for?
Vijay.
Why are you waiting? Serve
How could I tell her of
my sad story of love?
What would I say?
How would I say it?
Not a word escaped my lips
And tears welled in my eyes
Wonderful! Wow!
In the assembly of the ecstatic
In the gathering of the discerning
As they sat clasping
the cup of wine
I quaffed the wine,
I spilled drops, too
As they sat clasping
the cup of wine
I quaffed the wine,
I spilled drops, too
- Wonderful! Wow!
- Well said!
The disquiet of my feelings
came to my rescue at last
Perceiving my distressed state,
at last she deigned to love me
- Wonderful! Wow!
- Well said!
Who are the fortunate ones...
who love and are loved
in return?
What an appreciative house!
Even your servants are poets
I'll see to the food
Poetry is not the sole prerogative
of the rich
What were you saying, sir?
Why so silent? Pray continue
Who are the fortunate ones...
who love and are loved
in return?
When I asked for flowers,
I was given a garland of thorns
Who are the fortunate ones...
who love and are loved
in return?
...
When I searched for a world
of happiness...
a forlorn, dusty path
lay before me
When I searched for a world
of happiness...
a forlorn, dusty path
lay before me
When I sought songs of desire...
frozen sighs were offered to me
The ones who consoled me only
redoubled my heart's burdens
When I asked for flowers,
I was given a garland of thorns
Who are the fortunate ones
who love and are loved in return?
...
Parted from me...
Companions parted from me,
having shared fleeting moments
Who has the time to clasp
a pining lover's hand?
I have found my shadow
often weary of me
When I asked for flowers,
I was given a garland of thorns
Who are the fortunate ones
who love and are loved in return?
...
If this is called living,
then I'll live my life somehow
I will not complain,
I'll seal my lips
I'll swallow my tears
Why would I fear sorrow when
I encounter it countless times?
When I asked for flowers,
I was given a garland of thorns
Who are the fortunate ones...
who love and are loved
in return?
Wonderful! Excellent!
What were you saying?
...
I have come to see you
Yes
Mr Ghosh has gone to the
board meeting
You shouldn't have come
I have been very upset
since the party
You bear me many grudges,
don't you?
No, Meena. I bear no grudge
against anyone
So why did you sing that
heart-rending poem?
...
You revived my desires
Forget the past, Meena
I was trying to forget
I had remoulded my life.
I had controlled my heart
Why return to my life?
When did I ever leave your life?
You left me
Do not try to correct
your first mistake...
with another mistake, Meena
I made no mistake
Besides love, a sensible woman
needs the comfort of a home
She needs a little wealth
For those things I...
You married Mr Ghosh.
Selling your love for wealth
Don't accuse me wrongly
I loved you, but you were poor
and unemployed
In life, besides poetry and love
there is hunger, too
When you couldn't feed yourself
how could you bear my burden?
You never gave me the chance
When a man has responsibilities,
he learns to shoulder them
Don't deceive yourself, Meena;
you sought wealth and position
You wanted standing in the world
You have all that now, but you
regret it all. You know why?
Because you have always been
selfish
You left without caring
how unhappy I would be
And now you want your husband
to be unhappy
Life's real joy is found in
making others happy
You never understood that;
that's why you're unhappy
...
Wonderful! My wife's no better
than a streetwalker
You misunderstand. Vijay and I
hardly know each other
Stop fooling me!
How long has this been going on?
- I hardly know him
- Is that so?
Yes
...
If you won't admit it, let's see
how upset you are when I sack him
...
- Give me my money
- I earn my money the hard way
Scoundrel! Pay up
Scoundrel?
Constable!
...
Save me, do something
You? What's wrong?
You!
Sir, has a girl run this way?
No
Who is she?
My wife
Sorry, sir, I made a mistake
What's your name?
You...
Gulab
It's all clear now.
You can go safely
O friends!
Having endured the torment
of a long separation
Radha was overcome
with weariness
So one day she went to
her enchanting Krishna...
and she said:
Today, beloved, hold me in Your
arms, my life will be fulfilled
Ease the ache in my heart,
cool the fire in my body
Today, beloved, hold me in Your
arms, my life will be fulfilled
...
My hapless eyes have been
sleepless for countless years
Without You,
no place pleases me
I see no happiness ahead
Sorrow follows me everywhere.
Without You, the world is lonely
O my beloved, the nectar of love
O my beloved...
Let the nectar of love overflow,
so the world floods with feeling
Today, beloved, hold me in Your
arms, my life will be fulfilled
...
Make me Your own
Take me in Your arms. I have
been born again and again to serve You
Make me Your own
Take me in Your arms. I have
been born again and again to serve You
Slake the thirst in me
O beautiful Krishna,
slake the thirst in me
thirst consumes me to the depths
O my beloved, the nectar of love
O my beloved...
Let the nectar of love overflow,
so the world floods with feeling
Hold me in Your arms, beloved,
my life will be fulfilled
Ease the ache in my heart,
cool the fire in my body
Hold me in Your arms, beloved,
my life will be fulfilled
...
Gulabo, there's a millionaire
in the car. Come with me
Go away. I'm not coming
You won't? I've promised him.
Get up!
Let go
You won't obey me?
...
Pick up your cap!
I used my weak hand,
or else your face would be putty
Be seated.
This park belongs to me.
If anyone bullies you, call for me
I'll leave my clients
and come running
Where are you?
- Did you say something, Sattar?
- No. Who was talking?
I get it. What do You think?
She's gone?
- Who is he?
- Who?
I wouldn't need to ask if I knew
A postcard's contents can be
guessed at a glance
But I, a masseur, can read
between the lines
Your faraway look, oblivious to
the man sitting next to you
Deaf to a word.
Sure signs that you're in love
Slipping away is another sign
Tell me truly who he is
A poet
I have a poet friend.
What's your poet's name?
Vijay
That's my friend's name.
I'll ask him if he knows another Vijay
- Maybe they're the same person
- Not possible
Maybe they are.
I'll ask him what's the mix-up
Brothers, is everything all right?
What brings you here?
What's it to you if someone's dead?
Carry on loafing around
Who died?
- Whose last rites do you observe?
- Mother's
Mother?
Brother...
Don't call me brother.
We tolerated you because of her
Now she's dead, you're dead for us
Where will you go on
an empty stomach?
Who will look after you?
I don't want to stay in this house
for another minute
Let's see you dance.
I'll play the drums for you
Ask your friend to join us
Drink it! I'd even drink poison
for her if she told me to
Same here
He's shy
Come, sir, drink up. For my sake
Strange man.
Is he a man or a mouse?
He looks as if his grandmother died
...
He's a beginner, but he
finished it off in one go
You're a tiger!
When did you start drinking?
Sorrow became unbearable
In my anxiety I drank
This heart of mine
was so helpless
Out of pity for it I drank
The world has spurned me...
So he's a poet, too?
Indeed. He's composed
over 500 poems
The world has spurned me
countless times
Today I spurned the whole world...
and drank
...
- Bijli
Where are you going?
...
My child is ill
Damn your child! I need you, too
Tend to us first,
then see to your child
Here.
Start the music
These lanes, these houses
of auctioned pleasure
These ravaged caravans of life
Where are they, the guardians of dignity?
Where are those who claim to be
proud of India?
These twisting lanes, this infamous market
These anonymous men, this clinking of coins
This trading of chastity,
this insistent haggling
Where are those who claim to be
proud of India?
These age-old, dreamless, dreaded lanes
These crushed, pallid, half-open buds
This selling of sham celebrations
Where are those who claim to be
proud of India?
...
Dancing bells, chimes from latticed windows
The tablas play over weary breaths
...
These soulless rooms, echo with coughing
Where are those who claim to be
proud of India?
These garlands, these paan spittle stains
These shameless glances, these crude remarks
These wilting bodies, these ailing faces
Where are those who claim to be
proud of India?
Old men have passed through here,
young men, too
Sturdy sons, fathers and husbands, too
These are wives and sisters and mothers, too
Where are those who claim to be
proud of India?
This daughter of Eve seeks help
The kin of Yashoda, the daughter of Radha
The people of the Prophet,
the daughter of Zulekha
Where are those who claim to be
proud of India?
Summon the leaders of this land
Show them these alleys, these lanes,
this sight
Summon those who claim to be proud of India
Where are those who claim to be
proud of India?
Mr. Vijay.
Who is it?
It's you, Gulab.
Come with me.
Taking pity on me again?
Today I am not hungry.
I have drowned hunger in drink.
I have drunk a lot.
I've drunk my joys and sorrows,
I have swallowed everything.
Where are you taking me?
Come to my house, you need to rest.
Leave when you feel better.
Should I leave when I feel better?
I'll feel better when
I've left this world, Gulab.
Everyone has gone. My job has gone.
My mother has gone, too. Forever.
So what am I doing here?
Why am I alive, Gulab?
Don't talk like that.
The world needs you and your poetry.
The world needs nobody.
I tried so hard to make my poetry
reach the world.
But do you know how the world valued it?
Waste paper sold for ten annas.
My life is valued at ten annas, Gulab.
You want me to stay alive
for those ten annas?
Don't lose courage.
Others will stand by you in life.
Meena, for instance.
Meena?
How do you know her?
Her name was on your file of poems.
Who is Meena?
Meena.
A high-society, decent woman...
who loves when it pleases her...
and sells love for a comfortable life.
But why such an interest in her?
You were interested in her. That's why.
You mean you...no, forget me.
You will get nothing from me but sorrow.
I've never been able to make anyone happy.
Mr. Vijay! Mr. Vijay!
Juhi! Juhi!
You'll publish them?
Why? Am I crazy? Call that poetry?
The world needs you and your poetry.
You should know we publish famous
poets, not the trash of novices.
When you couldn't feed yourself,
how could you bear my burden?
Father has gone and with him his duty.
It wasn't our wish that our parents
produced such a good-for-nothing.
...
Have you read about the poet's suicide?
I knew him. I wonder what troubled him.
Serve us tea.
"Tragic Death of a Young Poet"
"A young man jumped in front
of the Burdwan night train
"His body was so badly mutilated,
identifying him was impossible
"A letter was found in the young man's pocket
"It contained a poem.
His last message to the world.
"The poet's name...
was Vijay."
...
Are you all right, dear?
Hmm.
Gulabo.
What's wrong, Sattar?
Salutations Ma'am!
SHADOWS
Send her in.
Go in.
Who are you?
Gulab.
Where from?
Sona...from Dharmtallah
Give me that file of poems.
So you know it contains poems.
Then you'll know they are beautiful.
I've come to get them published.
You came to show them to my husband?
What's your price?
- You'll publish them? - Maybe.
Name your price.
Price?
I haven't come to sell them,
I've brought them for publishing.
These poems are very precious to you, right?
- How did you know Vijay? - By good fortune.
What was your relationship with him?
Relationship?
I want to know how a fine man
like him met a good lady like you.
By good fortune.
You sell much for money,
why do you refuse to sell these poems?
Are you Meena?
My husband will be here any time.
You have to sell these poems to me.
- I'll pay 1,000 rupees, 2,000..., 3000...
- Not even 30,000
- What's that? - Nothing
Show me
"For Meena...
"whose memory lives in every word."
I brought them to have them published.
What is that?
My life savings.
I can't give more than this
for their publication.
It's vital to me that they're published.
If you will publish them,
I'll be eternally grateful to you.
...
All sold out.
A fine bookseller!
We want Vijay's book. You don't have it?
All sold out.
There's a new edition,
how can it be sold out?
You're selling it "under the counter."
Have the third edition tomorrow,
or we'll burn your shop! Get it?
If only you could see this with your own eyes.
- Good morning. - Good morning, doctor.
Have you established his identity?
No, he hasn't spoken since he was admitted.
Hello.
How are you today?
Let me know at once if he speaks.
Sure.
I can't pay more than 5,000 for them.
They're by Vijay, but the price is too high.
Do you want to cream off all
the profit and leave me nothing?
Then name a sensible price. Show some respect.
Sir, are rare treasures ever sold?
Vijay's last, unique poems.
I'll share fifty-fifty.
Impossible. I can't pay that much.
Nice to have met you.
Wait. You're a strange man.
My last offer: twenty-five per cent
or you may leave.
I wouldn't like you to think I'm unreasonable.
Here. Let's shake hands.
Scoundrel.
The shadows of thoughts and dreams stir
I adorn your hair with flowers
Your eyes lower, full of feeling
I do now know what I will say today?
My lips are parched, my voice is hesitant
The shadows of thoughts and dreams stir
I hold your soft arms in an embrace
My lips cast a shadow on your lips
You are sure we will never be parted
I guess we were one, but still strangers
The shadows of thoughts and dreams stir
"Shadows"?
Doctor. Doctor.
My poems. All the poems are mine!
This is my book
Of course. But what is your name?
My name is Vijay. See?
This book was written by me.
The Vijay who wrote this book is long dead.
Think carefully, what is your name?
Why don't you believe me? I am Vijay.
I tell you I am Vijay!
Why have you kept me here?
Let me go!
I think he has lost his mind
Telephone Doctor Sen at once.
- Sir. - Sir.
- Sir. - Please, sir.
Yes
So you are Vijay's brothers?
- His older brothers. - I am the eldest
What do you want of me?
- Tell him. - No you go ahead.
- Shall I tell him? - Yes.
All right. No you go ahead.
...
I asked what you want.
Well, I brought up Vijay and educated him.
Fed him with great affection.
I made him capable of being someone one day.
So did I.
My time is precious. Get to the point.
The point is, we're here to
collect some money from you.
What nonsense.
Are you sane?
We are the rightful heirs to all his property
including his songs and poems.
We have a legal right to the money
you are gaining from his works.
We don't want all.
We won't object to getting a share of it.
Yes.
I don't know you and I didn't
get the poems from you.
You won't get a penny. Understand?
...
Come in.
That's him.
No, it isn't Vijay.
Shyam!
That's right. He's not Vijay.
So you want a share in the profits?
Yes.
The rightful claimant is Vijay.
He's alive.
What?
Vijay is alive.
He's alive?
You must be joking.
I never joke.
However, you will get a share of the profit.
Two per cent, on condition that
you refuse to identify Vijay.
What? Why shouldn't we identify our brother?
- Do you consider us so nasty?
- Are we so low?
For a mere two per cent?
Make it sixteen per cent.
You scoundrel.
Very well.
Mr Ghosh is a real gentleman.
Massage! Oil massage!
- Massage! Oil massage! - Sattar.
...
A ghost! Lord, please make it vanish!
Lord, please make it vanish!
- Gone! - Sattar...
Let go of my neck! It isn't mine.
It's me. Vijay.
Look at me.
So you aren't dead yet?
He's really alive.
I've been forcibly detained.
- I see. - Get me out somehow.
...
What do you want?
I want to whirl my hands on your
head, only if you agree.
Massage!
Hold your cap.
If your head reels with pain,
or your heart sinks in gloom
Don't fret, leave it to me,
I'll make things right soon
Massage, oil massage
If your head reels with pain,
or your heart sinks in gloom
Don't fret, leave it to me,
I'll make things right soon
...
Brother.
Don't you recognize me?
I'm your brother Vijay.
Why are you so quiet?
Don't you want to recognize me, either?
Are you mad?
Vijay's dead.
Pushing your way in here, with the
nerve to say you're our brother.
As if you're my brother. Get out! Hurry!
Where are you heading?
To commemorate Vijay's death
anniversary. Are you coming, too?
Of course. Vijay was a great poet
and a friend.
Did you really know Vijay?
Yes.
Sit with me.
OK.
Don't block the way, move aside.
He was a fine poet.
A gem of a man.
He often used to come to me for help.
But for me, he would have died
six months earlier.
- How? - Of starvation.
Oh! I see.
- Hurry, or we won't get a seat. - OK.
Ladies and gentlemen, as you all know...
we are here to commemorate
poet laureate Vijay's death.
On this day last year...
the world's great poet was taken
from us in that terrible moment.
If it were possible...
I would have given my fortune
and my life to save Vijay.
But that could not be.
Why? Because of you all.
It's said he took his own life,
but in fact, you killed him.
If only he were alive, he would see
the world which made him starve...
is now ready to shower wealth upon him.
The world in which he was unknown...
is ready to crown him king of
hearts, crown him with glory.
It would rescue him from poverty
and install him in a palace.
This world of palaces, of thrones, of crowns
This world of division, enemy of man
This world of blind custom, hungry for wealth
Would I care if such a world were mine?
...
Bodies wounded, souls thirsty
Confusion in eyes, despondency in hearts
Is this a world or a place of bewilderment?
Would I care if such a world were mine?
...
Here a man's life is a plaything
Here live worshippers of the dead
Here life has no value, death comes cheaper
Would I care if such a world were mine?
...
Youth strays into crime
Young bodies are adorned for the marketplace
Here love is another name for trade
Would I care if such a world were mine?
...
This world where man counts for nothing
Loyalty and friendship count for nothing
Where love has no importance
Would I care if such a world were mine?
...
Burn it, blow this world away
Take this world away from my sight
Take charge of this world, you can keep it
Would I care if such a world were mine?
...
Stop his brothers, give what they want,
but they mustn't identify him.
Mr Ghosh, all your money cannot
stop Vijay being identified now.
How many will you silence?
No expense spared, I will buy everyone...
but I don't want it proved that he's Vijay
or else our name is mud, we'll be finished.
Save yourself. I know how to save my own neck.
What do you mean?
You think you'll get away with it
so easily? You denied him once.
I sway with the wind; I followed
you when it was in my interest.
Now I'll ally Vijay to a better interest.
- You scoundrel. Get out. - See you.
- See you. - I said, get out
Have you won the lottery?
Not yet, but I have my hands on
the king of fame.
I've got Vijay; I'll earn millions
from publishing his poems.
...
Well done, Sheikh!
You found a real gold mine, but do
you think you'll mine it all alone?
You'll share it with me.
Idiots! What are you gawking at? Get out!
Get out!
You are most unreasonable, young man.
- To whom have I the honor?
- No honor is high enough for me.
I can identify Vijay if I so choose...
and if I don't, he'll be
shut away in a mental asylum
Are you head of state to lock him away?
His brothers will identify him.
Of course we will. He's my brother, after all.
- He may not care about us.
- Others may have profited.
- But he is our blood.
- Why shouldn't we identify him?
Well said! That answers this joker.
See that? Brothers are brothers!
- I spent 5,000 on his education.
- 4,000 feeding him.
If we'd loaned that at interest,
we'd have 15,000 now.
Will you pay us 15,000 to identify him?
Fifteen thousand?
Yes. Fifteen thousand.
Gentlemen, but you have your
precious brother back.
What more could you want?
Old man, we don't want a brother,
we want money.
We can't eat him.
Vijay, my brother!
...
Is he Vijay? What proof have you?
Soon you'll say I'm not Sattar.
Do we believe him?
Then who came under the train?
We prove it.
- We are his brothers.
- The neighborhood knows that.
We say he is Vijay.
I prove it.
And I confirm he is Vijay, my boyhood friend.
The poet laureate Vijay!
Here a man's death
is valued more than his life
Would I care if such a world were mine?
- Long live! - The poet laureate Vijay!
Gentlemen...
Be quiet. Vijay will speak.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The Vijay you are ready to
open your arms to...
the Vijay for whom you shout slogans...
I am not that Vijay.
What?
Vijay.
I'm not Vijay.
If you aren't Vijay, why deceive us?
I always said he was an imposter.
A publicity-seeker.
Hit him!
...
Burn it, destroy this world
Take this world away from my sight
This world belongs to you, you can keep it
...
Are you mad? Stop them!
There is still time, tell them you are Vijay.
They have all come because of you,
why don't you explain to them?
I am not that Vijay. He has been long dead.
What are you saying?
Be sensible. Sheikh, your brothers
and friends say that you are Vijay.
Friends?
They are not my friends.
They're the friends of wealth.
Once they refused to identify me.
But now...
To take revenge on a few false
friends, why turn against yourself?
Why refuse fame and fortune?
If you must, reject your brothers,
reject those you begrudge.
I complain against no one...
not against any human being.
I complain against a society that
tears away a man's compassion.
That makes a brother a stranger,
a friend an enemy for self-interest.
I complain against a culture,
a world which worships the dead...
and tramples the living underfoot.
Where it is considered cowardice
to cry for the suffering of others.
Where it is considered weakness
to respect others.
In such an atmosphere, I shall
never find peace, Meena.
I shall never find peace.
That is why I am going far away.
Juhi, someone called out to me.
No one called. Go to sleep.
Gulabo, where are you going? You're feverish.
Someone called me. Let me go.
I am going far away, Gulab.
Where?
To a place where I shall not
have to go any further.
Is that what you came to say?
Will you come with me?