Long live Mian Tansen!
Long live the maestro!
Disperse
Tell the guards at the door
there must be no disturbance
Tell the constable, there must be
no music playing around the palace
l need complete silence
Wonderful maestro, wonderful!
l could die to hear that tune
Sounds like thundering clouds.
- Thunderous rainclouds!
Wonderful modulation!
Wonderful! Maestro, you are our Tansen!
There's music even in the way you cough
Bless you
Go on, maestro!
Stop singing!
- Why should l stop?
l have my admirers too.
- lf you want to sing, go elsewhere
You are not to create any disturbance.
- Not even breathe?
Mind your tongue! The court musician
Mian Tansen, is scoring a new Raga
You will not scream into his ears.
- l know all about scoring music!
Take the Raga Todi, change a few notes
and he creates music! Mian's Todi
Twist Raga Malhar, and he scores
Mian's Malhar!
Now he's adding a twist to Raga Kanara
to create Darbari Kanara. Get lost!
Silence! Create trouble, and you will
be forbidden to sing in this area!
Here come the bards.
Let's see you stop them!
Stop! Singing isn't allowed here
This isn't a song. This is a prayer.
- Whatever! Mian Tansen is scoring music
Singing in this area is forbidden.
By his orders!
Music is the essence of life.
Never can there be any restrictions
What are you staring at?
Stop them!
We are free men!
Do not mess with us
Son...
Baiju, my son...
My son...
you must never forget
what happened
lf ever time favours you...
you must take revenge against Tansen
for your father
You must avenge!
Your word! Give me your word, son!
Revenge!
That boy is stealing a sword!
Take the sword
- Thief!
Let him be
Why are you hurting a child?
- Who is he? He was stealing a sword
l'm no thief!
l am a very learned musician's son
Understand?
- And what've you learnt but stealing?
Why not? l have learnt all the Ragas
But why were you stealing a sword?
- l have to avenge my father's murder!
What an evil thing to say!
Against whom do you seek revenge?
A very big... prominent...
This boy is very dangerous!
He should be arrested
Just an innocent child, going wayward
because he's angry and unhappy
l'll bring him around
Come son
There's our village...
across the Yamuna
Mohan
Nice. lt takes a well-cultured voice
to deliver musical notes while talking
Who taught you singing, son?
l used to live in Gujarat
ln a village called Chapaner
My father was a bard.
He had mastery over music
He was taking me
to Haridas Swamy...
in Vrindavan for studying music. But...
Haridas Swamy? Tansen's guru?
Tansen!
Never mind, son
So what if your father is no more?
l will teach you music
Here comes Gauri
You always play your fiddle.
Where did you pick up a songster?
Songster...?
Whom was he calling out to?
- You answered his call
He answered yours. He heard your call
and he forgot he's mourning his father
Come
Come son
l won't let him miss his father.
What's his name?
Baijnath
l'll call him Baiju. Big-sounding names
are no good for village folks
What good will Baiju do?
- Baiju would help me row my boat
Master Baijnath wouldn't even
care to find out...
whether Gauri is tired of rowing
And it's going to be smooth sailing
for Gauri
Careful, my child
Greetings, Pundit. Back from Agra?
With this Tansen in tow!
No, no!
You don't know how to swim?
He knows only how to drown
ln the seas that is music,
there are many who will swim...
few are they who will dive deep.
You will see it for yourself, Mohan
Like Mian Tansen, this boy too will
become famous for his love of music
No! Not like Tansen!
- We'll even forget Tansen for you
On this hillock, here by
the banks of the Yamuna...
we built sand castles
when we were children
And here today in our youth,
dreams light up our lives
Never let the lights go out, Baiju
Which means that the light
is about to go out of your life
She's engaged to someone,
and she's marrying someomne else!
This is a matter of family honour!
This is no joke!
Something ought to be done!
Say it!
- What more have l to say?
She has said what
she was to have said!
Use this
Hurry up!
Can you make out a stick from a fiddle?
- Want me to tell you?
One plays music when plucked.
The other plays pluck on your head
The strings of fiddle win hearts over.
You can't beat Baiju with the stick
Nor can you win over Gauri.
- Forget it, Gauri
Look at this girl! Not ashamed a bit!
All day, she's with this boy!
Gauri, these days...
These days the cow is giving
very little milk
No wonder, she's going wayward
lsn't that so?
- No!
No...?
- Oh all right
Gauri, you aren't a child anymore.
You're a grown-up now. Understand?
What's the big difference?
Mohan, you better keep
your girl on a leash
All day, she's wandering around
with Baiju
She's going to lead the other girls
in the village astray
Were the other girls to be like Gauri,
we'd kill them, wouldn't we?
But Mohan would also have to lose face
Did you hear what the difference is?
And how did this shameless fellow
end up in our village?
No one even knows his caste
or his family!
What are you lost in, son?
You've taken up the Veena
after long time. Let's hear
The strings are broken.
- You can have new strings
l've forgotten my melodies.
- Forgotten your melodies?
Then how on earth will you make
a famous musician?
By dint of your blessings,
l surely will
lt's this earth that's taking
my music away
Gauri, will you row me over too?
Are you looking for something?
- Journey's end
There's a storm raging around us.
- And you've lost your way?
No! l want to get away from you.
My father will row you over
You're back to rowing after
so many days. Where have you been?
l had painted my hands with henna.
lf l rowed, the henna would wear off
Let me take a look
- l want to stay away from everyone!
For how long?
Till you've counted all the stars
in the skies for me
Stars?
Done.
- How? lt's daytime now
For you. When you're cross with me,
it becomes as dark as the night
You make me see stars even in the day!
l know all this.
Stop flattering me
Gauri, don't stay away from me.
You'll drive me mad!
They are right when they say
that like the Pundit...
you know nothing beyond music.
- Liars! l know everything
Like what?
- Outside music...
you are everything. Without you,
my song is only half-sung
You are my music, Gauri
Don't you talk these deep-meaning
things. l could drown!
You know how to swim.
Drowning is my lot
A drowning man might take
a swimmer down with him
Pundit, everyone in the village
knows about Gauri and Baiju
Time was when he was
seething with vengeance.
Now he has turned around
What has Baiju, that l haven't?
- Everything! Nose, ears, arms...
stomach, waist, everything.
Only fatter, so what?
Shut up! l lack only one thing.
l cannot sing!
And Gauri is going for a song!
- What an metaphor! Well said!
The hell with metaphors!
l'm losing her!
For Gauri's sake,
l must learn how to sing
My foe!
- Singing, you must learn
Wait...
ln Delhi...? No, not Delhi
Not there...
not there either
Yes, now l remember!
l know of a maestro in Agra
who could teach you
Never mind... forget it.
Forget what?
- No, he won't teach you
Now are you going to tell me, or not?
- He isn't going to teach you
Not teach me... what?
- He won't
l got it. He won't teach me.
- Who...?
Shall l tell you who
you're talking about?
You mean Tansen?
- Who's Tansen?
l'm talking about another maestro.
What a master!
He sweeps over the bow
You moron! Will you mention a name?
He hasn't a single name, so to say
His mother used to call him Lallu.
His father called him Ghasitu
The Emperor has given him
so many accolades
The Maestro of Maestros!
The Creator of Music!
The Master of the Sarangi!
Mian Huzoor Khan
Alias Ustad Ghasit Khan
(Ustad - Maestro)
Then l shall lay down all my wealth
at the feet of Ustad Ghasit Khan
Now go and get Ustad Ghasit Khan here
My lover waits on the hillock.
Here l am on the banks of the Yamuna
But l cannot go to see him
My feet are chained
Gauri, aren't you coming to the well?
You must! Today's the Spring Fest.
Poor thing, she doesn't
step out of the house these days
He's calling you.
Why don't you go?
You go. He's calling you
lf l go to him, you'll kill me!
- She's dying, poor thing
How will she kill someone?
- Poor thing
l warn you!
- About what?
You're nuts!
Just you wait!
The jar is empty!
What's she churning?
Her own heart
- Don't you tease me!
Don't you tease!
Are we teasing you?
lt's he who has been calling you
Wait
Go on
For my sake.
- Your sake? Get lost!
lf she won't go, we'll bring
him here. Let's go
No!
Who are you looking for?
Well...
The poor fellow is looking
for something he has lost
Not here. He lost something on
the hillock on the banks of the Yamuna
And look where he comes looking!
Then you know what l've lost?
Basanti is hiding what you've lost.
- l'd tell, for a reward
Are you trying to skin me?
You want something?
- l just wanted to ask...
My father isn't at home
Hello
My greetings
Where's the Ustad?
Can't you hear?
He's scoring music
A new Raga!
What Raga would this be?
Yes, the Coughing Raga!
But why behind closed doors?
- Singing here is forbidden
Only someone who sings better than
Mian Tansen can sing here
What if there be someone
who sings better than him?
He will have to enter into contest
with Mian Tansen
But if...
- lf he wins...
Tansen will kill himself.
- What a strange law!
Who is this impudent fool?
- l am, Ustad
Moron! Do you know how deep
music can strike?
Deeper than the shoe bites!
Don't l know that!
Shut up, you rogue!
You've ruined my exercise
Now what do you want?
- My master is a rich man
He wants you to teach him music.
- To hell with your master!
Am l a singer sitting
in a marketplace?
lf you're looking for a tutor,
move ahead
Out there is Tansen's house
How am l concerned about Tansen?
l worship the Creator of Music!
He looks like a smart boy.
A connoisseur
Who knows not Ghasit Khan's melodies?
- You will be paid whatever you wish
Very well. l will come.
Arrange for two horses
ls your wife coming along too?
- You moron!
l ride one horse,
and my Sarangi rides the other.
That's my style
lf you disagree, then move ahead.
Tansen lives up the sreet
l'm no court singer living off
the Emperor
l'm a singer of erudition.
l will remain what l am
And l will remain what l am!
Narpat, are you preparing
for the wedding?
Why not? l'm waiting for
Ustad Ghasit Khan
No sooner than he arrives,
l'm going to get married
To the Ustad?
- Get lost!
Not the Ustad. Gauri
Once l've learnt how to sing
Now when is the Ustad coming?
- Next summer
Shut up! By next summer,
l'm going to be married
And while Ghasit Khan is teaching him
how to sing...
Gauri will be up there on the hillock
teaching Baiju new Ragas
What nonsense!
Gauri has stopped seeing Baiju.
- By day. Not in the nights
ln the nights?
Where is Gauri's father?
Mohan!
So...?
- What happened?
ls that so?
- What's is it?
What a shame!
- About what?
Every night, Gauri goes up the hillock
to meet Baiju
Drown in shame!
l'll break the bones of the man who
spreads canards about my daughter
And never mind who he might be!
l'm calling in the village council
to decide about this!
Where the hell is she?
Pundit...
At this hour...?
- Where's Baiju?
He should be on the hillock
by the river
Come dusk, and he goes to
the hillock with his Veena
He returns only very late at night.
He is so devoted to music
Someday, he will challenge Tansen.
You will see
But Pundit...
- To tell you the truth...
more than me, it's Gauri who is
to be credited for his success
l am the teacher.
Gauri is his inspiration
Every day, she sits before him.
He composes for Gauri
And Gauri inspires him
to reach for the skies
So what l am hearing is true?
- True, and beyond doubt
l have been there, and l have seen
for myself several times
You yourself?
But who is to stop tongues from
wagging? How will l face the council?
l have to marry Gauri off as soon
as l can to Narpat
Gauri is married already.
To Baiju
To Baiju...?
- Yes
Baiju is the composer.
Gauri is his music
Baiju is the singer.
Gauri is his song
Baiju is the melody.
Gauri is his Veena
And where Gauri is his music,
Baiju is her crescendo
The union of the two of them
is the doing...
of that artiste whose art
inspires pure, unbeguiled love
Consider this a marriage, Mohan.
No one can set them apart
The council might.
l have given Narpat my word
lf you go back on your word,
you will have to pay a fine
But if try to take the light away
from the lamp...
the lamp will be extinguished,
and light will be no more
And there will be darkness
all around
l'll pay the fine, l will!
Gauri is the light of my life
And Baiju is the light
of Gauri's life
No one will set them apart.
No one
Where are you going
so late at night?
You...?
- Yes
Caught you!
Have you lost something
on this hillock?
Your brains is what you've lost!
All for nothing you told my father...
that l come to this hillock every night
to meet Baiju!
Now he's coming after me with a sword!
l'm running away from this village!
Listen...
Wait Gauri, stop!
What a fool l've been to be carried
away with what the villagers say
Come Gauri, l'll reason
with your father
No! He's going to kill you!
That must be him!
We've reached our village
This is called ''The Gate to Agra''
Come
- Stop
My master's house isn't far away.
- Set his house on fire!
Why?
- He's a cad and a knave!
lmpudent ass!
- Whom are you all praise for?
Shut up! Your master should've waited
outside the village to welcome me
And he should've bowed before me
l'm not a musician...
who goes to people's houses asking
for bows, like court musicians
l'm an erudite musician!
Understand?
My master mustn't have expected
the maestro to arrive at night
Fool, don't you know that
l was born at night?
And at night l shall die.
- Do not speak of dying Ustad!
You're still in the prime
of your youth
l'll inform my master in a trice,
while you water the horses
Gauri, listen!
Listen to me, why are you
getting angry?
But Narpat...
- Listen to me
lf your father comes by, tell him
that you're here to hear me sing
l'll take care of everything.
Now let me sing a song for you
Do you know what this Raga is?
''Sarkari Kanara''
Damnation! Which fool is that,
singing out of tune?
Who the hell is that?
Moron! Mules don't sing!
Drop that Tanpura!
Don't be the murder of music!
- You old fool!
l'm going to smash this Tanpura
on your head! Bloody ox!
Am l an ox?
- Am l a mule?
Undoubtedly! A complete ass...
bereft of any sense of music!
Uncouth! Get lost! Or l'm going
to hang you upside down!
Such impudence! What a pest!
My father has said yes!
Father said yes!
Ya Allah! What have
l landed myself in?
2000 gold Ashrafie for our Chief.
Else, we'll burn this village down
Only last year you looted us
of 2000 gold Ashrafie
We will come every year
to collect this tax
Tax? But we pay our taxes
to Raja Man Singh
How can we pay taxes to both of you?
- Say what you want to our Chief
The tax goes to ones who can collect.
Pay up 2000 gold Ashrafie
Else, at the sounding of this gun,
this village is going to be plundered
Have mercy on us!
Please reduce the amount
Those who rob don't make deals
Where are we to find so much?
You will have to come with us
With you?
- Not a bad deal, singer
You've saved your village from carnage
for very little a price
What are you thinking?
You have won everything
l have lost something
Say, do you agree?
Agreed
No Baiju, no!
l won't let you go! Ever!
Plunder tha place!
We aren't staying here forever
Stop! l'm coming with you.
- You can't!
l have to, Gauri.
- Never!
You won't, you won't go away Baiju!
Father, please tell her
l'll be back soon
Let him go
Today, Baiju is saving
the whole village
Father... !
- Do not worry, my child
Baiju will certainly come back
But l wasn't able to tell him
what l wanted to say
Fortitude, Father. And give me
your blessings
Baiju! Listen to me Baiju!
Gauri, l'll be back soon
Sit
You didn't recognise my voice?
l do not feel the need to
For once, try to remember
What do you want?
- Only a song
Music that will reverberate
through the emptiness of my life
ln my songs is a calm that will
contain the storms of life
Leave that decision to me.
Only l know...
the storms that lie hidden
in your music
lf my music be storm, build bastions
to withstand the storms
Bastions stronger than a woman's heart
... have you ever known?
The heart of a woman!
But what does it mean for you?
lf at all, you are a fake!
A bandit, a plunderer
Singer, is that what you see
in these eyes?
Ones who plunder homes
cannot steal hearts
Bewitching eyes and a black heart!
Begone!
For you, l have neither song
nor any treasure
Do not insult my love like this.
l am not a bandit
Loot and plunder isn't my calling.
Your village was once my father's fief
Raja Man Singh took it from us
forcibly. He killed my father
l was orphaned! l was in a rage.
l took to the sword
And ever since, l have sworn
to avenge my father
Father...
Father!
lf ever time favours you...
you must take revenge against Tansen
for your father
You must avenge!
Revenge!
Singer, have l hurt you?
Tell me, tell me have l said
anything wrong?
No, l had forgotten.
- What?
l was supposed to have
avenged someone
ln life, it's my prime duty
Gauri's affections made me forget.
You have reminded me
Gauri...?
- That girl back in my village
You sweet words haven't made me forget
her affections
But vengeance fires my emotions now!
- Vengeance?
Yes
From Gauri, l picked up
the fragrance of love
From you, l have taken the
razor-sharp resolve
lf Gauri is my flower,
you are my sword!
Princess, you can give me nothing
but this sword
ls that an excuse for
going back to Gauri?
lf l live, l surely will. But as
of now, l want to forget her love
My father's soul calls me!
Let me go!
Take me along. l might be
able to help you
No, l shall perfom my duty myself
Stop him! He's leaving
No, wait... let him go
The artiste can never be trapped
Who are you?
- l want your head
You are lying
lf what you want could've come
by beheading me...
you would've beheaded me.
Why did you destroy my instrument?
What want of yours is fulfilled?
The sound of your music
was draining my resolve
My sword-arm weakened
You seem to appreciate music
Music isn't only your fief, Tansen!
Not my fief, but music
is surely my life
Young man, no sword may end
Tansen's breath
lf you have resolved
to slay Tansen,...
sing out the pathos in your soul
For that, Tansen would die
Who is this? A rebel? What do you
want done to him? Beheaded?
ln this house, only hearts may bleed.
And that too, for music's sake
How else is he to be punished?
His punishment is to live
for years...
to suffer again and again
at the hands of life
Escort him out
Sing the pathos in your soul
The pathos in my soul
Where do l find it?
ln the mountain echoes?
ln the gurgling streams?
ln the dry desert sands?
No, without a guru, this knowledge
l can never imbibe
Only diamond can cut diamond
The diamond that was polished
at the hands of Haridas Swami
Vrindavan
They say that God's world...
is full of music
From all things God created,
l have tried to seek music
And now, l come to you
For without the Guru,
there is no knowledge
And without knowledge man's quest
is not fulfilled
What do you wish, son?
l wish to imbibe the entire knowledge
of music, for revenge
Music for revenge?
You are mistaken, son
Music relates heart to heart.
Music elevates the soul
Music turns enmity into love
Music doesn't extoll revenge
No! l want revenge. l must!
And through music
So long as you nurse the feeling
of vengeance in your heart...
you can never learn music.
To learn music...
fill your heart with love.
lnstead of hurting others...
fill your heart with pathos.
- Love and pathos l have forgotten
lf you refuse to teach me,
l shall die at your doorstep
Son, fire cannot quench fire.
Water quenches fire
Darkness is not dispelled by darkness.
Light dispels
Hatred cannot end hatred.
Love does it
l give you the symbol of my love
Play this Veena
When the string strike a chord
inside your heart...
when you find peace of mind,
come to me
Whatever l know, l shall teach you
Blessed be the name of The Lord
Lord, l hear of the three reasonances
of Aum upon which rests all of Creation
Aum is the primal sound.
The first to be
Of these three, have come to be
the seven notes
ln these seven notes l wish
to immerse myself
But in the fires in my heart
all seas are dried up
Of life, l have received nothing.
My guru has rejected me
Now l come unto Thee
Here, l sit before Thee
To stir Your heart of stone
Or l shall be silenced forever
But even after l have died,
my ashes will await resurrection
That day too, l shall tell You
the same, Lord
Give me music!
Give me music, give me music!
''You and l, we shall consummate
our love''
Whither consummation?
Baiju, where are you?
Here it was that you sang
that immortal song of love
lt was here you swore,
here you made your promises
Have you forgotten?
''Do not lose heart, son''
l am far away from you.
But my soul is with you
Rise and sing
Sing the Lalit
lmagine the fair maiden bedecked
in flowers, with a smile on her face
Her eyes, like lotus petals,
sing the Lalit
This is the Gaur Malhar
Sung to the accompaniment of
the melodious Sarangi of Gaur
Sing along with the pattering
of the rain, The Gaur Malhar
This is the Puriya
Resplendent in regal finery,
the bejewelled crown, the halo...
he carries his weapons.
ln praise of benevolent Kings...
the Puriya is sung
This, the Bageshri...
sung to the praise of
the conquest of knowledge
Sing the Bageshri to invoke
the Goddess of Knowledge
Father!
This is sin!
ls it sin?
My child, what your thirsting eyes
seek everywhere...
you cannot bring yourself to speak.
l've already grown old looking for him
For me too, this is a dream
What words have l to give you hope?
Mohan...
- l have heard enough
l hear Narpat had convened
the village council yesterday
Yes.
- What was decided?
The council expressed gratitude
to Baiju
But they also said that a daughter
cannot be given away as a reward
Her engagement to Narpat
cannot be annulled
Not even if you pay a fine?
- What do l get out of paying a fine?
Where is Baiju? People were giving
my daughter a bad name all for him!
So what if l annul the engagement
to Narpat? lf Baiju doesn't turn up...
who else will marry her?
lf l die before my daughter
is married off, l will go to hell!
She gives herself a bad name,
and now she weeps!
Tell me, do l console her, or
do l stop people from talking?
lf l care for her emotions,
l will fail in my duty as a father
Have patience, Mohan
There is so much that
man wishes to do
But what happens,
is what God wills
Come in
Baiju, you did not return
And everyone else here
has decided my fate
But l shall refute this decision
lt was here,...
that l drank
the elixir of love
And today...
it is poison that
l am being made to drink
You!
You're the one who took
my Baiju away!
Tell me, where is my Baiju?
Has he come with you?
No. He went away long ago.
Where to?
- Some say...
he went towards Agra. Others say,
a madman called Baiju...
roams the forests of Vrindavan.
Some say that...
he has become a disciple of
Haridas Swamy, and lives with him
l was on my way to look for him there
when l heard that...
the council has decreed
that you be married off
Baiju spurned my love.
l have come to pay him back
Are you ridiculing my love?
No, l have come to help you
l had driven out one of a pair
of lovebirds in Eden
lf l let this Eden wither away...
the lovebird will have nowhere to
return to
For your Baiju's sake, you will have
to live. l've come to take you to him
Come with me
But...
- Do you not want to go to Baiju?
Then, have faith in me.
Come away with me, quietly
Come with me, sister
No reason for worry, Swami.
Use this salve
And walk a while every day
Apothecary, when l step down
from the bed,...''
my legs collapse
And you ask me to walk?
Without worship to the Lord,
l cannot have any peace.
My soul thirsts for The Lord
Lord!
l beg for your grace
l have scaled the heights of music
But there is darkness ahead
Show me light, Guru
ln your music,...
l have seen my God
By the grace of Lord Krishna...
your name, your music
will be made immortal
The years of schooling...
is now bearing fruit
lt is all by dint
of your blessings
No. The one l thought was lost,...
now shines as brilliant as a diamond
l have only brushed,...
burnished and tempered it
But the talent that was hidden within
is God's own gift
Son, l'll be back
Till then, practice the Todi
to perfection
l will
Now!
Now is the time come.
Father, l will avenge you
You haven't gotten over vengeance yet?
Son, leave vengeance to The Lord
Forget all that, and put in your best
Now is the time come.
Father, l will avenge you
God! Cast my heart in stone
... in stone, like yours!
Turn me to stone!
Of music, You have forged the world!
Does my music bear nothing
upon Your heart?
Loveless music has no bearing
lt is with love that man
reaches out to God
And love... love lies at your feet!
Do not spurn love!
Love is God!
Do not leave me!
No!
God! What am l to do?!
Show me the way!
God!
Gauri! Go away!
Go away Gauri!
- Where will l go?
No one but you can embrace me!
And l will have my recognition...
only when you make me your wife
For me, marrying you now,
would be making a widow of you!
lf l lose against the one
l seek vengeance...
l will be beheaded
Vengeance? Against whom?
Tansen
Tansen? How come...?
By defeating him in
a contest of music
l can marry you only after
l have defeated Tansen
The power to defeat
as great a musician as Tansen...
do you have it in you, Baiju?
- l'd rather die...
than dishonour the promise
l made my father
lf l live, l will come directly
to you
But till then, consider me dead
No! l've been through so much
to find you!
l'm not going to let you go!
Come back with me!
Have you forgotten the hilllock
by the banks of the Yamuna?
lt was there that l foreswore
the promise l made to my father
Go away Gauri, go away!
lf l leave you, where am l to go?
l have burnt all my bridges.
You are the only one l have!
Take me with you, Baiju.
Let's sink together, if we must
No, with you around, l will forget
my mission in life
You have disrupted my schooling
You and your love will be my undoing!
l will never be able to defeat Tansen!
Blessed be the name of The Lord
Guru! l'm going mad!
This is why l have come to give you
one last advice
Forsake hatred. Let love blossom
in your heart
Without love, your heart
will be bereft of pathos
Without pathos, your music will not
be able to melt stone
And pathos you will have,
once you have been hurt
Hurt...?
Why do l not die?
Hurt...
Love
Gauri!
What happened to you, Gauri?
How did this happen, Gauri?
l have removed myself from your path
Why have you done this?
Now nothing lies between
you and your music
Now, you....
you will be able to defeat Tansen
No! l'm not going to let you die!
l won't let you die!
She sleeps
She will not talk to you
She will talk to no one
She will only talk to me
What happened to Gauri?
- Snake!
Get out of here! Run!
Looks like she has been bitten
by a snake
Snake?
l remember!
lt was this snake!
The snake that bit Gauri!
You are the witch who set us apart!
Have you come to set us apart again?
No Baiju, l brought Gauri here.
- No! You brought her ashes here!
What do l do with ashes?
l must go and find Gauri!
Baiju! Come to your senses!
Where are you going?
Leave me alone! With Gauri,
l've died too
But Baiju...
- Aren't you sated yet?
Go on, put the corpse to fire!
And revel in the fires!
Dance, dance!
The mind takes the toll in a battle
between the mind and the heart
Baiju has gone mad!
Baiju is insane!
Laugh! You laugh too
while l weep!
This brooks no delay.
We must hurry
But Baiju...?
- This is no time to talk to him
We'll come back for him later
He's here! My disciple is here!
Some lunatic
Looks like a madman
- Do you not know the law here?
Somebody stop him!
Sing on!
Stop singing!
Who is this?
Do you care for your life?
Don't you know?
Singing is forbidden here!
l do not know.
l know nothing
Nor am l singing
lt's someone else within me
... who is singing...
and l have no hold
over him
lf you can, stop him
But...
let him sing on
We need his pathos
Let the hearts be overcome.
Let us weep too... and let
the skies, the earth, weep too
Wonderful! Sing on!
Face the palace and sing!
l tell you, your voice sings a note
deeper by the thousandths than earlier
What are you staring at?
My disciple! And no joke!
Disciple... yours?
And haven't you told him that
the one who sings here...
must better the royal bard,
Mian Tansen? Else...
he is punished!
- Then let him face this challenge!
The wheat will be separated
from the chaff!
ls that so?
Arrest him!
Why are you holding me?
He's the one who's singing
The Emperor has decided.
Do you hear?
Unless you contest within a week,
both of us will be hanged!
We're going to be dead!
What have l landed myself in?
This madman doesn't even answer!
How do l answer, Gauri?
They won't let me sing
They haven't forbidden you.
Thay are telling you to sing
You must sing before Emperor Akbar
No, l will sing before no one.
l will only sing to Gauri
l'm no Gauri! l'm Ghasit Khan!
Don't you see my beard?!
Are you a wizard?
- Wizard...?
Turn me into a firefly!
l want to burn in the fire!
Lord! There's no escape now!
Gauri is gone!
What noise is that?
ls someone being executed?
Lord!
Come on! l'm here to help you escape!
You're the bandit!
You've come back for him?
Silent!
Else, you too will be silenced
like the guards
My men are waiting outside
for us
What has come over you?
We cannot be here for long!
Come with me!
- No
Once you had said that, earlier.
''Come with me''
Don't go Baiju. She's fooling you
l have come to take you to Gauri
You are a liar! Gauri is waiting
across the river for me
Will you take me across?
- Not across
Here! Gauri is alive
We took Gauri to an apothecary
who knows about venoms. She...
You are telling a lie, a ruthless lie
just to take me out of here
No Birju! l'm telling the truth!
l went back to that temple in ruins
to tell you. But l didn 't find you
lt's true that Gauri lives.
But she keeps saying that...
''For Baiju, l'm dead.
Don't tell Baiju that l'm alive''
''Else, my sacrifice
will have gone waste''
''He wants to defeat Tansen.
And for him, l am a hindrance''
Yes! Gauri is alive!
She is alive!
She has gone back to her village.
- And you want me to escape...
so that l can go back to her?
- lt should not have been so
But this is what the heart says...
the heart you once called a stone
Someone is coming!
Come on!
This is the bandit queen!
Arrest her!
Move
Roopmati
She has been wanted for ages.
Got her now
Where are you off to Ustad?
- With you. Home
Your home is here, Ustad.
- Let me go!
- Out of my way!
Let me go!
Let me go! Gauri is alive!
Baiju! Baiju! Baiju!
Where did he come from?
He brings my daughter to disgrace,
and he brings me to dishonour!
Come the time to marry her,
he absconds!
Scoundrel! Rogue!
- Father!
Silent! Aren't you ashamed?
All this is your doing!
Without a thought, you did
what you wanted to!
Had l not used ruse, people would say
that Mohan sent his daughter away...
because the council gave it's ruling.
Even at my age...
you haven't a care for my honour!
- That's why l've come back
l'd rather you were dead!
What do l do? Even Death
has deserted me
Kill me! With your own hands!
l'm going to kill myself
if you refuse to marry Narpat
But...
- What...?!
Will you still wait for the madman?
Everyone looked for him
Even you went looking for him.
Did you find him?
Then forget him. Your wedding has been
fixed for the next full moon
You have only two options.
Marry Narpat, or kill your father
This is my final decision
Open the door.
- The doors of luck don't open...
time and again. When she was trying
to get you out, you were meditating!
You can see Gauri only
if you sing against Tansen
l must sing!
God!
Give me music! That l may fulfill
the promise l made to my father...
that l may have my Gauri
l will sing!
This contest has not ended
Tansen, the Emperor ordered you
to sing the Todi to attract the deer
Young man, you have done the same
But you have not shown
anything charismatic...
to prove yourself a better
musician than Tansen
My Lord, if l may speak without fear,
l wish to say something
You may speak
My disciple looks like a madman.
But in his music...
lies the power to melt stone!
l ask for my disciple and Mian Tansen
are to sing the same Raga
ln that crystal bowl filled with water
is kept a block of marble
The Emperor waits. Prove it that...
stories of stone melting to music...
is not mere folklore. Show us
that it can be true
The contest may begin
Bravo my son!
You have honoured your Guru!
My The Lord preserve you!
Non pareil!
A miracle!
The Emperor has a doubt. The crystal
did not shatter. lt was shattered
Sing again
Lord, l cannot lie to absolve myself
of defeat
Music has found a new exponent,
not an adversary
Baijnath, The Emperor recognises
your victory
Tansen, l regret your loss deeply
ln Tansen's loss lies music's victory!
The Emperor, Tansen...
and all of Hindustan must rejoice!
For here has been unearthed....
a most precious
diamond that will...
dazzle the annals of music
lndeed. This sparkle of this diamond
does proud the court of Emperor Akbar
The Emperor is pleased with
your performance. Seek what you will
lf The Emperor so grants,
l shall ask for only three gifts
You may
First, the freeing of music
from the confines of law
Second, Roopmati's release
and repatriation of her fiefs
And third, the very life of music
The very life of music...?
l do not understand
The very life of music is Tansen
Lord, grant Tansen life,
and save music from death!
You have the soft heart
of an artiste, Baijnath
But the law is heartless
Akbar's laws are humane,
Your Majesty
l beseech You
in the name of kindness
l am leaning towards
your principles, young singer
The one who showed me music
in a new light...
the one who gave me a new life
... the one who has lit...
a million lamps... how can
l bear to see him dead?
You are truly an exponent
of art, Baijnath
The Emperor cannot but appreciate
your commitment to art
Your performance today,
and your lofty ideals...
forces an Emperor to allow humane
consideration...
to assume primacy over the law.
Your petitions are granted
Long live Baijnath!
Baiju!
Baiju's voice!
Do you hear?
My Baiju is back!
Baiju! You're back!
- Yes, l'm back''
Gauri is getting married today.
- Gauri... getting married?
Gauri's wedding?
- Yes son
Row me across!
- l cannot!
The river is in flood! How can l cross?
My boat will sink
All my hopes are sinking!
l have to go! l must!
Baiju is back.
- Baiju..?
My Baiju is back...?
Baiju is back!
Don't take the boat
into the waters, Baiju!
Where have you hidden Gauri?!
You scoundrel!
You have no sense of dignity!
But l have my honour!
Tell me! Fie on you!
Don't enter the water!
The boat will capsize!
What are you doing?!
- Let me go!
The river is in spate!
- Let me go! She'll die!
Baiju, have you won the contest?
- Yes
But l'm losing the battle for my life!
You will not be able
to save me, Gauri!
Swim back to the bank.
- l have crossed my forge!
You know how to swim!
Go back, Gauri!
All you know is l can swim.
But with you, l can even drown!
ln the waters then...
we are to wed, Gauri!