Courier
Cuddapah - Andhra.
Escape.
No...
They tried to escape.
Singamuthu, you are an elder.
Don't you have any concious.
Look at their state.
This place is surrounded
by a 2 km. electric fence.
My boys with guns.
I've recruited them like any army.
All this for what?
So that, none of you escape.
But they escaped from the bus in midway.
We won't let them go.
So, I'm grooming a hunting dog,
Cuddappah Raja.
He caught them by their throat.
How dare you hit him?
Brother...
How many more should I kill?
If everyone goes to the hospital,
who will work here?
If you commit 1 wrong,
I will cut your legs.
2 wrongs, I will cut your hands.
If you try to escape,
I will cut your head.
- Get up, brother.
- What happened to my brother?
Where will you escape?
Will you go to the police?
Will you go to the collector?
No matter where you go,
I can't be touched.
Because I am Konda Reddy.
I'm not just an MLA,
this village is mine.
You bastards!
Even God can't save you from me.
Hang him.
What happened to my brother?
I don't know whether God
will come to save us,
but my son will come.
When he comes to know
about we suffering here,
your countdown starts.
If this stone has some power,
my words too have a power.
He will come. I swear...
Not only your son,
anyone who dares to come here,
this will be his fate.
Get inside.