[TEMPLE BELL]
Students, I had told you to
write four lines on your mother.
- Have you all written it?
- Yes, teacher.
Very good.
Raju... Did you write it?
I'm asking you, did you write it?
Come here.
You've not written anything.
Do you sleep in the classroom?
Answer me?
You won't speak like this.
This stick will make you speak up.
Show me your hand.
Tell me. Tell me.
Teacher, don't beat him.
How can he write about his mother?
He has no mother.
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
- Hello.
- Call from Delhi.
Call from Delhi. Hang on.
Sir, your call from Delhi.
- Hello.
- Prem.
Yes, Prem here.
- Shrivastav here.
- Who? Shrivastav?
- Uncle Ramu.
- Yes, dear?
- Who is father talking to?
- To someone in Delhi.
Delhi? Delhi is so far away.
Forget Delhi, these days.
You can even talk to somebody in the sky.
- Even above the clouds?
- Yes.
Don't worry. Your work will be done.
Come on, Raju. Freshen up.
We'll have our meals.
[BELL CHIMES]
[CRICKET CHIRPING]
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Hello. Telephone exchange.
- I want God's number.
- What? What number?
God's number. I want to talk to my mother.
Is your mother with God?
Yes. She died when I was born.
Tell her it's her Raju's call.
Hang on.
- Neeta.
- Yes?
It's a boy. He wants God's number.
He wants to talk to his mother.
Talk to him. It'll make him feel better.
Get lost. Don't bore me.
Please. For my sake.
What's the harm in talking
to him for two minutes?
Fine. Give.
Dear, talk to your mother.
- Hello.
- Mother.
Mother, Raju here. Your Raju.
I know, son. Can't I recognise my Raju?
Mother, you've recognised me. How are you?
I... I'm fine.
I miss you a lot.
Take leave from God and come to me.
Please.
Dear, I can't come. I'm helpless.
Why can't you come? Don't you love me?
I love you a lot, son.
Then why can't you come?
Have I erred, mother? I apologise.
Now I will neither err nor trouble you.
- But Raju, son.
- Don't refuse.
I want to see you. I want to talk to you.
I want to sleep in your lap.
Don't cry, son.
You're my brave son.
Look, Mother. Let me tell you clearly.
Tomorrow is my birthday.
If you won't come, I'll starve to death.
No, son. Don't say that.
Then promise me you'll
come on my birthday. Okay?
I'll come, son.
Don't forget, Mother.
I won't cut the cake until you come.
Your mother will surely
come on your birthday.
Okay, Mother.
Father.
Mother is coming. I just spoke to her.
She said she'll surely
come on my birthday.
Your mother will surely come, son.
She'll surely come on your birthday.
[CHILDREN PLAYING]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Raju, quickly cut the cake. I'm famished.
Not now. Only after mother comes.
After your mother comes?
The dead don't come back.
My mother will surely come.
She has told me.
He even spoke to his mother.
It must be your mom's ghost.
You call my mother a ghost. I'll kill you.
The power failed.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
What happened to the electricity?
Raju.
'As usual, father lied to me even today.'
'Even today, he didn't bring my mother.'
Laxmi.
Mother.
Son.
"It's a joyous day."
"I got what I wanted."
"Today my mother called me son."
"It's a joyous day."
"I got what I wanted."
"Today my mother called me son."
"Mother. My mother."
- Teacher.
- Yes.
- My mother.
- Is that so?
Aunt, she's my mother.
Yes, son.
"Mother, I've to grow
up under your shelter."
"Holding your finger,
I've to walk with you."
"You're the answer to my prayers."
"You're my God."
"You dwell in each temple and idol."
"It's a joyous day."
"I got what I wanted."
"Today my mother called me son."
Do you see what I'm seeing, Mainawati?
Yes, Tota.
My name is Totaram, not Tota.
Have your medicine on time.
Don't forget it.
- Sister. My dear sister.
- Brother.
My dear sister. Why did you leave us?
I swear. After getting
married, I've become lonely.
- Really, sister. What do I tell you?
- Brother.
He is shedding tears like
a municipal drainage.
Not municipal drainage. Water pipe.
It's one and the same thing.
Brother-in-law. Now we won't leave you.
No. Don't cry, Totaram.
- If you want, you can stay with us.
- Really?
Laxmi, take him inside.
I'll meet the collector. -Okay.
Brother-in-law is great.
Brother-in-law seems to be
an emotional guy, sister.
Have you got the bungalow,
land and the wealth...
...transferred in your name?
Brother, don't worry.
Very soon everything will be ours.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Sister, we're ruined. We're doomed.
- Do you see this Will?
- What is written in this Will?
This will is going to ruin my sister.
I got my sister married to widower Prem.
...to seize his wealth.
But things are different.
Prem is worthless.
She's just the trustee.
She has no right on the wealth.
[COW MOO]
Raju's mother was a cunning woman.
Before dying she bequeathed
everything to Raju.
Oh, my God. It's terrible.
Not terrible. It's horrible.
That witch has also willed...
...that until Raju doesn't get married...
...and his wife's doesn't
give her consent...
...Raju can't transfer
the wealth to anyone else.
It's fine by us,
but what about sister's to-be born child?
- He should get his right.
- Yes.
My child will surely get his right.
[BIRD CHIRPING] - Just watch, brother.
I'll cast such a spell on Raju...
...he'll chant "mother" day and night.
He'll live for his mother.
He'll die for his mother.
- How many tons have you sold?
- 16 tons.
- Fine. Recover it on the route.
- Okay, ma'am.
- Son.
- Yes.
Do you know how educated
this accountant is?
Mother, he's highly educated.
He even speaks in English.
So why is he bowing down in front of us?
Because educated people respect others.
No. It's because we're really rich.
And your father has earned
this wealth by farming.
He achieved this only by studying.
No, son. I'll explain it to you.
Come along.
Yes. -Look, everybody bows to your father.
That man in black coat is a lawyer.
The one in the suit is
the officer-in-charge.
The others too are educated people.
Only education can get you a job.
I don't want to be a servant.
I'll be the master.
If you want to become a
master, work in the fields.
Because the real wealth is in the
ground, not in the books.
I'll work in the fields.
Very good.
So what is the need for all this?
Give. I'll throw it.
Not this. Your name is written on this.
If you say so, I'll tear this.
[PAPER RUSTLING]
Look, son.
This part of our land is
lying barren for many years.
Forget crops,
not even grass can grow here.
With your hard work,
you've to turn this land into lush fields.
What are you doing?
You're handing a big
task to this small child.
Even strong men couldn't
grow a twig of grass here.
How can this child make
this barren land lush?
Move.
Mother.
Mother. -What are you doing?
Put me down. Leave me.
Are you happy?
Look how lush the fields are.
This was barren land.
I would've even turned a
desert into lush land for you.
How can the son not obey
his mother's command?
Has he put stones in his bag?
- Already you are tired?
- This is the sixth bag.
I feel Ramesh is going for ever. I'm dead.
What are you whispering to your wife?
Don't you get time at home?
Have you kept the luggage properly?
- I'm doing it.
- Don't shout at me.
- Am I?
- Yes.
Okay.
Shut the trunk properly.
Nothing should be left out.
Got it? Greetings, sister. [FOOT STEPS]
- Ramesh, hurry up. We're getting late.
- Yes, Mother.
- Take care.
- Bye, Uncle.
I'll miss you all. Do you miss me?
Goodbye.
Am I a devil?
Why did she scream on seeing me?
If you had been a devil,
she wouldn't have screamed.
But anybody would get
scared of a naked man.
Naked? You've worn your clothes.
- But you've not worn it.
- What are you saying?
Take this towel.
Why are you stopping the car like this?
Move aside. We're getting late.
I'm only making you late.
But you've caused chaos, Laxmi.
You've seized my land.
Which land are you talking about?
It's my land. And it'll remain mine.
You're lying.
That land belongs to my ancestors.
And if you didn't hand
over the land to me...
...I would have to use foul means.
Scoundrel. You threaten me.
Do whatever you want.
I don't argue with filthy men like you.
Let's go, driver.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[TRAIN HORN ]
It's time for the train to
depart, but Raju isn't here yet.
Mother. [FOOT STEPS]
- Mother.
- Son, where were you?
I had gone to buy almond
sweets from Chandu's shop.
- So I got late.
- Okay. [TRAIN HORN]
- Come on, Ramesh. Get in the train.
- Okay.
The train is leaving.
Stop. Stop. Seek mother's blessings.
- God bless you, son.
- Hurry up. Get in.
- Or the train will depart.
- Okay.
- Bye, Mother.
- Okay, son.
Ramesh, I forgot to give you the sweets.
Eat it every day with milk.
It'll make you bright.
And look, this is your last year.
Study really hard.
Mother wants you to
become a famous doctor.
And you've to fulfill her wish.
Got it, Ramesh?
- Yes. Brother, now leave.
- Take care.
Inform us as soon as you reach there.
- What does this mean?
- It's crystal clear.
Quietly sign on this. Or...
You are threatening me, scoundrel?
You call me a scoundrel and what are you?
The whole village knows how wicked
and immoral a woman you are.
When a thousand sinners die,
a sinner like you is born.
You abused my mother?
You abused my mother? I will kill you.
I won't spare you.
I will kill you.
[HORN BLARING]
Leave me.
Raju.
Move.
- Leave him, Raju.
- No, Mother.
Today I won't spare him.
You're under my oath, leave him.
[MAN CRYING]
Is this called justice?
Tiwari was asking for his rights.
And he tried to kill him.
He doesn't know about right and wrong.
He's only blind about his mother's love.
God knows what spell she has cast on him.
He's a step-son.
But he loves her more than a real son.
He's mad.
Raju is only her step-son.
She even made her husband mad
and locked him up in a room.
Sir.
Before that witch comes,
quickly eat your meal.
I don't want food, Pandu.
Even animals eat anything and survive.
But I want to live like a
human and not like an animal.
I want to get out of this hell.
I feel suffocated here, Pandu.
I feel suffocated.
Have patience, sir. Have patience.
Shall I ask you something?
How come you're in this dungeon?
I don't understand.
It occurred 20 years ago...
...when I got a mother for Raju.
But I didn't know she
married me for wealth.
When she found the wealth
is in Raju's name...
...she didn't let Raju study
so that she could control him.
And when I found out.
I'll break your legs if
you didn't go to school.
What are you doing?
Don't beat this innocent child.
I've told ma'am many times.
But she too.
What? Laxmi knows everything?
- Hurry.
- Laxmi.
'Then my wife and her brother
planned to get rid of me.'
- Laxmi.
- And...
Give brother-in-law another
portion when he wakes up. - Okay.
Laxmi, I'm feeling dizzy.
Drink this medicine.
Everything will be fine.
I won't to drink this medicine.
Taking advantage of my
unconsciousness they...
...drugged me to make me insane.
And I thought the rope is a snake.
Snake. Help.
It'll bite me. Snake. Help.
It'll kill me.
I understood it was my wife's ruse.
After instigating everybody against me...
...now you want to snatch my
innocent Raju from me too.
You think I'll spare you. I'll kill you.
You've hurt my nephew.
- I'll kill you.
- Tie him up.
After that day I was labeled insane.
The whole world thinks I'm mad.
I don't mind it.
What I regret is my own son...
...Raju too considers me to be crazy.
Sir, I know. Nothing has happened to you.
And someday even brother
Raju will find out the truth.
Come, sir. Sit.
Eat your meals. Take it, sir.
If you repeat this mistake,
I'll banish you from this house.
Now why are you staring at
the chicken piece? Get lost.
Go away, scoundrel.
Brother-in-law,
would you like to eat delicacies?
Would you like chicken?
Here. Have millet flatbread and onion.
It is good for health. Eat. Eat. Eat. Eat.
- Raju.
- Coming, Mother.
Mother, what happened?
Ram Prasad has invited
us to his son's wedding.
What will I do there? You go there.
Son, he's our close relative.
If we don't go, he'll feel really bad.
Fine. When do we've to be there?
By tomorrow morning.
- Tomorrow morning?
- Yes.
Shalu. Saraswati. Vimla.
Come soon. The wedding procession is here.
Move. Let me see the groom.
- Is your name Raju?
- Yes.
The groom is waiting for you. Come.
She.
I think I was dreaming.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Where is Raju?
He's a young man.
He must be taking a stroll.
Here is he.
- Greetings.
- Where were you?
- Mother, I.
- Forget it. Sit here.
The auspicious time has started.
Call the bride.
Priest, she'll be here soon.
Just two minutes.
What?
Quick!
[GRUNTS]
- Raju.
- Yes?
- What happened, son?
- Nothing, mother. Hiccups.
Sit.
[HOLY MANTRA CHANTING]
- Snehal. Let's go.
- Come.
[HOLY MANTRA CHANTING]
- Raju.
- What happened, mother.
- Now where are you going?
- Mother, hiccups.
- What is happening to you?
- Water.
Fine. Go and have water.
[HICCUPS]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
[LAUGHING]
That.
There.
Great teeth.
Do you use monkey brand toothpowder?
I too use it. Look.
Ma'am, sherbet.
No. Don't drink this.
Take this away.
Stop. Why not? I'm thirsty.
It's better if you don't
drink this sherbet.
Why are you staring at me?
Come on. Leave. [GLASS TINKLE]
Why are you stopping me
from drinking the sherbet?
Look. what's your name?
Saraswati. Forget that. First answer me.
Look, Saraswati.
That sherbet had ice in it.
If you had drunk it,
very soon you would've sneezed.
You would've got cough and fever.
Your entire body would've ached with pain.
And gradually the fever
would've increased.
And then. you would've got pneumonia.
And if you had got pneumonia,
I wouldn't have liked it. Right?
Your friend got angry.
- There is only one way to appease her.
- What?
Saraswati loves roses.
Roses. But here roses.
Remove the rose from that
fatso's hair and give it to her.
She'll be happy.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Saraswati. Look.
Now we'll have fun.
Take this.
Sister. I wanted the rose.
But the wig came off.
Don't do that.
I've given you the promised Rs. 3 lakh.
Now from where will I bring 200,000 more?
Look, you had promised.
But the prices have escalated.
So I've increased my son's price too.
Now this marriage will take
place only if I get 500,000.
- Or I'm leaving with my son.
- But...
Mr. Ram Prasad. Please come here.
- What happened?
- You too come here.
Look, Mr. Ram Prasad.
I'm your well-wisher.
And it's my duty to
give you correct advice.
Government has become very
strict against dowry seekers.
If somebody complains the
police will thrash you.
Is that so?
And then they'll drag
you out by your hair.
- Is that so?
- Come on.
And then you will get three
years of imprisonment.
And every day you will grind
the flour in the prison. -Yes.
Come on.
Father, I won't grind the flour.
I too won't do it. Sit at the dais.
Priest, I've come. Start the rituals.
Badriprasad, now we'll leave.
You've honored me by
coming for the wedding.
This was my duty. - Bye. - Bye.
- Sir, where will I find Saraswati?
- Why?
To give her the photographs
which she had clicked.
Give me these photographs.
I'll give it to her.
- Who are you?
- I'm her.
I see. Take this.
Come on, Raju. We're getting late.
Come on, Mother.
[BIRD CHIRPING]
[GIRL LAUGHING]
[HEART BEAT]
Ouch!
"My heart is beating."
"I'm feeling scared."
"Beloved, leave my hand."
"Don't entice my youth."
"Hearts have united."
"Why are you shy of me?"
"You're my beloved."
"You look fabulous."
"My heart is beating."
"I'm feeling scared."
"Beloved, when you called me yours..."
"...I started weaving sweet dreams."
"When I saw you..."
"...my heartbeats started singing."
"You've cast your spell on me."
"I'm enticed by it."
"I forget myself."
"I have kept you in my heart."
"Beloved, now this bond has been formed."
"Hearts have united."
"Why are you shy of me?"
"My heart is beating."
"I'm feeling scared."
"Your black tresses are entangled."
"Let me remove the tangles."
"What's the hurry?"
"Let the time of our union arrive."
"Don't make excuses."
"My beloved, come in my arms."
"Don't lock eyes like this."
"If somebody saw what will they think?"
"There is merriment all around."
"Come and embrace me."
"My heart is beating."
"I'm feeling scared."
"Beloved, leave my hand."
"Don't entice my youth."
"Hearts have united."
"Why are you shy of me?"
"You're my beloved."
"Or my sweetheart."
"My heart is beating."
"I'm feeling scared."
"Hearts have united."
"Why are you shy of me?"
Oh God! Where did she disappear?
And where did you come from?
Since two hours you are
making me exercise...
...and are now asking where I came from?
It is good that I stopped
you at the right time...
...or else I would have been dishonored.
Dishonored.
I was seeing such a beautiful dream.
You ruined everything. Donkey.
Dream? Brother Raju,
tell me who came in your dreams?
Her name is Saraswati.
She lives in Gangapur.
And you have fallen in love with
her, right?
Don't worry, brother Raju.
This disciple of yours promises...
...to get both of you
united tomorrow itself.
- Please give me Rs. 200.
- Forget Rs. 200. You keep Rs. 400.
But fix me a meeting with her.
Don't worry. Consider it done.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
Look st this.
You steal without giving
the protection money.
Come to the police station.
God will bless you.
Give me something. Thank you, sir.
From morning until noon I
am searching for her. -Yes.
- But we've still not found her.
- Yes.
- Listen, Pandu.
- What?
- You search there. I'll search here.
- Okay, brother Raju.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
- Khan.
- Oh, my God.
Khan.
What happened, Sultana?
Khan, a loafer teased me and fled.
- He teased you?
- Yes.
Oh, my God.
What is this?
This one.
Not a single girl is nice.
This is good. Give me this.
Sister-in-law.
- Help.
- Khan.
What happened? What happened?
This loafer was harassing me.
I won't spare you. Scoundrel.
You've harassed my wife
for the second time.
Not the second time. It's the first time.
- First time.
- Yes.
It's the last time.
- I won't spare you.
- Is this real?
- Yes.
- Look. Who has come?
Run. Run.
[GUNSHOT]
[INDISTINCT LAUGHTER]
You laugh at me. You at mock me.
Why do you hit me?
Brother Raju. Brother Raju.
What happened? Did you find her?
Yes. I found my death.
Now you'll die.
You lied for the money that
I'll find her at the fair.
Now, I'll punish you severely.
Listen. Actually.
What happened, Pandu?
That girl.
Found her.
Found her. Found her. Found her.
Tell me. What did you find?
He's that same fool who was
after me at the marriage.
Before he follows you
again, let's flee. -Okay.
- Found her.
- Tell me. What have you found?
He has found his sweetheart.
Let me see too. Where is she?
She's there.
How is this possible?
My sister-in-law was fine.
She turned into a jelly before marriage.
Now my brother Raju too will
have to become a donkey.
Fool. She's not your sister-in-law.
- She is.
- No.
- She has got only two more legs.
- Shut up. Come.
- I'm coming, sister-in-law.
- Come on.
Do you see that giant wheel.
Let's ride it.
We'll have great fun.
Can't you see where you're going?
- My darling.
- Hey!
What a flirt this old man is.
- Let's go.
- Come.
Please, darling.
Old man. You're old with no teeth.
And you want a kiss?
You don't kiss with the teeth.
You kiss...
- ...like this.
- Lecherous old man.
You, pervert old man!
When I ask you to kiss me...
...you make an excuse that
you don't have teeth.
Now here you are to kiss
stranger women, aren't you?
Come on! I will kiss you so much that
you will remember them for life!
Understood? Lets go home now!
I will repair your jaw!
She slipped off our hands just because
of your craziness. -
You were no less either!
- Fine. But where can we find her now?
- How would I know?
Just for two rupees!
- Come to me! Try new...
- Hey!
I have an idea, Raju!
- How much money do you have?
- Why?
Why do you care? Just tell me, will you?
- Rs. 5000!
- Is it?
- You can be young.
- Move! Making young, as if!
Push off!
Listen, gentlemen.
An important announcement.
Friends, well-wishers. Listen.
This girl has been lost in the fair.
Friends, look for her carefully.
Look. Look for her carefully.
The one, who will find
her, will get Rs.5,000.
Rs.5,000?
Rs.5,000.
I'll find the girl for Rs.5,000.
Come on.
Rs.5,000. Quickly find her. Rs.5,000.
- Move.
- Come on.
Where is this girl worth
Rs.5,000 in the name of God.
Where are you going?
Snehal, sit. I'm feeling dizzy. I'm going.
Found her. Found her.
Sorry. Are you hurt?
Take me to the oil store.
I'll take you there.
- God bless you.
- Come.
- Come. This way.
- What's the time?
- 11:30.
God bless you.
Scoundrel. You harass my wife. Leave.
- God.
- Sir. Come.
Come, dear. God bless you.
May God always bless you.
Drop me there. God bless you.
Dear, drop me there.
Khan, look there.
Khan.
Scoundrel.
- Khan.
- Where are you going?
You tease my wife.
- You tease my wife. I won't spare you.
- Hit him.
How much? - Rs. 2 for one. - Okay.
[SCREAMING]
I won't leave you.
Leave me. Leave me.
- Take it.
- She's that girl worth Rs.5,000.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY]
I'm searching for that
girl worth Rs.5,000.
- Constable.
- What happened?
Those goons are after me.
- Go away. I can't help you.
- But.
She's the girl whom we're
looking for Rs.5,000.
- I can help you.
- What are you doing?
Found her. Found her.
[LAUGHING]
What? Can't you see that he has found her?
- I saw this girl first. My Rs.5,000.
- Move.
I've handcuffed her.
I should get Rs.5,000.
So you've made them come after me.
What do you want?
I feel shy to say it.
You feel shy,
but like you're after me shamelessly.
What is our relationship?
People call this a
relationship of many lifetimes.
Relationship of many lifetimes.
And with you.
Have you seen your face
in the mirror? Fool.
- Constable, open this.
- Have patience.
Open it quickly. - Okay.
- Acting like a prince.
- What a strange girl.
- Sister-in-law got angry.
Rana. My name is Bhairav Singh Rana.
Nobody can forget my face.
I got two years imprisonment...
...on the basis of your
father's testimony.
What had I done? I had just raped a girl.
And today I'll rape you
in front of everybody.
- Leave me.
- Leave me. Leave me.
He's taking the girl. Leave me.
Bitch.
Leave me.
Bride come. Look, priest.
Get this donkey married to him.
So that he never ogles at
any other village girl.
Do it quickly. Do it.
- Wedding.
- [HOLY MANTRA CHANTING]
Hurry up. Quickly chant the mantras.
[HOLY MANTRA CHANTING]
It's almost dusk.
Come, I'll drop you home.
- Pandu. Tell mother I'll be late.
- Okay, brother Raju.
- Let's go, Saraswati.
- Yes.
[THUNDER RAIN]
This storm has made life miserable.
We'll have to stay here
till the storm abates.
Right, Saraswati?
You're shivering from cold. Sit. Sit.
I'll arrange to light a fire. Sit.
[THUNDER RAIN]
Listen. Sit close to the fire.
Or very soon you'll start sneezing.
Then you'll start coughing.
You'll get fever.
Your body will ache with pain.
And then gradually the
fever will increase.
- And then.
- Then I'll get pneumonia.
And you won't like that. Right?
Raju, you did me a big favour
by saving me in the fair.
What favour?
If a man can't save a woman's honor...
...his life is futile.
You've hurt your hand.
This is nothing. It's a minor wound.
It'll get cured.
Hang on.
Raju, now it's a minor wound.
Gradually it'll become severe.
It'll become incurable.
And then the poison will spread.
If the poison spreads,
your hand will have to be amputated.
And if that happens, I won't like it.
Right?
You too are very smart, Saraswati.
You have used my logic.
"Your voice is sweet like a cuckoo."
"Your face is so innocent."
"Your eyes are lined with eyeliner."
"Your lips are salacious."
"Seeing you I lost my heart."
"Your talks are melodious."
"It entices me, beloved."
"Your complexion is lovely."
"You're unique."
"Seeing you I felt something."
"You're the queen of beauty."
"Your body is fragrant."
"When I come near you,
my breath become fragrant."
"You're the queen of beauty."
"Your body is fragrant."
"When I come near you,
my breath become fragrant."
"Your body is gorgeous."
"My heart craves for you."
"Your bangles make me lose my sense."
"You've made me fervent."
"You stole my solace too."
"Your talks are melodious."
"It entices me, beloved."
"Your complexion is lovely."
"You're unique."
"Seeing you I felt something."
"You touched my body and it
kindled passion in my heart."
"My heart skipped a beat
when your veil swayed."
"You touched my body and it
kindled passion in my heart."
"My heart skipped a beat
when your veil swayed."
"I'll fill my life with your love."
"I've given you my life."
"I'll come to your house as your bride."
"I crave for you."
"I can't explain my restlessness to you."
"Your voice is sweet like a cuckoo."
"Your face is so innocent."
"Your eyes are lined with eyeliner."
"Your lips are salacious."
"Seeing you, I lost my heart."
[THUNDER RAIN]
Listen!
- Listen!
- Yes!
Where were you lost?
[THUNDER RAIN]
Thinking about somebody!
Tell me who you were thinking about.
- Do you want to know?
- Yes!
Come with me!
It's you!
Did I make a mistake?
Yes! You've made a grave mistake, Raju!
A grave mistake!
So consider this as a mistake, Saraswati!
I love you. I truly love you.
For God's sake, keep quiet!
It's a sin for me to hear all this!
I'm going to marry somebody else.
I'm engaged.
Saraswati!
I've hurt you unknowingly.
Forgive me.
Come. I'll escort you home.
[WIND HOWLING]
Look! They've come!
I had told you! I don't believe this!
Yes! If you say...
Look there!
[WIND HOWLING]
Mr. Diwan,
ask your to-be daughter-in-law...
...where she was the whole
night and what was she doing!
Mr. Shyamlal, you only ask your daughter!
Where were you the whole night? Answer me!
What were you doing with this scoundrel?
Father, you too are misunderstanding me!
If a young daughter doesn't
return home the whole night...
...what will her old father think?
What will he explain to the people?
I wish I were dead before seeing all this.
Uncle, this isn't so!
Actually we got stuck in a storm at night!
Which storm are you talking about?
The storm of lust which
had engulfed you both?
Or the storm where without
caring for anything...
...an unmarried girl
forsakes her coyness...
...and she becomes naked in front
of an unknown man? -This is a lie!
If this is a lie,
were you worshipping her the whole night?
Along with herself,
she has slandered the entire village!
Now who will marry the
women of our village?
Who will form a bond with the villagers?
Her fiance will break the bond!
You're right! I break this alliance!
I won't make such a characterless...
...and derogatory woman
my daughter-in-law!
Let's go, son!
Stop! Listen to me!
They're falsely accusing her!
I swear on God!
She's chaste like holy Ganges!
We've not committed any sin!
Don't break this alliance!
Forget making her my wife!
I won't even make her my mistress!
Had you not been her to-be husband...
...I would've retaliated!
What did you say? You would've retaliated?
You commit a crime! And you act smugly!
Move!
Villagers, what are you all looking at?
Teach him a lesson for sleeping
with the women of our village!
Beat him!
Stop!
I say stop!
If anybody touched him, I'll hit that man!
Whom are you threatening? Beat him!
Bhairav, if you have guts, beat him!
Hariya! If you have guts, beat him!
Beat him! Come on!
Come on, beat him!
You are brutally beating an unarmed man!
What do you all think?
He's a coward! Or he can't fight back!
He can kill you all in one blow!
But he's quiet only because
he wants to give me justice!
Got it?
And you! You're worried about me!
Yesterday you had come
to rape me at the fair!
If yesterday this man had not been
there, you would've raped me!
And you? You were my to-be husband!
You wanted to marry me!
But I think you don't know...
...the foundation of a husband
and wife's relationship!
It's trust!
The man who can't trust
his wife for one night...
...can't stand by her all her life.
Just now you said you won't
even make me your mistress!
Then today I say in front of everybody...
...forget being my husband,
you can't even be a pimp!
Here are your bangles! And get lost!
Father, for me you're my
mother and you're my father.
You've raised me.
You've imbibed values within me.
Your daughter can die.
But she can't do such a derogatory deed...
...for which you have to feel ashamed!
I won't let you feel ashamed, Father!
Your Saraswati won't let you feel
ashamed in front of the world!
She won't!
[TEMPLE BELL]
Will you marry me?
- Greetings, brother!
- Greetings!
Dear, what are you looking at?
Seek her blessings.
- You're lucky!
- God bless you, dear.
By fixing Raju's marriage
with my illiterate daughter...
...you've done me a big favour!
My daughter will live here like
a maid and not a daughter-in-law.
Then finalise the marriage
date on the full moon night!
As you say! [CAR ENGINE STARTS]
Greetings!
I don't understand, sister!
Why did you fix Raju's
alliance with this pauper?
If you had found a rich family...
...you could have asked for
as much dowry as you wanted!
Don't be foolish, brother!
Don't you remember Raju's mother's will?
In this, it's clearly written that...
...Raju can't give this
wealth to anybody...
...until his wife
doesn't give her consent!
I understood, sister!
You've found an illiterate
daughter-in-law...
...so that like Raju, you can make
her give us her thumb impression...
...and get all the wealth!
Wow, sister!
[LAUGHING]
[BIRD CHIRPING]
- Ma'am! Brother Raju has come!
- Is that so?
Raju!
- Raju!
- Yes, Mother!
Where were you the last night?
I was so worried for you!
Mother, I was stuck in a storm!
Let it be!
Sit!
Today I'll give you great news!
You'll be delighted!
Mother, I too want to give you good news!
What good news?
Saraswati!
Saraswati, she's my mother.
She...
She's your daughter-in-law, Mother.
The situation was such
that we had to get married.
Won't you take your mother's blessing?
- Mother!
- God bless you!
Mother, are you happy with this marriage?
How can a mother not be
happy to see her son married?
My happiness lies in your happiness!
Really, Mother! Did you see?
My mother is so nice!
I had told you she won't be angry with us!
If you're happy,
I don't want anything else!
Sister! We're ruined!
Our dreams are shattered!
The way you're supporting that girl...
...I feel very soon we'll have to
pack our bags for a pilgrimage.
Do something, sister!
She went without saying anything!
In Mahabharat's 33rd episode
Shakuni too had smiled like this.
But in the 34th episode
Draupadi was disrobed!
Don't worry, Mainawati!
Sister will surely think of a ruse!
My daughter-in-law is really gorgeous!
I'm proud of Raju's choice!
Even if I had wanted...
...I couldn't have found such a
pretty and cultured girl for my son!
Daughter-in-law, sit!
Daughter-in-law, take this!
I had made this bangle for Raju's wife!
Let me give it to you!
What's the matter, Mother? You're crying!
At times God gives joy and
sorrow at the same time!
I don't understand!
How do I explain it to you?!
Because what I'm going to say
is about Raju's life and death!
What are you saying?
I had kept it a secret.
Today unwillingly I have to tell you that.
Look! This is Raju's horoscope.
- Do you know what is written in this?
- What?
It's written that if Raju
marries before he turns 25...
...and if his wife conceives...
...the child could be a
danger to his father's life!
That's why I didn't get Raju married.
Because there is still a few
days left for him to turn 25!
Mother, you too...
I knew you'd say this!
You don't believe in such orthodox things!
But what do I do?
I'm a mother.
And as his mother, I beg for Raju's life!
Daughter-in-law, for God's sake,
don't let this terrible thing happen!
Don't let it happen!
Mother!
Daughter-in-law, it's just for a few days!
Listen to me!
- I beg you!
- What are you doing?
Fine! I'll do as you say!
God bless you, dear!
Look, daughter-in-law!
My Raju should never come to know!
Saru, your love has given me a new life.
We'll begin the first night of
our lives amidst these lamps.
It'll fill your life with happiness.
Saru, I've not left
any place for darkness.
No place at all!
No, Raju!
Why not?
Because I'm saying no.
Today your Raju won't hear your refusal!
Come close to me!
I'm saying no, but you won't listen.
Stay away from me! Don't touch me!
What are you saying, Saru?
Did I make any mistake?
Have I made any mistake? Tell me, Saru!
Raju, please leave me alone!
Leave you alone! That too today!
Why, Saru?
I don't have any answer!
If you don't want to go, I'll go!
No, Saru!
You don't have to leave this room!
I'll leave!
I don't know what lies in your heart...
...and for what you're punishing me.
But I assure you...
...I'll never come to you to
assert my right as a husband!
I'll never come, Saru!
Sister, wow!
Even Totaram bows to you!
You've played such a nice ruse!
Like a politician.
You should've been in parliament.
[LAUGHS]
By lying about Raju's life,
you've trapped her in such a way...
...that on your word she herself
ruined her nuptial night!
Now go on adding fuel to the fire.
And think of an idea to make this
girl leave this house in four days.
Our work is done! Now let's go to sleep!
Wow! What a great mother-in-law you are!
Your daughter-in-law just
stepped in this house...
...and you've started
showing your true colours!
But remember one thing!
You can add as much fuel as you want!
If I didn't teach you all a lesson...
...I'm not my father's daughter!
What's the matter?
Today you're being so romantic!
The weather is for romance today.
What are you doing? Are you fine?
Mainu, I'm fine!
But I want a flower to
blossom in our courtyard.
There are so many flowers here!
How many more do you want?
- I'm not talking about these flowers!
- So?
I'm talking about the child
which you'll conceive!
You couldn't do anything in your youth!
Now what will you do at this age?
What? You're always laughing!
I had gone to the market
to buy vegetables.
- Go and cook lunch for me!
- Fine!
- Mainawati, give it to me!
- Here!
You had asked me to bring the vegetables.
Gourd, cauliflower...
I'm talking to you. Are you listening?
Yes. Say whatever you'd like!
My Pandu, you're looking so sad today.
What else do you want me to be?
Do you know yesterday was
brother Raju's wedding night?
Yet he was sleeping at
the back of the house.
- What are you saying?
- I'm telling the truth.
Brother Raju's is very unfortunate.
His mother turned out to be a witch.
And the wife, exactly the same.
Here comes the madam.
Pandu, what are you making?
Can't you see? I'm making gourd vegetable!
I'll make it.
Here, make it!
Why are you talking to me like that?
I don't respect a woman who...
...doesn't have any
respect for her husband.
- But what have I done?
- See what you've done!
Yesterday was brother
Raju's wedding night.
Still he was sleeping at the back
of the house. Why? Answer me!
If you didn't consider him
worthy, why did you marry him?
Who says I don't consider
him worthy of me?
The truth is I'm not worthy of him.
Then whatever I had heard...
All that was a lie.
You don't know.
The elders of this house
want to separate us...
...for their own selfish reasons!
They want to break our marriage.
But I'll never let them
fulfill their desire.
Just think. He protected me...
...and saved me from defamation.
Won't I respect him?
You don't know, Pandu,
he dwells in my heart.
Forgive me, sister-in-law,
I misunderstood you.
- You can hit me with your sandals.
- What are you doing?
Pandu, quickly bring the food!
- I'm dying of hunger!
- Die!
Coming!
What a big glutton they are!
They're never content no
matter how much you feed them.
Champa, first go and feed father.
- Then we'll feed these animals.
- Okay.
What is this?
Father is fed this food.
What can I do, sister-in-law?
I feel sad too.
- But those...
- Don't worry about them.
From today I'll take food for father.
Father.
- Daughter-in-law, you!
- Yes.
The family members eat and the
head of the family stays hungry.
It doesn't look nice.
Come.
Today I'll feed you.
Sit.
Father, you're crying.
For the past 20 years I
was craving for this love.
I was hungry for someone's affection.
Can I ask you something?
Why is this injustice going on
in this house for so many years?
Why doesn't anyone stop it?
I tried to stop her alone.
But along with her brother my
wife proved me to be insane...
...and left me in this hell to die.
I wanted to bring a mother for Raju.
But I brought a vamp.
She didn't let my Raju study.
She kept him as an illiterate.
So that she can take advantage of it!
My Raju considers that witch a Goddess!
He worships her!
Before she kills my Raju, save my son.
Save my Raju.
Gauri, Rani work carefully.
- Sir, where should I keep this?
- On my head.
Look, if the crop this year is not...
What are you doing?
You fool! Did I ask you
to keep it on my head?
- You said it.
- Keep it there! Go!
What is it, brother Raju?
You're looking very sad.
Seems like he didn't
sleep the entire night.
Stop blabbering and work.
- We're working.
- [BIRD CHIRPING]
Oh God! Brother Raju,
here comes your bride.
Brother Raju, what spell have
you cast on her in one night...
...that she doesn't even
leave you during the day?
Why have you come here?
I want to talk to you.
Whatever you want to say,
say it in that hut. Come.
He's taking her in the hut.
- Listen, I want to tell you...
- I know what you want to say.
You want to say I'm not worthy of you.
- Listen to me.
- I've heard it. You said at the fair...
...you'll marry only a prince...
- ...not a fool like me.
- But...
Saru, I'm your husband.
But I never tried to
assert my right on you.
Why didn't you?
What are you doing?
Marriage is the union of two souls.
Then let this union take place today.
[BIRD CHIRPING]
Do you think that you will
melt me by behaving like this?
I will die but will not
let you come close to me.
- Please agree, my prince.
- Never.
Listen. Don't force me to be 'Meneka'
(Indian mythological danseuse).
Listen. I am not sage 'Vishwamitra'
(Indian mythological sage)...
...that I will get lured.
- Is it? Is that what you think?
- Yes.
Yes, that is it.
Do you think that if you do all
this something will happen to me?
- Can you feel anything?
- No.
How about now?
No...
- What now?
- Yes, I can.
- Now?
- Can you feel now?
- Yes, I can.
- Gauri. Hey, Gauri.
- What is it?
- I am going home.
- Why?
I am missing him.
Hey, listen.
"Tell us, what did you say
sneakily to your beloved?"
"My eyes will lower with shyness."
"I'll feel coy."
"How can I just say
what happened with me?"
"Ask me, friend."
"Tell us, what did you say
sneakily to your beloved?"
"You're under our oath,
don't hide anything from us."
"Tell me, how did your
garland become a mess?"
"Tell us!"
'Tell us!'
"There was a bee in my garland."
"I was shooing it away with my hands."
"It was delicate."
"It was delicate.
It broke as soon as I touched it."
"And the flowers got scattered."
"Tell us, what did you say
sneakily to your beloved?"
"Tell me, why there are
teeth marks on your lips..."
"How did you get nail marks here?"
"Tell us!"
"I saw a parrot in the night."
"I was enticed seeing it."
"I went to pet the lovely parrot."
"He pecked on my lips and flew away."
"Tell us, what did you say
sneakily to your beloved?"
"Why are your tresses entangled?"
"Why are you clothes so wrinkled?"
"Tell us!"
"There was an unknown pain in my heart."
"My restlessness grew,
I started suffering."
"When I couldn't tolerate
the pain anymore..."
"...I held my heart with my own hands."
"We can't understand this problem?"
"Why have you worn the
skirt the wrong way?"
"Tell us!"
"You've been caught!"
"Look, she has been caught!"
"Come here."
"I'll tell you everything."
"I'll not keep any secret from you."
"What do love-birds say to each other?"
"What the lamp does with the wick."
"What the Earth sings to the sky."
"What the bee tells the bud."
"Even we said that to each other..."
"Listen, friend."
Mother!
- Mother!
- What is it, son?
Look, Ramesh has become a doctor...
- ...and brought so many degrees.
- Really?
- Mother.
- Bless you.
Now your dreams are fulfilled.
Right, Mother?
- You're happy?
- Yes, son.
I'm very happy that Ramesh
has become a doctor.
Ramesh has finished his education.
Now find a nice girl and get him married.
So Ramesh, shall we look for
a girl or do you like someone?
Mother, that...
What? Tell me who that girl is?
How is her family?
What does she do? What is her name?
Brother, her name is Kunika.
She's from a very rich family.
But there is only one problem.
What problem?
She's a modern girl.
She wants a court marriage,
not the traditional kind.
We don't care about that.
We only want a daughter-in-law. Right?
- Raju is right, son.
- You got mother's permission too.
Now arrange to bring daughter-in-law.
Come.
What is all this commotion?
It's not a commotion.
We're bursting crackers for your arrival.
Shut up, you bloody servant.
Ramesh, you've brought daughter-in-law!
- Champa!
- Yes.
- Champa, quickly bring the lamp.
- There is no need for all that.
All this is old tradition.
I don't believe in it.
I just want to take a cold water bath.
Come on, darling, let us go in.
Yes, daughter-in-law. Come.
[BIRD CHIRPING]
- She's a modern girl.
- Yes.
Oh God! Such a long journey!
My entire body is aching!
If you're tired,
shall I massage your legs?
- If you don't mind?
- Of course not.
Brother Ramesh, tea!
I didn't see anything!
What an era! It has been 40
years since independence...
...but still the husbands of our
country are their wife's slaves.
- Right, Ramesh?
- Stop this nonsense and serve the tea.
Here. I was about to do that.
- Tea.
- Have it.
- What happened, madam?
- What happened?
What disgusting tea.
What are you saying, madam?
People come from far to
drink the tea prepared by me.
And you're calling it disgusting.
I think something is wrong
with your taste buds.
Your husband is a doctor.
Ask him to check you up.
- Crazy servant!
- She's calling you.
I'm telling you...
Look, madam! My name isn't 'servant'!
My name is Pandu Dhondu Bhikajirao!
You argue with us, donkey?!
What an era! You're kicking
me and calling me donkey.
- Why you...
- Ramesh!
Pandu, what is all this?
Just see sister-in-law, this servant...
- My name isn't servant, my name is...
- Pandu!
That's right.
That's not the way to talk to your master.
Do your work.
Kunika, did you take father's blessings?
No, I can't go to that madman's room.
He might break my head or strangle me.
Kunika, aren't you ashamed to say
that about your father-in-law?
Ashamed of what?
The entire world knows he's mad.
He's a crazy madman.
- Do you know what you're saying?
- Sister-in-law, she's right.
Ramesh!
She was acting so smart.
Come, Father.
Come.
Why did you stop?
Daughter-in-law, you don't know.
- Those people...
- Nothing will happen. Come.
Come on.
My kin left me to rot in that hell.
You're a stranger,
yet you freed me from that hell.
Bless you, dear.
Come, let's go to the temple.
Sister-in-law! What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
Bringing this madman in this
house can be dangerous...
...like bringing a wild animal!
Yes, brother.
In this house wolves roam freely...
- ...but cows are tired to the pole!
- Shut up!
Shut up you!
[GIBBERISH]
Darn mad goat, talking nonsense!
Look, madam,
even I know how to abuse in English!
But I'm from this country
which believes in modesty.
And in this country,
the daughter-in-law of the family...
...covers her head in
front of her in-laws.
They don't stay nude like this.
Take my towel and cover yourself.
- You crazy servant.
- She's calling you?
You!
Come, Father.
You can't take him along!
Keep your delicate hands to yourself.
Use them only for brushing your tresses...
...or I'll break them. Got it?
- Darling...
- Come, father.
That's why I was saying not to lock horns.
You got defamed yourself.
- Shut up, you servant!
- Yes, madam!
- Run!
- You!
You didn't do the right thing
by bringing him out of the room!
I know what's right and what's wrong.
But maybe you don't know it.
Now you'll teach me right and wrong?
Yes, when the elders
of the house forget...
...the difference between
right and wrong...
...it's the duty of the juniors
to show them the right way.
- Daughter-in-law!
- Don't shout!
Husband is considered God!
But you treated your
husband worse than animals!
You aren't even worthy
of being called a human!
We're animals!
Why didn't I go deaf before hearing that?
Thank God that my son Raju didn't hear...
...whatever you said.
I want him to hear it!
I want him to know how greedy
and selfish his mother is! -Suru!
If you say another word against my
mother, I'll not spare you!
Raju, you don't know the
kind of woman your mother is!
She didn't let you study,
kept you an illiterate...
...to take advantage of you!
Your mother doesn't have any
love or affection for you!
She just desires your wealth!
The mother you worship is
a witch and not a Goddess!
What did you say?
I'll not spare you today.
I'll kill you!
You called my mother a witch!
- You called my mother a witch!
- Raju.
- Move away!
- Leave her!
- She called you a witch.
- You're under my oath! Leave her!
Did you see the greatness of my mother?
You abused her so much, but she saved you!
Or else I wouldn't have spared you today!
But remember one thing.
If you want to stay in this house...
...you'll have to apologise to my mother!
Or else there is no place
for you in this house!
I don't want to stay in such a house...
...where you're punished
for telling the truth!
What a women she is, sister!
See her stubbornness.
She didn't even respect her husband.
Indian woman! You're great.
[BIRD CHIRPING]
Since I've come in this
house, I've been ruling it.
And no one could change it.
You're nothing.
So heed my advice.
Open your mouth only to eat food.
Or else I'll make your
life worse than hell.
'I swear on my husband...'
'...until I don't eradicate
the injustice in this house...'
'...I won't rest peacefully! '
[WIND HOWLING]
Raju.
I've hurt you!
Please forgive me!
I should apologise, Suru.
I treated you like animal.
But what can I do?
Whenever someone says
something against my mother...
...I lose control over myself.
You can abuse me all you want.
But never say anything against my mother.
I beg you.
What has happened?
I've punished myself for slapping you.
Raju.
Forgive me.
I didn't know you loved me so much!
I'll never leave you!
"Beloved."
"Beloved, beloved."
"I'm yours, you're mine."
"We don't care about this world."
"I want to give you all the happiness."
"I'm yours, you're mine."
"We don't care about this world."
"Sweetheart."
"Sweetheart, sweetheart."
"You're mine, I'm yours."
"We don't care about this world."
"I want to give you all the happiness."
"I'm yours, you're mine."
"We don't care about this world."
"I'll abide by all the vows
of the nuptial rounds."
"I came in the palanquin."
"I'll leave only on the bier."
"I'll abide by all my vows too."
"I'll never hurt you again."
"There is nothing without you."
"You're my world."
"We don't care about this world."
"I'm yours, you're mine."
"I'll never leave in either
happiness or sorrows."
happiness or sorrow."
"Now I'll never leave your hands."
"It was my fate that I got you."
"The Lord has sent you for me."
"You're in my heart, in my soul."
"I can't leave you."
"We don't care about this world."
"You're mine, I'm yours."
"I'm yours, you're mine."
"We don't care about this world."
I had a broken leg,
now I'll have a broken back too.
I've loaded your goods. Give me the money.
Mr. Totaram, here are Rs.200,000.
Give me. - Bye. - Bye.
- Daulatram, Rs.200,000.
- Close it.
Totaram, should I write down
Rs.200,000 in the account?
Write in the account book...
...due to fire in the storehouse
there was a loss of Rs.200,000.
But... -I know you'll say in the
previous months there were fires in...
...the fields and well
and the pumps were burnt.
- But there's a fire this month too...
- Quiet.
Quickly. Put it in.
- Ramlal, water the garden properly.
- Start. [BIRD CHIRPING]
Pandu, my husband toils day and night!
And you don't care at all.
There has been so much loss? Useless!
Saru, what are you doing?
Pandu is our old servant
and you're slapping him.
Then ask him...
...why was there a fire in the
storehouse, the fields and the well.
Fire! Forget the storehouse and fields...
...in the last two years there wasn't
any fire in the entire village, Saru.
I'm not saying it.
It's written in the accounts books.
It's written there has been a loss of
millions of rupees due to the fire.
Loss of millions of rupees!
- Who writes the accounts book?
- Accountant!
Accountant, how is this week for me?
Tell me.
Your misfortune is going to start!
- Accountant!
- Yes!
Yes, sir!
What's written in this accounts book?
Read it out.
- The storehouse of the grains...
- Why are you looking around?
Read properly what's written in it!
Read it quickly.
Due to a fire in the
food grain storehouse...
...there was a loss of Rs. 200,000.
Seems like your eyesight has become weak.
It's written that there has
been a profit of Rs.200,000...
...because of the sales.
And you're saying there was a loss!
Betrayer!
Uncle, there is no need to act too smart!
My wife is educated.
She told me everything!
Accountant, tell me clearly!
Was there a fire in the storage house?
That... there... it...
You won't tell me like that!
Pandu! Where is my whip?
The whip will be of no use in this matter!
Here is the gun.
There are real bullets in it.
One shot and the truth will come out.
Shoot him!
Now tell me the truth!
How much money have you embezzled?
Sir, I haven't swindled the money.
Totaram has done everything.
- Uncle!
- Where are you running?
Leave me!
Don't try to run...
...or else I'll shoot you!
I'm your only uncle. Don't shoot me.
Stop acting, Uncle!
Tell me, where is all the swindled money?
What's happening?
Sister! Save me!
I'm being punished so
severely for a small mistake.
Mother, being your brother...
...I gave him the responsibility
of maintaining the accounts.
And he deceived the one
who gave him shelter!
And swindled millions of rupees.
I've realised my mistake. Forgive me.
Get up, brother.
Let it be, son.
What has happened has happened.
- Forgive him.
- Forgive me.
Fine, Mother.
If you say so, I'll forgive him.
What are you saying?
If he had deceived just you,
it would've been fine...
...but he has deceived
your great mother too.
- How can you spare him?
- Absolutely right.
Mother, you're very innocent.
That's why everyone deceives you.
We shouldn't trust a person like him.
Tell me, uncle,
where have you kept the swindled money?
- Or else...
- Don't shoot.
Snake! Snake!
There is a snake in my room!
- I won't let you take the mattress.
- No.
I won't give you this mattress.
There is a snake in it.
- What happened?
- There is a snake in this mattress.
He's mad. To him, a rope is a snake.
If you don't find a
snake in this mattress...
...you can send me to the asylum today.
Let this madmen mumble. Listen to me.
Pandu, bring the mattress outside.
- My mattress!
- Move.
Don't sleep on the mattress.
The snake will bite you. -Move.
Raju, I admit there is
a snake in my mattress.
But it's my pet snake.
My dear pet snake.
I've kept it for 15 years
in my bed like my child.
Get up from the mattress! Get up!
What? You don't believe me?
You've insulted me, my holy snake!
Now I can't live in
this house for a moment!
I'm going along with my holy snake.
Far away from the society.
Mainawati, you shouldn't
live where there isn't peace.
Wait, uncle!
Pandu, come and take this mattress.
I'll not let you take the mattress!
No way! -Give it.
I won't leave it!
I won't let you open it! -Leave it!
Or else I'll blow your brains out!
My snake!
Scaring me with the gun!
I never thought you could
do such a lowly act.
If you're burned alive,
even that's too less a punishment.
And listen, from today you're
a servant and not the owner.
You'll work like the laborers
who work in our field.
That's your punishment!
- I'll not work in the fields!
- Quiet!
I'll work in the fields!
But I've a small request!
What? -My wife was a
partner in this deed too.
- I want her to work in the fields too.
- Why not?!
You dare hit your husband.
I've kept all the money in this bag.
Give it to mother.
Wait! What are you doing?
Don't you have any sense?
By giving money to mother you're
endangering her life. You know that.
How is that?
You're so innocent.
Mother keeps the suitcase
near her head while sleeping.
What if someday uncle
gets wrong intentions...
...and he crushes mother's head
with a stone and steals the money?
You're right.
- Give this suitcase to Saru.
- Me?
- Who else?
- No.
This is risky work. You take care of it.
Fine.
Whatever you feel is fine.
If you say so, I'll take this risk too.
I can do anything for mother.
Right, Mother?
Congratulations,
I have to praise your plan.
You're very good at it.
I've learnt it from you, mother-in-law.
But remember one thing...
...I'm an old player of this game.
No one can compete with me.
Mother-in-law,
till now you were playing with amateurs.
You never come across
expert players like me.
Start worrying about your pawn.
You don't know what a
dangerous game you're playing.
Without danger there
is no fun in the game.
And I don't often get a chance
to play with players like you.
You like to play a lot?
Fine.
Tomorrow before 12 o'clock,
you'll give this money to me.
That's my challenge.
Madam, your telegram.
[BIRD CHIRPING]
Whose telegram is it?
Ramesh has been rusticated
from the college. -What?
Then how did he... What are you doing?
Don't leave home.
- No, daughter-in-law. Listen to me.
- Not at all!
I won't stay here another minute.
My father isn't a poor man!
If I go to him,
he can do anything for my husband!
Our honour is at stake.
I beg you!
Mother, what's going on?
I'll tell you.
My husband has studied to be a doctor.
And he wants to build
a hospital in the city.
For that, I asked your mother for 600,000.
But do you know what your mother said?
She said this wealth belongs to Raju.
And his money can't be
given to anyone else!
Brother is the only successor
of this entire wealth.
Is brother the only successor of
this family? I'm the step-son.
What are you saying, Munna?
Mother must have said
this without thinking.
But why are you saying that?
You want to build a hospital?
Tell me, how much money do you need?
- Rs.600,000.
- Fine.
- Saru.
- Yes?
I gave you money yesterday to keep safely.
- Bring it.
- Yes.
Brother, I'll return your
money with interest...
...as soon as my hospital opens.
What did you say?
Don't be mad? I'm not a stranger.
Munna, everything belongs to us!
- Here.
- Give this money to Ramesh.
Brother, I'd like to take this
money from mother's lucky hands.
Yes, that's even better.
- Saru, give this suitcase to mother.
- Yes.
Just a minute.
Brother, what's the time?
Two seconds left for 12 o'clock.
Give it, daughter-in-law.
She's defeated.
Listen, can I say something?
Instead of opening a
hospital in the city...
...let's open a charitable dispensary
in the village in mother's name.
She'll be so honoured!
Wow! How nice!
A charitable dispensary in mother's name.
Now that will happen.
Calm down!
My dear brothers and sisters!
Today, we're going to lay...
...the foundation of a charitable
hospital in our village.
It'll be inaugurated by
my great mother-in-law.
And this hospital will be named after her!
Applause! Applause!
[APPLAUSE]
Give it.
And the second garland is for our doctor.
He'll treat you with his skilled hands.
I'm referring to my dear brother-in-law.
He studied day and night in the city.
After receiving several degrees
he has come to rid your sorrows.
Applause! Applause!
Sister-in-law, this garland...
This is just the first
garland brother-in-law.
- You still have to wear a lot of garlands.
- What do you mean?
I mean, this garland marks
your victory brother-in-law.
Stop it!
Mainawati, do you see them
adorning him with garlands?
When I went to the
goddess's temple earlier...
...they were putting garlands on
the goats much in the same way...
...before they were sacrificed.
I feel there is something wrong.
Will they...
- Inspector.
- The inspector is here.
See, mother is so famous.
The hospital's foundation
has still not been laid...
...and the inspector has
come for the treatment.
Come, inspector.
Have sweets. You too, constable.
I haven't come here for sweets.
I'm on duty and I've
come here for a reason.
What's the reason, inspector?
Nothing special. I just want to
see your brother's medical degrees.
You want to see his medical degrees!
Inspector, either you're mocking
my brother or insulting him.
I'm just doing my duty.
Ask your brother to show his degrees.
I'll be satisfied and leave.
You doubt my brother!
See... -There is no use in
blowing things out of proportion.!
Ask your brother to show them his degrees.
You're right, Saru.
Ramesh, show them your degrees.
Inspector, just a minute.
Please.
Inspector, please don't blow
things out of proportion.
- If you want, you can take some money.
- What did you say?
What are you doing?
Leave my brother's collar.
Why are you manhandling
him as if he was a thief?
Your brother deserves this!
As he's a conman and a cheat!
He was trying to bribe me.
You brother doesn't have any
degree and he's not a doctor!
How is that possible?
My brother had brought a
suitcase full of degrees.
They must have been waste papers...
...which you get cheaply in the city.
Such a betrayal by my brother!
He shattered my mother's dreams.
I'm arresting him for posing as a doctor.
Don't do that. Please don't do it.
We'll be defamed.
My mother won't be able to face anyone.
I beg of you.
Please spare him for my mother's honour.
Let him off the hook.
I'll leave him today with just a warning.
But if he errs again,
the consequences will be grave.
Thank you very much!
Useless! Deceiver!
You betrayed my mother!
- The entire village is taunting her!
- Raju.
Mocking her!
You betrayed her all her life.
You made her believe that you're a doctor.
- Raju, don't...
- Let it be, mother.
My brother-in-law can't
tolerate his beatings.
If you beat him too,
he won't be able to tolerate it.
- Leave me.
- No. Let it be. Spare him.
Leave me.
Keep it.
From today I want to see
you working in the fields!
Now go! What are you looking at? Go!
Go!
Raju!
What about the money that you gave Ramesh!
Give it to Saru.
Daughter-in-law,
the game is getting very exciting.
One after the other, the opponent
is losing his pawns. -Yes, father.
Earlier it was a pawn,
but today a minister was defeated.
Sister!
How much more will you make us
work, brother-in-law?
It's dawn. Do you want to kill us?
Get up. Move.
Why did you bring me here?
I was well off in the city.
- I miss my mother.
- I miss my father.
Food is ready! Come here, gluttons.
Food!
Food has been served!
You get what you're destined for. Eat it!
Daughter-in-law, what did you do?
Our food.
This food isn't for you.
- Pandu!
- Here.
Here is your food.
After toiling the entire day we
get this bread, chili and onion.
No, we don't want this food.
Fine, don't eat it. Go to hell.
I'll feed this food to Tommy. Tommy!
Eat it!
- Here.
- The dog is more fortunate than you.
Now you'll get food tomorrow afternoon.
Tomorrow afternoon!
- That means after 24 hours.
- I'll die!
Let us snatch it from the dog.
You dog!
The pawn is gone, the minister is gone.
Now only the queen remains.
Once the queen is in our grasp, that's it.
Then check and mate.
Pandu!
- Pandu!
- Come on. Pandu!
Where is he? Pandu!
Leave me! I say leave me!
We won't. We've caught
you with so difficultly.
Daughter-in-law, catch her tightly.
Don't worry, father,
I've held her tightly.
- Leave me.
- Saru!
- Why have you caught my mother?
- Son...
Blood! How is there blood?
- Nothing has happened to me, son.
- Mother, please lie down.
It's not right to speak in such a condition.
I'll tell you.
Mother was descending down the stairs.
Suddenly, she felt dizzy,
slipped and fell down.
It usually happens with
high blood pressure.
- High blood pressure!
- Yes, son. High blood pressure.
And it usually happens to
those who are arrogant.
- No, dear. Nothing happened to me.
- Nothing happened?
My friend's mother had the same ailment.
Because of her negligence,
she vomited blood 100 times.
She died such a terrible death.
- God save everyone from such a death.
- Don't say that, Saru.
She's right, mother.
Your life is very precious to me.
Lie down. I'll get the doctor.
- Listen!
- Yes.
You think we don't care for mother?
We've already informed the doctor.
He must be... Here comes the doctor.
I'm doctor T.B. Malaria.
MDA, RC, TUB, WXY.
Come, doctor.
See what's happened to her.
- What has happened to you?
- Doctor, she's the patient.
She's the patient. Patient...
Oh, God!
Wrong! Terribly wrong! Do one thing.
Arrange for 2 bamboos, 2 meter cloth...
...a pot and fire.
- What are you saying, doctor?
- Wrong! Terribly wrong!
Only prayers, no medication can help her.
- "Oh, God!"
- How could you say that?
First check her up.
[CLEARING THROAT]
I surely will.
- What has happened to my sister?
- Sister! Who is this old man?
He's my uncle.
Uncle, look what has happened to mother.
- Sister.
- Quiet!
No noise. We don't have much time.
I should quickly start the treatment.
- Catch this.
- Give it to her.
[SHOUTING]
Save me!
Doctor, what happened to him?
Seems like he has got epilepsy.
- Fine!
- What fine?
Oh, God, what has happened?
Stop shaking.
I've switched off the current.
Don't you see what you've done to me?
Her head is lit up with 440 volts.
That means this woman uses
her head a bit too much.
It's dangerous! Very dangerous!
Doctor, there must be some
treatment for it. -Sure.
She should be given
margosa leaves sherbet.
- Margosa leaves.
- Here.
Make her drink it.
- No, Raju. I won't drink it.
- Drink it, mother.
- You'll be fine.
- Yes.
It's very bitter. I can't drink it.
Mother, drink it for
your Raju's sake. -Yes.
- I can't drink it.
- Drink it for your Raju's sake.
- Drink it, mother.
Bravo.
A bit more.
Doctor...
...will my mother survive now?
It's my duty to try.
I've given her the medicine.
I have to give her injection.
Doctor, this injection is quite big.
It's very effective too.
One day I injected a jenny.
She came first in the horse race.
- I won't take the injection!
- You have to.
- Hold her limbs.
- No.
- Take the injection, mother!
- Raju!
[SCREAMING]
It's done.
I did what I could.
She needs lots of rest.
No food. Don't get down from the bed.
What are you saying, doctor?
She looks after the
entire house and business.
She has to open and close
the safe many times a day.
Who will take this
responsibility from now on?
Wow! When will this
daughter-in-law be of use?
I'm educated!
And doing such menial work is below me!
If I slap you,
you'll forget your education!
- You'll have to take the keys!
- But...
No ifs and buts!
- Mother, give me the keys.
- Keys!
- Son, I...
- Give the keys.
- She won't be able to take care of it.
- I'll make her.
- Raju.
- No.
From today the responsibility
of the entire house is on you.
- Keep the keys.
- I'll not take it.
- I told you...
- Daughter-in-law!
It's your duty to shoulder
your mother-in-law's burden.
Keep the keys, dear.
- Fine.
- No.
If you say so, I'll keep it.
- We lost the keys too.
- She ruined everything.
Saru, what has happened to you?
Oh God, who has cast an
evil eye on our house?
- Doctor, please...
- What are you doing?
I know what has happened to me?
You're laughing.
Tell me what's the matter. -That...
Tell me what's the matter.
You're going to be a father?
That's fine but...
- What? I'm going to be a father?
- Yes.
Saru, I'm going to be a father! Mother!
I'm going to be a father!
You're going to be a granny.
Father, I'm going to be a father.
- Pandu!
- Yes, sir?
He has gone to the fields.
If there is any message for him, tell me.
Ask Pandu to quickly
go to my father-in-law.
And give him this news.
Yes, sir.
Saru!
What are you doing?
[GRUNTS]
What is this, doctor?
What has happened to her?
What are you doing?
What has happened?
Doctor, what's wrong with her?
Seems like my injection is taking effect.
In three to four hours
she'll win the race.
Doctor!
Mainawati!
Ramdas, what has happened?
Sir, the clutch plate and
fuel pump isn't working.
Oh God, now how will we
plough the field in a day?
Pandu, listen.
Let's buy the tractor
parts from the city. -Yes.
- Champa.
- Yes.
Tell everyone we'll
return tomorrow morning.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Bye. I'm getting late. I'll come again.
And yes, I've brought
all this for all of you.
And this saffron for Saru.
Why saffron?
Brother, our ancestors say...
...if a pregnant woman drinks
saffron mixed in milk...
...the child born is fair and beautiful.
Ask her to mix it in milk
everyday and drink it. -Yes.
I'll leave now.
- Yes. Good bye. - Good bye.
Come on, start.
After a long time,
we've got sweets to eat.
Have patience, brother!
Sister, if Saru arrives we'll
not get to eat all this.
- Again, millet bread and vegetable.
- Listen to me first.
- Ramesh.
- Yes, mother.
Take the key...
...and bring the poison
bottle from my cupboard. -Yes.
Sister, why are you asking
for the poison bottle?
Do you want us to commit suicide?
Brother, didn't you ask me
what my last move will be?
- This will be my last move.
- I didn't understand you.
The situation has gone out of control.
Now either she'll live
in this house or me!
Absolutely right.
Now that you've taken the
step, don't retreat!
Her death is our life!
Here, Mother.
She wanted to compete with me.
She doesn't know that I like a serpent.
And a serpent devours her own children!
Then how can I spare you and your child?
- Raju.
- Yes, Mother.
Saru's mother isn't alive.
And this is her first child.
So we'll have to take care of her.
Her father came today
and gave this saffron.
Mix it in the milk and make her drink it.
What for?
So that the child that's
born is fair and beautiful.
Really? Then I'll make
her drink it right away.
Saru, look what I have...
What are you doing?
And that too in this condition.
Come down.
Why have you put up
such a big snap of mine?
It's a secret.
First take me in your
arms, then I'll tell you.
Here.
It's said that the child
resembles the person whose face...
...a pregnant lady always sees.
- Really?
- Yes.
And so I've put up your snap.
So that your face is
always in front of me...
...and in a few days a small
Raju is born just like you.
Then remove this photo
and put up your snap.
- Why?
- Because it'll be a girl first.
- It'll be a boy.
- I'm telling you, it's a girl.
- It'll be a girl.
What is this?
Saffron! Oh, where is the milk?
Where are you going?
Your father gave this saffron.
He said that if you drink
this saffron mixed in milk...
...the child born will
be fair and beautiful.
Drink the milk before it cools down.
Just a minute!
I'll add more saffron so
that the baby is very fair.
Enough! This saffron is
for the entire month.
Do you want to finish it today?
If it's finished, I'll get more.
Drink the milk quickly.
Feed me.
I'll feed you.
What happened?
I'm drinking this saffron
milk for the first time.
I'll bow in front of God.
What's the matter, Champa?
Why did you stop me?
Sister, the saffron milk that
you were going to drink...
...contains poison.
What? Poison!
Yes, I saw madam mixing poison in it.
No.
- That can't be.
- It has happened.
I swear on my husband, it has happened!
Saru, what happened?
Have you finished your veneration?
Come quickly. The milk is getting cold.
Have you finished the veneration...
Here.
What is the matter? What is this for?
I'd like to die by the
hands of my husband...
...rather than being
poisoned by someone else.
Take it and kill me!
What has happened to you suddenly?
You had mixed saffron in the milk!
There is poison in that saffron!
Poison! What nonsense?!
There is poison in the saffron!
Your father had given this saffron.
Why would he poison her daughter?
My father had only given the saffron.
But your mother added poison in it!
My mother mixed poison in the milk!
Are you out of your mind, Saru?
Don't say that!
I'll have to punish you for it!
You can even kill me if you want!
Because I knew you'd never believe me!
- Pick up this axe and kill me.
- Saru.
Don't accuse my mother
of such a grave crime.
Don't accuse her!
Before my mother becomes a
murderer, the sky will fall...
...sun and the moon will
change their course!
The Earth will change its position!
But all of them are in their place.
That proves everything you said is a lie!
You're lying!
I'm lying!
If I'm lying, my unborn child will die!
If you strongly believe in
it, my faith is unshakeable!
Now we have to prove...
...whether this milk is poisoned or not.
There is no need for mother to prove it.
I'll drink this milk and do it.
No!
No! What have you done?
I became the reason for your death!
If I knew you would drink the
milk, I would've drunk it!
What shall I do now?
Come with me to the doctor!
- Come, I'll take you to the doctor.
- Leave me!
You can go to the doctor if you want to!
Nothing has happened to me.
I'll be fine here.
Oh God! What should I do? Where can I go?!
Father!
Witch, tell him!
Tell him there was poison in the milk!
Or else my Raju won't survive!
Murderer, why are you standing quietly?
Tell him there was poison in the milk!
Don't dare say anything against my mother!
I'll kill you!
I...
I'll call the doctor!
Did you see, Mother? She suspects you!
She went to call the doctor!
Let her call him. She'll know too.
You've loved me more than your own son.
And she was provoking me against you!
She has called you a murderer!
She said that you've
mixed poison in the milk.
That unfortunate girl doesn't know...
...that a mother's love
turns poison into milk.
'My father had only given saffron.'
'But your mother mixed poison in it.'
[ANTIQUE CLOCK TICKING]
Mother! The first word
that a child says...
...after being born is mother.
He learns and says a lot
of things while growing up.
But I didn't learn
anything other than mother.
I didn't say anything else.
Tell me, why did you do all this?
You should've just told me.
Look, Raju. I want your entire wealth.
Put your thumb impression here.
I swear I would've cut off my thumb.
If you had asked me,
I would've killed myself.
Then why did you do all this?
Tell me.
Why did you do it?
Mother...
...your unfortunate son has a last wish.
Please fulfill it.
It's forbidden for women
to come to the crematorium.
But please come for me.
And before my pyre is set on fire...
...call me son once from your heart.
So that I can die peacefully.
I don't want anything else. Nothing else.
[COUGHING AND VOMITING]
Doctor!
Come quickly!
Quickly!
Come.
All this... -There is no need to be
scared, daughter-in-law.
We've locked your husband in the room.
And we have the key to it.
It's good that you've brought the doctor.
He's counting his last breath.
But we'll have to save his life.
But for that you'll have to
bear a small inconvenience.
You'll have to sign on the will.
Scoundrels, all your life you
made Raju's life miserable!
Now you want take
advantage of his death too!
Even animals aren't so heartless!
You want wealth? Take it.
Tell me where I have to sign.
Ramesh!
You'll not sign on these papers!
Open the door, daughter-in-law!
- Have you gone mad, Mother?
- Leave me!
Thieves have an honour too.
They're afraid of God.
But us, we stooped so low...
...that we were adamant on
killing that innocent Raju...
...who kept worshipping a
witch like me all his life!
But today if we save him...
...maybe we can repent for our sins!
Maybe the Lord will forgive us.
But...
But if he dies today,
it won't be just Raju's murder.
It'll be the murder of all the mothers!
It'll be the murder of the word "mother"!
And I'll be the murderer! A mother!
What nonsense are you uttering, sister?
How did you develop
feelings for Raju today?
We can't lose the wealth for which...
...we waited for 15 years.
At least think about your own son!
Kaykeyi only exiled Ram for
14 years for her Bharat.
But I sentenced my Raju
to death for my son.
Ramesh, if you love and respect
your mother even a bit...
...give me the keys.
But first give me the property papers.
Look, son... Saru!
- Saru, that...
- Give me the property papers, Mother.
Or else I...
You behave with your mother in this
way, scoundrel!
Bravo, son!
Good!
You've returned your mother's love nicely.
But it's not your fault, Ramesh.
It was the Lord's justice...
...in the form of this slap.
You've proved it today...
...that a serpent can give
birth only to a snake...
...not a son like my Raju.
But remember.
Even if you kill me,
I'll not give you this property papers!
Mother, better give me these papers...
...or else I know other means!
She has gone mad!
Snatch the papers quickly!
- Give me these papers, Mother!
- I won't.
You won't.
Raju!
Ramesh, quickly snatch the papers!
Raju! Dear Raju!
Raju!
No!
Dear Raju!
Raju!
Raju! Dear.
Mother!
Raju!
- No!
- Mother!
No!
No! Raju!
[BIRD CHIRPING]
Father, I'm leaving this house.
I know it's the duty of a son...
...to look after his
parents in their old age.
But maybe it was not in my fate.
So I've transferred the
property in mother's name.
Father, take care of my mother.
Come, Saru.
Mother, what are you doing?
I know, son, I'm your culprit.
Punish me if you want.
But please don't leave your mother.
I don't want this property!
Nothing!
I want my son, my Raju.
I want my son.
I want my son, Raju.
Mother.
"It's a joyous day."
"I got what I wanted."
"Today my mother called me son."
"It's a joyous day."
"I got what I wanted."
"Today my mother called me son."
"Mother! My mother!"
"Mother, I have to grow
up in your shelter."
"Holding your finger,
I have to walk with you."
"You're the boon of my prayer."
"You're my God."