'Mangudi - Nellai District'
You've come after 2 years
You must hear the latest gossip
Please spare me
You know-who's become tame after
marriage
- What a swinger he used to me
- Enough
Muthiah's wife ran away with
Bahadur's son
They met at the Cinema house
Keep quiet
Sethu had a baby girl, Sixth one
But the speed is not lesser till now
The last monsoon was heavy,
but no great harvest
- In that rain..
- Get lost
You walked out of this house
went to Bombay
But you're back now
I'll leave if you want
Stay! What righteous Indignation!
Inherited from you
I said I inherited that from you
You went so far away to study
Have you got through
He'll definitely pass with good grades
I agree, But what next?
I only asked what you intend to do
He's got a job in Bombay
He's going to work also
study Journalism
Heard that?
- What Ism was that?
- Journalism
And the fees?
Who will pay that?
Money doesn't grow on trees?
I've got a job as proof reader
with a Newspaper
That will see me through
So! You don't need your
father's help, right?
You'll do what you like, but you
won't return to the village, right?
You haven't fallen for a
North India have you?
Nothing like that
We're a respected Pillai family
in this village
Don't bring home some Gujarati
or Punjab girl
That would be terrible Eat now
Did I come from Bombay only
to escort you around?
You don't lose anything by doing
that, do you?
- Greetings
- Do you know who is it?
Narayan Pillai's son
Doesn't dad told you to be
a responsible elder brother?
He's totally jobless
- Hasn't your father come?
- He's gone to the town
- I was your Tamil Teacher
- Yes
"Quick, my dear parakeet
Find your pair discreet"
"Oh girl! So beautiful as moon
exchange the garlands soon"
"If your beau visits you at night
make a knot by hugging him tight"
"Keep safe it in your heart
whatever your spouse taught"
"If your beau comes to you at night
make a knot by hugging him tight"
"Keep safe it in your heart
whatever your dearie taught"
"Since I laid eyes on you, I've been
blinded by love"
"Having stolen my heart, why do you
still remain silent?"
"I know not who you are
Yet you create waves in my heart"
"We've not exchanged names
Yet we have exchanged hearts"
"There's no opportunity to speak"
"What's the cure for the love sick?"
"Since I laid eyes on you, I've been
blinded by love"
"Having stolen my heart, why do you
still remain silent?"
"I know not who you are
Yet you create waves in my heart"
"We've not exchanged names
Yet we have exchanged hearts"
"There's no opportunity to speak"
"What's the cure for the love sick?"
"A piercing glance from your eyes..."
"Sends waves of ecstasy in my heart"
"I saw your face at a glance"
"The blood races through the veins"
"The mind is agitated like a leaf
in a storm"
"What can the poor dew drop do?"
"When there's fire in a forest
of Bamboo?"
"She's on fire like the Bamboo"
"Since I laid eyes on you, I've been
blinded by love"
"Having stolen my heart, why do you
still remain silent?"
"I know not who you are
Yet you create waves in my heart"
"We've not exchanged names
Yet we have exchanged hearts"
"There's no opportunity to speak"
"What's the cure for the love sick?"
"Quick, my dear parakeet
Find your pair discreet"
"Oh girl! So beautiful as moon
exchange the garlands soon"
"If your beau visits you at night
make a knot by hugging him tight"
"Keep safe it in your heart
whatever your spouse taught"
"If your beau comes to you at night
make a knot by hugging him tight"
"Keep safe it in your heart
whatever your dearie taught"
"Your glance pierces me like
a flash of lightning"
"That has evoked in me pangs
of yearning"
"I'm not myself, I feel I'm in
a different world"
"If I lose you I'll be
a flower without Nectar"
"I ask myself if this is real
or just a dream"
"Just a look at you
I'm lost for words"
"Since I laid eyes on you, I've been
blinded by love"
"Having stolen my heart, why do you
still remain silent?"
"I know not who you are
Yet you create waves in my heart"
"We've not exchanged names
Yet we have exchanged hearts"
"There's no opportunity to speak"
"What's the cure for the love sick?"
"Since I laid eyes on you, I've been
blinded by love"
"Having stolen my heart, why do you
still remain silent?"
"Since I laid eyes on you..."
Listen to me, If we trespass
they won't spare us
Let's not court trouble
But we're just standing here
That's trouble enough
Saheb's coming
I'll kill you if you leave from here
What're you doing here?
Greetings, sir
They will behead us if they know
we're eyeing the girls
Let them
You're in love, not me
They're coming
That's it, we're done for
- Which one of the girls?
- How the hell should I know?
It's not too late let's split
- Which one is her? Can you make out?
- No
All this fuss for nothing
Let's go
- Shekhar, one veil turned around
- Which one?
Red Bag
Do you like him?
Keep quiet
Don't lie to me
I know everything
What's your name?
Why did you close the door?
Hurry, There's a lot of work
I'm coming
Are you crazy?
Crazy girl
- Banu
- Mom
I am sure my dad will not sign
in this progress report
There is a chance
I'll discontinue my studies
I will not come to school tomorrow
Let's exchange bags, quick
What for?
Don't question
Just give it to me
What is the need for us
to exchange our bags?
Who is it?
Oh gawd!
Hey, red
So he's the reason
He has come close to us
Give me a minute..please
I have something to say
I don't know how to say it
but I'll tell you anyway
Don't cry! Why're you crying?
I haven't said anything yet
I saw the red bag and mistook you
for someone else
Come inside
- Chemistry Book
- Just a minute
Lakshmi's gone inside
Here it is
Don't forget to bring it to
class tomorrow
They will chop off your hand, Shekhar
Let them I've 2 hands, Isn't it?
Why the hell are you playing with fire?
I'll fix you a better bride
- Marry her yourself
- Please listen to me
I beg you, don't do this
Don't nag
Come faster
- Is that Zeenat?
- Who else?
Taking her own sweet time
walk carefully, dear
Zeenat will be engaged soon
No wonder she seems so happy
Careful, or the boat will capsize
Don't be silly
Is Zeenat so inferior to you?
You said you wouldn't come today
Did you get the signature?
Where's your bag?
How can you forget your bag?
What's the matter?
Screaming like a woman in labor
What happened?
Zeenat, hold her hand
No
Hold her hand tight or
she may fall overboard
No need
I'll forsake everything for you
will you come with me?
I Love you all my life
I'll wait for you at the fort tomorrow
Come there, if you love me
Here is kerosene, grandpa
Why're you so late?
The ration shop was crowded
Serve father coffee
- Find some other to send to stores
- Then you find some other house to eat
Tropic of Cancer and Capricorn are...
It seems a deadly wind blowing
It's going to rain
Banu, pour rice into the bowl
Go and keep safe dried savories
Sister Banu, Zeenu was looking for you
"Dearest one, come
become one with me"
"My beloved, make me
one with you"
"Memories, become a part of me"
"Oh fair Moon, become
one with the sky"
"If there is love, let it bloom
before my eyes"
"If fate intervenes, make me
one with the dust"
"Dearest one, come
become one with me"
"Memories, become a part of me"
"There's life in my body as I
await the breath of my life"
"If my little flower doesn't come I'll
turn to ashes on this mountain side"
"I don't care if I lose my life"
"That's not the reason for this song"
"To have a bright future with you"
"That's what I long"
"Is it the beginning or the end?"
"I've left it in your hands"
"Dearest one, today I've become
one with you"
"I've overstepped my limits for
the love of you"
"Memories, you've become
a part of me"
"Dreams, you've become a part
of my reality"
"If there is love, let it bloom
before my eyes"
"If fate intervenes, make me
one with the dust"
"Dearest one, today I've become
one with you"
"Memories, you've become
a part of me"
"Just one look I lost myself"
"How could I stay away from you?"
"When one eye lights up with love"
"Won't the other one will
brighten up too?"
"Like a river flows through the rocks
I came to see my beloved's face"
"Like the gently wafting breeze"
"I came to hear my beloved's voice"
"Even my tears taste sweet today"
"Dearest one, come
become one with me"
"My beloved, make me
one with you"
"Memories, become a part of me"
"Oh fair Moon, become
one with the sky"
"Like rain come and touch the soil
I've come and mingle with you"
"As the consent of my mind willingly
I've come and reached your boundary"
"Dearest one, today I've become
one with you"
"Memories, I've become
a part in your life"
I'm Shekhar, Narayan Pillai's
younger son
I know, Sit down
- Serve him some tea
- No thank you
It's Okay. You're our guest.
I work for a newspaper in Bombay
I'm studying Journalism too
I don't know anything about
these things, I'm a Village man
I wish to marry your daughter
Shaila Banu
Get out, How dare you abuse
my hospitality, you dog
I've just finished my prayers
or I'd have killed you
Did you hear? He wants consent
to marry our daughter
Not consent, We wanted to
inform our elders
Get out..Shaila go in
Banu, stay here
If this Basheer Ahmed gets mad
he will kill you right here
What audacity to..
Who are you? who are we?
Our blood will never mix
Give me your hand
Our blood will mix
- Where's he?
- He's inside
What's this?
How did it happen?
It's nothing
Did you tell him about the proposal
for his marriage?
Madhampatti Sivarama's daughter
Why Isn't he answering?
Tell him I'm not interested
How long will he exist on
dry rotis in Bombay?
The girl is nice, from a respectable
family, She will graduate soon
- Ask him to go see the girl
- No
- Why?
- I know when whom to marry
What's all this about?
I've already chosen a girl
Is it so?
Is she from Bombay? Have you now?
Where's she from? Is she a North Indian?
That's why I told you not to send him
to Bombay, you didn't listen
She's not from Bombay
She lives here
Who's she?
- Who's she?
- If I tell you you will yell at me!
Tell me, who it is
Basheer Ahmed's daughter
Is he the one who
manufactures bricks?
Convince him
Where's my Elder Son?
Come, let's go
Go and call for Basheer
Tell him Narayana Pillai
wants to meet him
If your daughter comes near my son
there will be a murder here
I'm poor, but I've my pride
If anything goes amiss, the 2 families
will be wiped out
Are you trying to lure an educated boy
from a well-to-do family?
Who wants money? We've dignity
that's enough for us
- You're calling us shameless, then?
- That's not for me to say
You can't control your daughter
You're a fine one to talk
Why should your boys go after our
girls like dogs in heat?
Who's a dog?
Be grateful, I spared your son
when he came here
- Let's see, who kills whom
- Give me the sickle
Stop it! If you continue to fight
it will go to the village council
Then both the families
will be driven out
- Let's see how it happens
- Say the word I'll finish them
Lay a finger at your own peril
Shut up, you insignificant creep
Stop it Stop it I say
Stop this, we're the parents of the
boy and girl
And you people talk of killing
What's this nonsense?
So, all of you, You too
This is not good, I warn you
Satisfied?
You've disgraced me
Are you satisfied now?
- Nothing bad has happened, father
- Could things get any worse?
Has a day gone by when I haven't
visited the temple?
I've been the temple trustee
for the past 20 years
No decisions are taken without
my consent
I'm held in such high esteem
During festivals, deity is brought to
our house 1st before Public procession
How's that possible now?
My son's chasing a Muslim girl her
father's after our blood
What's on earth's happening?
Enough of this nonsense in
the name of education
Shaila Banu's a nice girl, dad she
studies in my school
Shut up
If your brother marries a Muslim girl
who will marry you?
Find her a Muslim boy, then..
I would slap the daylights
out of you
You're not a child anymore
But you're impertinent
Because of your education
So, what if I marry a Muslim girl?
Are Muslims enemies?
Marry her and be happy
But after I'm dead gone
I can't wait for you to die
What did you say?
What on earth is he saying?
Listen, you're very dear to me
If you love me, listen to me
If you love the Muslim girl
more go away
Leave forget all about us
Why do you talk like that?
Beg for your father's forgiveness
Dad, I'm going to Bombay.
I won't return
"If there is love, let it bloom
before my eyes"
"If fate intervenes, make me
one with the dust"
"Dearest one, come
become one with me"
"Memories, become a part of me"
How are you grandma?
- Where's Banu?
- Over there, why?
"There's life in my body as I
await the breath of my life"
"If my little flower doesn't come I'll
turn to ashes on this mountain side"
"I don't care if I lose my life"
"That's not the reason for this song"
"To have a bright future with you"
"That's what I long"
"Is it the beginning or the end?"
"I've left it in your hands"
Banu! Where's she?
Is your mother telling the truth?
Tell me
Is he writing to you from Bombay?
Answer me
You've disgraced me
I will kill you for this
Couldn't any of you women
bring her up properly?
Stop crying
You were born after my
first visit to Mecca
For whom am I
struggling like this?
For you, And you've disgraced me
Promise me that this won't
happen again
You will be married in 10 days
To a boy of my choice
Shall we get married?
- What?
- Aren't you scared?
I'm terribly scared
but I won't cry
Are you sure I don't cry?
Shall I take off my hand?
- Sit down
- Are you Shekhar?
- Yes, I'm Shekhar Narayan
- Your certificate, please
I registered a month back,
Our names have been on the notice board since then.
- That means..Oh shoot
- Do you have a witness
- Over there
- Who're they?
Those 3 are my friends
They're my colleagues too
- Are you from Madras?
- No, I've never seen Madras
We're from Mangudi,
South of Madurai
Do you know Madurai?
Heard of Tamil Sangam?
We both are from the same place
He's been here for the past few years
I came only this morning
- You're next
- Thank you
- Did I say anything wrong?
- No
- Why did you also stop me then?
- Only if you stop soon, he'll go
Only if he goes will we
get married soon
And I can kiss you
- What's your name?
- Shekhar
- Your father's name?
- Narayan Pillai
- Your name?
- Tell him
What's this?
You've betrayed me
Good gracious!
Did you marry her?
What could I do, grandma?
Her dad brandished a sickle and..
Threatened to cut me up if I didn't
marry her, So I married her
- Don't trust him
- I did, look at my plight
I've waited all these years
for him as a young girl
Don't let him escape
Hold on to him
This is my wife
We got married today
You didn't tell us
What's your name?
Sounds like a Muslim name
- Yes, I'm a Muslim
- Are you already married?
- Please keep quiet
- Why should I?
We do worship daily
How can we allow her?
I told you, Let me find out
Please ignore her
Some guests have come
Kids will stay with you
I'll manage
Please go inside
- What's the matter?
- They've got guests from Sholapur
So the kids will stay with us
for a couple of days
Is that all?
What a wonderful first night
Not just tonight. It'll be so
for a few more nights
- What?
- Shut up go to sleep
- Shekhar, you look odd
- Your eyes are red
- What happened? Are you unwell?
- What's up? You seem tired
Sleepless night?
This is not the time to joke
get going
Your eyes are red
Why're you so tired?
Spent a sleepless night?
Mother, you daughter got married..without
fanfare, Without her Mom Dad
Please forgive me
Please break the news
to father gently
However angry he may be, I'm
still his daughter
No one can change that
I'm very happy here, mother
What?
You said you've to attend classes
after work, that you'll be late
I can't even embrace my newly
wedded wife, How...
How can I attend class or study?
Just do what you've been doing
all these years
- I wasn't married all these years
- So?
I'm scared, Somebody may see us
So what? After all, we're
husband and wife
Confine that to our room
It's hardly ours now
- Then be patient
- How's that possible?
We've been married 36 hours,
10,000 more couples would've been married after us.
By now, the others...
For you
Mother, forgive me
Your letter
Letter's from home
It's from my father
- Aren't you going to read it?
- It can wait
I can't stand the suspense
If I read it, we'll only fight
No, we won't
He has sent money
He must've cooled down
I've washed my hands off
my 2nd son
But your mother can't get over it
Your brother took her to the doctor
she has high blood pressure
I don't need to say who's the
cause for this
What kind of a girl.
Read on
What kind of a girl will
elope with a man?
She is as shameless..
As her parents
My parents are not such
indecent people
That's why I said
I wouldn't read it
Let anyone comment about me
but not about my family
Do we pass nasty comments
about your family?
I didn't write it..He did
Read on
I know she's nice girl
But I never thought you
Don't tell lies..Read
What he's written
I'll send back his money
I know why you got married
in haste
I'm sending Rs.1000
Take her to a good hospital
Get rid of it send her back
to her parents
Tell her I'm sorry
Tell him it's Okay
- Should I change my religion?
- What?
Should I change my religion?
Tell him there's no need
Tell her I love her
He says he loves you
You promised to marry me and
ditched me
I didn't, I'll definitely marry
you in my next birth
- What about me?
- You too
- Poor girls
- Are you just teasing or...?
- He says he loves you
- Shut up, fatso
I think our landlady likes us
That's why, she has packed off her guests
What're you waiting out here for?
Go in
"On that shore of Arabian Sea
I saw a beauty""
"I saw that maiden breeze.."
"Disrobing herself!"
"A Lotus of the Mosque"
"I saw your feet.."
"Slowly as your silk half saree
slipped down.."
"I saw rest of it!"
"When the tip of your saree hit me..."
"Oh! What an happiness!"
"When the tender fingers
touched the heart.."
"Oh! What a pleasant feeling!"
"Mind is overcoming with ecstasy
as blood curdles.."
"Are kisses 100's of varieties?"
"When disrobed, will shy, modesty,
ignorance vanish?"
"On that shore of Arabian Sea
I saw a beauty"
"I saw that maiden breeze.."
"Disrobing herself!"
"A Lotus of the Mosque"
"I saw your feet.."
"Slowly as your silk half saree
slipped down.."
"I saw rest of it!"
"After teaching and giving..."
"There're still a few kisses left.."
"After lights are switched off
And earth is overlapped with darkness.."
"Still there's light in the eyes.."
"Even after the earth get's wet
after a rain..."
"Still there're few
showers of merriment left.."
"After urges are pacified and
desires get drowned.."
"Love has blossomed!"
"On that shore of Arabian Sea
I saw a beauty""
"I saw that maiden breeze.."
"Disrobing herself!"
- Oh it's you!
- Who else?
I forgot where I was
I got scared
Where're you going? What's this
At this time...
No one need come here claiming
relationship with my daughter
I'm not here for that
I want bricks, Son, ask him if I
can get them or not!
I want a truck load to
send to North India
Why come here for that?
Don't they've bricks in the North?
Why waste words? Ask him the price
and When can I get them?
One brick is 75 paise, one load is
Rs.2000, Tell him that..
There is Rs.1000 as advance.
I want 'Ram' inscribed on every brick.
- Dad, what're you saying?
- You scoundrel
We're building a temple for
Ram in Ayodhya
Each family is contributing
one brick
We're collecting from the villages
and sending it there
I should've finished you off
that day itself
Hold him
Give him Rs.3 must be alert
with this man
I must speak to my wife
I've been promoted from
proof reader to reporter
My pay check is better
My wife brings me luck
This Pankajamma knows
all about you
You're trying to break this
old lady's heart
No, I...
Traitor!
Pankajamma, would I betray you?
Come later
I've something to tell you
Later..
What can I do, if the
cooker is noisy?
I got scared, It's all a mess
You're the one who scares me
I only asked you for a minute
To tell you something important
I could've told you by now
If I keep it to myself any longer
my heart will burst
What's it?
Tell me
"There's no lock for flowers
There's no route for Air"
"Whom does this earth sky belongs to?
Whom we belong to?"
- How will we care for it?
- Allah's there... for that
Our child has 2 Gods
They will care for it
"It's a joy to talk
It's a joy to lend a hand"
"If we become one
happiness at its best"
"It's a joy to talk
It's a joy to lend a hand"
"If we become one
happiness at its best"
"Gardens don't have regrets
Birds never cry"
"There are no nights on Sun
There's no restriction for Heaven"
"Eyes are for vision only
not to shed tears"
"No one's ever hurt when
clouds fall on earth"
"Eyes are for vision only
not to shed tears"
"Life's there only to live
not to fall from grace"
"God never differentiated
Men by religion"
Sir wants to talk to you?
- Who?
- The senior
Your daughter's written to us
She's not my daughter
That's what I thought too
But they don't seem to care
They went away and got married
- And she's pregnant now
- She's pregnant?
She's written to us without
my son's knowledge
- No need to claim relationship now
- I have better things to do
I don't want our animosity to affect
the child, That's all
But remember one thing
The child will follow our faith
How can that be?
A child should follow his
father's faith
For you, For us, the mother's lineage
is important, So...
The child will be a pure
Saivite not a Muslim
The child shall grow up a Muslim
Whatever you say, it'll go only
to a temple
I'll make it pray 5 times a day
I'll make it chant our hymns
Let's see how that happens
Big talk, I won't allow him to
carry the child
Wait, What's all this about?
There're formalities to be observed
by a pregnant girl's family
Please go away or there will be an
earth quake here
They've come here to pay respect
Why do you send them away
But you don't like
It's not for you or me
It's for the unborn child
Take them inside
Please come in, move out
of the way
"Heart is there only to sing
Why are you silent?"
"Allow your desires to develop wings
and open its shackles to dance"
"Bravery is only for Victory
not to kill"
"Join hands and touch the sky"
"Eyes are for vision only
not to shed tears"
"No one's ever hurt when
clouds fall on earth"
"Eyes are for vision only
not to shed tears"
"Life's there only to live
not to fall from grace"
"It's a joy to talk
It's a joy to lend a hand"
"If we become one
happiness at its best"
"It's a joy to talk
It's a joy to lend a hand"
"If we become one
happiness at its best"
- Is your father home?
- Someone to see you, dad
Wait, I will see
We're from the Sakthi Samaj
We're building a Ram temple
at Ayodhya
We're collecting donations from
every Hindu household
If you can contribute
Whatever you can
Please step aside..
It's for the temple I know
December 6,1992 - Ayodhya
2 children, Did you see...
Our lives are in danger.
How will we notice anything?
What's your name?
Tell us
Are you a Muslim or a Hindu?
Burn them Give me a match-stick
'Intermission'
What's the matter?
Kamal, what's the matter?
Go to sleep, It's just a bad dream
It'll go away
My body's aflame, Daddy
No... Nothing like that
They're setting fire to me
My body's burning
Look... your brother's sleeping
Look, mother's here
Nothing will happen
I'm here, It's all over
Then why're they chasing
me everyday
No one's after you
Am I Hindu or a Muslim?
They ask me that again and again
Tell them not to ask me
It's all over, They won't bother
you again
Is it really over?
Dad, I don't want this ever
I beg of you, please
Look who's here!
Please come see.
Apart from bringing you into this world,
how've we wronged you?
What happened, father?
It's in the papers everyday
That the whole place is ablaze
that there are riots everywhere
Shouldn't we know whether
you're okay or not?
Couldn't you write?
No, I did I..
I'm your father, I said many
things in anger
I disowned you in my letter
Does that mean you have to stay aloof
Alright. come in
Don't stand out-side
I haven't come to behave
sentimentally
I only came to see if
my son's alive
I can't face another loss
before I die... So I came
Dad, why do you...
What is this?
I was so frightened
Do you know who this old man is?
You're grandpa... grandpa..
What's your name, little one?
Kabir Narayanan
- And your name?
- Kamal Basheer
- Just a couple of questions
- It's over
- 227 have died since December 6
- 56
Post-mortem reports show 227
Investigations show only 56 dead
Are the hospital reports false then?
Among the casualties, 75% are
innocent people
Don't the police care about this?
This was only reaction to
what happened there...
When the police intervene during riots
there are bound to be casualties
Instead of shooting below the knee
Why did the police fire above?
You saw it? Did you see it?
I did
I saw the corpses piled in the hospital
I spoke to the Doctors too
Police are human too, can they
stand with folded hands...
And watch an incensed mob hurling
petrol bombs?
How many have you killed
under that pretext?
How many lives have been
lost needlessly?
Don't the police care that people are
still mourning their dead?
If the police fire, you people protest
against police brutality
If they don't fire, you accuse
them of inaction
- 227 have died
- Only 56, That's all
- Don't you respect this profession?
- I do, Immensely
My children are alive today thanks
to a police Officer
I don't know whom to ask
I can't speak to him about it
So I'll have to ask you
It's taken 6 years for this old man
to hear his daughter-in-law speak
- He I...
- Yes!
Yes... tell me
You won't separate us, will you?
I know, you won't
But you've come after 6 years..
He the children are all I have
Please don't separate us
I won't I swear on
my grandchildren
Even If I wanted to
Would I succeed?
Go, girl your father-in-law's
hungry give him some food
Go... go my daughter
The police came and fired at
some of our comrades
I had painstakingly saved money
for my daughter's wedding
Everything was looted
They killed my husband right
in front of me
Someone's outside to meet you
Someone has come
- Come here, Kamal,
- I'm Kabir
Shaila, there's someone
at the door
You ignored me all these years
I've cried everyday these 6 years
Why, mother?
Even I was able to live without you
but your father couldn't
Please come in, Dad
What're you here for?
The same reason as you
You revealed your true colours
Didn't you?
You've painted the kids foreheads
with stripes
Should I hang around till you put
caps on their heads?
Mother wants to know if you want
tea or coffee
Anything is OK little one
Basheer is old, so less sugar
for him
Half their blood is ours
Remember that
Half is ours That's pure blood
Oh Allah!
Siva... Siva
This place seems dangerous
I'm thinking of taking them
back to the village
How can you?
Why do you think I came here
before you?
Are you fighting?
Nothing like that
We're from the same place
So we're just chatting
Mom, they're not quarreling
Let's come to an understanding
We'll take them home
But the children will stay with me
They will grow up weak vegetarians
like you
I know how they will grow up
in your house
Dad is here
Other grandpa's here
Both grandpas are secretly fighting
What's your father-in-law
and mine staying
Both of them want to bring
up a child
They're welcome to
How can you say that?
Let them suffer
We can live in peace
What about us then?
We can have another child
Oh gawd!
Find some other woman
Just one pretty little girl
Why suddenly?
It's been so long since
I saw you round and pregnant
I want a little girl at once
What shall we do?
Mom... mom
No hope
Both grandpas are quarreling
It's unbearable
You both are welcome to your respective
fathers, we don't want them
Tell her I want a cute little girl
Want a cute little girl
Tell him he won't get one
You won't get one
"Oh! Rakkamma!!
I want a girl child"
"When the world sleeps
When the cock crows"
"Oh! Rakkamma!!
I want a girl child"
"When the world sleeps
When the cock crows"
"Slim Rakkamma won't come... she won't
give you a girl child to pamper"
"The world has not slept
the Cock has not crowed"
"Slim Rakkamma won't come... she won't
give you a girl child to pamper"
"Rabbit likes snow the
nightingale likes Sun"
"Deep root likes soil"
"Hey! Father likes daughter"
"King's son likes sword"
"Crying child likes Milk"
"When wife is with her husband
she likes Parrot"
"Will the fish in the river shiver even
if it drenches forever"
"Will you get pain if
I hug you?"
"Hey! Give me a girl child"
"Enough... Leave me..."
"Switch on the light
switch your shyness"
"Slim Rakkamma won't come... she won't
give you a girl child to pamper"
"The world has not slept
the Cock has not crowed"
"Slim Rakkamma won't come... she won't
give you a girl child to pamper"
"The world has not slept
the Cock has not crowed"
"There's no bird without Feathers"
"There's no lamp without vision"
"I'll not stay without you
Don't you understand it?"
"If the soul leaves the body
There won't be any life left"
"There's no language without sound"
"If you're not alive
I won't live"
"Don't you know this?"
"If the revolving earth stops"
"There won't be differences
in the earth"
"If there's no husband, there won't be
life for a wife"
"The desire in my heart"
"Is seen on your forehead"
"Your touching will make me to lose
my control... stay away"
"Slim Rakkamma won't come... she won't
give you a girl child to pamper"
"The world has not slept
the Cock has not crowed"
"Slim Rakkamma won't come... she won't
give you a girl child to pamper"
"The world has not slept
the Cock has not crowed"
January 5, 1993 Dongri, Bombay
'2 laborers were killed in the
Dongri area in Bombay'
'Their bodies were mutilated
beyond recognition'
'This has sparked communal riots in
several areas in Bombay'
When will this
Hindu-Muslim riots stop?
Why're you asking me?
When will the Hindu-Muslim
riots stop?
We're not responsible for that
I want Hindus and Muslims
to live in Harmony
But who started it all?
They beat up our men
Our patience is at an end
We won't remain silent any longer
Who started this fanaticism?
Who demolished the Babri Mosque?
If our men demolished the Babri Mosque
I'm proud of that
There's no protection for Muslim here
We're orphans
So, we have to take care
of ourselves
They're entering Muslim households
and committing atrocities
If we're to live her
We've to take up arms
Tell me one thing
Where do these people get
their weapons?
From there
80% of the people killed in the
riots were Musilms
The police were watching when
they demolished our mosque
While dispersing the crowd here
they shot our men, why?
Because 75% of the police belong
to the Shakthi Samaj
People who've no respect for India
can leave
Innocent people are caught in
the cross fire of ideals
Bombay is burning
When will this end?
Innocent people are caught in
the cross fire of ideals
Bombay is burning
When will this end?
It'll never end
Then that ogre grew as tall as
four palm trees
The people were frightened and
went to Ram and Lakshmana
They...
Are you feeling sleepy?
Where are you coming from?
From the Hindu prayer meeting?
Why did you come this side, old man?
What's your name?
Brothers' wait a minute
What's happening here?
What're you doing?
He's one of us
I'm telling you, he's one of us
Go
Let's go
Would they've stabbed us?
Come How can they Basheer?
Threatening an old man child?
- Nothing's happened
- How can you say that?
If you hadn't come
They'd have killed us
What did you tell them?
Nothing
Please tell me
I said you're my brother Come on
Get water
Get more water
Go and get everybody
You go Bring water
Give it to me Bring water
Leave it Let's go
Let's go, leave all this
Dad... dad
Where's my father? I'll bring him
You go
Basheer, come
- My Koran
- I'll bring it, go
My children!
Sir, my kids... It's dangerous
I won't go there
No, I'm a family man
Sir, have you seen my grandpa?
Sir where is the bus stand?
I don't know, get lost
Take us to our father
Wait, I'll send you all inside
Did you search properly?
I did
What were they wearing?
Kabir was wearing white
Pyjama Kurta
Banu, what was Kamal wearing?
Blue shorts and yellow T-shirt
Don't cry, you will definitely
find your children
I know
I believe
"Stop..stop..stop.."
"This is our motherland
This is our lovable country"
"Why are you shedding blood
on this land?"
"It's not written in religions.
It's not called 'Fate'!"
"This foolishness is the brainchild
of misguided people"
"Stop this war!"
"Stop this bloodshed!"
"You're not a Hindu
you're not a Muslim"
"You're an Indian"
"Religion may be different
but blood is the same"
"Bear this in mind be an Indian"
"Stop this fighting"
"Stop this bloodshed"
I've been looking for
you everywhere
Can't you see what's
happening outside?
And you're sitting here
Where're my children?
What are they doing?
They're not here
Your children are somewhere
out there
Get up, come
My children will come here
They will come here looking for me
I won't leave this place
without them
If we don't have we won't
live to see our children
I want Kamal Kabir
Mother's Saree
What happened?
My father
What happened to him?
What happened to your father?
Can't you see for yourself?
They saved us, but they're gone
Run away from here
Clear the roads otherwise
We will shoot
Listen carefully!
Anyone stepping out of his house will
be responsible for his own demise
What're you doing here?
Where's your house?
You don't come, I'll go
I've to look for my children
My children Are twins
More than 6 children are dead
Many are critically wounded.
See if your kids are amongst them.
My children aren't here
So many people's children are...
Why's this happening?
Please, don't cry
Why should they suffer?
Such small children
My babies...
Kill them, don't let anyone escape
What's the matter with you?
Are you crazy?
Do you know what you're doing?
He's a Hindu, Shekhar
Kill me too, I am also Hindu
They're destroying our shops
and houses
They want to destroy us
or drive us out of the country
Don't talk of your people
and my people
This Hindu-Muslim camaraderie
will never work anymore
Why are you talking like this?
He belongs to Sakthi Samaj
Ask him, didn't they seek out
Muslim houses to destroy?
Yes, with no regrets
They think they can lord over us
One Law for them, one for others
Enough of this nonsense
Politicians are scared of them
They give them minority privileges
This is India, not Pakistan You've to be
put in your places
Stop this!
A true Muslim won't stop
A true Hindu won't remain silent
You're a true Hindu and
You're a true Muslim
You're not the only one's getting hurt
Look around you
Look
Why should innocent people like us die
because of fanatics like you?
What did we do wrong?
You forget you're a Hindu
No, I'm not a Hindu
Your children are half Muslim
No, my children are not Muslims
We aren't anything
We're just Indians
Does your Koran tell you to
kill Hindus
Does your Gita tell you to
kill Muslims?
Why all this killing?
My children are missing
because of you
If anything happens to them...
a Hindu like you Muslim
like you are responsible
Get lost both of you
Why're Hindus and Muslims
fighting like this?
I don't know, son!
They were friends this long
Suddenly they're killing each other
Who's at fault?
No one's at fault
They rake up some issues
We only get affected
We're the victims of the strategies
of the powerful people
Here, eat this
What does being Hindu
or Muslim mean?
You are asking big questions
of this eunuch
I don't know if I'm a
Hindu or Muslim
You eat
Religion is one way of reaching God
Hinduism is one way
Then why're both fighting?
That's what I don't know, son
I want my mother
Brother, eat this
What's your name?
Shaila Banu
What's the matter?
My children...
They're asking me to search
among the corpses
Look patiently for about 5 minutes
Say they aren't there
That's enough
Come
Stay here I'll see to it
What is all this?
"This is our own dear motherland"
"What's the reason for all
this bloodshed?"
"Religion does not preach it"
"Fate does not decree it"
"Is this all the devious
work of man?"
"Stop this fighting"
"Stop this bloodshed"
Enough of all this
There's only blood and burnt flesh
after the carnage
Stop in the name of God
I beg of you to stop all this
Stop
Stop, I'll not spare you
I beg of you, there are children here
Go away
For God's sake, stop all
this bloodshed
There's been too much of it
Enough of this
The City has burned enough
Burn him
Go ahead
I won't give way
I'll not allow you
Can't you understand someone's instigating
this unnecessary conflict?
Why do you kill each other then?
Politicians are setting the place ablaze
and watching the spectacle
Hooligans are looting the people
The bigwigs are causing this
religious conflict
Kill them first then come here
Throw away these weapons
You're a Muslim too Kill him
Burn this fool first
Yes, burn me
Stop this, please listen to me
Set fire to me
Burn me
You want to kill someone
Kill me, you murderers
- Burn me
- No
Burn me
No
This is my child
And this is my sister
Dad!
Dad!...!
"When flowers are joining together,
why people are fighting with each other?"
"Let the madness of religious
fanaticism be buried"
"Let the world find
solace in religion"
"When flowers are joining together,
why people are fighting with each other?"
"Let the madness of religious
fanaticism be buried"
"Let the world find solace in religion"
"There is no sorrow in these tears"
"Blood doesn't have different colours"
"Breeze doesn't have stipulated
direction and animus"
"Let our hearts join together"
"When flowers are joining together,
why people are fighting with each other?"
"Let the madness of religious
fanaticism be buried"
"Let the world find solace in religion"
"Let our souls merge
and form a sea"
"Let that sea merge in the ocean"
"Let the clouds merge and become rain
and let it merge with the sky"
"There is no night without dawn
Let the light merge with light"