"Who am I to you?"
"My eyes are restless!"
"This is the effect of love!"
"Can't be mum, all I can say is that..."
"...who am I to you?"
"Who am I to you?"
"I had to restrain myself, my love."
"Ultimately, I had to say it."
"In my dreams... why do you come?"
"Who am I to you?"
"My eyes are restless!"
"This is the effect of love!"
"I'm sort of lost...
please don't ask me..."
"...who am I to you?"
"Who am I to you?"
"How should I tell you
the feelings in my heart?"
"Try to read my face sometimes."
"You may call it my shyness!"
"Who am I to you?"
COMMENTATOR: We welcome all
the spectators to 'Prem Nivas'.
Hello!
- Greetings to one and all from Lalloo Prasad!
The match is about to begin
in a short while from now.
I will be giving the live commentary.
The sky is absolutely clear...
there are a few clouds.
The umpire has inspected the pitch
and is about to take his place.
The batsman is ready. Fielders, be alert.
Presenting to you, one who bowls
at a speed faster than the wind!
I will hit him for a 6,
off the first ball itself.
Should I hit him for a 4 or a 6?
Go, Lalloo Prasad!
How's that?
Hey Lalloo,
you are always out to the first ball!
- I just gave the bowler a chance.
- What did you say?
- It's your turn to bat.
- No, it's my turn. I will play too.
You must be aware as to what
happened when Rita last came to bat.
She broke her leg.
Oh, shut up!
Prem will coach me this time.
Won't you, Prem?
Will I coach you?
Go and field on the boundary line.
You always ask me to field.
It's similar to what you've been doing
to hook Prem for all these years.
What?
You will field, while Prem will bat.
- You will go and bowl.
- Yes, sir.
LALLOO: Kapil Dev, come to my rescue!
Protect yourself from my attack, Prem.
Here comes Lalloo with his googly.
Hey!
LALLOO: Rita, catch the ball.
BHAGVANTI: I'm dead. I'm dead.
- Don't utter inauspicious things.
My back is broken.
- I'm sorry, auntie!
- You fool, what are you doing here?
Oh...
Auntie, she had come here
to learn to play cricket.
This game of cricket
is becoming a nuisance.
- Kids will always play!
- Quiet!
Greetings, auntie!
How many times have I told
you not to call me auntie?
Not only humans, but dogs too
are pampered here in this house.
Why are you staring at me? Come with me.
- I'm dead!
- Uncle, why is auntie in such a haste?
She's come to talk to your uncle
about your brother, Rajesh's wedding.
Honestly speaking, Rajesh is worth
every good word spoken about him!
Not only me,
but everybody is of the same opinion.
It's not a joke to manage this
big business at such young age!
- What do you say?
- Perfect!
You have to think about his wedding now.
Tell me, if you know of any good girl.
- I have seen the girl.
- Is that so?
You have met my brother from Delhi,
Rita's dad, haven't you? - Yes.
I was referring to his elder daughter,
that's Rita's elder sister, Sweetie.
Sweetie has always been with him
in Delhi and Rita's been with me.
Sweetie is a very beautiful,
understanding and decent girl!
- Isn't that so?
- Yes. She's failed in B.A.
She thinks in terms of
the present generation.
She's already had a couple of
broken engagements. Isn't that so?
So what? Think about the big family.
Their business is worth millions.
The wedding will be a pompous one.
She'll bring along something
worthwhile as dowry, too.
But you won't understand
these norms of life!
After all,
you are a professor at the college.
If you agree,
I will inform my brother accordingly.
Rita, it's time for our kitty party.
Let's go!
- We're leaving.
- Thanks!
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
- I'll leave, brother.
- Okay!
Come on. You're quite a hog.
Wealth is all that she thinks of!
We don't want her rich brother's daughter.
What we want is a down-to-earth
and a lovely daughter-in-law!
One who will bless this
house with her love and care!
You have brought up this
house with so much love!
Rajesh and Prem were so small
when sister and her husband died.
You abandoned your studies too
to look after these children.
You started off with a small job.
For their future,
you only thought of hard work as your goal.
You didn't marry too!
You've brought up these
children with such good values!
That's the reason for Rajesh's success.
Prem too has stood first
at the MBA exams this year.
Am I right?
Brother, I have seen a girl for Rajesh.
Sometime back,
I had gone to Pune for a conference.
I met Professor S. S.
Chowdhury over there.
- Would that be Prof. Siddharth Chowdhury?
- Do you know him?
We've studied in the same college.
We were very good friends.
I met his elder daughter over there.
Just saw her for once, and she's
made a home for herself in my heart!
I liked her so much that I
brought her photograph too.
Her name is Pooja. She's passed B.A.
Very sweet in nature!
- They'll make a good pair.
- I agree!
Professor has gone on a pilgrimage
with his family to Ramtekdi.
As soon as he returns, we'll pay him a
visit. It's just a trip of 3-4 hours.
All that's required is for them to like
each other. - That's the main problem.
Whenever I talk about marriage to
Rajesh, he ignores it.
How can we make the two of them meet?
There is a way.
Why don't we go to Ramtekdi too?
It would be a combination of
a holiday and a pilgrimage.
And also the selection of sister-in-law.
- Great!
- Very good idea!
But brother shouldn't be aware of this plan.
Everyone should be alert.
It's a top secret!
Big brother is here. Come on, uncle.
So you're back, Rajesh.
Your meeting took a long time today!
What did the foreign collaborators say?
We had a detailed discussion.
They'll study our report now.
Uncle, if everything works out properly...
...like you said, this factory will be
the first of its kind in this country!
Prem, your brother is setting up
such a big factory to launch you.
LALLOO: Big brother, the food is ready.
Hey, there's a feast out here!
Is it some special occasion?
- Actually, big brother...
- Well, we all are very happy today.
Happy?
Well, big brother, we have decided
to go to Ramtekdi for our holidays.
Ramtekdi? But uncle, you were
insisting on going to a hill station.
Ramtekdi is a very holy place.
My uncle and aunt go there every year.
- They make vows too!
- The program is fixed.
This time we'll take that
new dress of yours, too.
- Why is it needed over there?
- Why not?!
You never know...
- What did he say, uncle?
- I didn't hear.
We don't interfere in such matters.
Chameli, let's get some food.
Strange! Nobody is telling me anything.
What should we tell you, brother...
as to what we will get at Ramtekdi.
Hurry up, dad!
Mom will be mad, if she catches you
doing this experiment in the kitchen.
Let her be angry. I'm not afraid of her.
If she notices these sweets,
she'll be tempted to break her fast.
PROF. CHOWDHURY: Are you listening?
- What is it?
- It's not me, but mom.
PROF. CHOWDHURY: Very angrily he
said, "You foolish man!"
Seeing everybody scared
and Sita restless...
- Who broke the jar?
- What?
Who broke the jar?
Pooja, when Lord Rama
broke Lord Shiva's bow...
...Parshurama very angrily asked
as to who had broken the bow.
Lord Rama, with all
simplicity and love replied...
"''O God, someone from your slaves
must have broken Lord Shiva's bow."
Have some shame. We've got two grown
up girls. What will they think?
What will they think?
Did I say something wrong, my love?
I didn't say anything wrong. I was just...
It's difficult for both
of us to win against you.
- If anyone can win against you, it will be...
- Nisha!
MAN: Hey...
Good morning, manager uncle!
Devil! You always come
like an express train!
Dad has sent the books from the
library and has said thanks.
Okay!
- Brother, your bill?
- Here's the bill. You remove the books.
- Then, I'll leave...
- Okay, that's also fine.
Nisha child,
will you do me a small favour?
Will you add this up by the time
we come back from the storeroom?
- Sure!
- Very good! But, listen...
...don't indulge in any mischief.
Come on, now. What are you staring at?
Excuse me!
Is this Ram Narayan guesthouse?
Didn't you read the board outside?
Where was I?!
- 75 and 9...
- 84!
What is it? - Can you tell me
which room Prof. Chowdhury is in?
- Why?
- Well... I had some work.
- I understood.
- What?
- Stand up!
- Pardon?
Stand up! You people don't
study the whole year...
What?
Yes, you don't study the whole year
and then panic at the time of exams.
And now, you've come here
to enhance your marks.
You better enhance the number
of your glasses, madam!
Wonder what you think of yourself
after sitting on the manager's chair!
- Well...
- POOJA: Nisha!
Oh, God!
POOJA: Nisha... - I'm over here, sister.
You're sitting here!
Mom is waiting for you out there.
- What were you doing?
- Well, I was... I was...
Welcome! - Uncle,
you proceed while I keep the baggage.
- Okay, dear!
- Come, let's go!
You were asking for Prof.
Chowdhury, right?
These are his daughters, Pooja and Nisha.
Pooja child, he is Mr. Kailashnath.
He's your dad's pal.
- Greetings!
- He wants to meet the professor.
- Please, come.
I'll take your leave.
Oh, manager uncle...
Take this. I've calculated it.
You have? That's great!
Here's your reward.
Thank you!
Manager, you please recalculate.
People say that beautiful girls
are always wrong at calculating.
- What did you say?
- Do you eat chocolates, Miss Nisha?
Don't mention my name.
These snacks taste great, professor!
Have it with this 'chutney' and you
will forget the famous 'Mathura snacks'.
Mr. Siddharth!
Hey... Kai...
- Kailashnath! What a plesant surprise! Wow!
- My younger nephew, Prem.
- May you live long, child!
- Your uncle has lost a bet.
- Which one?
He had said that only I would go
bald, but he has lost his hair too.
Have a look!
Hello, see who has come...
- Greetings! Recognize me?
- How are you?
He has to be fine. After all,
he's one of the top industrialists!
Come and have a seat.
Truly, whenever I read about you
in the papers, I feel very proud!
It's all right!
Prem, you may not be aware about
the history of the three of us.
We were in college together and we
had a lot of fun. Right, Kailashnath?
Keep it here.
- You've already met my daughters, right?
- Yes.
Do you come here every year?
I've come this year with
a very special mission.
Really?
I'd like my nephew Rajesh to get
married to your elder daughter.
PROF. CHOWDHURY: Pooja?
MR. KAILASHNATH: Yes.
That's if you don't have any objections.
Objection? What are you talking?
After all, he's your nephew!
Still... Rajesh has come with us.
You meet him, once.
- Go and call brother.
- You mean...
Yes! Go, right ahead.
Kailashnath!
- Thanks!
- Professor, I should be thanking you.
God has given me everything!
The love of these children...
...a big business empire...
but the house seems barren!
Rajesh has had his share
of motherly love...
...but Prem has been
deprived of that love.
- Come on, brother!
- Come in, Rajesh.
The Professor... and his wife.
- Greetings! Please, sit...
- Have a seat, child.
Apart from your work,
what are your other hobbies?
Brother paints very well.
Isn't that right, brother?
- Is that so?
- Just a little bit.
Pooja paints well too, isn't that so?
Pooja...
Go!
Yes, dad. - Show Rajesh that painting
of the temple that you're doing.
Brother, let's go and see the painting.
We'll just be back, uncle.
Come on brother,
let's have a look at the painting.
- Where are you going?
- How does it concern you?
You let them talk. You can talk to me.
- What should I talk to you?
- Why?
Are you still angry with me?
Miss Nisha...
Don't mention my name.
- Mom...
- Dad...
- It's a very nice painting!
- Thank you.
You paint too, don't you?
Yes.
I do paint but... not so beautiful!
Give it to me.
Brother, did you like the painting?
I've been noticing since the afternoon.
You've been asking me the same
question every 15 minutes.
- What's the matter?
- Matter?
Well, I will go and get you some nice tea.
Wait!
Tell me, what is the truth?
Promise me that you will neither scold
me, nor will you beat me.
- Promise?
- Yes, it's a promise.
Did you like the painting?
Yes.
- Did you like the colors of the painting?
- Yes.
Did you like the one who did the painting?
That's great! We had brought
you here to hear this. Congrats!
- Uncle...
- You wait!
Uncle, brother's life is made.
Prem!
Greetings, priest!
- Sister-in-law, save me!
"You're great Lord...
what a pair you have created!"
"Congratulations to my
brother and sister-in-law!"
"More than any other
ritual in this world..."
"...the relation of hearts
is the most important!"
"Thanks to you, this event has
seen the light of the day."
"Congratulations to my
sister and brother-in-law!"
"More than any other
ritual in this world..."
"...the relation of hearts
is the most important!"
- "You're great Lord!"
"You're great Lord!"
"My brother, who is sitting so quietly."
"Sister-in-law,
have a look at his stubborn posture."
"But, he is a very good guy."
"He is a very good guy,
but a bit naughty."
"You're the only one
that he has fallen for!"
"My sister is acting tough now!"
"Congratulations to my
brother and sister-in-law!"
"More than any other
ritual in this world..."
"...the relation of hearts
is the most important!"
- "You're great, Lord!"
"You're great, Lord!"
"Brother-in-law, for your sake..."
"...my sister has prayed a lot!"
"She's been to the temples..."
"...prayed day and night!"
"She's been invoking
Almighty all the time"
"I've got a daughter-in-law
as I had desired!"
"Congratulations to my
sister and brother-in-law!"
"More than any other
ritual in this world..."
"...the relation of hearts
is the most important!"
- "You're great, Lord!"
"You're great, Lord!"
Tuffy... Tuffy... Tuffy...
That's a nice garland you've
brought, Tuffy!
Tuffy too knows that this evening,
folks from brother's in-law's place...
...are coming with the ritual offerings.
There shouldn't be anything amiss
in welcoming them. Right, Tuffy?
Great!
- Big brother, is she coming too?
- I'll just be back, uncle.
- What happened?
- You'll always stay a fool!
Why?
Uncle, does the girl come
over before the wedding?
How do I know? We aren't married as yet.
Brother!
Yes?
Come!
You are needed desperately
down here in the hall.
The doctor has come, too.
What does he think of himself?!
Let him come. I'll take care of him.
- Greetings, doctor.
- Greetings!
What's the matter? Why are you so angry?
Are you asking me?
You ask him that question.
He confirmed Rajesh's marriage,
chose the daughter-in-law.
I get the news today.
- Doctor...
- What?!
What is it? I don't want it.
I'm very angry today.
I will neither eat, nor drink today.
I'm leaving. Congratulations!
Goodbye. Move aside!
The photo of my daughter-in-law
is on the table.
How did you like daughter-in-law?
Pal...
Her simplicity reminds me of a poem.
Sit down. Doctor will recite a poem.
- It goes something like this...
- Wow, wow...
Let me start the poem.
'I've turned into a photo
after looking at the photo...
Wow!
'I've turned into a photo
after looking at the photo...
...l'm so jealous of my
friend's good fortune.'
Wow, wow!
Have a look!
He told me that he is very angry.
Told me not to talk to anyone.
One look at daughter-in-law's
photo and your anger vanished!
Welcome, sister-in-law!
I can understand that you
are a heart specialist...
...and sister-in-law
is a child specialist.
What I can't understand is this
combination of a doctor and a poet.
That's something he has
taken very seriously.
Uncle, why do you indulge in this poetry?
Poetry in its truest form
is always in front of you!
What did you say? What did you say?
Wait! Did you hear that?
This younger one talks a lot these days.
Shall we get you married
too, along with your brother?
- Auntie, why delay something good?
- Shameless!
- Hi!
I heard doctor auntie's talks.
It's your turn to search for a bride.
I'm just coming. Somebody is calling me.
- Hi!
- Oh, no!
Whenever I want to talk to you,
somebody always calls for you.
But I know very well how
to win over your heart.
The formula to make
sweets in half an hour.
First of all, the utensil... where's it?
Utensil...
Oh, no!
Stupid, I'm hurt.
How could I know that
you were standing here?
- Quiet! Give me the utensil.
- Utensil...
By the way, baby, what are you doing here?
- I'm making sweets.
- So you're making sweets for Prem!
Are you making it as per this book?
- Don't touch!
- Don't touch.
Just answer whatever I ask of you.
- Where's the semolina?
- It's over there.
- Butter?
- Right next to it.
- Sugar?
- In that jar.
- Baby, you are...
- Stupid!
Listen!
- What happened?
- She brought salt instead of sugar.
- Why don't you tell her?
- Let it be. She called you stupid.
Congratulations, brother!
The news of Rajesh's engagement
has gladdened my heart.
I've just been to the
temple to offer my prayers.
She's coming from the beauty parlour.
What happened?
Okay!
I've heard that daughter-in-law's
dad is a professor at a college.
Yes, right!
In that case, there must not
have been any talks of dowry.
He must be like him,
a simpleton all his life.
Don't say that.
He's from a very big family.
But he is his friend.
Whatever he gives has to be accepted.
If my Sweetie were to come,
she would have brought a lot.
So much that the safe wouldn't be
able to accommodate everything.
My Rajesh is worth millions!
Something worth millions
is being made... Sweets!
Sweet!
- Rita baby is making it.
- Is baby making it?
- Will you taste it?
- Give me some.
I'll get it, right away.
- Baby, is the sweet ready?
- Yes!
I've praised your sweet a lot outside.
Really!
Your aunt wants to die... I mean taste it.
I'll just go and give it.
Baby, you've learnt a lot.
Auntie, eat with this big spoon.
Baby has made it.
Have it.
- What happened?
- Auntie liked the sweet a lot.
Have all of this, auntie.
Is this what you call sweet?
It's full of salt.
- Salt?
- Yes. It's very bitter.
My dear, it's your tongue that's bitter.
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
The girl's family is about to come.
You wipe your face.
Yeah... okay, okay!
Move aside with your sweet. - Rita,
you won't be able to make this sweet.
If I can't make the sweet for
you, who can?
Greetings! Please, come.
Oh, Mr. Kailashnath!
- How are you?
- May you live long!
May you live long, son. How are you?
Fine!
How are you, son?
- Hi, Nisha!
- Hi...
Welcome!
Thanks!
Computers!
You're studying computers? Wow!
Nisha... Lalloo and Chameli
have come to meet you.
- Greetings!
Meet him, too. He happens to be the
most loved member of this family.
- How sweet!
- He never bites.
He only loves.
- Brother-in-law! You show us your paintings.
- Definitely, come.
Rajesh, please come here, dear.
This father-in-law of yours
is a very interesting person.
I'll just be there.
Prem, you please show Nisha the paintings.
Wow!
Really...
...brother-in-law is truly great.
This is so good!
- And this is... beautiful!
- Beautiful!
I'll show you the most beautiful painting
done by my brother. Please, come.
- Chocolates?!
- Oh, chocolates! Thanks... please, come!
How is it?
Do you know to play the
instrument or are you just posing?
People tell me that I play very well.
You may make a decision, when you hear it.
I almost forgot. Sister has sent this
gift for you. - Sister-in-law sent it?
Wow!
I told her that it wasn't necessary.
Open it.
Wow! A Brooch!
Put it on your coat. It will make a
good impression on your girlfriends.
Miss Nisha!
Please help me put it.
Move aside!
Ouch!
Sorry!
Did that prick?
So, just like that? - I would have
felt this way, if it had pricked.
Very smart!
Ouch!
- What happened?
- This time, it pricked.
When it pricks, it feels this way.
Brother!
You two are wanted downstairs.
It's time for the religious ceremony.
Shall we go in, Miss Nisha?
It's time for the
relation to be confirmed.
Very smart!
Hey... hey!
Kailashnath... Rajesh is ours now.
Come and give me a hug.
Henceforth, I won't be in demand.
Why? - Well, I'm from the girl's side.
I have to bow down!
I mean...
We won't spare you two,
by just hugging each other.
- What then?
- We will have some song and dance now.
No problem!
Get the musical instruments.
The party is on,
but who will put life into it?
Shall I tell? It's a day of the in-laws.
One should sing and the other dance.
- Dear in-law, sing something for us.
- Me?
Yes.
I don't have that charm.
You're the charming one!
Not really!
- Shall I reveal your secret?
- No.
Why not? You've done it to me so many
times, when I was young! - Quiet!
It's about the time,
when we three used to study together.
His uncle, me and my wife.
Her smile is beyond comparison even today.
There was a time when everyone
was dying for her one look.
- I'll just be back.
- Where are you going?
Your loving uncle too,
was one among those crazy about her smile!
- Brother, you?
- Uncle, you?
No...
Don't lie. Don't lie.
Sing something for the sake
of your shyness and her smile.
Rajesh, you please tell
your father-in-law.
CROWD: No! No!
Okay, one minute! One minute!
Why don't you request him on my behalf?!
It will make a difference.
Please, sing something.
Great!
"There's this strange
conflict in my heart today."
"I'm singing and my
in-law is in front of me."
"I should sing something
which is her wish, too"
"I'm singing and my
in-law is in front of me."
"The earrings on her ears look
like the Moon and the Sun!"
"The earrings on the ears look
"This 'Banarasi' sari looks great too!"
"I'll tell you a secret..."
"I'll tell you a secret."
"My in-law is tickled even today
when her anklets make a noise."
"It's a secret...
he is tickled even today..."
"...when her anklets make a noise."
"The smile on her lips...
the shyness of her eyes!"
"Such innocence is a boon!"
"I'll tell you a secret..."
"I'll tell you a secret."
"My in-law is truly blessed! She is
like 'Laxmi' the goddess of wealth..."
"...who has transformed
this house into heaven!"
"My in-law is truly blessed! She is
like 'Laxmi' the goddess of wealth..."
"...who has transformed
this house into heaven!"
"There's this strange
conflict in my heart today"
"I'm singing and my
in-law is in front of me."
"What I have to live up to is
a very delicate relationship!"
"I'm singing and my
in-law is in front of me."
"She's my shade who's
moving into your house."
"She's lived like a dream on my eyelids!"
"I'll tell you a secret..."
"I'll tell you a secret."
"This life time earnings of mine..."
"...is the brilliance of
your lawn henceforth."
"It's a secret,
this life time earnings of mine..."
"...is the brilliance of
your lawn henceforth."
"It's a secret,
this life time earnings of mine..."
"...is the brilliance of
your lawn henceforth."
It seems that my sister will
die of hunger over here!
Why? - Have a look,
my brother-in-law isn't eating anything.
- Nothing like that.
- Take this, you feed him yourself.
- Open your mouth.
- No.
If you feed him everything over here,
what will you do for the wedding?
You'll come to know about our
hospitality, when you come over.
- You'll come, won't you?
- I'll definitely come.
When I come,
there'll be fireworks all around.
Bring it here.
Bhola brother!
- Bhola brother, Bhola brother!
- Hey... Oh....
What is it? - Please,
do us a favor. Please, have a seat here.
I'm very busy Nisha,
the marriage procession is about to come.
If you do our work, I will tell your
mom to choose a nice bride for you.
All right, then. Here I go.
Sorry, brother.
Nisha, will you make your
brother-in-law sit here?
He'll be sitting there. This seat
is for his brother and his friends.
Let them too know about our hospitality.
I'll do the introductions.
- Uncle, can I have a group photograph.
- Why not?
He's Bhola Prasad.
The son of my wife's brother-in-law.
- Greetings!
- That's enough, son!
Bhola is doing a research on the
works of Kalidas' Shakuntala.
By the way, he's on the look out
for a Shakuntala of his own too.
You!
Let us click the photograph.
The stairs will be a nice place.
- Thank you!
- Thank you...
Come on!
Let's go!
Wow, it's a perfume!
Hey, Tuffy... Tuffy!
Stupid!
Shakuntala!
- Come, brother-in-law.
- Where are you taking him?
He'll sit with us.
They all want to meet him.
He's your brother-in-law! Take him.
- You come, too.
- We too?
We have to take care of you, too!
- Something's fishy, brother.
- I like a challenge.
So, what should we do?
Let's check it out.
Friends, we'll be back soon.
Let's go!
- Excuse me!
- What is it?
You please, don't go there.
- Why?
- There's danger over there.
Danger?
Please have a seat, brother-in-law.
- You have a seat, too.
- Should we sit over here?
Come brother, come. Come fast!
Please, sit down.
There won't be a noise when you sit down.
- Okay!
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
- You sit!
- Okay!
Wait! I'd like to investigate.
- May we?
- Sure!
- Is everything all right?
- Yes, everything is all right.
- Please, sit.
- Yes, we will sit but there is a condition.
You all will sit first.
That's not done. You are the guest.
You please sit down.
No! We are gentlemen, ladies first!
- What's the matter, Prem?
- Brother, one needs to be very cautious...
...wherever your loving
sister-in-laws are present.
Wafer?!
- I'll just be back, brother-in-law.
- Excuse me!
Before you leave,
please show me the place where I can sit.
Please, come.
I will give you the most special seat.
Don't feel shy. Please, come.
You go and sit there. On top of it.
What happened?
What news have you brought?
They've kept brother-in-law's shoes
in a red and yellow sweet box.
Really?
A, B, C, D, E, F, G!
Sister, why are we stealing the shoes?
It's bad to steal.
Shut up!
This is a tradition. We'll get cash
from brother-in-law for the shoes.
- Really?
- Yes...
The red and yellow sweet box...
the fun starts now.
Nobody will doubt that we
have hidden the shoes here.
Be quiet!
We have a lot of enemies over here.
Look, sister-in-law is coming.
- Excuse me!
- Yes?
- Are you Prem?
- Yes.
There's a call for you.
Call for me? Who could it be?
Be cautious! I'll just be back. Let's go!
Thank you!
- Hello!
- Recognize me? I'm Suman.
- Who Suman?
- Excuse me!
- Yes, tell me!
The one who was sitting
with you is calling you.
Is he? You go ahead. I'll just come.
Tuffy, be cautious! I'll be back soon.
Tuffy, will you be my friend?
Tuffy, this is Munia and this is Gudia.
Now, bye. Okay? Bye!
Come on!
Hide it on the table, fast!
Believe me,
I don't know any Suman or her dad.
What? I loved her? When?
I see, in my last birth?
Yes!
Tell me, something.
How is Nisha for this birth?
Hung up? These girls are truly selfish.
What are you doing here? - I was
waiting for you to finish your talks.
- You called me, didn't you?
- Yes, I... did I call?
Yes, you called me and now you deny it.
We're finished!
That breathes life into me!
I was so afraid.
- I'll check it up. It's full of sweets.
- What nonsense!
The shoes have turned into sweets.
Give it to me!
Have a look.
NISHA: Only sweets look
good in a sweet box.
Prem brother,
these girls have truly fooled us.
- Have you accepted defeat so soon?
- Defeat? No way!
I'll just be back with some courage.
Good luck!
Oh Lord, you are the worker of miracles.
You can do anything.
Lord, please do something so that
we win and they become the fools.
Hail Lord!
Please do something, Lord.
Please, do something.
It'll come off in public.
Are you keen on insulting me in public?
I think, he wants to take us somewhere.
I guess, he knows where the shoes are.
Come on, good boy Tuffy!
Come on!
You have worked a miracle, oh Lord!
Brother, here are the shoes.
Good, Lalloo!
Now go and keep this box in that place.
Hide the shoes in such a place,
where she just won't find it.
- Definitely not!
- Girls, please listen to me.
- Let's settle for 500 rupees.
- Definitely not!
We will take nothing less than 1001.
Only then, shall we give the shoes.
- What do you say, dad?
- Yes, this is a rare opportunity.
Ask unflinchingly.
Rajesh, be seated bare footed.
You are too much!
You're sitting amongst these children!
- Get up, Nisha! It's getting late.
- Getting late? Definitely not!
- Repeat along with me. 1001 rupees...
- ...cash.
- Cash?
- Yes!
It's time for me to get up, now. Why?
- Is it your wedding?
- No child, I was...
In that case, you please sit down.
Doctor, these sisters-in-law
are very smart.
Indeed!
- Where's our tiger?
- I'm over here, uncle.
Look at you! Instead of helping
us, you are busy eating.
Say something. - You do the negotiations
first. I'll speak at the end.
- What say, Lalloo?
- Yes...
What do you say?
- Well children, now...
- Definitely not!
Well Rajesh, give the cash.
Just a minute, uncle!
Uncle, tell them to give the shoes
first and then take the cash.
That's perfect! Give with one
hand and take with the other.
- That's fantastic, Prem!
- All right. We'll get the shoes.
Girls... follow me!
PREM: For beautiful girls...
a beautiful gift.
Sister, who has taken the shoes?
"You sisters-in-law of the
groom with the green drapes."
"Return the shoes and take the cash."
"You brother-in-law of the
bride, don't show off so much."
"Give the cash and take the shoes" -
"Give the cash and take the shoes."
"Return the shoes and take the cash."
"Count the cash" - "Get the shoes."
"Enough of your fuss" - "Get the shoes."
- "Am I a fraud?"
- "You should know better."
"You are stubborn" - "Whatever you say!"
"Things will get out of
control" - "So be it!"
"We'll demand more" - "Doesn't matter."
- "Don't act smart!"
- "The shoes first!"
- "The cash first!"
"We've taken the shoes,
haven't robbed some jewellrey."
"You brother-in-law of the
bride, don't show off so much."
"Give the cash and take the shoes."
"Return the shoes and take the cash."
- "Have a drink!"
- "Not in the mood."
- "Have some snacks!"
"Have an ice cream" - "We've had a lot."
- "Have a betel leaf!"
- "We've had a lot."
"Some 'Rasmalai '!" - "It's for you."
- "So much of sweet!"
- "It's for you."
"The shoes first" - "Will you eat them?"
- "As you wish!"
- "Not at all!"
"You tuneless songs of some lousy poet."
"You sisters-in-law of the
groom with the green drapes."
"Return the shoes and take the cash."
"Give the cash and take the shoes."
"Whatever I've learnt from here..."
"...l'm taking it all along
with me to my husband's house."
"I'm taking it to my husband's house"
"I'm leaving for my husband's house."
"With these memories,
your beloved is leaving..."
"...for an unknown house."
"How can I forget, dad..."
"...all the stories that
I've heard from you?"
"Mom, I'm leaving back..."
"...all the memories of my childhood!"
"My loving sister,
take care of that house too the same way."
"This house of my birth has
become alien to me now."
"I've found myself a new world!"
"I'm tied up now to this new relation."
"My father-in-law is my dad
and my husband is my God now."
"My brother-in-law is like Lord Krishna."
"I'm leaving for my husband's house"
Miss Nisha!
If I've made any mistake
while doing all the fun...
...then please, forgive me!
May you live long and always be a bride!
Please, come.
Let's go!
You come here. Where are you going?
You're happy, right?
You are responsible for this relation.
What all has that professor given?!
Has he?
He's given a lot.
Diamond necklace, imported car, TV and VCR.
- Did you get it all?
- No.
Why?
When we weighed all that against
the weight of our sister-in-law...
...the weight of all that goods was
negligible, so we left it there.
Left it there?
And you, were you just applauding the act?
What is this?
I'll give this to our
daughter-in-law as a blessing.
Yes, give her the books.
If it was my Sweetie, who had come...
...I would have laded her with gold.
Daughter-in-law,
this necklace belongs to Rajesh's mom.
You alone are the wealth
of this house, now!
Hey, it's okay!
May you live long!
This is for you, daughter-in-law.
I'm giving you 'The Ramayan '. Sita is in it!
Daughter-in-law!
'The way a ring is enhanced by
the presence of a diamond...
...it's my sincere wish that you two
always live happily in the same way.'
Wow!
- Take this, Rajesh, my child.
- Doctor uncle, I...
- What?
- Uncle...
Why are you looking at your uncle?
Didn't you take pennies from me
when you used to go to school?
Now that you are big,
have you become rich?
Keep it. - At least,
don't scold him this way in front of her.
I will scold him this way
even in front of his children!
Hey Rita... that... Yes!
This is for you.
Distribute all this among the rest.
Come here, Lalloo.
Daughter-in-law, this is Lalloo, my son.
- Take this.
- No sir, you have given me such respect.
You've also given me such a
good sister-in-law. I'm blessed.
Will you at least accept it from
the hands of your sister-in-law?
Didn't you tell me that Pooja
resembles your own sister-in-law?
Just consider that she is in front
of you and is offering it to you.
What will I get, uncle?
Yes brother,
give your younger one something too.
What he'll get is some duty.
Well, the sister-in-law loves
her brother-in-law the most.
So make sure that she never ever
longs for her maternal home.
- Have you understood?
- Yes, I have understood, uncle.
I promise that I will give my
sister-in-law all the happiness!
Hi, sister-in-law!
- What's happening?
- She's teaching me to speak English.
Write, Jawaharlal Nehru.
- Should I start Jawaharlal with a J or a D?
- Start with a Z.
Yes, yes.
- You are fooling me.
- You fool, does anyone study on Sunday?
I do!
- Sister-in-law, let's play cricket.
- No... no.
- She'll not go anywhere.
- Come here.
What's the matter?
Chameli, try and explain to him.
I've had a tough time getting
brother to agree to play cricket.
Have you understood anything, you fool?
Sister-in-law, let's keep the
rest of the studies for tomorrow.
Now... it's time to play.
- Come, sister-in-law.
- But Prem, I don't know to play cricket.
- In that case, you sit and watch.
- Yes, sister-in-law.
- There are clouds in the sky...
- Hi, sister-in-law!
Hi...
Brother, it's your turn to bat. Let's go!
- Sister-in-law, catch!
Let's go, Lalloo!
- What's happening?
- Come on, let's play cricket.
You move this side. Field properly.
- Are you through with your fielding?
- Take this, big brother.
Hey Prem, at a cricket ground,
there's no permission to only watch.
One has to play too.
All right. Sister-in-law,
you will have to bowl. - Me?
- It's a matter of prestige.
- No.
It's very easy.
You just have to do this much.
That's it!
Spectators, a loud round of
applause for our new player.
Applause!
Come on!
Our new player is moving
towards the bowling crease.
- Welcome, sister-in-law! Best of luck!
Best of luck, sister-in-law!
I guess,
I said something wrong.
Umpire, ready?
- How's that?
Our new player has grabbed
the attention of one and all.
Off the very first ball,
she has clean bowled a seasoned player.
Sister-in-law, it's your turn to bat now.
Our new player is moving
towards the batting crease.
Bat, please!
Gloves, please!
- Shall we?
- Please!
Ball, please.
The match has entered a
very crucial moment now.
Our seasoned player has
rolled back his sleeves.
He is all excited and is out for revenge.
LALLOO: Our new player has taken her
position with absolute confidence.
Come on, sister-in-law!
The ball has been bowled...
and the ball is racing towards the sky.
It's racing towards the
boundary and... and...
How's that?
CROWD: No ball!
Tuffy, you fool!
"Sister-in-law,
you're the treasure house of happiness!"
"From the time the first rays show up..."
"...my sister-in-law is
awake from that time."
"She takes care of all and
works till late in the evening."
"From the time the first rays show up..."
"...my sister-in-law is
awake from that time."
"I've been missing all
this since childhood!"
"I'll be married too!"
"All of them seem to be telling me so."
"You make a choice and
don't listen to anyone"
"I'll be married too!"
"All of them seem to be telling me so."
"You search for a replica of
yourself and get her here."
"Till when should I be the youngest?"
"Let someone younger than me come too."
"Give these arms of mine a
laughing and talking toy!"
"Till when should I be the youngest?"
"Let someone younger than me come too."
"We ask of you for a lovely offering!"
"Sister-in-law,
you're the treasure house of happiness!"
- Come, brother.
- All the work is over.
I've spoken to the confectioner and
have told him about the function...
...that we have to celebrate the
arrival of a new member in our family.
- Good day, everyone!
- Good day!
Uncle, I've brought for you...
fresh and refreshing tea!
Very good!
- Please!
- Wow!
Daughter-in-law, you've transformed
Lalloo into an Englishman.
Englishman!
How will a monkey appreciate
the taste of ginger?!
Auntie!
This is for you.
- Ginger tea!
- What?
Ginger tea, auntie.
Oh, henna problem, no problem.
For you... tea with straw.
That's great!
This tea is really good.
But uncle, why are you laughing so much?
Well, call up the professor.
I'd like to ask them about their
time of arrival for the function.
Hello!
Who?
- You! Tell me.
- Your sister will speak to you.
Sister-in-law!
Hello! Hi... Nisha!
Hi, would-be-mother! How are you?
Talk to mom.
Hello, Pooja! May you live long, child!
Well, it seems difficult for
us to come for the function.
Seems difficult to come? Talk to uncle.
Greetings! What's the matter?
His college exams, instead of
being postponed are due these days.
- But at least somebody should come.
- Miss Nisha!
Miss Nisha! Call... Miss Nisha!
- At least, send Nisha.
- Just a second!
- Will you go?
- To sister's place? Yes!
- Nisha will be coming.
- All right!
Prem will be there
tomorrow to pick up Nisha.
You'll go, right Prem?
Yes, I'll go.
Nisha! Nisha!
Get up, child! Get ready, fast. Get up!
What is this, mom?
What a girl you are!
Nisha!
Get up, child.
Prem should be here any moment.
Your slave is at your service!
- Hi!
- Hi, Tuffy!
Oh, God! I love her!
Miss Nisha!
- Thank you so much!
- Thank you?
- For what?
- For waiting for me.
I didn't wait for you.
In that case, were you counting
stars in the day on the roof?
People say, when a beautiful girl
lies; she looks more beautiful.
MRS. CHOWDHURY: Have you come, son?
Hello, auntie!
How are you, auntie? Where's uncle?
Good morning, son! A special snack.
- Taste it.
- Uncle, have you made it?
Yes, it's your auntie's favorite.
It's a secret. This snack mixed
with butter pleases the wife.
Actually, we aren't on talking
terms for the past few days.
- Why auntie?
- It's our daughter's first child.
It's her baby shower and we're not going!
I'll take you with much fanfare
on the birth of our grand child.
At least, taste it now.
Catch her hand. Taste it.
Can I ask you something?
Why have I got these flowers, today?
Basically, whenever we've
met, we've always fought.
Flowers were the best way to
strengthen this acquaintance.
Why did you ask me to forgive you
while leaving after the marriage?
I was just trying to impress you.
- If I tell you the fact, you will laugh.
- I won't. Tell me.
It was that touching moment!
We were taking sister-in-law home.
You were bidding her good bye.
Thought to myself,
why not share some of your sorrows.
Saw that, Tuffy?
A genuine man has no value!
I wasn't laughing at you.
Sometimes,
a human errs in judging a person.
You aren't the type I thought you
were, when I first met you.
Then...
- ...how am I?
- I'll think of it at leisure and tell you.
There's a surprise for
you in the back seat.
Surprise?
Have a look!
Chocolates?!
For you.
What's the matter, Tuffy?
Flowers first, then chocolates!
Is it some special day?
For the first time today, a girl is
sitting in the front seat of my car.
People say that this day
occurs in every person's life.
Today happens to be
that special day for me.
Miss Nisha!
Yes?
- What happened?
- Nothing.
I'm sharing my secrets with you
and you're with your comics.
It's not allowed to read
or write while travelling.
Travel should be full of songs and fun.
What do you say, Tuffy?
From the time I saw you singing on the
roof, I've become your fan.
You share some secrets, too.
- I won't tell anyone.
- Some other time.
- Why?
- I've a sore throat.
Tuffy, before the third comic opens,
I guess I have to impress her.
"Ten... Nine... Eight... Seven..."
"Six... Five... Four... Three..."
"Two... One... Let's start the fun!"
"The drapes are flying
in the cold breeze."
"The heart is beating fast,
it's because of the teen age."
"No control over the heart...
what sort of magic is this?"
"This the magic of the season, pal!"
"No control over the heart now, pal!"
"My gaze has lost and gone insane..."
"...the sight of you is so breathtaking."
"This the magic of the season, pal!"
"This fair girl with the city boy..."
"...looks like the shining moon!"
"These beautiful flowers and the buds..."
"...this naughty call of the wind!"
"They signal to me to
spend my time over here."
"Previously, never ever would
these flowers talk to me this way!"
"This the magic of the season, pal!"
"No control over the heart, pal!"
"My gaze has lost and gone insane..."
"...the sight of you is so breathtaking."
"This the magic of the season, pal!"
"Tell the truth and
don't keep it a secret."
"From where have you'll come
and where do you want to go?"
"I'm taking her with me to my place."
"Well, a strange acquaintance
and a strange place!"
"Why then have you come so far with
me, my dear?"
"This the magic of the season, pal!"
"No control over the heart, pal!"
"My gaze has lost and gone insane..."
"...the sight of you is so breathtaking."
"This the magic of the season, pal!"
Big sister.... hi!
- Nisha!
- Hi!
Be careful!
Whoops!
- Hi, Chameli!
- Miss Nisha!
- Nisha child... welcome! May you live long!
- Uncle!
- Hi, Nisha!
- Brother-in-law!
LALLOO: Good evening, Miss Nisha!
Oh, my!
Good evening, Mr. Lalloo!
Miss Nisha, welcome home!
KAILASHNATH: Daughter-in-law,
the in-laws have sent a lot of things.
- Mom has sent a letter for you.
- For me?
Wow, that's great!
'Respected in-law, I
hope, you all are fine.'
'I was very happy on seeing Prem today.'
'Do send Rajesh over here, for once.'
'The professor also
wants to say something.'
Oh, God!
'Well Kailashnath,
I've heard that these days you wear dhoti.'
'Every day, you listen to
daughter-in-law's rendition of Ramayana.'
'We haven't aged so much.
I'm sending a suit piece for you.'
'I have stitched a similar one.
You do the same.'
'On the joyous occasion
of the child's birth...
...both the grand fathers will
dance in similar outfits.'
Yes!
Take this, uncle.
Truly, daughter-in-law,
Nisha's coming has gladdened our hearts.
Tomorrow's function will be
very special now. - Right!
LALLOO: Welcome! Greetings!
WOMAN: Greetings!
I say, this place is decorated
in a different way today.
It has to be. It's our
daughter-in-law's first function.
- Right!
- Please, come.
Greetings! Please, come.
- Welcome, sister-in-law!
- Not sister-in-law, but my auntie.
Is that you, Bhagvanti?
- You look like Pretty Woman, today.
Naughty boy!
That's great, uncle.
Shut up!
Welcome, sister-in-law!
Welcome, elder brother.
All the guests have arrived.
Bhola has come, too.
Greetings, brother-in-law!
Greetings, Mr. Prem!
- When did you come, Mr. Bhola?
- He's here since the afternoon.
I have struck up a very good
friendship with your brother-in-law.
Come!
- Auntie... Oh, oh...
- What happened?
Wow, you are out to kill today!
- Really?
- Yes!
If not for this age difference... today...
Get lost, you shameless creature!
- Let go of my hand, you rascal!
- Auntie...
RITA: Prem!
Oh, God! Here she comes!
- Where did he go?
- Baby, who are these flowers for?
- They're for sister-in-law.
- Oh, the queen of the flowers has come.
WOMAN: You look very good today.
Come with us, please.
- Excuse me!
- Shakuntala!
- You?
- Yes.
Look, mister!
My name is Rita, not Shakuntala!
RITA... understand?
My knowledge of the English
language is a bit weak.
But whatever you just said,
I found it to be very sweet.
Stupid!
Brother, he has found his match.
- Lalloo!
- Yes?
Where's my girl?
'These hours of waiting just
don't seem to get over.'
Wow! Very beautful!
DOCTOR: These hours of waiting
just don't seem to get over.
The eyes are longing for
the love of life to appear!
Wow! Very beautful!
It was great!
That poetry suits you perfectly.
DOCTOR: The heart exclaimed,
the moment I saw the glamour of my love...
The heart exclaimed,
...who has brought her here
from the glory of heaven?!
Wow! Very beautful!
- Greetings, doctor uncle!
- May you live long, child!
Doctor uncle, please repeat the
poetry that you just recited.
What's the matter, dear?
You seem very poetic today.
You never appreciated my poetry before.
Till today, he couldn't fathom
the depths of the poetry.
I mean, he didn't get it!
What do you say, Miss Nisha...
I mean, brother?
Doctor uncle, once more please!
Okay!
'These hours of waiting just
don't seem to get over.'
'The eyes are longing for
the love of life to appear!'
'The heart exclaimed,
the moment I saw the glamour of my love...
...who has brought her here
from the glory of heaven?!'
Wow! Very beautful!
Are you all going to pile
on here all the time?
No, we were just about to leave.
Let's go, doctor!
Your snacks are ready for
you, on the lawns outside.
Daughter-in-law is about to come.
We have to start the function.
Come on, girls!
Shall I come, too?
Sorry, gents now allowed!
Uncle, is this ladies' program
something great? - Yes.
- How do you know?
- As a child, I sneaked in and saw it.
I used to wear a girl's
dress and sit among them.
What, uncle? Shame!
You are decent children!
These elders of ours are quite smart!
- Yes!
- We'd never do something of the sort.
- Shall we go?
- Yes!
Nisha, you start your program now.
- Auntie!
- Yes?
Greetings! Greetings!
Why are you'll sitting over here?
We wanted to see the program.
- What?
- Bhola wants to see it.
- Who wants to see?
- Just a minute!
Bhola, this is a ladies' function.
You go out.
Yes.
We'll meet outside... we're going.
Bhola, you don't get
misled by these two guys.
They're shameless and will spoil you, too.
- Why are you laughing?
- Just like that.
Just like that?
Get out!
Be careful, auntie!
The waist might get a sprain.
Leave!
Get out, out!
Your problems are over.
Excuse me, excuse me!
What's happening?
You don't bother. You just carry on.
Brother, let's have a close up of auntie.
What say, auntie?
Mine? Go right ahead.
What's this new problem?
It's such a big function.
They want to capture me on a video.
Isn't that true, Prem?
I tell you, they don't want to shoot.
I've seen this before.
They're here to impress the girls.
- What are you referring to?
- I'll explain. Get me my sandal.
Sandal?!
All of you guys, get out!
He is a true gentleman.
All men, out!
Get out!
Wait! What is it?
What are you up to?
No matter what happens,
I will definitely see the function.
What's this?!
"Sister, your brother-in-law is crazy."
"Oh Lord,
he's trying to impress the girls."
"It's sort of a habit with him..."
"It's sort of a habit with him."
"Oh Lord,
he's trying to impress the girls."
"I told him to bring tamarind,
but that fool brought something else."
"I told him that my heart
desires for something."
"He brought a watermelon when
I asked him to get a lime."
"He's crazy, somebody guide him"
"He's crazy, somebody guide him."
"Oh Lord,
he's trying to impress the girls."
"Sister, your brother-in-law is crazy."
"Oh Lord,
he's trying to impress the girls."
"I told him to get some mountain mud..."
"...but that fool got some sweets."
"I told him to get some sour thing..."
"...and he got sweets from the market."
"It's difficult to trap me"
"It's difficult to trap me."
"Oh Lord,
he's trying to impress the girls."
"Sister, your brother-in-law is crazy."
"Oh Lord,
he's trying to impress the girls."
"Sister-in-law, I admire your sister!"
"Oh Lord, it's the age of girls!" "Oh
Lord, it's the age of girls!"
"Lord, save me... Lord, save me!"
"Oh Lord, it's the age of girls!" "Oh
Lord, it's the age of girls!"
"It was your command that I
disobeyed, I'm your sinner."
"I agree to any punishment
that you decide on."
"When will I be rid of my problem?"
"I'm tired of my own self"
"I'm tired of my own self."
"Oh Lord, it's the age of girls!" "Oh
Lord, it's the age of girls!"
Hello!
Where were you going?
Do you like this antic of
yours to sneak on girls?
I just had to see your dance.
Henceforth, I'm a fan of your dance too.
I made so much fun of you.
Didn't you mind?
These days, I don't mind whatever you do.
Why? What has happened these days?
Just...
Whatever you say,
whatever you do, I like it all!
Why did you hit me with the missile, then?
It is bad manners.
Next time you do that to
someone, think twice.
I don't have the time to
think of anybody else.
I can take the liberty of
doing this only with you.
Why? Who am I to you?
Shall I tell?
Well, it's time for the test.
Go right up to the gallows.
1... 2...
I hope, no one is watching.
- What were you saying?
- Nothing, I...
Hello!
Darn it!
I love her.
Yes.
- Pooja, where's uncle?
- In the study. Why?
Come over, I'll tell you.
See this, the fax has just come in
from abroad. -
The collaborators out there
have liked our new scheme.
Great, brother! You've done it!
Brother, is this scheme of that same
factory you are setting up for Prem?
It's all the reward for his hard work.
Great!
Pooja, they've called
me there for a few days.
- Mr. Joshi, please arrange for my departure.
- Yes!
- Lalloo, are my things ready?
- Yes.
Sister-in-law is just
packing something to eat.
- This isn't required, Pooja.
- It's already packed. You have to take it.
Brother, you will have to
take this overcoat too.
Shall we go, Rajesh? - Uncle,
you won't go to the airport so late.
Why not! Once Tuffy's and my
program is fixed, it stays fixed.
Well, it will also serve
as an outing for us.
We're waiting in the car.
It's time for the flight.
Come on, Tuffy!
I'm leaving. Take care!
What's the matter, Prem?
Brother, sister-in-law can
deliver any moment now.
Right now, she needs you the most.
At such a crucial juncture,
leaving her alone...
...you have to go abroad for my sake.
So, that's the case. Come with me.
Pooja, just listen to what
your brother-in-law has to say.
What's the matter, Prem?
- What's the matter?
- He says that the delivery is imminent.
He says that at this stage
I have to go abroad for him.
Prem, along with uncle,
we all too have a dream.
That you prosper and make a
name for yourself in this world.
Your brother is going
to fulfil this dream.
As far as I'm concerned,
when you're here, do I need to worry?
Is there any other friend greater than
a brother-in-law for his sister-in-law?
Come on, brother!
I really enjoyed the food
that you cooked, Nisha.
It's amazing! Both the sisters are similar.
Full of good values!
Be happy!
Daughter-in-law, it's been quite
some time that Rajesh has gone.
Is there any news about his return?
I just spoke to him today.
The work is almost over.
In that case, he must be coming soon.
- Well, I have given him a list.
- Wow!
He's gone to work over there and
you've given him a list of nail polish.
What's the harm?
After all, he's my loving nephew.
You love him a lot!
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
I understand everything
that you mumble to yourself.
Don't consider me to be a fool.
Auntie, some Aniseed.
Thank you.
Okay bye daughter-in-law, brother...
You come over.
Thanks for saving me.
She was about to start the third world war.
I'm leaving, too.
Good night, everybody!
- Good night!
Daughter-in-law, you rest too.
It's quite late.
Well uncle, Prem should be
back from the office soon.
He's busy with his work. He's taken
over all of Rajesh's responsibility.
He might be late. Chameli,
take daughter-in-law to her room. - Yes.
Nisha, please call Prem at the office.
Ask him, when he's coming.
This service station... shift it to no.
10 block... -
Excuse me!
Hello!
Who?
Tell me!
Your sister-in-law is enquiring
as to when you would be back.
I'll be late. Tell sister-in-law to rest.
Tell Lalloo to keep the food ready for me.
As for you, thank you for calling!
Yes, Mr. Ramnathan, Mr. D'Souza...
let's continue!
It was my mom's phone.
Sorry, guys!
No messing around during work time.
Plot no. 10 has got to
be at service station.
LALLOO: This is my home.
- My home is very beautiful.
- Lalloo!
Have you come, brother?
Got very late today. Has sister-in-law
gone to sleep? - A long time back.
Good!
- Shall I serve the food?
- Yes, do it fast! I'm very hungry.
I'll do it, right away.
Miss Nisha!
I'll go in and reheat the food.
You're awake so late?
Why are you awake so late?
Your food.
From where should I start?
You take so much time to
select the vegetables.
Wonder how you work in the office!
Start from here.
Your favorite sweet.
How do you know that this is my favorite?
Here are some piping hot
'parathas '.
So it was you who told her
about my liking for this sweet.
If someone asks me about your
likes, I have to be truthful.
She has done the cooking today.
You have?
It's fantastic. Just taste it.
I'm feeling sleepy. I'm going.
Let's go, Tuffy! Time to sleep.
Why interfere? You fool! Good night!
There's magic in your hands.
It's the first time that I taste
such tasty sweet. It's the truth.
You might consider me to be a fool.
I'm a fan of your singing,
your dancing and now...
...l'm a fan of your cooking too.
Miss Nisha!
You haven't answered my question.
Why were you awake for me?
Do you know about your drawback?
You talk a lot while eating.
Oh, really? Is that so? I'm sorry!
You have a weakness, too.
You believe in everything very soon.
You are unbelievable!
When I want to ask you something...
...you stop me and when I'm
quiet, you criticize me.
Shall I ask you something?
Who am I to you?
"It's the first love...
it's the first time."
"In spite of knowing this,
my love acts so strange!"
"It's the first love..."
it's the first time."
"Her looks... look at me
from the corner of her eyes."
"Her looks... her shyness..."
"...they reveal the secret of her liking...
her shyness."
"One who will serve without being noticed...
my love is that type!"
"It's the first love...
it's the first time."
"She is Nisha...
she is the direction of my life."
"She is Nisha... she knows..."
"...that she controls my life...
she knows that."
"My love is cut off from the whole world!"
"It's the first love...
it's the first time."
it's the first time"
Somebody is coming.
- Brother!
- What's the matter, Chameli?
Please, call doctor auntie.
We might have to shift
sister-in-law to the hospital.
Congratulations! It's our grandson.
Uncle, I'm an uncle now!
Congratulations! Congratulations!
"Everyone will have to sing today."
"Sister-in-law, I thank you."
"Let's all get together and thank her."
"My eyes were longing for this
sight, my dreams have come true!"
"God willing,
you too may have a poetic attitude!"
"Childhood days have returned!"
"This mute animal too is
happy knowing that..."
"...there'll be a lovely sound
echoing around this lawn now."
"Tuffy is asking the child
to keep on smiling always!"
"Sing it!"
"Grandma and grandpa will dance too!"
"Listen to what the kid is saying."
"He's asking you to be
closely related to him."
"Son, this uncle of yours
is up to something."
"If I don't get you, I'm sure to
renounce life and become a priest."
"Come home and take the alms."
"My dear!"
"Live long, child.
The child is very lucky."
"These fireworks... this brightness."
"They reveal the happiness of the heart!"
"The earth and the sky
are happy for our baby."
"And it's apt that at such time,
the father of the child arrives."
- Dad, this is the model of Prem's factory.
- Wow!
Kailashnath,
you started from just a small room.
Rajesh has striven to reach this stage.
And now, Prem will make sure
that he does his bit for success.
Prem, give it your best shot.
We won't be here for the inauguration.
- Where are you going, uncle?
- We're going back home.
We have the tickets for the evening train.
Are you'll leaving today?
We were waiting for Rajesh to come back.
Now, we'll be leaving.
Brother, think, stop them.
Prem, what is this that I'm hearing?
Is the professor going?
Yes. They're leaving today.
- Today?
- Yes.
Brother, will you listen please?
- Didn't you tell them to stay?
- He didn't.
They've got tickets
reserved for the evening.
The tickets can be cancelled.
Forget him. I'll see how they leave.
- Uncle, you're so sweet!
- Doctor!
You stay put.
- Prem...
- Sir...
The paper.
Welcome, doctor!
Are you all set to leave, professor?
Yes. I enjoyed your
company all these days.
Sister-in-law,
can I have a look at your tickets?
- Lalloo, get them cancelled.
- Cancel?
You're impossible! Your son-in-law
has just come and you're leaving?
I had a mind to stay for 4-5 months but...
What are you saying?
It's our daughter's in-law's place.
It's our daughter's in-law's place
now, but it's my friend's house always.
You may be angry,
but we won't let you go today.
- Spend some time with Rajesh, too.
- Yes!
Stay, please!
Mom, please stay.
- But...
- Mom... please!
All right!
I will take care of this thing.
Just a minute!
We'll stay on one condition.
- What's that?
- Nobody will sleep tonight.
We'll have a night of
merriment among friends.
You just wait and watch the fun.
It'll be out of this world.
DOCTOR: This night is truly happy...
This is a fantastic gathering.
Stop this poetry now and get
into the mood of the game.
Son, for how long will we
continue sitting over here?
What do we have to do?
It'll be fun. It's a very easy game.
We will be playing the music.
This pillow will be passed around.
Whenever the music stops,
whoever has this pillow is a goner.
We will punish that person in
any which way that we desire.
- Okay?
- Okay!
Where are you going?
We want to trap you first of all.
I'm not the type to be trapped.
I'll sit and watch and ensure fair play.
I will check you out.
What a style!
Professor, my dad used to
play the gramophone for us.
- Do you remember the song?
- Thanks, child.
"One mansion needs to be made" - Yes!
"One mansion needs to be made"
Brother Prem, should I start?
Yes, start!
"Your black hair, your golden complexion."
"Your youth... my, oh my!"
"Sweetheart, sweetheart!"
Hey, Lalloo out!
- But...
- Stand up!
Get up!
I'll go and fill the water.
What should I do?
Your sister-in-law has taught you
to speak in English. Say something.
Just a minute!
Jawaharlal Nehru was born
on 14th November, 1889.
He was our first Prime Minister.
He loved children very much.
Children used to say,
"Long live uncle Nehru!" Victory to India!
PREM: Claps!
"Your laughing, lustrous face."
"Your black hair, your golden complexion."
"Your youth... my, oh my!"
"Sweetheart, sweetheart!"
Brother, you're caught.
- What should we ask him to do?
- I won't do a thing.
- Hey, why's that?
- No, no...
- This isn't fair.
- No way!
- Don't be a spoil sport.
- Yes, brother!
- All right!
- Start!
I will say something in your praise.
'Her complexion may be fair or dark...
...lucky is the brother-in-law
whose wife has a sister!'
Oh!
Please, proceed. - 'One whose wife
has a sister is a blessed man.'
'An eye on the wife's sister
and the wife for company.'
- Are you listening, daughter-in-law?
- Yes, I am.
'The poet has rightly said that
nectar is full of goodness...
...and that the wife's sister
is almost like a wife.'
- What's this?
- He was out, but he didn't take it.
Are you watching, your honour?
Sister-in-law, no cheating!
No cheating!
Dad... 'Mughal-E-Azam !'
KAILASHNATH: What's Mughal-E-Azam?
Who are you watching? Son-in-law?
Why feel shy in front of your son?
Dear in-law... let us hear.
Lights off!
PROF. CHOWDHURY: Anarkali!
KAILASHNATH: Hey professor, over here.
So, what did Anarkali say to Prince Salim?
Your honour, the sunlight brightens
up all the gardens of the world.
Why then, did the Sun take the trouble?
My dear prince,
don't rob the dreams from my eyes.
I'll die!
"First your eyes robbed me from afar."
"Now you look upon this
injustice with pride."
"Oh crazy one, oh crazy one...
what do you know?"
"Yes, what do you know?"
"What my heart's restlessness is like..."
The time has finally
arrived to do something.
One... two...
Lalloo, give me that chair and the bottle.
Kailashnath brother, move aside!
Listen, what are you doing?
I've lost already,
I may as well do it with style.
Thank you. Thank you for the chair.
Film, Sholay! Dharmendra, drunk scene...
Auntie!
You're great, Mr. Dharmendra!
Villagers...
Villagers, this Basanti...
I was supposed to get married to her.
- But this old auntie...
- What did I do?
Villagers, if I don't get
married, then... suicide.
And then, all of you would be behind bars.
Churning the flour mill,
churning, churning...
I'm ready! Now, please step down.
Should I? Villagers,
auntie has agreed and so has my Basanti.
So... so...
the program of dying is cancelled.
Great!
"Your black hair, your golden complexion."
"Your youth... my, oh my!"
"Sweetheart, sweetheart!"
After his excellent show, what can I do?
Uncle, Michael Jackson!
You'll get a slap.
Why?
Uncle, whatever suits you.
Yes, uncle!
Good!
'No matter if the world is our enemy...
...may this friendship
of ours be forever!'
'We won't separate even after death,
we have the promise of friendship.'
'If someone asks us for our address...
...we say, we stay in each other's heart.'
'We don't have any other place.
May this friendship be forever!'
Great!
It seems to be my turn now.
My blood pressure is going up!
140!
160... 180... 200!
Heart fail!
What are you talking, doctor?
You're a strong man!
Let's hear something out of this world.
- What do you mean?
- Recite some other poet's poetry.
That would be the worst
punishment for a poet.
Brother!
"I am not... a poet..."
"...but, oh my beautiful..."
"...from the time I set my eyes on you..."
"...I got hooked on to poetry!"
That was great, doctor!
Well, Prem and Nisha,
only the two of you are left now.
Let's see who the winner is.
Bhola, start the music.
"Torture me and strike me
to your heart's content."
"It's all bearable,
just love me a little."
"You are in my heart,
oh you are in my heart."
"My heart is in trouble,
oh my heart is in trouble."
"Now don't you multiply
my heart's troubles."
Thanks a lot!
- That's great, you've won.
- He has cheated.
- What did I do?
- What did he do?
He...
What do I have to do?
What are you asking her to do?
Ask her to tell us some
dialogues from a film.
Tell her to imitate a song from any film.
Why the imitation?
Let her do something original.
Do it, Nisha. It would be fun.
Come on, do it!
MRS. DOCTOR: Let's hear! - DOCTOR: Great!
"O mother, the crow on your
roof foretells that..."
"...your darling daughter
has renounced this house..."
"...and has fallen in
love with a stranger!"
"O mother, the crow on your
roof foretells that..."
"...your darling daughter
has renounced this house..."
"...and has fallen in love with a sage!"
"The fireworks are sizzling."
"The drumbeats are my messengers."
"That sage was illuminated
like the moon..."
"...he came to my door
and proclaimed his love!"
"Having rubbed ashes on his body..."
"...having rubbed ashes on his body..."
"...he remained awake the whole night."
"Your darling daughter has
renounced this house..."
"...and has fallen in love with a sage!"
"Listen, O Darling! Dance, O Darling!"
"Dance and colour this atmosphere."
"You had taken a religious
vow for my wedding..."
"...now you should get me
engaged with that sage."
"Apply henna on these hands."
"Apply henna on these hands..."
"...and tie the auspicious
thread of the ritual."
"Your darling daughter has
renounced this house..."
"...and has fallen in love with a sage!"
"O mother, the crow on your
roof foretells that..."
"...your darling daughter
has renounced this house..."
"...and has fallen in
love with a stranger!"
Sister-in-law, we have a complaint.
You were here for so long but
never came over to our place.
- My dear, when did you call?
- You better be quiet!
Do we have to invite our own?
You're right. Sister-in-law,
we promise to come the next time.
Shall we go, now?
It's time for the train to leave.
But my in-law is not to be spotted.
What's the rush?
I wanted to bid you all a proper farewell.
- Nisha!
Daughter-in-law!
This is for you.
But what about our gift?
Hey, it's okay!
Dear in-law, this heart is so crazy.
Whatever it gets, it always expects more!
The other day, we stopped you all.
Now, the heart once again desires
to stop you all for a day.
Brother, please do me a favour.
I want a photo with Nisha.
That would be a remembrance
of her loving stay with us.
- Sir, one photo for us too.
- Me too!
Me too!
All right! Prem, get the camera.
Are you going?
There's no excuse now...
so that I can stop you.
Can I ask you something?
Will you tell me the truth?
What?
Why did you stop me yesterday?
I wanted to speak to you
on a couple of topics.
What?
Immediately after the
inauguration of the factory...
...l'll speak to sister-in-law
about our marriage.
What are you all staring
at, my dear friends?
Our Prem is the big boss today!
Salute him!
- Good!
- Thank you!
Are you going to your
maternal place tomorrow?
Yes, mom and dad remember
the little one a lot.
- I will go with her.
- I'll go.
- I'll go...
Shut up!
We both will go.
- There's a letter from your village.
- Letter from my village?
What does it say? Please, read it.
- What is written?
- Your sister-in-law is very sick.
She has been admitted to a hospital.
They've asked you to
come over immediately.
But...
Sister-in-law...
You make the arrangements to leave.
You will get the afternoon bus.
I'll make the arrangements for you to leave.
Who are you giving this cash to?
I'm giving it to Lalloo.
He'll need it for the treatment.
This is what I feared.
I know these servants very well.
- This sickness is an excuse to get some cash.
- Auntie!
Letters like these are
available for 5 bucks.
Neither will this cash
come back nor will he...
It was my duty to caution you.
Now it's left to you to decide. Servant!
Lalloo!
I swear! This letter is not fake.
It hasn't been bought.
It's a false accusation.
It's because I'm a small man!
From when have you become small?
You call me sister-in-law, right?
Keep this.
I'm afraid.
What if something happens to her?
Nothing's going to happen to her.
Come with me.
I'm confident that nothing
will happen to her.
Go!
Listen!
When she is cured,
tell her that you've found yourself a girl.
- So, are you leaving?
- You come along, too.
I'll come over to bring you back.
Let's go, sister-in-law!
Just a minute! Let us have tea, at least!
- There's no time for tea now.
- Give the child to me.
Only one chance, okay?
So, you're ready to go?
Uncle!
Lalloo went yesterday.
You will go today. I will be restless.
The work of our factory has started now.
Please get my brother-in-law
married and get us a companion.
That's great, sister-in-law!
A sister-in-law should be like this.
Did you see that, Rajesh? What times!
Daughter-in-law, it's your responsibility
now to find a bride for him.
I love you, sister-in-law!
What's the matter, brother-in-law?
I'm going to my maternal place
and you are the one who's excited.
One word about your marriage and
the weather seems transformed!
Yes, sister-in-law! I love you!
Let's talk something serious now.
Uncle has given me your
responsibility now.
Tell me, would you like a love
marriage or an arranged marriage?
Sister-in-law, a love marriage
that you have to arrange.
- What?
- I love you, sister-in-law!
Did you see that, son?
Your uncle is smarter than your dad!
He has already found an auntie for you.
Even he likes his auntie.
He has seen the photo.
What do you say, little one? Say, yes.
Show me the photo, too.
You talk about photo,
I'll show you her face itself.
So, is the destination
of your love on the way?
It's on the way,
sister-in-law, on the way.
My destination has
arrived but where's yours?
Sister-in-law, the destination
of both of us is the same.
Nisha!
Welcome, sister-in-law!
Hey!
Come on in.
Sister-in-law, have a seat.
Think of it as your own home!
- What is all this?
- You read this first.
'Mom and dad have gone out.'
- 'Won't return till evening.'
'You have your breakfast-Nisha!'
I got it! You and your madam
have pre-arranged this program.
What love!
Call up your brother at the office.
Why? - Let me give him the good news too.
- Sister-in-law, where are your feet?
- Call up!
Hello!
- Is brother in?
- No. He's gone out for some important work.
- Gone out?
- Leave a message.
Tell him to call up sister-in-law,
as soon as he returns. - Yes.
Now, please get up.
Put this on Nisha in front of me.
Sister-in-law, how can I? Your sister
is so shy that she's not coming down.
If she's not coming down, we'll go to her.
We're from the boy's side.
We'll take along the marriage procession.
"I'm going..."
"I'm going with my brother-in-law's
marriage procession."
"No music, nobody else,
only the message of happiness"
"I'm going with my brother-in-law's
marriage procession."
"Brother-in-law becomes the groom
and wears the turban on the head."
"Sister-in-law gives him her blessings."
"The buds of love blossom and
we get happiness all the time."
"I bless you from the bottom of my heart."
"Astride a horse,
this groom goes to get his bride"
"I'm going..."
"I'm going with my brother-in-law's
marriage procession."
"That's great Lord!
What a pair you have created!"
"Brother-in-law and sister-in-law...
congratulations!"
"More than any other
ritual in this world..."
"...the relation of hearts
is the most important!"
"The all-important moment has arrived."
"Till yesterday, I was the only
daughter-in-law of the house."
"I will command and I will stare too."
"And she'll just watch with awe."
"I come with a thousand dreams"
"I'm going..."
"I'm going with my brother-in-law's
marriage procession"
It must be his phone.
Nisha, please take care of him.
Sister-in-law!
Doctor, she's trying to say something.
Injection Atropine, quick!
Please do something, doctor.
What's the matter, doctor?
I'm sorry!
Have it, Tuffy! The one who used
to feed you won't be coming!
She was here only for a few
days to distribute her love.
Have it, dear!
Be brave, brother.
Wonder what magic she had!
Without her, we've forgotten to live!
We've forgotten to live, doctor!
Hey, brother. Stop!
How are you, brother? Take this cash.
Brother, a miracle
occurred a few days back.
Jagan... Jagan!
All the doctors had given up.
They said that she wouldn't survive.
But I had faith that
nothing could happen to her.
After all, my sister-in-law
Pooja had prayed for her!
And that's what happened.
She opened her eyes and smiled.
I told her that it's because of
my sister-in-law's blessings.
I'd like to give this good
news to my sister-in-law.
That blessing which was over
us has been snatched from us.
Big brother, what happened?
What has happened, big brother?
Sir, she gave up her life
for the sake of my tears!
She blessed and gave the gift
of life to my own sister-in-law.
Big brother, do ask God as to why
he takes away all the good people.
Why does he call them?
Ask him, big brother.
Laloo, your sister-in-law
Pooja was a goddess of love!
She was so full of love and care!
He is hungry for love, too!
He needs love, too!
Uncle!
The love and care that you talk about...
...that was rightfully
due to our little one.
What will happen of him now?
Big brother, what will
happen of our little one now?
Big brother, tell me,
what will happen of our little one?
Go child, go and put him
to sleep in his place.
Yes!
- Is the child asleep?
- He's trying to sleep.
He considers his auntie's
lap to be his mother's.
After Pooja's departure,
when we miss her so much...
...just think of Rajesh's plight.
Rajesh is not very well.
He may not say a word...
...but we have been observing
him for the past few days.
He is mentally disturbed thinking
of the welfare of the child.
- But doctor, what is the cure?
- There is a cure.
Brother, we have to set
up his life once again.
Professor... 'This is the way of
life that can't go unnoticed...
...the breath stops but life goes on!'
For a child, the shadow of
a mother is very important.
I'd say, at an appropriate moment,
do speak to Rajesh about it.
Please drop me to the dispensary.
I'll give Rajesh's medicines too.
I'll leave, professor.
The doctor was absolutely right.
Rajesh, you need not
worry about your child.
Do heed my advice and remarry.
You haven't aged!
You will still get a lot of proposals.
Well, my Sweetie is all ready
for marriage even today.
If Rajesh had got married to Sweetie...
...we would have been spared
the agony of this day.
Bhagvanti!
You better be quiet!
Rajesh, my child,
I have already spoken to Sweetie.
She has only one condition.
The maid will look after the child.
What?
- Will a maid look after the child?
- Yes.
Big brother, I beg of you. Don't hand
over our little one to such a woman...
...who doesn't know the
meaning of the word 'mother'.
- You don't interfere!
- Lalloo is right.
This choice of yours doesn't
have the qualities of a mother.
To love somebody else's child,
one needs to understand one's customs.
Do you understand?
Look!
Sister-in-law, he is right.
He's talking a lot of rubbish
and affronting my niece.
Which girl would like to be a step mom?
Which parents would hand
over her daughter to Rajesh?
Forgive me, I'd like to ask you...
...will you get your
Nisha married to Rajesh?
Bhagvanti!
Stop it. That's enough now.
You be quiet.
Keep the lectures for your college.
I ask you, what's the harm in the
condition laid down by Sweetie?
All this argument for
the sake of a mere child.
How does it matter? Children do grow up.
Bhagvanti!
Disgusting!
This nature of yours might be
responsible for us to be childless.
I'm sorry... sorry!
No, uncle!
I don't want a step mom for my son.
All the step moms aren't necessarily bad.
- Brother!
- No, Prem. I won't marry again.
Come in, professor.
Rajesh isn't ready to marry.
He is right too. How can he hand
over his cherished one to a stranger?
Dad, for my son and me,
Pooja's thoughts would suffice!
But, someday,
you will have to get married.
Today, we all are there to
take care of the little one.
His grandfather, grandmother...
but we won't be there always!
In life, at every step, one needs support.
And then, bringing up a child
is a major responsibility.
But chances are that my
son might get such a mom...
...who might ignore him in the future.
For him, the mother that
would come would be his own.
Kailashnath, what if Nisha comes
into this house in place of Pooja?
From the time she's gone from here,
she's been talking about this place.
The child too is in her
care throughout the day.
Get married to Nisha, Rajesh.
In these conditions...
...if anyone can take the place of his
mom, it would be his auntie.
What do you have to say, Prem?
- Please do agree brother.
- The child will get a mom.
Please ask Nisha, first.
I deemed it right and spoke
about Nisha to Kailashnath.
If Nisha goes into that
house as a daughter-in-law...
...and brightens up
Pooja's house once again.
I don't think we can ask for
any happiness greater than that.
I'll ask Nisha and if she agrees
we'll get her married with fanfare.
Due to Pooja's absence,
we must not be found lacking in any way.
You...
Nisha!
What is your wish, my child?
Whatever you'll deem fit.
I'll just call up Kailashnath.
PROF. CHOWDHURY: Hello, Kailashnath!
Nisha has agreed.
I'll call up the priest today and find
an auspicious date for the marriage.
That's true.
Yes, absolutely!
"O mother, the crow on your
roof foretells that..."
"...your darling daughter
has renounced this house..."
"...and has fallen in
love with a stranger!"
Welcome, Kailashnath. Welcome, son.
Are you through with the preparations?
Yes, the cards have already been printed.
We'd gone to Ramtekdi for blessings.
Thought that we'd meet the little one too.
- Where is our little one?
- He's upstairs in Nisha's room.
- Child, please go and get the little one.
- I'll do that.
How is Nisha? - She's fine.
She's applying henna on her hands.
Sister, auntie has asked me to
bring the little one downstairs.
- May I take him?
- Yes. Be careful.
Don't worry!
Just have a look at what I have in my hand.
Her wedding card.
Please, read it.
'By the grace of God the
marriage of our daughter Nisha...
...has been fixed with
Rajesh.' 'You are welcome...'
- What are you reading? Read properly.
- I'm reading properly.
'By the grace of God the
marriage of our daughter Nisha...
...has been fixed with Rajesh.
You are welcome to bless the couple.'
- Give it to me.
- What happened?
"O mother, the crow on your
roof foretells that..."
"...your darling daughter
has renounced this house..."
"...and has fallen in
love with a stranger!"
"You had taken a religious
vow for my wedding..."
"...now you should get me
engaged with that sage."
"Apply henna on these hands."
"Apply henna on these hands..."
"...and tie the auspicious
thread of the ritual."
Uncle... this...
Nisha!
You've done us a big favour by
agreeing to get married to Rajesh.
You have given a new lease
of life to two people.
You've given them a new life.
See!
Nisha!
- What happened?
- She was all right, just now.
Please, call some doctor.
- Nisha!
- Child...
She's perfectly all right.
I've given her an injection.
She'll be conscious very soon.
- Doctor, how come, all of a sudden...
- It's a matter of marriage...
...must have felt giddy
due to the exertion.
Don't be afraid, professor.
I'll take your leave.
- Bhola...
- Yes...
Thank God. We'll take your leave too.
- Okay, little one!
- Come here...
- Good bye!
Mom, I'd like to meet Nisha for once.
- Come.
- Not now. I don't want to disturb her.
- Please, give her this letter.
- Okay!
RAJESH: Nisha, the step that you've
taken for the sake of the little one...
...l'm grateful to you for that.
Everyone is very happy with this decision.
But I know that every girl has
her own dreams, her own ambitions.
Nisha, if there is something in your
heart, please let me know.
Nothing is greater than
your happiness. Rajesh.
Hello!
Who?
"I will erase the memories
of love from my heart."
"For the sake of my responsibilities,
I will forget everything."
"The responsibilities that
you have to live up to!"
"How will I repay you for this favour?"
"As a mark of respect,
I bow in front of you."
I bow in front of you"
Auntie, let me hold my nephew.
Come to your uncle, my dear.
Go!
Come, child.
Oh God, what troubled times are we facing?
Prem brother has taken an
oath from me not to speak out.
He's made me helpless.
But you aren't helpless.
Oh God, work out such a miracle today...
...so that your devotees
trust you all the more.
O God!
'Prem, my sister strengthened
our love with this necklace.'
'She wished that her brother-in-law's
wife should wear this necklace.'
'I'm returning it. Nisha.'
Tuffy, please do me a favour.
Please give this to Prem.
Please come, Rajesh.
Tuffy!
NISHA: Prem, my sister strengthened
our love with this necklace.
She wished that her brother-in-law's
wife should wear this necklace.
I'm returning it. Nisha.
RAJESH: Nisha!
What is this, Nisha?
Did you see Pooja,
what the two of them were about to do?
What would I've done?
If they had taken this step.
What's the matter, Rajesh?
Why did you come up all of a sudden?
Please read this and tell
me if this is justice.
Uncle, this cherished one of yours...
...one who used to come to me
for the smallest of advice!
Today, hiding such a momentous
thing in his heart...
...keeping it behind the
facade of his smile...
...he has made me a stranger!
Prem, what you did isn't right.
Mom!
After Pooja's departure,
I had only one wish.
That my child never misses his mother.
I ask of you Nisha,
if you had accepted him as an auntie...
...would your motherly
love have been reduced?
Tell me, Nisha. Tell me.
Why are you quiet, Nisha? Answer me!
You fool! Were you out to sacrifice
your entire life and happiness?
Rajesh, you should be proud of them.
Whatever they did, they did it
considering it to be their duty.
I too have a duty now.
Pooja's incomplete dream!
Actually, it was my fault.
I couldn't understand what you were
trying to tell me... while departing.
Dad, I have a request.
Please get Nisha married to Prem.
Kailashnath!
I might have done some good
deeds in my last birth!
I'm blessed by getting such sons-in-law!
"We all admire you today!"
"I'm so full of happiness!"
"What else can my heart ask for?"
"I've got everything that
I could ever ask for!"