Arvind
Madubala
Nazer
Janakaraj
Pankaj Kapur
Srinagar, Kashmir
Take whatever you can
We will flee from here
All of you escape from here
I will manage them
All of you retreat
Kashmir militant leader
Wasim Khan arrested
Sundarapandiapuram
Tirunelveli District
Small desire
fluttering desire
Pearl like desire
stored up desire
Desire to kiss the moon
Desire planet earth
to orbit around me
Small desire
fluttering desire
Pearl like desire
stored up desire
Desire to kiss the moon
Desire planet earth
to orbit around me
Small desire
fluttering desire
Wish to become a jasmine flower
Wish to garland the breeze
Wish to touch the clouds
Wish to leave all sorrows
Wish to tie the world
in my flocks of hair
Small desire
fluttering desire
Pearl like desire
stored up desire
Desire to kiss the moon
Desire planet earth
to orbit around me
Small desire
fluttering desire
Pearl like desire
stored up desire
Wish to dance in
muddy field and plant seedlings
Wish to catch fish
and release back to river
Wish to wear the rainbow
Wish to lay inside the dew drop
Wish to wear a saree
from month of 'Chithirai'
Small desire
fluttering desire
Pearl like desire
stored up desire
Desire to kiss the moon
Desire planet earth
to orbit around me
Small desire
fluttering desire
Pearl like desire
stored up desire
Hey, What are you
searching early morning?
My sheep herds are missing
Some rustler has driven it away
Don't make noise
wait for sometime
Hey, little girl
is the car coming?
What are you searching?
My sheep herds
are missing old lady
She never bothered
about her lost hubby
Is she going to
retrieve your missing herds?
Are you watching
fun here, go and search
Mad guy, come here
Why do you ask them?
Your sheep is being
cooked in Ambi lyer's house
Go and see there
Samikannu's Sheep, be quiet
Roja, car is coming
Hey, run
little girl, come down
Don't stand like a tree, Go
Is he the groom...?
- Gosh, cigarette
- Yes
If you like it so much
I can leave you behind
Duck now
He turns, run
Samikannu Brother
your sheep's are straying
and you are watching the fun
Shouldn't you be responsible?
The herd has blocked car of
my sister's prospective groom
Go and drive them away
Brother careful
they will abuse you in English
If you don't know, ask me
Boys go and see it
Useless fellows
Sister's groom has come, Come on
Looks like a star
Talks English
Are you going
for bathing, Come soon
- Come, we have seen
- Vehicle has come
Come, the groom has come
- Chenbagam sister
- Where were you?
I asked you to
decorate and pluck flowers
- But you are roaming
- Mom where is sister?
What will happen
if your dad knows...
Sister, seen
I have seen
- What?
- Not for you, close your ears
He is fair,
handsome and very tall
He talks English grandma
Seems to be well educated
He smokes, but
seems to be a nice guy
I like him very much
Right match for my sister
Why are you eulogizing him?
Is the marriage
for you or your sister?
Keep quiet grandma
I want to study further
I don't want to marry
This is my sister's marriage
I vowed to pour 50
pot full to Goddess Muthalamman
Sister, stay as you are
Don't move
Pray now, Shall I pray for you?
He must be
the nicest guy in the world
He should like you
the moment he sees you
Within 4 days your
marriage should be celebrated
You must travel
in car, with him to the city
Before you go
I should hug you and weep
We have come to see just one girl
Will one of them select me?
You only said you
don't want a Madras girl
and want a village girl
What is this
they murmur in English?
Because they are from the city
- What is the groom doing
- Cryptologist
What cryptology?
Couldn't understand
- Don't you know?
It means photography, -My God!
- What is your salary?
- Not bad
Does it mean
1000, 2000 or 5000? Tell us
- Periyasamy, groom is evasive
- Yes
- Hey old lady
- Stop it
Is the groom fit as a fiddle?
Is there any deformity?
You have come to village
leaving aside city girls, so...
Ponnatha, shut your mouth
It is our fortune
They want a bride from our village
- Don't mistake us
- Yes brother
What is wrong in asking?
We are giving our girl
Should we not know whether
he is a man or a monkey
You can tell me
- You can count
and check my fingers, -Not that
Shall I carry you till that house?
- No, no
It is OK, - Come on
- Not required
- Come on
Be brave
If he asks in English
Respond in English
Don't worry, I have prayed
to all Gods in the village
- You stay here
- Why mom?
Prostrate to them
Sit down
With so many of us around
she may not look up
He will also not feel free
Let them be alone
Let them talk and decide
How can it be, Madam?
Before marriage
how can we allow them
- to talk in seclusion
- Don't crack jokes
Because you are from city
we brought the girl
Else the boy can see the girl
only after the engagement
In villages this may not
find acceptance
She was only kidding
Wait, there is nothing
wrong in what they ask?
After marriage
they are going to live together
Nothing wrong in
them talking to each other
Gosh, Rosa did you hear this?
They are going to
talk in seclusion
For 5 years, many times
I have lighted camphor here
Somehow make
him agree to marry sister
I will feed 10 people
I will light a lamp also
Somehow make him give his consent
Talk bravely
Are you going to
excel me and my hubby's
talk in the
plantain grove, those days
Where did you
allow that man to talk?
You imprisoned him
just like that, in a basket
Next day morning
only you released him
Don't we know about that?
Looks like a Granny's conference
I was born, bred
and brought up at Madras
I had never been to villages
But I want to marry
a village girl, this is my wish
I like this place,
the paddy fields, the falls,
the soil, this fragrance...
...these old ladies
I like everything
What are they talking?
Are they Reciting Ramayan?
Are they going to do
what you haven't done when young
Ah, Nalayani, she drove
her husband with in 2 years
Talk something
I will hear your voice
Tell something, say Sridevi
or Kollangudi Karupayi
I don't like this marriage
Don't shout
Tell them
you don't want this marriage
Tell my dad
that you don't like me
Chenbagam, don't
lean on wall like this
Give that coffee to him
Poor girl
She feels shy
My uncle
Soundarapandi is there for me
Long ago I have
decided him as my husband
There is a family feud
between mine & his dad
So they are looking
for a groom outside kinship
if I don't marry him
I will not be alive
Please don't agree
to this marriage
Wait
Then why did you
send your photograph to me?
Why did you make us
travel 500 miles?
You could have
told your dad earlier
Like my hubby, the city guy
doesn't want to stop talking
OK call your dad
I will tell him
If he comes to know
about this he will kill me
What can I do for that?
If you look at his face
and talk, this will happen
Wipe it
You should somehow save me
- Do you like the girl?
- Speak out without any shyness
Who will dislike our Chenbagam?
His face tells it all
Rishi do you like her?
Can we exchange the trays?
Say 'like her'
Say 'I like her'
I like this girl
Is it fair?
You have come from city
and are well educated
You came to see the eldest girl
Now you say
you like her sister? Is it fair?
Damn with your education
If any local guy said this
He would be flogged
Have you thought about her?
Who will marry her?
What will happen to the family?
All these old
ladies are telling you
Don't fall a prey to our curse
I can tell you this much
I told you not to
allow her to walk across
Did you bother to listen?
She has become
an adversary to her sister
- What did I do dad?
- Why are you hasty, you donkey?
You have ruined it
She hasn't done
anything wrong, young girl
- What did she do?
- She was gyrating before him
He was charmed under her spell
Now he is obstinate
that he will marry only her
Don't blame me dad
Do you know
how I prayed for her marriage?
Marriage is a
1000 year crop, it is all destined
If he likes Rosa
Let him marry her
Grandma, I will not marry
Be quiet
It is all because of you
This no misfortune
You can't find a groom like this
It is your good fortune
They came on their own
Rosa is also
old enough for marriage
What are you talking mother?
When the eldest
is yet to be married
How can you
think of her marriage?
There is a groom
waiting for her
Ask your brother in law
Chengiah to come
and finalise her
marriage with Soundarapandian
Do you want me
to forget the 30 year old enmity
Am I so thick skinned?
What great enmity?
Your dad started it all
You fanned it to great heights
Do you want the
posterity to continue it?
Don't do it, they are girls
They have to lead a life
They are going to
beget you grandchildren
Don't avenge them
Your mom is telling this
Go, Conduct both
the marriages jointly
Beat the drums
Rukkumani,
what is the sound in vicinity?
My ears can't bear tenor
find out what makes the sound
Rukkumani,
what is the sound in vicinity?
My ears can't bear tenor
find out what makes the sound
It is the sound of
kisses by married couples
The sound of joy
from the intermittent cot crackles
This sound won't
stop until the rooster cries
Rukkumani,
what is the sound in vicinity?
My ears can't bear tenor
find out what makes the sound
The little girl
has a lot of desires
Like an ant trapped in sugar
Step by step
Move up to the cot
The pearl beaded anklets
whine at sound of kissing
The Jasmine flower blossoms
Why does the scalp sweat?
Desire spreads the mat
But fear latched it
Rukkumani,
what is the sound in vicinity?
My ears can't bear tenor
find out what makes the sound
When Spouse
catches the index finger
The point where
the finger touch tickles
Was a concert at the Cupids palace
The bangles of the fille,
composed music
Kisses are exchanged
Life is in a crisis
Mind heats up
This birth gets gratified
Rukkumani,
what is the sound in vicinity?
My ears can't bear tenor
find out what makes the sound
It is the sound of
kisses by married couples
The sound of joy
from the intermittent cot crackles
This sound won't
stop until the rooster cries
We are obliged to you forever
We can never forget your help
- Why?
- Where is Roja?
She was there, inside
- She is not there inside
- Isn't she?
Happy journey
Bye, dad
Grandma
Take care
Sister
Small desire
fluttering desire
Pearl like desire
stored up desire
Desire to kiss the moon
Desire planet earth
to orbit around me
Small desire
fluttering desire
Pearl like desire
stored up desire
Don't know whether
you like our cooking or not
- Can I use this much of salt?
- Yes
Little less
Heard you are good
in cooking, your Grandma told me
You can prepare a feast
for fifty people in half an hour
But this Rishi isn't
interested in food at all
Always reading, music...
Or his computer
Half of the time
is spent at the library
Will read Newspaper in the
bathroom for half an hour
Crossword too is done there
Just go and look there
You'll find 8 to 10 books
He has never
appreciated my cooking
Try if you can make
him appreciate your cooking
First you ask him to quit smoking
- What is it?
- Smoke
Look
It was unintentional
Still angry with me?
I said sorry, Forget it
I am not bad
Little decent too
Don't I look innocent?
We are going to meet
my chief Dr. Chandramurthy
We are doing computer
software for Indian Military
Coding and Decoding
many confidential matters
Security clearance is
required for those who work
and for their family members also
I am taking you to my Chief
Do you understand me?
Wait
Next Saturday?
Is the work going well?
No problem
I will be there in Kashmir
2 to 3 days is enough
for any Crypto code
Sir, she is my wife
Who?
- Why did you stay here?
- You told me to wait here
OK Come in
I am Rishi's chief
But only in the office
My name is Chandramurthy
Finally got a
gullible girl for Rishi
Did you marry him out of interest?
What is your name?
You keep quiet
do not interfere in this
- What is your native?
- A rural village
Not so, It is Sundarapandiapuram
Tirunelveli district
Girl from our place
That's why it is so charming
It's long time
since I heard chaste Tamil
His Tamil, is not good at all
Madras dialect
Isn't the Muthalamman
Temple situated in your place
No, it is about
40 miles east of our place
We used to go
there for the flower festival
- Is it in the month of Chithirai?
- No, in the month of Thai
For this we take basket
full of flowers in the cart
I have never seen
Sir I have brought her
for the security clearance
I am your chief
Are you threatening me?
Did he threaten you?
- Does Mother and son
speak English at home -Yes
What else did he say?
You do not know
how to talk with the superior
So keep quiet
If you open your mouth
your ignosense will be revealed
He is a book worm
Don't be afraid, I'll take care
Look, this girl is from our place
She will not be
shy or timid, bear in mind
Roja, do you know
how to prepare 'Paniyaram'?
We have come
for security clearance
No clearance is required
for a girl from our place
Do you know this
milky white Paniyaram?
Do you know how to prepare?
I can prepare it very well
I will be back
from Kashmir by next week
I will come directly to your house
You must serve me that
hot and steamy Paniyaram
What? She is not
assuring and inviting me
I won't be here next week
I am going back to my place
It is just 4 days
since your arrival, what happened?
I want to see mom
You have been
with mom for the past 18 years
- Isn't that enough?
- I will go to my place
My dear villager,
hereafter this is your place
This is your house
and I am your husband
No, this is not my house
I do not like this place
doesn't draw me
I must not be here
My sister is
supposed to be in this house
You have deceived my sister
Is that the cause for your anger?
Is that why, you were
silent for all these days
Don't you have conscience?
Tell me frankly
Can you justify what you've done
- You can't find a girl
like my sister, -Let me speak
Even if you scout for
7 births all over the place
- You have rejected such a person
- I didn't say so
You talked to my sister and suddenly
and said you want to marry me
How badly
she would have been hurt?
How can I face my sister now?
- For rest of the life, I can't face her
- Listen to me
All of them damned me
that I have enticed you
Will you let me speak?
What is the use of
education, if there is no heart?
- It may be a game in city
- Will you listen?
- You rejected her
- You are not listening to me
- Is it a mock marriage?
- Listen to me
Won't you listen to me?
I did not reject her
but she rejected me
I don't like this marriage
Don't shout
Tell them
you don't want this marriage
No, you are lying
She can never
talk like that
Chenbagam, don't
lean on wall like this
Give that coffee to him
Poor girl
she feels shy
My uncle
Soundarapandi is there for me
Long ago I have
decided him as my husband
There is a family feud
between mine & his dad
So they are looking
for a groom outside kinship
If I don't marry him
I will not be alive
Please don't agree
to this marriage
How can I believe this?
This is the fact
Believe it or leave it
I spoke to sister over phone
She is very happy
Said you are like God to her
I was angry
with you out of ignorance
Forgive me
I swear, I am sorry
I am not bad
Little decent too
Don't I look innocent?
When?
Which hospital?
What happened?
Prof. Chandramurthy, is admitted
in Trinity Hospital
I will see him and come
What happened?
Don't be alarmed
with these gadgets?
This is a hi-tech plot
by the doctors to make money
- You should do me a favour
- Tell me
I was supposed to go to Kashmir
for an important assignment
I could not go
You may be required to go
- For what? - There is
a military out-post in Baramulla
Messages from foreign nations
are intercepted there
which are encoded in Crypto
You should decode it
It is a 2-day assignment
Sunil Tandon
will arrange everything
It is an urgent assignment
In a situation like this in Kashmir
I am worried
about sending you there
Never mind, Kashmir is in India
Why should we fear
to go to any corner in India
The military security
will make all arrangements
I will take care
Remember, white Milk Paniyaram!
Recover quickly and get discharged
I will prepare it for you
Rishi, you are the witness
I telegraphed to your father
he will pick you up
You can go back to
your village as you wish
You come back
whenever you feel like
- Do you understand?
- What work do I have there?
Don't leave me
Take me with you
To Kashmir?
Didn't I apologise?
No need,
you go back to your village
- Aunty, come, - Where
- Come quickly, - What?
- What is it?
- Come and have a look
Aunty, ask him not to leave me?
Ask him to take me with him?
Only one week ago you got married
How can you leave her and go?
- Why are you teaming up with her?
- Poor girl
She is young and
newly married, take her with you
My baggage is also ready
Why the streets are isolated?
Roaming on the streets prohibited
- Why? - To control
the movement of terrorists
I am little scared
Where are you taking me?
The fresh silver
rain falls over here
This dazzling
moon light drenches my body
It is chill in the places
which cannot be revealed
Mind wanders in
search of warmer places
The fresh silver
rain falls over here
This dazzling
moon light drenches my body
It is chill in the places
which cannot be revealed
Mind wanders in
search of warmer places
If you become the river
I will be the bank
If you become the little bird
I will be your sky
The fresh silver
rain falls over here
This dazzling
moon light drenches my body
Men do not ask for flowers
where there are no women
Plants do not bloom
The earth blooms
when the free end
of your saree unfolds
This idea was not sung by Kamban
who prompted it into your ears
The fresh silver
rain falls over here
This dazzling
moon light drenches my body
It is chill in the places
which cannot be revealed
Mind wanders in
search of warmer places
The fresh silver
rain falls over here
This dazzling
moon light drenches my body
Life flower will
blossom when you hug
If you run suddenly
Life flower will wither and wilt
Does your eyes survey
womanliness untouched by hands?
The virgin moon
come and dance with my chest?
The fresh silver
rain falls over here
This dazzling
moon light drenches my body
It is chill in the places
which cannot be revealed
Mind wanders in
search of warmer places
If you become the river
I will be the bank
If you become the little bird
I will be your sky
- The fresh silver rain
- falls over here
- This dazzling moon light
- drenches my body
- The fresh silver rain
- falls over here
- This dazzling moon light
- drenches my body
- Ram Singh, - Yes Sir
- Did you see my wife? - No, Sir
God of the North
I don't know Your name
My Grandma has told me
that all Gods are same
That is why I have come to You
Do you understand Tamil?
You are God
You know everything
Before I left my village
I fought with my God
Telling you have
given me a hubby like him
I won't worship you anymore
and won't even visit you
Now I realize that
He has given me a nice hubby
I spoke in ignorance
North God, You should go
and persuade my God
I will break the coconut here
Won't You inform Him?
Will You forget?
It is a false alarm
Let's go back
My Goodness!! What is this?
- Is it wrong to break
a coconut here? - Yes
- Is the North God speaking?
- Madam
- That too in Tamil
- I can speak all languages
I can speak Tamil,
Telugu, Malyalam, Kannada...
...Hindi, Urdu, English,
German, French, Greek...
...Arabian and Persian languages
I can tell the Past,
Present and the Future
Are you a Tamil?
I am Achu Maharaj from Pollachi
Here I am a Tourist Guide,
Astrologer, Ayurveda...
...Allopathy
Homeopathy, Seethapathy,
...Ganapathy and Lakshmipathy
It is all me, many in one
Come, show your hand
I will tell your fortune
Earlier lot of tourists
used to come here
Now only terrorists come here
Are you a tourist
or a terrorist?
No, it is an official visit for my hubby
What official work do you have
in this troubled state of Kashmir?
It is a big job
He said some Cryptology
but I couldn't follow
Is there something like that?
Look, my dear
I am leaving for Pollachi next week
I have taken Rail ticket,
bus ticket, Platform ticket
I am not for this game
of guns and bullets
Already my life line has a break
Next time you can meet me
only at Pollachi for Palmistry
He is my hubby
This guy?
Leave him
INTERVAL
Listen to me, my husband...
8 to 10 people
Dragged away
my husband in a vehicle
What is your problem?
Kidnapped and dragged
away my husband in a car
Don't know
she is talking in Madrasi
What is she telling?
What do you want?
Around 8 to 10 people
wearing masks
and armed with heavy guns
My husband
Call someone who speak
Madrasi language
Please help, they
dragged away my husband
Be calm
The interpreter is coming
Please wait for one minute
Why should I wait?
A group of 10 people
abducted my husband
What do you mean by
wait for a minute now?
They were disguised and armed
Don't you sympathize a bit?
Don't you have wife and children?
What is the matter?
Please tell us what happened?
Abduction?
When?
Today morning
- Where?
- Temple
Rishi Kumar a computer
engineer from Tamilnadu
has been abducted
at Srinagar this morning
He was abducted
by an unidentified group
near the famous Gulmarg temple
Chenbagam sister
come immediately
Mr. Rishikumar from Chennai
Went to Kashmir
to advice Indian army
on telecommunication techniques
The army, BSF
and Jammu Kashmir police
are on high alert
since abduction of Rishikumar
All efforts are taken
by them to find out Rishikumar
Brother
Beating a woman
Have you brains? Effeminate
Shut up your mouth
We won't hurt you
Don't be afraid
But if there is a valid reason
We won't hesitate to kill you
Killing you, is not a big job
How do you speak Tamil?
How do you know Tamil?
What do you all want?
Independence
- Whose Independence?
- Our Independence
Independence of Kashmir
Independence of each
and every Kashmiri
Independence of all
His independence... my Independence
Independence of even
the new born babies
Independence of the land,
mountain, its greenery and all
Freedom from your nation
Aunty
I am Roja
Got any information?
Not yet
No news on his whereabouts
How did it happen?
All happened before my eyes
A group of tall people came
At gun point, threatened
and dragged him away
What can I do, aunty?
Roja, Don't cry
I think it's my ill luck
Because he married me
this has happened to him
Roja, don't say like that
Shall I come over there?
No, I can manage it
Please make vows in all temples
Please call
Dr. Chandra Moorthy and tell him
Yes, I spoke to him
Said he has moved it
at the ministerial level
He assured to take all efforts
Hot news
Buy paper
I will call later
I have finished
Buy paper
Nav Shathi Times:
Terrorists threaten to butcher Rishi
You'll live for 20 more years
After 30 years
you will get a lot of money
- Give me my fees now
- Have it
- Life line itself is missing
- Yes
- You will live longer
- Tell me more
Oh! My lifeline is in danger now
What will I do now?
Sir, look at my palm
or return the money, don't cheat
Why are you
running after seeing me?
Oh it's nothing there is a
'Pooja' in Sardarji's house
To bring holy water from Ganga
What is in this paper?
Is anything mentioned
about his whereabouts?
Is he fine?
Tell me Achu
Nothing to worry about
Photographed among armed people
and written something
Please read it and explain to me
It says Wasim Khan is in jail
If he is released in 3 days
they will release your husband
What else is there?
Read it further
- If not released within 3 days
- If not released?
There may be troubles
Read it fully and tell me Achu
If not released...
his fingers will be
parceled to the town hall
Next day, toes
will be left near the temple
Within a week
engineer's body will be minced
It is written like that
Sinners!!
Roja, where are you going?
Stop, I will also come
Wait, you are coming frequently...
Look, what they have said
What are you going to do now?
Sir, regarding
what is mentioned in paper
Have you got any information?
The case is not with us now
The army has taken charge
We can do nothing
I don't know about all these
You have so many policemen here
Please send 10 or 20
of them and find him out
She doesn't understand
We are helpless
Better you meet Colonel B. Rayappa
- OK Sir, I will tell her
- Do not nod your head
They have given 3 days deadline
What is he going to do?
He is helpless
because the case is now with Army
Only Colonel Rayappa can do
Let him come over here
Tell them
I won't leave until he comes
- What is this?
- No matter how long I wait
Unless I know
I won't leave this place
Come
Poor man's food
Don't know if you would like it
How do you know Tamil?
What is he saying?
I have studied in your state
At Coimbatore
In Agricultural college
For four years
Eat slowly, don't be afraid
Once the Govt. Releases Wasim Khan
We will free you too
Explain it to him
Have food
Don't be afraid
Once your Govt. Releases Wasim Khan
We will free you too
That's what he said
Understood, have your food brother
Who is this Wasim Khan?
How many murders he has done?
I am not ready
I don't want to be released
in exchange of a murderer
What?
We don't want your consent, eat
Even if it costs my life
You can't get
Wasim Khan by pledging me
Is it a Tamil's arrogance?
No, Indian Arrogance
Colonel Sir
This is Rishi Kumar's wife
You can speak in Tamil
It is 3 days
since my husband is missing
His whereabouts are not known
You say Army, Military
You are all holding high ranks
But still you
can't trace my husband
Didn't he come for your work?
You assured for his security
You don't even search for him
When will you trace my husband?
When will you release
that useless Wasim Khan
and rescue my husband?
Do you know who is Wasim Khan
Who is he to me
I want my hubby back
He has killed 43 people
If we release him for your sake
He may kill 43 more
Is that OK?
I want my hubby back
If we release him
he will kidnap someone else
and ask us to release
50 persons from jail
What will happen to the Nation?
I am not worried
about the Nation, but my hubby
Shut up
Who are you?
Aren't you born in India?
Is this not your Motherland?
Don't you have right in this soil?
No honor? Is your
house important to you?
Is the Nation
not important to you?
Terrorists are trying
to disintegrate the nation
You care about your house only
Is the soil not important?
Do you know how
many people work in this camp
Do you know?
3000 persons
Despite rain, snow and cold
they are guarding the border
Their families
are 1000 miles far away
If they too were like you
this nation would not exist
Do you know
what's going on here? War
how many perished so far?
Innocent soldiers
women, children and gullible
Is your hubby important
than all these people?
Instead of my hubby
if a Minister's son
or daughter was abducted
Will you tell the same?
Is a Minister's daughter
more valuable than others?
In what way
my hubby is inferior?
Govt. Has assigned you
this rescue mission
You are responsible
if anything happens to him
I won't leave this place
until you trace him
I won't leave you too
Hi rustic
Darling!!
- I have brought you something
- What is it?
What is it?
Close your eyes
then only I will give
- Please give my clothes
make it fast, - I won't
Your village wife
will die in the chilling cold
- Petticoat
- Nothing, come out with it
- Gosh, I beg you to
- Come, - My God!!
- My dear fool!!
- I feel shy
- Whose sweater is this?
- Yours - Isn't it mine?
- Give it
- My God! - Give it
- No
- Give it
Don't run stop
- Am not I begging you?
- Stop, - What is this?
- Got you
- No
My dear VILLAGER!
Will you follow English?
A little, tell me
They are asking for time
to release Wasim Khan
Your Govt. Wants proof
that you are alive
They want to hear your voice
Tell them if Wasim Khan
is not released I will be killed
Say it
Victory to India
- Victory to India
- Javed
Delay in release of
Rishi Kumar, Computer Engineer
Oh my love Roja
where are you?
Tears are rolling down, dear
Oh my love Roja
where are you?
Tears are rolling down, dear
You are there in eyes
You are there in tears
When eyes are closed
You appear in the mind
Tell, what happened?
Oh my love Roja
where are you?
Tears are rolling down, dear
The touch of breeze
reminds me your saree
Seeing tender flowers
reminds me your body
The silver stream speech
reminds me of your words
When two clouds merge
reminds me our cuddle
No words when there is mouth
No life when you are not with me
Does Kisses have thorns?
Oh my love Roja
where are you?
Tears are rolling down, dear
You are there in eyes
You are there in tears
When eyes are closed
You appear in the mind
Tell, what happened?
Oh blowing breeze
Stop you have no job
Oh whispering moonlight
Go away, no feminine here
Oh garden with flowers
Wither it all
no more lovely hair
Oh sky vanish
and fade away to a spot
No dames are necessary now
What is service
after once life has gone
Does Kisses have thorns?
Oh my love Roja
where are you?
Tears are rolling down, dear
You are there in eyes
You are there in tears
When eyes are closed
You appear in the mind
Tell, what happened?
I want to meet Wasim Khan
Who?
The one who is in jail
That murderer
Better to please
the opponent than the witness
Leave me alone
I am going back home today
Don't want Wasim Khan and Kashmir
35 dependents are
there in the native place
Even if you don't
come I will meet him
Why are you obstinate?
Why do you insist
on meeting Wasim Khan?
Will you take me there or not?
No, I wish to stay alive
Leave me please
Are you so particular
about going there?
He is coming
I am scared
Greetings Brother
No, Salaam Male kum
Is everything OK?
Ask him to release my husband
Sir, her...
Tell him
Sir, her husband is with your gang
Please release him
Get lost!!
Tell him, we were
married just 1 month back
Look at this sacred thread
He is a good person
Killing an innocent
can't be justified
Are you Hindustani
We don't care
go away
- He is asking us to leave Come on
- Tell him I won't go
Tell him I want my hubby
If they are angry with the Govt.
Why do they torture my husband?
Tell me what wrong he has done
This is War
War for the liberation of Kashmir
He has killed a lot of innocents
Including new born
babies without mercy
That's why he is jailed here
But what err did my hubby do?
Ask him why he
is captured by his men?
Go, time is up
They say the it is time
Let us go
Don't know why they kill innocents
Can't they leave,
if they hate India?
Why are they avenging us?
This is our goal and target
We will do anything
to achieve it
What type of person are you?
Destroying one life
to save another's
How many more murders
will quench your thirst?
Leave me
I want my hubby back
Don't tempt me to kill you
I swear
Check upstairs
Oh my love Roja where are you?
Tears are rolling down dear
How many people you have killed?
Twenty?
Thirty?
- More than that
- Why?
Liberation is our goal
We are ordered by our leaders
Who are the leaders?
Are they from here
or the neighbouring nation
Will you kill anyone
if asked by the leaders?
He is your younger brother
Will you slay him
if you are asked to?
I will do
Your younger sister?
Your mother?
- I will do
- Why?
- Jehad
- What does it mean?
You won't understand it
It is Holy War
Against whom?
Your India
Oh! Tamil's, don't cry
it will dawn
Will holding a gun
solve your problems?
Will killing without
mercy make everything OK?
What about the 3 lakh families
who were living
in Kashmir for ages?
Where will they go and survive?
Don't they own this soil?
What about the hapless
infants without food and shelter?
Is it fair
to drive the inhabitants
of a house and claim ownership?
Wandering with guns
for someone's call
Blindly instigated
by foreign nations
You are destroying
your own people
The most invaluable
thing in the world is life
You are losing it
Life is not important
to us, Kashmir is important
Your life itself isn't your own
You have no right
on someone else's life
Your problem
can be solved through talks
This won't be solved through talks
This will be solved by separation
Won't be separated
India won't split
Chenbagam Sister
Hope you are living happily
and good things
are happening to you
I must have
committed a grave sin
Otherwise why should I
suffer like this
I am unable to bear
Visiting here everyday
Hoping to receive some information
A belief that they
will trace him somehow
I am panic stricken
I have no idea
about his whereabouts
Searching every
place with his photo
hoping that someone
would recognise him
Yet to find a clue
But I will not
come back without him
Sister, please encourage me
Sister, encourage me to trace him
How is Roja?
Has his hubby come back?
Who has abducted our son-in-law?
If all of us go there,
can't we bring him back?
Any information
about Roja's husband?
What man?
Someone has abducted
the son-in-law of our village
You are wasting your time here
Try and do something
For rescuing hostage
engineer Rishikumar
Kashmir terrorist leader
Wasim khan can't be released
Decides high level
committee of central Govt
Abduction of celebrities and release of terrorists
in lieu of that are to be prevented and this
decision is in line
with that, said the official
Liyakath, kill this betrayer
Their Govt. Has
refused to release Wasim Khan
Community may vary
but virtue is same
Place may vary
but land is same
Language may vary
but voice is same
Staff may vary
but flag is same
Direction may vary
but land is same
Music may vary
but sound is same
Our India is one and one only
Modern India is common
Hard toils created it
It was created
with diversity as manure
So is strong as a subcontinent
Oh human! It is strong
Separation not in this land
Rise up
- Who is that?
- It's me Achu
What?
- Colonel asked me to bring you
- Where?
Come... just to identify...
Who? What happened?
Nothing, you come, I will tell you
Tell me in detail
Please come, I will tell you
Why did you bring me here?
Someone with
bullet pierced at 5 or 6 places
Even face is not identifiable
That's why I brought you here
You have to identify correctly
Come
I won't come
Achu I won't go
- That's not my husband
- Come
I know, that's not him
Ask them to search for him
I know, I will not look at it
It's not him
Didn't I tell you?
Nothing will happen to him
It is not him
Going across the border
For training
Sir
She is Mrs. Rishikumar
Wife of the abducted engineer
She wants to meet
the minister for a minute
Minister has a meeting at Jammu
You can't meet him now
Give me the petition
I will hand over to the minister
Sir I want to meet
the minister for 2 minutes
Will you please take me to him?
I am begging you
Beti, I understand your problem
You are calling me "Beti"
Doesn't Beti mean Daughter?
I plead like your own daughter
Please rescue my husband
She is asking you
to rescue her husband
Born and brought up
in a rural village of Tamilnadu
I don't understand
this language, this situation
I don't understand politics
Someone was murdered
I was asked to identify
if it is my husband
Unbearable
Negotiations are going on
Said it will take few more days
What if time lapses like this?
If something happens
to him before that
I am unable
to wait in anticipation
Many days passed
since his abduction
We are not Very lmportant People
Are we not Indian Citizens?
Shouldn't the Govt. Protect us?
See daughter
It is all in your hands
You have to rescue him
I trust you like God
Please don't say, No
Please rescue my husband
We are trying our level best
Yesterday evening
at the Indian border
13 armed youth from Kashmir
were shot dead by Pakistani Army
when they tried
to cross the border
This unreasonable action has caused
utter dissatisfaction
among Kashmiri's
The situation in Kashmir is tense
There were rallies in protest
Your younger brother
was a good person
Good hearted
It should not have
happened to him
Betrayal
Fight against India
We will see the rest
That's what we were told
Now
They have shot our boys to death
Not only my younger brother
13 persons
All were 15 year old boys
Betrayal
We fought all
these days, for what?
This blood
This violence
This extremism
Why don't you stop it
when you know it's wrong?
We are at half way in war
Can't retreat now
Whether we are right or wrong
We must fight
Let the enemy be good or bad
He should be killed
Liyakath, you pray
for 4 times a day
Tell me honestly
The extremism
and other atrocities done by you
Will your God Allah accept it?
Will your religion accept homicide?
Today these 13 boys got killed
Are we happy about it?
Leave the guns and terrorism
Be a human than a terrorist
Has anything happened to him?
Did they do anything to him?
Wasim Khan is going to be released
Decision was taken at Delhi
Your husband will be back
- Is it true?
- It is true
Your appeal
to the minister is fruitful now
Wasim Khan was
caught after 35 days search
Now his handcuffs
will be removed and sent off
Is that enough?
Do you know why?
I am happy
You are going to
get back your husband
You are happy
A scientist is
going to be retrieved
Politicians will get a good name
They are also happy
HAPPY
Very happy
A person who was
caught after a hard chase
will go Scot free
15 personnel clad in uniform
Lost their lives while
attempting to capture him
Their sacrifice is a waste now
Happy
Very happy
That Wasim Khan will come out
and will kill more people
Very happy
He is coming back
He will be back
I told you earlier
Achu's prediction is right
that he will be back for sure
By God's grace
Wasim Khan will be released
Your life
is valuable to your Govt.
For your sake
they are releasing Wasim Khan
Take him back
and lock him up
So that he doesn't escape
Some other day
if not today, we will be liberated
and you will witness it
Why did they do like this?
Where is he?
Why did they not bring him here?
I hoped to unite you
with your hubby somehow
Please don't say so
Nothing has happened to him
Did you see
anything happening to him?
You have seen
only his blood stains
But nothing has
happened to him, I know
My mind says
that he is still alive somewhere
I will not be daunted
I will somehow trace him out
Where will you search?
Going to visit
each and every terrorist's house
Won't there be women like me?
I will beg to them
or will brave out
I am not scared
anymore, I won't be afraid
Wait
I will accompany you
Until we find your
hubby, I will be with you
Hey! Ensure that he doesn't escape
I'll go this way
Don't let him slip
What are you going to do?
You cannot kill me
When your younger brother died
I noticed how you wept
This terrorism is a camouflage
Deep inside you are a human
You are a man with conscience
You cannot kill me
I am going
Do whatever you like
Go
You have reformed a terrorist
VILLAGER!
Oh! Tamil
tomorrow is ours
the nation is also ours
Oh! Tamil
tomorrow is ours
the nation is also ours
Say my house is
Mother Tamilnadu
Be firm that
you are an Indian
Oh! Tamil
tomorrow is ours
the nation is also ours
Community may vary
but virtue is same
Place may vary
but land is same
Language may vary
but voice is same
Staff may vary
but flag is same
Direction may vary
but land is same
Music may vary
but sound is same
Our India is one and one only
Oh! Tamil
Don't shed tears
It will dawn
Don't get distressed
Oh! Tamil
Don't shed tears
It will dawn
Don't get distressed
Is there an Indian's blood in you?
The United India will protect you
Oh! Tamil
tomorrow is ours
the nation is also ours
Modern India is common to all