Attention!
Stand at ease!
Major Vijay Malhotra reporting sir.
- Come. Sit down.
- Thank you.
- Yes Vijay?
- Sir.
The truck carrying arms to the border
Met with an accident last month.
And the task to enquire
the fire in the jeep,
I've prepared its' report.
- So what's the outcome?
- It was a plan not an accident.
The aim of being stealing of arms.
Means our people are involved.
Must hand the case to intelligence.
I have a request.
The truck that is to leave tomorrow
give me the responsibility of taking
it to the border security force.
If this happens again,
the arms looters will be uncontrollable.
Okay.
Why doesn't this plane fly?
What are you saying, son?
Do toys ever fly?
Buy me a flying plane.
First grow up. Then you'll see
you'll have more planes
than people have cars. Go.
For the time being, make do with this.
If you fill A, B, C...
in his mind instead of this
he'd learn to write his name.
He will learn.
The alphabets are not leaving India.
But look at his age.
He's grown so big.
You neither showed him a
book, nor did he see a school.
Aren't you at all worried?
Buy a couple of buffaloes with
the money you'll spend on books.
The boy will drink milk
and become as tough as us!
He'll become as clever as brother.
You won't believe it.
- What is it?
- Sir has called for an urgent meeting.
What meeting?
Nothing as such but he
has called everybody.
BALDEV: Subhedar Pratap Singh has come.
That's fine but what about the cash
for the arms we gave last time?
He's given this bag full!
- How much is it?
- I can't count much.
I'll weigh it if you say.
Must be 7 or 8 kilos with the bag.
No need. You wait at the corner,
- I'll change and come.
- Okay.
Are you doing the duty for which the
government gave you this uniform?
Of course! That's what I'm doing!
You were but no more!
Earlier 3000 rupees used to come
on the first of every month.
Now millions come at any date!
I am asking, why? What do we lack?
What an illiterate woman!
I want to live, enjoy!
By selling your country?
Do you want me to spend
all my life carrying a gun?
And die at the enemy's hand someday?
You want to be a widow?
That widow is better than a woman
whose husband is a martyr for the nation.
I can bare to see you dying by a bullet.
But I can't bare the
stigma of a traitor on you!
- Shanti!
- I am saying it for the last time
don't be loyal to me.
But if you're disloyal to your
country, I won't forgive you!
- Mother!
- Don't try to teach me!
I can leave my wife for money!
Subhedar Pratap Singh has come.
What's the matter?
DK always meets after delivery of arms.
What meeting is this beforehand?
I've called this meeting
because the truck of arms which is
going to the border with you tomorrow,
you can't loot it easily.
- Why?
- Because... another in charge is coming.
Major Vijay Malhotra.
How did you find out?
From our fourth partner,
Jaswant Dalal, Major's driver.
He is a very strict officer.
With him around,
forget trucks we can't steal a nail!
Opportunity never strikes again.
The truck carries latest arms worth
10 crores that sell like hot cakes.
Each of us 4 partners can earn 2.5 crores.
2.5 crores?
Let it happened anything,
we will have those weapons.
Best of luck gentlemen.
The soldiers who play
with guns and cannons
do not fear the police's
revolver, Mr. Dinesh.
I came stealthily yet you found me out.
We soldiers have 4 not 2 eyes.
- Oh brother, you...
- Hello.
How come you came suddenly?
Mr. Dinesh Kapoor.
Sub-inspector of police.
I've come from Delhi to
give you some good news.
- What is that?
- Not now.
First some good piping hot
breakfast, then the news.
- Done.
- The good news is I've been promoted.
I have to join duty in
Bombay Within a week.
- Wow! Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Dinu. All the best.
And to celebrate we're going
to Simla by evening flight.
Here are the tickets.
Mr. Vijay Malhotra, Mrs. Geeta Malhotra
master Raju Malhotra
and Mr. Dinesh Kapoor.
Dinu.
We won't be able to go.
I'd promised Raju we'll go to a
hill station if he stands first.
Trucks with arms are going to the border.
- I'm in charge of it.
- Hand it to somebody else.
If it was given by an officer
I would have done this.
But I've asked for this assignment.
You've ruined my plan.
Doesn't matter.
I'll go to Bombay today itself.
Jaswant Dalal reporting sir.
- The jeep is ready sir.
- Wait for me.
Stop the jeep.
Driver, take it reverse.
Sir.
Why have you stopped the truck?
There's an oil leak.
So the wheel is jammed.
I'll try to contact headquarters.
Hello. Hello.
What's wrong with the wireless?
- Listen.
- Sir.
Some soldiers will remain
here with you for security.
Sir.
The rest will come with me.
- I'll get help from the nearby station.
- Sir.
- Any doubts?
- No, Sir.
Back.
Quickly.
Pile it in.
Bastards!
These weapons are not bought from
the gold in a king's treasury!
But by the sweat and
blood of 90 crore Indians!
You swore to protect the
country but you loot it!
It's a shame for this uniform
to be draped on your body!
You'll get only some copper or
bronze medals by arresting us.
Become our partner.
We'll give you one half!
You want to buy me off!
Bastard!
Who are not on sale? Everybody is for sale.
At their own price.
What will we soldiers do in this
environment by being honest?
Silence!
Our nation is safe because of our honesty!
Or it would lose its' identity!
People don't sleep because the sun sets.
It's because we guard the border
when the country sleeps in peace!
If we sell our honesty
another color will fly
in place of our tricolor!
You are under arrest!
Hey, get up.
Sir, a fax from Interpol, Australia.
Send a message to ACP Dinesh Kapoor.
For an urgent meeting.
- Good morning sir.
- Morning.
Please sit down.
Jaswant Dalal reporting sir.
This is Jaswant Dalal.
We've got a message from Australia.
He deals in illegal arms smuggling.
He's coming to Bombay
by a cargo ship today.
If we arrest him, we can find out
about illegal arms smuggling here.
I've called for a secret meeting
so nobody outside hears about it.
Otherwise people attached to
him, who'll suffer by his arrest
will have to kill him.
You'll be in charge of the
operation to nab Jaswant.
And I want him alive
under any circumstance!
Okay, sir.
VICKY: Hello.
- Got the fax?
- VICKY: Yes.
The police want him alive.
You know what you have to do.
Remember he must not get into
the police's hands alive.
- DINESH: I cannot help you in this.
- VICKY: All right.
- Is everything ready?
- Yes sir.
He can't escape.
There are more policemen
than workers here.
Sir.
Jaswant has come.
Shall we begin the movement?
Yes!
Who are you? What do you want?
- To save your life.
- Whom do I fear?
Whom every criminal fears.
The ones outside are
the police not workers.
Police?
The police can be recognized
by their shoes not clothes.
If you want to get out of here
do as I say.
Okay.
Sir. Jaswant is not to be seen.
Nobody here.
Hello!
Jaswant is in the container
that is being off loaded!
There's another man with him!
Should we surround the container?
- Hello!
- Yes.
- All units alert!
Surround the container being off loaded.
- Stop the container!
Bring the container down.
Nobody will fire. We want him alive.
Good.
So far I did what you said.
Now you'll do what I say.
Stop the car.
Stop.
Out.
Come on.
Hands up.
Move.
Good.
You're very useful man but my principle is
job finished, man finished.
And my principle is man
finished, job finished.
I want the killer not your sorry!
Seal all the ways of going out.
And remember he should not
leave the city! Got it!
- One Minta Car Road please.
- Yes.
- Are you an Indian?
- You recognised me?
- No.
- No?
- Now?
- No.
No, I didn't recognize you.
- Why you started crying?
- It's a sad story.
Once there was a fair of Kumbh.
- In Australia?
- No, India.
I have a twin brother named Sohan.
I'm Mohan.
He was left and I right
- and in the center was...
- Your mom.
My dad. We were happily
going when all of a sudden
- he ran away with my bag.
- Who, your Dad?
No, a thief.
I am helpless.
I screamed, Dad!
He's running away with the bag!
- He ran after him.
- Who, your Dad?
My brother was behind the thief.
They were running and I screamed
and he fell with a thud!
- Your brother?
- My Dad!
He was drunk and the police caught him.
- The thief?
- My Dad!
- And started beating him.
- But why?
They thought he was the thief.
In the meantime he ran away!
- The thief?
- My brother!
Since then I'm looking for him.
- The thief?
- No! My brother!
But if he was lost in India why
are you looking for him here?
That was different. He ran away.
He had two hobbies,
to see kangaroos and pick pockets.
Tell me, is any place better
than trams to pick pockets?
That's why I took this job.
I thought someday he'll come here
to pick pocket and I'll see him.
And I'll meet him. It's come!
- Your brother?
- No, your station!
Oh!
Listen! Listen! Listen!
If you ever see that
rascal whom I'm looking for
- give him my card.
- Whom? The thief?
To my brother, Sohan!
Turned my head round!
- He is turning my head!
- What me?
No! He.
"He appears in my dreams."
"He drives my sleep away."
"He appears in my dreams.
He drives my sleep away."
"He makes my heart pound,
he drives me out of my senses."
"My beloved."
"My beloved"
"will come someday."
"My beloved."
"What mischief has taken over?
I'm dazzled."
"Even when I look into... I feel shy."
"My beauty has blossomed"
"like the Sun coming out
from behind the clouds."
"It's the intoxication f a first love"
"that clouds my eyes."
"He torments me, he drives me wayward."
"He torments me, he drives me wayward"
"he sets my heart pounding,
he drives me out of senses."
"My beloved"
"will come someday."
"My beloved."
"To kiss my lips"
"to take my hand"
"he will someday come to me."
"My beloved, my sweetheart."
"He will look better than the moon."
"I'll ask him to take me away"
"in a bridal palanquin."
"He holds me in his arms,
he possesses me in his breath."
he possesses me in his breath"
"he sets my heart pounding,
he drives me out of senses."
"My beloved."
"Will come someday."
Who will be Miss Valentine in
today's function at the club?
Me.
- Why are you laughing?
Oh my God! Accident!
- Oh shit!
- My tail light!
This was my new car!
- Cool down. Cool down.
- Oh my God! Oh my God!
You damaged my car!
Why do you drive abroad
when you don't know driving!
Why don't you drive bullock
carts in your own country?
These days Indians drive pilot planes,
jet rockets and space shuttles!
You braked and the car stopped.
I braked and my car didn't.
- It's a little thing.
- Little thing?
So it may be big. But not so big
that Vicky can't compensate for it!
How much? 50, 100, 200, 300 400, 500?
You'll remember you met a wealthy Indian!
- Here.
- Thank you.
- You stupid!
How dare you touch me!
Dress like a modern girl
and talk like an old woman!
- Police! Police! Police!
- Excuse me.
Madam this is Australia not India.
You can't stop and talk midway.
Go and talk about love in a garden
Sing, dance, makes no difference.
Try to understand my problem.
We're not talking about love.
He crashed my car.
- Look. Please arrest him.
- Oh.
Both of you will have to
come to the police station.
Preeti? Why are you wasting time?
Officer? We take back our complaint.
- Very intelligent girl.
- Thank you. Thank you.
This is understanding.
You lose some to gain some.
Try to understand my problem. Okay?
I'll see you.
When and where?
Shut up!
She...
- You?
- Yes, me.
- You have a twin?
- Yes.
- Who was lost in the Kumbh fair?
- I met him.
- Where?
He's a tram conductor.
He is Searching you.
That tram conducter is me. Mohan.
You're talking about Sohan. I thought...
He must have graduated
from picking pockets.
And he'll steal somebody's car
and break the signal to escape.
And I'll catch him.
So I became a traffic policeman.
Why did you make kumbh fairs, Lord?
No! No! No! Yes! Yes! Go! Go! Come, come!
Friends, friends, friends.
Today is Valentine's day.
A day for lovers.
You all know, we in India Club
choose a Mr and Miss. Valentine.
And this years' Miss Valentine is.
Ms. Preeti.
- Congrats.
- Thanks.
Preeti, please come up.
- Welcome and congratulations.
- Thanks.
Friends, amongst you whoever
answers 3 of Preeti's questions
he will be chosen Mister Valentine!
He will get an opportunity to dance
and kiss Miss Valentine's hand!
Quiet, quiet, quiet please.
She sets one small condition.
If you can't answer her questions
you'll have her pretty
sandal not her hands to kiss!
What's the matter?
Can none among you answer her questions?
I'll give answer.
- Vicky!
- Well, give him a big hand.
Think again. If you lose
you'll have to kiss her sandal.
Don't worry.
One who is kissable from head to toe
her head and toe are the same.
Ask the question.
First question.
What is her favorite fruit?
The sweetest fruit is of labor.
But Miss Valentine is
miles away from hard work.
So her favorite fruit can't be
mango, sweet lime or orange.
Because you have to peel it to eat it.
Her favorite fruit is one that can
be popped in the mouth and swallowed.
That is grapes.
Right. Absolutely right.
Thank you. Thank you.
Next question please.
Next question. What's her favorite sport?
Man likes games according to his nature.
And her nature... fight, fight and fight!
So she likes WWF wrestling.
Wonderful! This is the right answer.
Thank you. Thank you.
Tell him to answer simply.
Why is he beating round the bush?
So what? He's answering right!
Next please.
Now the last question.
Which of the 7 wonders is her favorite?
I'll have to answer this
in a roundabout manner.
Yes, Yes, It Will do!
The wonder she likes is very
different from her nature.
She hates the word love.
But likes the wonder
that is a symbol of love.
The symbol of love. Taj Mahal.
And he is right.
This year's Mister Valentine is Vicky!
Thank you. Thank you.
She asked three ordinary questions.
If she had to ask anything today it
should have been of heart and love.
I would even answer that.
What's in her heart.
My foot!
The heart in you is Indian.
And Indian heart is not a loafer.
It likes the whole world.
But belongs to an Indian.
All of you can participate
in today's Valentine Day.
Come on Preeti. Come on Vicky.
"Oh the colour of your
skin, oh your gait."
"Oh your beauty, oh your cheeks."
"One look at you, and I fell in love."
"My heart was lost to you."
"Oh no."
"No, I don't want your heart."
"You're not the last man for me."
"Come to me, my love...
that'd be gracious of you."
"Liar! You are evil at heart."
"Your blouse hugs you
tightly, your scarf flies."
tightly, your scarf flies"
"come my Indian beauty, become my Queen."
"I'm a girl from Punjab,
I flaunt a silk scarf."
"I'll teach you a lesson you
won't forget all your life."
"Oh no."
"Oh no, I can't do without you."
"No, I can't do without you."
"The sight of you sends
my spirits soaring."
"Don't stare at me.
Don't wear your heart on your sleeve."
"Let me go... don't bother me."
"He's mad to fall in love."
"Take care of him...
he's of no use anymore."
"Oh my love, my sweetheart."
"Oh for her consent and for her refusal."
"I set my eyes on you and fell in love."
"I've lost my heart to you."
"Oh no!"
"Oh no, I don't want your heart."
"Oh no, I can't do without you."
"No, I can't do without you"
I can't do without you".
"The sight of you sends
my spirits soaring."
"No, I can't do without you."
"The sight of you sends
my spirits soaring."
"No, I can't do without you."
You just see Sheetal, I won't leave him!
Don't ever leave him!
He's so handsome, so intelligent.
Shut up! Just because
he answered my questions
you think that fool is intelligent!
He's great.
He even said what I hadn't told him.
- You told him all this?
- Yes!
I won't spare you! Stop!
'Destination is nearby'
Good luck.
'Your next destination.
Little India restaurant, table no 7'
Waiter.
- Yes sir?
- Which is table 7?
That one.
But don't sit there.
- Here's your best drink.
- Thanks.
I'm sorry sir.
- You?
- Yes.
- You have a brother? Twin?
- He's searching for you all over.
- Where is he?
He's become a traffic policeman.
- Traff... That was me.
- But you were in the police.
Yes. I was in police.
I tried that job too but
Mohan didn't meet Sohan.
So I became a waiter. He loved one thing
of seeing dances.
And English dances are shown here.
So I joined here.
Someday he will come here, I think.
No. No.
- Please don't sit on this table.
- Wow! Vicky!
Please sit on any other table.
- Oh my god!
- I beg of you.
He's come here!
Did you tell him we're coming here?
I swear this time I didn't tell him.
You can't sit here because
this is Jojo's table.
Who is he?
The son of the most dangerous man here.
He always keeps smiling.
- Something like this.
- It's good for health.
I know that but when he stops
laughing other's health suffers.
When somebody else sits on his
table, he stops laughing.
Then you know what happens?
So what happens?
This. Their only fault
was sitting at this table.
Jojo saw it and thrashed them.
- Idea. Sheetal.
- Yes?
No better chance to get him beaten.
Hope nothing goes wrong.
- If I get him beaten?
- Bet 100 bucks!
Bet! Yes!
I don't want a nice man like
yourself's picture be stuck here.
Get up my Pop! Or he'll throw you out.
- Hi Vicky!
- Listen to me.
Great! Did the sun rise in the west?
May I join you please?
- Sure, sit.
- No!
Don't join on this table or
your joints will be disjointed.
Please join at another table.
Mohan, What's going on?
Don't you know how to talk to customers?
- This is table 7.
- So what?
That's Jojo's table.
Why are you standing here?
It's time for Jojo. Get his order.
Who?
Jojo!
I'm the hotel manager.
Please get up from here.
- If this table is reserved.
- You should have kept a reserved plate.
You don't know. Jojo is very dangerous!
What do you think? If he is dangerous,
Then Vicky is double dangerous!
- Isn't it Vicky?
- Yes, not double, triple dangerous!
Now I won't move from here.
Whether Jojo comes or bow wow!
Jojo has come.
- Come on baby, Dance! Come on baby.
- Please leave me.
Please be seated.
Sit.
Excuse me please.
I think she didn't like your face.
I've trapped him so that he
goes straight to the hospital!
Go away.
Swallowed the cap? Are you so hungry?
Whare is he?
I am finished! Sheetal.
Let me go!
- Leave me!
- Shut up!
Put me down. Help!
Help! Let me go!
I have just went to the loo
and you showed your colors!
I know she wanted to get me into trouble.
But that doesn't mean you carry
her off as if she belongs to you!
The damage they have
suffered because of you
pay for it.
Now onwards when you laugh
people will laugh at you.
I got the money for the damages.
But in return Jojo's Dad
will damage you a lot.
That's what I want.
Let's go meet him.
Listen...
Is it paining a lot?
Yes.
Here are 50 dollars for treatment.
Is it less!
These are the days of inflation.
Doesn't matter. Keep 500.
Consult a good doctor.
I saved you from a gangster like
Jojo, risked my life for you!
I fought with his henchmen,
shed so much of my blood
and you are insulting me
instead of thanking me!
Deeds of a loafer and
talks like a soldier!
- Yes.
- Look yourself in the mirror!
Saying yourself Soldier! Let's go Sheetal.
Oh no!
Don't forget to wipe the tomato sauce.
Very sour.
- Hello.
Who?
The one who knows
everything about your heart.
You? How dare you call me!
With great difficulty I've
mustered courage for my finger.
So that they could dial your number.
Don't disconnect without talking.
- Okay. Tell me what is it?
- I'm going to India forever.
That is why I want to meet
you for the last time.
- What? You're going back forever?
- Yes.
Yes!
So you want to meet me for the last time?
Yes.
All right. Okay. Come over.
Okay.
- What the blazes is this?
- There is very less time.
- Okay. Why do you want to meet me?
- I want to give you this card.
- Card.
- I'm getting married.
Which poor girl is jacked?
Here.
Are you going to marry her?
I won't do anything.
She'll do all that has to be done.
But how did you agree to marry her?
What can I do? I'm helpless.
- What's the problem?
- Twist in story.
Shall I sit and tell you?
Okay.
My dad and her dad were friends
and her granddad and
mine too were friends.
And her granddad made my
granddad promise on deathbed
they would marry us to continue
their friendship for 4 generations.
Tell me, what can I do?
I can't put of my Dad,
this marriage can't be put off!
This marriage is firm!
Oh I see.
Family problem.
What can I do?
- Give me a present.
- What preset?
Give me one of your sweet smiling evening.
Which will spread light in
the darkness of my life.
Will you meet me?
Okay.
A drunken man never lies.
Correct.
He can't lie.
Your car banged into mine at the signal.
It didn't crash. I banged it on purpose.
What? Banged it on purpose?
What could I do?
Had to make friends with you.
For that I had to meet you.
I needed an excuse for it.
That's why...
And my tail light down.
But this method of friendship was wrong.
Correct.
And the method of giving money?
Absolutely wrong!
No experience of love.
Then it's all right.
I'll tell you something.
Tell me.
I goaded you into fighting Jojo
at Little India Restaurant.
Very bad.
No experience.
Then okay.
Please be seated.
Did I say sorry for troubling you so much?
- No. Did I say sorry?
- No.
Let's apologise to one another.
Sorry!
One minute. In your country
that's not how you say sorry.
How else?
Like this.
What are they doing?
Saying sorry to each other.
Good you told me.
I thought something else.
Let's say sorry to each other.
Ready? One.
- Two.
- Three.
Wait.
When two people say sorry to each other
why don't their noses clash?
What a wrong time for the nose!
You don't know? Doesn't matter.
Let's ask somebody.
Brother!
Brother! Tell us something.
When a girl and a boy
say sorry to each other
why don't their noses clash?
Say something.
Sorry, I'm new to this place.
The nose doesn't clash?
No problem. We'll ask somebody clever.
Where do you want to go?
We're not going anywhere.
Just want to ask one thing.
- Ask as many questions.
- When a boy and a girl
say sorry to each other,
why don't their noses clash?
What are you thinking of?
We don't have all night.
I'm not thinking of that.
It's been 20 years since my marriage
I never said sorry to my wife.
How will I know why
the nose doesn't clash?
Both of you say sorry
to each other and see.
You'll find out why
the nose doesn't clash.
I'll go home and say sorry to the
wife to see where the nose clashes!
And the car goes there!
Thank you.
So clever.
We'll say sorry and see.
Okay.
Wait! How can you say sorry to me?
- Why?
- Because sorry is only said to
- the one you will marry.
- That's what I'm doing.
See the card if you don't believe.
'I love you, Preeti.'
Where is he?
'The one who has eyes only for you'
'how can he marry another girl?'
'Yet if you don't accept my
love, tear this card and leave.'
'I'll go away from you forever.'
'If not, shut your eyes
and say in your heart'
'I love you.'
'I'll appear again.'
'Loafer.'
Loafer.
Soldier.
'And if not,
shut your eyes and say in your heart'
'I love you.'
'I'll reappear.'
I love you.
"Having caught my gaze."
"Having cast a spell."
"Having given me a heart-ache."
"Having hovered around me."
"Soldier, Soldier, with your sweet words
you have stolen my heart".
"Having caught your gaze."
"Having cast a spell."
"Having given you a heart-ache."
"Having hovered around you."
"Soldier, Soldier, with his sweet words
has taken your heart away".
"My no, no, no... turned into yes."
"It's you...
who has come to mean the life to me."
"Why oh why have I fallen in love?"
"That's the way you admit it."
"I swear it, you're a liar."
"And you're the one, my love,
who has plundered my heart."
"Having caught my gaze."
"Having cast a spell."
"Having given me a heart-ache."
"Having hovered around me."
"Soldier, Soldier, with your sweet words
you have stolen my heart".
"Come, come to me."
"Go away...
don't awaken a thirst in my heart."
"Do you really feel the ache?"
"Yes, oh yes. I'm in a bad way."
"You do know how to cast a spell."
"But I'm hardly in control of myself."
"Having caught your gaze."
"Having cast a spell."
"Having given you a heart-ache."
"Having hovered around you."
"Soldier, Soldier, with his sweet words
has flown with your heart".
"Soldier, Soldier, with your sweet words"
you have stolen my heart".
"Soldier, Soldier, with your sweet words
I have stolen your heart".
Preeti! Are you thinking what I am?
Let's go in and get married.
You'll have to talk to my dad for this.
I'll talk to him. Where is he?
Hello.
Hello my darling daughter. How are you?
Dad, I am very happy.
I want you to meet somebody.
- The young man who is with you.
- Strange. How did you know?
I even know what clothes he's wearing.
I keep track of you like any good dad.
Where you go,
with whom and who is meeting you.
But when are you coming?
Today dad.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Come Pratap. Come. How are you?
Absolutely fit. And you Baldev?
I'm fit if my brother is fit.
Come, come.
Why did you want to meet?
- Bad news.
- I know.
You want to say Jaswant is dead.
No, even worse.
I've got reports that DK had him killed.
DK? Absolutely wrong.
Sir can never kill his
partner of 25 years!
DK can do anything for money.
Even if he did, it's good.
Had he escaped alive, the police
would've beaten everything out of him.
And handcuffed us and
taken us back to India!
Here.
Try to understand Viren.
Someday he might even finish us off.
If he kills us who will supply
him American arms in India?
Listen to me. Right from beginning
his intentions were not true.
That's why he never told us his address.
He can contact us anytime
but we can never reach him.
What do you want? What should we do?
Before he attacks us,
we have to finish DK!
The idea is not bad.
We were 4 partners.
Jaswant died and three remain.
We will kill DK and 2 will remain.
You kill me and only you are left.
Do you think I'm a village idiot?
You want to grab the entire organization?
I find your intentions
dishonorable not DK's.
- Shut up or...!
- Control yourself.
You'll be finding your fingers
if they touch the trigger.
I'm not Jaswant.
Firstly I won't die so easily.
Even if I die, I won't become
a police file or news in paper.
If you have a file on me,
I have a file of your deeds.
That file will go to the
police as soon as I die.
What's the matter?
Changed your tune by seeing the gun?
Laughing instead of crying.
Hats off to you friend!
I was talking about killing DK
because I wanted to know if you
had a hand in killing Jaswant.
If you were responsible
you would agree with me.
So what have you decided?
That you haven't changed.
You're still a friend of friends.
As you were 20 years ago.
Nobody can divide us 3 partners.
Except for death!
Yes. Except for death!
Do you see that island?
Dad bought it for my last birthday.
And that island?
That was on my first birthday.
Really?
So your dad buys you a new
island for every birthday?
Yes, and that to in my name.
Don't tell this to anybody else.
- Why?
- It will let out your age.
You!
Look there. That's my dad.
Hi.
- Come my darling come, come, come.
- Hi Dad.
- This is...
- Vicky.
Wow!
You know his name without telling you?
When he knows the color of
my clothes from miles away
- he can know my name too.
- While giving a daughter
work is seen in addition to name.
- Whatever he does, is great!
- Really?
We'll see. You go in,
we have to talk about business.
Okay.
Tell me, Vicky.
First tell me who gave you
the contract to kill Jaswant?
So you know about my work?
Anyway hear my principles too.
I see the cash while accepting a
contract, not the payer.
You haven't seen the man who gave
you a contract to love my daughter?
Pratap Sir! I accept contracts for
killing not to play game of love!
Preeti's love and mine is not a game.
Maybe but a dad won't
give his daughter to a man
whose hands are tainted with blood.
If mine are tainted,
are yours milky white?
Even I know about you.
We belong to the same community.
Community but not position.
You are a paid ass in this
business Whereas I'm a lion!
You've reached here because
you came with my child.
Otherwise my security dogs wouldn't
have let your bones come near me.
For the first time,
I've seen dogs guarding a lion!
Just Listen to 2 things
that I have to say.
In today's world,
lions can be safe in only 2 places.
In the circus and in the zoo!
Secondly, regarding position.
I can take you to that place
that you're dreaming of for 20 years.
But can never reach it.
Means?
Hello.
Saw what I broke in place
of two teeth of mine?
Pomeranian Puppy!
Give the line to your Pop, the bulldog.
Dad.
- What is it?
- He called me a puppy!
And me?
Bulldog.
He called me a bulldog? Give me the phone!
Are we a family of dogs?
I didn't find you or
I'd have broken you too!
You won't believe, I'm very bad!
When you will meet me,
You will become nervous.
We're a family of tigers not dogs!
We bite not bark!
We eat raw people!
Are you frightened?
Why aren't you speaking? Hello?
Can you hear?
I'm talking to you not myself!
I've been yelling for ages! I'm not mad!
Total 8500.
- Plus 100% tax.
- What?
Total 17000. Round figure 20000.
Which figure are you
rounding and squaring?
This is the damage your
son did to my house.
- You'll take money from me?
- Not rupees, in dollars.
My bill will reach you at 3.55
I'll come at 4 to take the cash.
And leave at 4.05.
10 minutes for giving and taking.
Take those 10 minutes seriously. Got it?
- What happened?
- Nothing, he talks rot!
Says he'll send the bill at 3.55
and will leave at 4:05.
As if we're here to pay cash!
Are we donkeys?
The arms buyers would have come,
bring them in. Let me do some work.
Gentlemen.
We have machine guns.
Mouser.. AK-47, AK-56, AK-98
even those not yet in the market.
We have 2 lakh pieces of each.
We'll send you the guns you need.
Next.
This is a pipe gun.
This pipe gun blast people.
With every pipe gun,
you get a dozen Hamam soaps free.
Oh Hamam?
Now show them our bomb section.
Wow! Good idea to display bomb.
You have displayed bomb nicely.
Thank you.
- Dad.
- Yes.
- 3:55.
- 3:55?
This is real bomb.
- Run.
Dad! It's the phone ringing dad.
Hello.
Don't be scared. It's the bill not a bomb.
What do you think? I got scared?
I play with such bombs day and night.
I deal with them. Where are you?
- John!
- What happened dad?
- He's come downstairs.
Tell him I'm taking the lift up.
He is coming by lift.
- What?
- Yes sir.
Stop! Stop firing! Stop firing!
John!
Dad! Dad!
Well done.
You did very well!
I thought you were good for nothing.
But you proved to be very smart!
You deserve all the praise!
And you called me a bulldog!
Whether a dog bites or
licks, both are dangerous!
His pistol is empty.
Dad!
Don't move or else the bullet
will go off in your ear.
But it will bleed from some other place.
Cash.
Sir nobody is here.
Pomeranian puppy!
No, no, no. You please send
money within half an hour.
Baldev! It's a very big deal.
- Call George.
- He's in hospital.
- Then call Kalia or Rahim.
- They both are also in the hospital.
Is the gorilla also in the hospital?
Unfortunately he is also in the hospital.
What they are doing in the hospital?
Have they gone to get a corpse
or have they all got aids?
You know uncle.
This is all because of that Indian.
First he burnt my teeth
then he bashed up my men.
And on top of that he called
me a Pomeranian puppy and him.
Bull dog.
Then he did a miracle!
- What?
- He thrashed Dad.
He took money from him for all
the damage I did to his house.
Rascal! Recounting the tale of his
bashing as if he's won a medal!
He's not an ordinary boy.
Then is he a King Kong?
If the tale of my shame spreads
I won't have the face to return to Patna!
Go and take my marksman with you.
What do we say.. Yes, sharp shooter.
Go, shoot him! If you come without
shooting him, I'll shoot all of you!
The rascal's mother is coming.
He will go to the airport to receive her.
I'll kill him.
- Give me the gun.
- Okay.
Jojo Shoot.
Shoot him Jojo!
He went behind.
Now!
- Shit!
- Where's that rascal come from?
- Mother has come.
- Now kill him Jojo!
Shoot Jojo!
Sister-in-law?
- Stop!
- What's wrong?
This is my sister-in-law!
That means this is my elder brother's son!
This is our own blood!
If brother hears this good news,
he will give all his property of Patna.
Uncle will be happy to hear it!
Shanti.
- In Australia?
- Yes!
I am telling the truth.
The boy we went to kill is
actually your son Vicky!
My son! My Shanti!
I can't believe it Baldev!
Are you telling the truth?
Yes. Brother,
Jojo you tell him what you have seen.
Dad is right. We ourselves saw
brother Vicky touching her feet.
My son! Shanti!
You've come to the wrong address.
Vicky's mother stays here not your wife.
Think why fate has brought us
together in a foreign land?
Just, so that we can live together.
A child who pretends to be
an orphan will get his dad.
Orphans are those kids who
have neither dad nor mother.
And Vicky's mother is alive.
Don't be adamant. Today I have so
much wealth I can buy anything.
Then go and buy yourself a wife and a son.
People who sell themselves for
money don't live in this house.
Please forget everything.
I apologize on brother's behalf.
The man who sells his motherland
who is responsible for
the death of innocents
they deserve punishment not forgiveness.
You all may leave.
Shanti.
Shanti, Listen to me.
Brother, this is your son!
Vicky.
- Son, You don't know me, son...
- I know.
I have heard everything.
Son! My son!
Don't be angry with me.
I'm pining for you since 20 years!
Even I've been pining
for my dad for 20 years!
Blood is thicker than water.
Yes, uncle. Blood is after all blood.
- Now if Shanti agrees...
- Leave her to me.
I'll convince her.
Organize a great party now!
I'll announce to the world
that I'm not childless!
His son who will work with him
shoulder to shoulder has come!
Welcome, welcome. This is my son Vicky.
- Mr. Marshall.
- Hello.
Please sit down. Enjoy yourself.
Singhania sir, Come. Come.
- You?
- Yes me?
- You have a brother?
- Yes.
- Twin brother?
- Who was lost in the kumbh fair?
- Yes.
- He's come to look for you from India!
- Where is he?
- He becomes a policeman, waiter...
- And sometimes band master!
You always find me only!
I'm Mohan!
I thought my brother would
have become a smuggler.
They keep doing parties here.
Someday I'll find him singing and dancing.
Lord! Why did you make kumbh fair?
- Hey play man!
- Yeah.
Enjoy yourself.
Come Pratap! Come! Come!
- Welcome!
Hello Viren!
- How are you Baldev?
- I am fine.
She's my daughter. Preeti.
- Hello uncle.
- Hello.
You've grown so big! Where do you live?
- I haven't seen you for ages.
- I stay separately as I'm studying.
Congrats for finding your
wife and son after 20 years!
- Where are they?
- My wife hasn't come.
I'll introduce you to my son.
Come here son.
Excuse me.
Is this your son?
Yes. You got shocked?
And why not? Till yesterday
Pratap was our equal every way.
But after son's arrival our
strength has grown 4 times!
No uncle! The enemy gets startled.
Not our friends.
And Pratap sir is our friend not enemy.
Thank you. Congratulations.
In India, elders give
blessings not congratulations.
Do you know each other?
Viren! Now it's your turn to get startled.
He's your son later.
First he has become my to-be son-in-law!
Means?
Means your son and my
daughter are in love.
- What?
- Yes, uncle.
For her, Vicky brother burnt my teeth.
So my son hasn't come alone!
He's brought his bride along!
Baldev! What are you looking at?
Open up champagne immediately!
It's a double occasion!
"She's the one my eyes were...
at the gathering."
"I did my best but they
were still drawn to her."
"What am I suppose to do?"
"What a heart will do?"
"Oh, what am I suppose to do?"
"He's the one my eyes
were at the gathering."
"I did my best but they
were still drawn to him."
"What am I suppose to do?
What a heart will do?"
"What am I suppose to do?"
"This season has arrived my love"
"my heart is immersed in your memories."
"Neither is it my fault,
nor is it your mistake"
"yours is the intoxication
that has left me in a daze."
"Face to face with you,
my heart has skipped a beat."
"I did my best to avoid her gaze
but they were still drawn to her."
"What am I suppose to do?
What my heart will do?"
"Oh, what am I suppose to do?"
"Soldier, soldier, with your sweet words"
"you've stolen my heart."
"Soldier, soldier, with sweet words"
"he has stolen your words."
"My loneliness feels
there's nothing to express."
"In your arms, want to sleep in your
eyes, want to live."
"Your breath and my breath
are now tied together."
"This is a bond that will not
be broken by the world's might."
"In your arms, I lie shattered."
"In your arms, I lie shattered"
"you've saved me, yet I'm broken."
"What am I suppose to do?
What will heart do?"
"What am I suppose to do?"
"She's the one my eyes
were at the gathering."
"He's the one my eyes
"I did my best to but they
were still drawn to her"
- "What am I suppose to do?
- What will heart do?"
"What am I suppose to do?"
Where are we going, Dad?
You are my heir so it's essential for you
to know what I've earned in my life.
And where I've hidden it. Come.
This path leads to that
secret place of mine...
That nobody including my brother
Baldev knows nothing about it.
I've brought you here so that I can
tell you the secrets of my business.
Finally you have to take over. Come.
Come my son. Come.
I'm very happy today. Very happy.
In one day you have
fulfilled my dreams of years!
A dad's dream is to get his son married.
Not for that but because you
trapped that rascal's girl
and brought him to my feet!
What are you saying?
Pratap is your friend.
What friend? If he gets the
chance, he'll gobble up his friend!
But I'm no less.
You must have heard the magician's story?
His life was in a parrot.
Pratap's life is in my hands.
- I didn't get it.
- That's why I brought you here.
Wait.
This is that parrot in which
the proof of Pratap's evil deeds
is written with dates.
Look.
This is our third partner Jaswant.
He is no more.
And this is our fourth partner, D. K.
He stays in India.
You are right.
Pratap's life is really in your hands.
But the problem is that
my life is in his hands.
Pratap has a similar file of mine.
That is why I've agreed to
have relations with him.
So that as his son-in-law
you can get my file from him.
Then you'll see how I will
give him a rat's death!
And then I'll put all my
burden on your shoulders.
I'll sleep in peace.
What's the use of that son who
can't put his dad into sleep?
He is DK?
Find out who owns the ship?
- Good morning, uncle.
- Good morning.
- Good morning Jojo.
- Good morning big brother.
- Uncle.
- Yes.
I haven't seen Dad since yesterday.
You won't believe the calls
that have come since morning.
So many inquiries.
But they will speak only if they know.
Hello.
Vicky.
What are you saying?
Yes, he's here.
Where will he go?
Come here.
Now you can't escape!
Your secret is out!
- What secret?
- Hear it yourself.
- Hello.
It's you?
You got scared! Right?
Do you remember it's a
girl's birthday today?
- No. Which girl?
- One innocent girl.
Who is trapped in a foolish,
absent minded boy's love.
If he's absent minded he
will obviously forget.
The girl should have thought
of this before falling in love.
She had no experience of love.
That's how she made a mistake.
Now what is she to do?
She must trust the boy.
I'll catch that fool and bring him.
How will that foolish
boy recognize that girl?
That won't be necessary.
That boy is so special
that the girl will come running to him.
It's also possible that the
boy will keep watching it.
And the girl goes away with another!
Fine, so let's see.
Hi.
Looks like somebody's heart is burning.
"She has sashayed through
my heart and my soul"
"a girl has just passed
through this pass."
"She has sashayed through
my heart and my soul"
"a girl has just passed
through this pass."
"Fair cheeks."
"Dark hair."
"Swaggering gait"
"she's 16... she's driven me crazy."
"Lord Almighty!"
Looks like there's a fire somewhere.
Should I call the fire brigade?
"He has sashayed through
my heart and my soul"
"a boy has just passed through this pass."
"Straight and simple."
"He torments."
"Straight and simple. He torments."
"He keeps me awake, appears in my dreams"
"he's driven me crazy."
"Lord Almighty!"
"Oh, your eyes"
"they're so piercing,
although you wear no kohl."
"Oh, your sweet talk"
"how I love it."
"Your charms have robbed me of my peace."
"You're the only one my eyes dream of."
"You've just arrived.
Wait... don't go away."
"Someone might spot us...
don't tease me like this."
"She's escaped my eye."
"A girl has just passed by."
"Fair cheeks."
"Dark hair."
"Fair cheeks. Dark hair."
"Swaggering gait"
"she's 16... she's driven me crazy."
"Lord Almighty!"
"You've promised to meet me tomorrow"
"make sure you don't forget it."
"Even if I forget it,"
"you can remind me."
"Life is but short-lived."
"All day and night, my heart seeks you."
"My thirst has awakened, how I pine."
"You are the one I
desire, it's you I want."
"He has sashayed through
my heart and my soul"
"a boy has just passed through this pass."
"Straight and simple."
"He torments."
"Straight and simple. He torments."
"He keeps me awake, appears in my dreams"
"he's driven me crazy."
"Lord Almighty!"
"She has sashayed through
my heart and my soul"
"a girl has just passed
through this pass."
"Fair cheeks."
"Dark hair."
"Fair cheeks. Dark hair."
"Swaggering gait"
"she's 16... she's driven me crazy."
"Lord Almighty!"
God! What have you done?
Taken my brother away!
- We have became orphan.
- What's he is saying?
He is crying for uncle.
Uncle, why are you crying?
Why are the police here?
You won't believe this son.
Somebody killed your dad!
- What?
- Killed him and fed the body to sharks.
If he could fed to dogs,
we could have found his bones!
- To cremate him.
- Now how will we do the rites?
- Vicky.
- Excuse me.
This cigarette lighter was
found at the murder site.
Do any of you recognize it?
I can't understand what he's saying.
He's asking whose lighter is this.
I don't know. My brother never...
Uncle.
This belongs to my dad.
Why did you say the
lighter belongs to brother?
He hadn't touched a
cigarette for 20 years!
I knew dad didn't smoke.
This belongs to the man who killed him.
I lied because the police cannot harm him.
Tell me who he is!
He fed brother to the fish!
If I don't feed him to the
maggots, shame on my name!
Tell me who he is!
Think of where you saw this lighter.
This lighter belongs to Pratap.
The scoundrel extended
his hand for relations
and cheated us!
I'll kill that bastard!
No! Those who work in excitement
are either under the earth
or over the pyre.
So we must work with our senses not anger.
Uncle! Collect all your men.
We'll attack Pratap together!
Check post?
Now what we will do?
- Hide the weapons.
- Call up.
- Hide all the weapons.
- Yes, sir.
Hide your weapons.
Why all the cabins empty?
I'll check.
Well done boys. Well done.
Well done! Vicky.
Pratap sir, I kept my promise of
killing all of Virendra's group.
Not full, Just half.
Where's my file which Virendra had?
You'll get that too.
First you keep your word of
giving Preeti into my hand.
Tell me, when?
Whenever the groom and bride wish.
"All I want is your heart"
"this much I promise"
"get the hint, please."
"Should I have you,
see the wonders I work."
"No, that's not happening."
"I don't want your heart."
" I don't want your heart."
"All I want is your heart"
"this much I promise."
"Don't do any mischief."
"Don't be afraid of love."
"Go on, let all that be."
"At least let me say something."
"Go on, lay off... stop bothering me."
"Don't drive me crazy in love."
"I'm leaving. Stop clinging to me."
"Listen, my love...
give me a bit of your love."
"No, that's not happening."
" I don't want your heart."
"All I want is your heart"
"this much I promise."
"Stop acting crazy."
"Fall in love with me."
"Let me go, I've got to go home."
"Don't look away.. please."
"How am I going to trust
you, that you will love me?"
"I will never betray you in love."
"Why're you following me around?
Why're you being stubborn?"
"It's bad to be angry, my love...
enjoy my love right now."
"No, that's not happening."
"I don't want your heart."
Right.
Same file.
I can't believe somebody
can love someone so much!
As much as you love Preeti.
You killed your own dad
just because I asked you to!
He wasn't my dad!
- What?
- A bastard like him cannot be my dad!
I made him my dad so that I can reach him.
If he wasn't your dad,
how did he accept you as his son?
Because of his wife.
His son was lost years ago.
I went to him as his lost son.
And it was not difficult convincing
a mother mad for her lost son.
What a trick!
Hunted so many with one arrow!
Virendra's wealth,
my daughter and my trust.
You achieved all three of them.
You turned out to be
smarter than I thought.
Today you killed Virendra
making him your dad.
Tomorrow you might kill me
after I become your dad-in-law.
But my dear son-in-law.
I'm not a fool like Virendra!
The file has come to me. Hence...
Good bye.
My dear father-in-law.
You're more foolish than Virendra.
You should check the bullets
before pressing the trigger.
The man who can remove your
file from Virendra's vault
it's not tough for him to remove
the bullets from your revolver.
I was joking, son!
Brother-in-law can be a joke.
Not between dad-in-law with son-in-law.
That is why listen to something serious.
I have killed Virendra for
DK not for your daughter!
- For DK?
- Yes.
He gave me a contract
to kill three people.
One was Jaswant. The other Virendra.
And you're the third.
Bless your daughter thanks
to whom you are still alive.
I used her as a step to reach you.
But I really love her so much.
That I can't see her e yes with tears.
You won Preeti's heart earlier
today you've won mine too.
Forget the heart and think with the head.
DK wants you dead to own 100%.
But I can kill him and make
you the complete owner.
- But his whereabouts?
- I know that.
Prepare to leave for India.
To kill that rascal, why just India
I'm willing to go anywhere.
So far I thought I was the
luckiest girl in the world.
But today after listening
to my dad and Vicky
I've lost faith in all relations!
If you hear, you'll die!
The one you think is your
son, is not your son!
He became your son so that
he could kill your husband.
Vicky killed your husband!
He made you a widow!
He is a cheat! He is a murderer!
I know it.
He is not my son.
He has not cheated me.
In fact, to lighten mother
earth of her sinful burden
I supported him by becoming his mother.
And he didn't kill my husband!
He punished a traitor for his sins!
Those who die for their
nation are called martyrs.
Those who kill for their country
are called soldiers not killers!
And this soldier's story
started not on foreign soil
but in the desert sands of India.
Where my husband and your dad
and their third partner,
Jaswant used to work in the military.
They stole arms from there and
sold it to a fourth called DK.
Once Vicky's dad, Major Vijay
Malhotra caught them red handed.
To hide their crime,
these traitors killed him!
And blamed him for the arms theft!
We were going towards the
border with the truck of arms.
The truck had a problem so Major
Malhotra sent us to camp to get help.
On the way we saw a
civilian driving the truck.
We smelled a rat and returned to see
all the guards were dead and
Major Malhotra and his men were
loading the arms into their truck.
We challenged him and he
fired upon us in return.
We had to fire back to answer him.
On the evidence of the eye witness
account of Subhedar Pratap Singh.
Lance Corporal Virendra Sinha
and driver Jaswant Dalal.
Late Maj. Malhotra is charged with loot
of arms meant for the nation's defense
he is guilty of killing the
guards defending the country.
So the army terminates his entire service.
We take back all the
titles, medals given to him
and declare him a traitor.
No! No!
Remove the decorations.
No!
He is not a traitor!
- Mother!
- Don't take his medals!
- Don't take them. Move.
- Mother.
- Mother!
- No!
Sir, you know how much
he loved his country!
Then why are they snatching
away the medals in front of you?
He is a martyr not a traitor!
He has sacrificed himself for his country!
Dad.
We won't let the body be burnt!
We won't let the body to be burnt!
We won't let a traitor be
cremated on our holy land!
Don't touch it!
Throw the body away!
- Don't touch it!
Mother!
Don't touch it!
- Don't touch it!
- Mother!
- Don't touch it! No.
- Mother.
Leave him! Mother!
Leave him!
Mother!
Dad!
- Raju! Raju!
- Mother!
Mother earth took that
martyr into her lap.
Yet these traitors had evil intentions.
They put the stigma of
shame on his mother's head.
And threw her out of the village!
Sister, I've come to take you and Raju.
We'll go and stay far away.
No. If I leave this place,
his soul will tell me
that like others me too
think he's a traitor.
Take Raju away if you can.
But how will he live without you?
His welfare lies in staying without me.
Son can forget his mother.
But the people here will remind
him of his dad and kill him!
Take him away!
Will you live without me, mother?
No, my son! No.
You are not going away from me.
You will be with me in every
moment in every breath.
Okay mother. I'll go if you want me to.
Yes, Raju.
And from that day, neither she saw her son
nor the son saw his mother.
For 20 years that goddess
is still in the desert
tolerating the barbs of the villagers
sitting in that same temple.
What's the matter?
I hope you are not feeling
guilty of making me a widow?
I considered myself a widow the day
when my own son died along with
other kids because of arms he sold!
The man who can kill the
husband's of hundreds of women
and is responsible for
the death of innocent kids
no Indian woman not only me
will adorn her hair with
the vermilion of his name!
I'm proud of you son!
The day that was lowered in shame
because of my husband's deeds
it is held high once again.
It is said, of all God's gifts
the most precious is mother.
I am so lucky that I have 2 of them!
I am sorry, Vicky.
Preeti! What you did was out of ignorance.
But after knowing what I'm going to
do, you'll hate not love me.
Your dad's name is top
most in my list of enemies.
If a wife can support you
against her husband in your fight
then a daughter can go
against her dad for mankind!
Hello.
I am Raj speaking.
Raj? Why did you call?
Keep contact only by fax.
No need for that now.
I'm bringing Pratap tomorrow.
My work here is done.
Now I have to come there and do one job.
Unmask DK.
Jaswant.
- Yes sir?
- The drama of my man who enacted
of killing you with fake bullets
that has made my plan succeed.
How long do I have to stay here?
There's no need for you to stay.
With the information you gave me my
partner killed Virendra and his men.
He's bringing Pratap here tomorrow.
So now you're free.
Yes.
It's so strange
the story will end where it began.
Looks like you know this place.
What's the use in hiding from you?
Our business started from here.
And this is the place where
death touched us and left.
There was a scoundrel
Major Vijay Malhotra.
He thought he was the
protector of the nation!
He caught us.
If DK hadn't reached in time,
he would have killed all of us.
That dog was very strong!
But fate was with us.
We gave that scoundrel such a death!
That it's quoted as an example.
What did you do?
We proved the martyr a traitor.
We didn't let him be cremated!
Some will die today too.
But won't be cremated.
Of DK and his men!
Why did you stop the car?
A goddess is sitting in
this temple since 20 years.
They say anyone who sees her
gets his wishes fulfilled.
Let's go see her.
I will definitely see her.
So that I can see DK's corpse very soon.
For 20 years these eyes have only
seen hatred and been shunned.
I have seen them everyday.
But...
for the first time,
I'm seeing eyes filled with tears.
Raju.
Mother!
- Raju.
- Mother.
I kept you away for 20 years!
Despite being a mother,
I didn't give you that love.
Forgive me!
No, you were not away from me.
The dust of your feet was
always with me like a blessing.
Now it's time for your wait
and my pledge to be fulfilled.
See whom I've brought here!
'Your mother and son can't stay here!'
'She won't leave like this.
We'll put such a stigma on her forehead'
'that she won't be able to face anyone!'
- 'Throw him out!
- Yes, throw him out!'
Leave my child!
No! No! No!!!
'My husband is a traitor'
Geeta!
I'm the son of this goddess!
This is that goddess
of whose forehead you wrote
the stigma of shame, not pride!
I'm the son of Vijay Malhotra
who was called a traitor
despite being a martyr!
Do you know why I brought you here?
So that the soul where the
greatest injustice was done
justice too should be given there!
And my mother who has been
doing penance in this wilderness
can see justice being done!
Traitor!
People die but their voice don't!
Listen!
Listen to the voice of my dad's
torture in this sand!
Listen!
Listen to a child cry
and weep for his dad!
Hear the scream of a mother looking
for her husband's body in a storm!
Hear my mother's screams!
Listen!
DK.
Not DK but Jaswant.
Remove.
Jaswant.
I recognized you earlier itself.
You haven't come here
but been brought here.
According to Raju's plan I
informed you of Pratap's arrival.
I released you on purpose.
Because we know you would come
here to save him for your business.
And since Jaswant has
been forgiven by the law
you'll be tried as DK not Jaswant!
You cheated your partners
for their shares.
Not us.
You are under arrest.
Raju!
What did you think I'd
come alone to save my man?
Raju!
- Raju!
- Mother!
Mother!
Wanted me to hear screams?
Now you scream!
No! Raju!
Leave him.
Mother!
- Mother!
- Raju!
- Beat him!
Raju!
Mother!
- Mother!
- Raju!
Mother! Mother!
Raju!
This rascal is Vijay Malhotra's son.
His dad was buried here after his death.
Bury him alive!
Mother!
Let's go or else he'll kill us!
Raju!
Don't kill us!
Forgive us.
I'm your dad-in-law.
Will you kill me, son?
No! Raju, no!
No!
I won't kill you.
He's so merciful!
After all he's my son-in-law.
Look up.
No! no.
These vultures will eat our flesh!
- Shoot us!
- Yes, kill us!
- For God's sake!
- I had pledged
that you will neither get
the flames of a cremation
nor the lap of mother earth!
- Raju No!
- No!
No!
Raju I gave false
evidence against your dad!
I had whipped him to death!
We are butchers!
Remove your revolver and kill me!
You are educated, sensible.
Why don't you kill us?
Villagers! We accept all our crimes.
Save us from the vultures.
We can't even walk!
Kill us! Wait! Where are you going?
On your goddess like mother's
forehead, I had written
your husband is a traitor!
You write on my forehead with bullets.
That I'm a dog, a pig, a swine!
- Stop!
- Don't leave us and go!
Guards!
General salute!
Gun salute!