Beep.
This story's name is...
The wolf and the seven lambs.
It all happened many years ago.
In one such dense forest
there lived a sheep
with her seven lambs
in a little house.
One fine day
as the sheep was heading out,
she told her lambs...
"Kids, until I get back home"
"do not open the door
for anyone else."
But...
Guess who was hiding outside
and eavesdropping on them?
Who?
A ferocious WOLF!
Once the sheep left
the wolf knocked on the door.
Thud!
So the lambs called out -
"Who is it?"
The wolf replied...
"Your mother."
Who's there?
BHEDIYA (Wolf)
No.
Sir...
Sir... Sir...
Sir, he seems to be in an angry mood.
Why are you so scared?
Sir, I'm not scared of him.
I just don't like dogs.
Dog?
How would you feel
if he called you a dog?
Sorry, boss.
Now who's the boss here?
Sorry, Boss!
Okay.
Now let's talk business.
Speaking of the North-East project...
The land survey is complete.
The papers are ready.
Are you done with your prep?
Yes, sir. I have a local contact there.
I've already made all arrangements.
Land acquisition won't be easy.
In the jungles of the North East.
You don't get paid big bucks
for the easy jobs.
You know it better than anyone.
This is a major contract.
Many major companies had their eyes on it.
But it finally went to a small time
contractor like you.
Do you know why?
Because I like your hunger, baby!
And I like your hunger, too, baby!
My bossy vossy...
Thank you, Mr. Bagga!
And believe me,
I'll get the job done.
The point is
it needs to be done on time.
Sir, I mortgaged my house
to pay your security deposit.
I'll give it all I've got.
What say, Boss?
Does he really mean it?
- He approves of you.
- Yes, sir.
You son of a gun!
The government budget regulation
is basically affected by
active, permanent
and structural factors...
Done packing your bags?
Yes, long ago.
Bro, where are we going?
Why do you care?
I have to prepare for the IAS exams.
I won't budge unless you tell me.
You love nature, don't you?
The place we're going to is right
in the lap of nature.
And the girls are also pretty there.
Your mother was saying
we should get you married.
No way, man.
I'll only marry after
I become an IAS officer.
Then forget about it.
Yes, Dad?
I heard you're leaving
for Arunachal all of a sudden?
It's not sudden.
I'm going there on important business.
How will you manage all alone?
I won't be alone.
I've got Janardan with me.
Greetings, Uncle!
Yeah Greetings...
Aunty was saying he still gets seizures.
All right, take him along.
He will keep you company
in that foreign land.
It's not a foreign country, Dad.
- Arunachal Pradesh is in India.
- Yes, whatever...
Don't teach me geography now.
Okay, I'll call you later
I'm having lunch.
Hello... He...
I see! Arunachal Pradesh...
So we're going to Imphal?
Imphal is in Manipur.
Oh, right!
Sorry our ticket must be for Meghalaya?
Meghalaya is a state.
We're going to Guwahati.
Oh, right! So sorry.
Guwahati is the capital
of Arunachal Pradesh. Right!
Guwahati is in Assam.
The capital of Arunachal Pradesh
is Itanagar.
Since when?
Just pass the curd.
IAS isn't your cup of tea.
Honk! Honk!
That's it?
Couldn't you pack some more luggage?
No, bro. A wise man once said...
Carry knowledge, not burden.
So this is all I got.
Is this knowledge?
These are my books! I've got to study!
Bhaski!
Hey, Jo!
How've you been?
All good, pal.
- After four long years.
- I know.
- Your hair looks great.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Even you got this macho beard.
- Yeah, I try.
- Did you travel alone?
Here's my cousin... Janardan.
JD, JD..
Hello! Jomin!
Chow mein?
Jomin...
Hello, Jo... Jomin!
- "Hey! All good?
- Yeah, kind of!"
- " All good?
- "All good?
- Yeah, kind of!"
- "What about you?
- "All good?
- Yeah, kind of!"
- "All okay with you?
- Yeah, I guess!"
- "And you?
- Yeah, kind of!"
"Such a lovely view!
Why the sudden silence?"
"Look at the sun go down
oh so slowly!"
- "All good?
- Yeah, kind of!"
"Why don't you say something, pal!"
"We're just killing time
counting the miles past!"
"When the road finally
starts to smoothen out..."
"Could you please pull over
so I can pee!"
"We have been through
such a rough patch of road!"
"My whole body is rattling
like loose nuts and bolts!"
"Jungle all around,
this area isn't safe"
"There are mosquitoes everywhere, and
the mosquitoes have dengue and malaria"
"There's a chance
we might find a jungle beauty"
"following the beauty
we might find some wild wolf instead"
"What if the wolf comes?
What if he eats us all?"
"Anyway I hear that wolves
are big on keto diets lately"
- "All good?
- Yeah, kind of!"
- "What about you?
- Do you want it on paper?"
Hey, mister!
"We're just killing time
counting the miles past!"
"The tanker of life has a leak,
on top that the network too is weak."
"To add insult to injury,
you ask me if all is good?"
"All good?"
- Hey!
- Watch out!
Why are you so scared of dogs?
I'm not scared of them.
I... I just hate dogs.
- Good doggy!
- Oh, my, my!
This house is made of bamboos!
What if one of them breaks?
It'll shoot straight up your...
That's how we do it here.
This is great.
Then it won't be a waste.
It has many uses.
Bhaski, it is actually made with bamboos!
Why is it so dark in here?
- Turn on the lights.
- Hold on.
Where's the switch?
Is this what you call a great place?
Turn on the heater.
I'm on it.
Come on...
Don't break anything.
We'll have to pay a fine.
Can I get some water, Jomin?
Will bamboo water do?
I think I see something.
- Huh?
- What?
- I saw something move.
Where?
I think it's a bat.
Yuck.
It's so ugly.
Aww, it's cute.
So have it in a soup.
Sir, you haven't turned on the lights.
Mummy!
Bhaski, help!
So many bats!
Where have you brought me, Bhaski?
Let's go.
Bhaskar sir!
Welcome!
Welcome to Ziro!
- Jo, who is this clown?
- Welcome, welcome...
Thanks for coming!
- Thanks for bringing... Thanks than...
- For me?
- Take this one. This one's coloured.
- Sure!
Sir, it's okay.
Shut up.
This colour... Okay.
- Meet our Liasoning Officer Mr. Panda.
- Panda?
- Nice to meet you, Mr. Panda.
- Same here.
- Are you from around here?
- No. He's not.
- He's an outsider.
- I was born in another state.
But I've been here since I was a child,
so I'm a local.
Right!
That's why we need your help
- to build a road here, Mr. Panda.
- This way, please.
- I will surely help you.
- Good.
But forget about building a road here.
Why?
I mean, it's easier said than done.
If we have a friend like you
it's as good as done.
This is the biggest infrastructure project
of your state.
Our route begins
from the jungles of Ziro
- and goes straight...
- Through the middle of the jungle?
Can't it be built around
the boundary of the jungle?
Yes, true.
Mr. Neri, you're a senior engineer.
You should be aware
of how costly that would be.
Believe me. If a job that costs 100
bucks can be done in 10.
We will save 90.
Out of which, you will get 20.
And so will you, you too could get 20.
And if something is left,
us paupers can keep the change.
You have our full support.
Even I'll extend full co-operation.
- Thank you.
- But the tribals dwelling in the jungle..
Will they agree to this?
Why won't they?
Sir, the Apatani tribal folks
have been living in this jungle
since over 20 generations.
This is not just their home
but their entire livelihood.
They worship these forests.
I don't think they'll give up
their land so easily.
Come on, Mr. Panda.
They'll have to give it up.
For how long will we live like cavemen
in the name of conservation?
What about the environment?
Sir, we needn't worry
so much about nature.
Ask yourselves.
Who cares about nature in these times?
The plants in our balcony
is the closest thing to nature for us.
Believe me, sir.
Once this road is built in your town.
Ziro will be Number 1.
- Sir...
- Yes?
You've got the how's and when's
of the project very well.
But you haven't grasped the why.
Why?
Why hasn't a road been built
in this jungle yet?
Why?
Because it dwells in the jungle.
It?
- What do you mean by 'It'?
- Hold on.
Mr. Panda, what are you referring to?
Yapum!
- Yapum!
- What nonsense!
They're just rumours among locals.
Rumours can be true sometimes.
It sounds scary!
What on earth is Yapum?
A virus...
A virus from the depths
of the jungle.
Yapum, Virus...
Coming here was a mistake!
- Mr. Panda, whose side are you on?
- Sir...
I work for you,
so, of course, on your side.
Mr. Panda, money is
the biggest disinfectant.
Bacteria, viruses, parasites...
It destroys them all.
Just fix a meeting with the locals.
We'll handle the rest.
- Right, bro.
- Hey! What are you doing!
Look!
Look! Look!
Bro... A python!
Awesome!
Then wrap it around your neck.
Just run it over.
Let's get out of here.
No, no, sir.
No.
If we don't harm it
it won't harm us, either.
What if it bites someone?
It's roaming outside freely!
Sir, this jungle is its home.
It's you who is the outsider.
And so are you.
- Let's go.
- Inside the forest?
My home is nearby.
Here?
A person that understands his people
is considered family.
And the one who doesn't
is the real outsider.
Bhaski, look!
A Chinese buffalo!
- It does look like one...
- No, no! No, sir.
No Chinese.
It's called a Mithun.
Never insult a Mithun.
Its ego is really huge.
Oh!
Sorry...
See you around then.
- See you.
- He's right about that.
This man seems like trouble.
We cannot trust him.
Who names an animal after a celebrity?
I'm sure his goat is named Mumtaz.
Why Mithun?
Call it Jeetendra, or Dharmendra even.
But no, Bhaski.
One should never insult a Mithun.
It's revered, here in Arunachal.
Really? What about you insulting
our actor Mithun?
Even we think highly of him.
And he's a cobra.
Hey! Stop it.
Hey!
Mummy! Mummy!
Mummy!
We're alive!
Can't you drive properly?
- I saw something back there.
- Idiot.
Come on.
- What do you think?
- Mithun!
Mithun!
Go on, insult him some more!
You hurt his ego.
Yes, bro.
He seems mad at us.
Rubbish!
Do you mean this Mithun caused
the accident?
Who else then?
Of course it was him.
Let's get the car out, please!
Come on.
Let's see.
- He should do it, it's his car after all.
- Jo, hold on.
What's wrong?
Something's over there.
Something's moving.
Where?
You scaredy-cat!
Check if the radiator is blown.
Let me check.
- Hold this, JD.
- Hold on.
- Hello! Hello!
- Dad!
- Hello!
- Dad! Hello...
Son, I cannot see you!
I never see you properly.
Did you mortgage grandpa's house?
Why are you worried about that?
I'll take care of it.
If you want any money...
Of course I want money but that doesn't
mean you mortgage grandpa's house.
- Hello!
- Hel...
Hey! Answer me!
Hello...
- Hey, JD!
- What?
- Behind you!
- What?!
The Jungle!
Go ahead, laugh some more.
Go on.
- Coward!
- Laugh away.
He thinks this is funny.
"When I fell in love with you"
"my life went for a toss!"
JD! Jo! Help me!
- Don't look back this time.
- JD!
- Fool me twice, shame on me.
- Help! Jo!
Help!
- Help!
- Such overacting. My God!
- JD! Jomin!
- Hey, JD.
- Yes?
- He's really not there.
- Help! Help!
- Bhaski!
JD! Jo!
Hey...
JD! Jomin!
- Help!
- Bhaski!
Bhaski! Slow down, bro!
Help!
- Bhaskar!
- Bhaski!
Help! Help!
Hey! What's that!
It bit him!
- Jo! Please do something!
- What can I do?
Do some Kung fu or something, dammit!
Give it here!
Hit this thing, not me!
- What are you doing!
- Sorry, pal!
Throw it! Throw it!
Good job, Jomin! Very good. Once more!
It ran away!
It ran away! It ran away!
Bhaski!
- Come on.
Oh! Bhaski...
Bhaski... Bhaski! Are you okay?
Bhaski! What happened?
He bit my brother's bum!
He bit his bum!
What do we do?
Let's get out of here!
Let's go! Let's go!
- Oh God...
- Hang on, Bhaski.
Jomin, he's bleeding bad!
How far is the hospital?
- No! Not the local hospital.
- Why?
If anyone finds out
that Bhaski was bitten by an animal
rumours will fly everywhere!
Even the project will stall.
Where do we take him then, a temple?
Forget the project.
He could die!
Wait, give me a second.
I'll think of something!
He'll think of something!
We've reached!
Where have you brought us?
I said hospital,
you've brought us to a stable!
- Come on, quick.
- Bhaski.
- JD, pick him up.
- Yeah, you go ahead.
- Come on.
- Hurry.
Come on, Bhaski..
Okay, come on!
Hang in there, buddy.
- Come on.
- It's dripping so much!
Veterinary clinic?
A veterinary doctor?
Have you lost your marbles?
I don't know,
but this is the best option here.
Option? His buttock is missing
and you're counting options!
- Yes?
- Don't know what you mean...
- Jomin!
- Hi, Anika!
- What happened to him?
- He was attacked by an animal.
- Please help.
- Where did it bite him?
Over here..
- It's bleeding badly.
- Oh, s**t! Which animal was it?
Looked like a wild dog.
Can you help him?
Me?
I can manage, I think.
Are you even trained?
Trained enough for this situation maybe.
I think? Maybe?
A doctor should not talk this way!
Don't worry, JD!
Trust the doctor.
- She's a doctor for animals!
- Even man is an animal.
- Did she just quote an idiom?
- She can handle it.
My brother's life and a**...
I mean, his posterior
is in your hands now.
Posterior what?
He means bum.
- Hurry up, please!
- Don't worry! Don't worry!
Save him please!
I can't even bear to look at it.
Neither can I.
It chewed up his bum like
it were an apple!
That rascal dog!
Had I not taken his wallet
his bum would've been safe.
- It carved a crater into it.
- What do you mean?
- I meant, a hole.
- It's more like a ditch.
- It can fit an entire tennis ball.
- Yes.
How will he survive
with just a single bum?
He can. People manage
to survive on a single kidney.
How will he ever ride a bike?
He will ride it fine,
but his balance will be shaky.
How will he sit on the toilet?
Which pocket will he put his wallet in?
How will he live
with a disfigured bum?
- His sex appeal is gone forever!
- Stop your commentary.
I can hear you all.
Sorry, bro...
Sorry, Bhaski!
Just hang in there.
Will you please do the hon ours?
- Do you even plan to?
- What? Oh! Yes.
Pal, let her do it.
Be patient...
What's this?
Sorry! This is meant for horses.
Should I inject him?
Is she really asking us!
- Anika, do it.
- Yes?
Go ahead.
D-Deep breath...
Yuck!
Does it hurt to sit on a chair?
It's your first day with half a bum.
How does it feel?
Hold on. Can I touch it?
Does it hurt?
No.
Actually, I feel better.
That's like my brave cousin!
The doctor helped after all.
What's that fragrance?
But I haven't even showered yet.
Seems like that animal injection
worked after all.
He's strutting like Anil Kapoor!
What happened, bro?
Hey, Bhaski!
Hey!
Yuck! What are you doing?!
What are you doing?
I could smell this back
at the guest house...
Are you crazy?
The guest house is so far away.
- How could you possibly smell it?
- Bhaski, throw it away.
You'll fall sick.
He's Mr. Bhaskar.
He's from the government.
We want to build a road
passing through your jungle.
And for that we need
some of your forest land.
Some of you may lose your houses.
But if a road is built,
everyone will gain from it.
It's better if you give it up,
or the government has its ways.
- What?
- They're refusing, sir.
Mr. Panda...
We're here to help you out.
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, sir!
- Sorry, sir!
- Okay! Okay! Okay!
- Okay, we're leaving.
- Bhaski, let's go!
Bhaski, go!
Sorry, aunty!
What's wrong with them!
- They pulled out swords!
- It's not a sword. It's called a Dao.
Panda is screwing us over.
He's a real shady fellow.
We need to find someone else.
No, pal. He was appointed
by the government.
- But Jomin, he knows nothing...
- Mr. Bhaskar!
Please come here, sir.
- What's wrong with your people?
- They won't agree, sir.
You better drop this idea
of building a road.
He's right.
It's wrong to cut down the jungle
to build a road.
And keeping the state disconnected from
the rest of the country and calling it China
isn't that wrong?
How can there be development
without a road?
- People don't get it.
- Hey!
It's you who doesn't get it.
Do not forget, Bhaski.
If there's nature, there's progress.
- Good boy...
- Really?
Mr. Panda...
Just set up a meeting
with the youngsters.
- Hope you can do this at least.
- Definitely, sir.
Always at your service, sir.
Sir, you better talk to Prakash,
- the timber contractor.
- Yes.
He's the youth leader.
People here listen to him.
Take him into confidence.
Your village is really mind-blowing!
Amazing!
I mean...
Look! There are huge malls there!
Oh, my God! A multiplex, too!
You can go watch movies there!
There's a coffee shop, too!
I can smell the coffee!
Smell it.
There are MNCs, too,
in the village centre.
There are corporate centres
and big industries!
There's a giant airport as well!
Look, I see planes flying!
What are you looking at?
There's nothing.
Do you see anything?
This forest has turned you all into
frogs in a well.
We want to cut down this jungle
and connect you to the outside world.
and build a road.
But the old generation won't get it.
They don't even know
what this generation wants.
You want Netflix, not nature.
You want i-Pads, not trees.
You want Starbucks, not black-bucks.
You prefer Jungle Book
over jungles
and Tiger Shroff over real tigers!
Because development should be done
of the youth, by the youth,
for the youth.
- Do you want to make Ziro number 1?
- Yes.
Then folks...
We need your cooperation for this project.
- Will you extend it?
- Yes!
- Sure?
- Yes.
But it's your duty
to convince the village elders.
And don't worry.
That rascal Prakash...
He bribed everyone
and took the timber contract.
Are you okay?
What's wrong, sir?
- Bhaski!
- Here...
It's okay.
- He fell sick suddenly.
- Bhaski!
- Make everyone sign the stamp paper.
- Okay, sir.
- Good.
- What happened, brother?
- Sir...
- My ears are ringing.
Sir, you better meet our Ojha.
- Who?
- Ojha, the healer.
I'm fine.
Sir, he's 120 years old.
Asia's best healer!
He can cure any ailment under the sun.
He's in town currently.
Mr. Bhaskar, come in.
He will fix you right up.
I've got stomach ache.
He's opening up your nerves.
Hey, Bhaski!
- Bhaski!
Bhaski...
Bhaski!
Bhaski, wait!
- Bhaski, are you alright?
- Bhaski...
He dipped you in like a tea-bag!
What a crazy old man!
This is impossible!
How can such a deep wound
heal so fast?
There are other problems, too.
What problems?
People lose their hearing,
but mine is somehow heightened.
- A little too much!
- What do you mean?
When a phone rings, it feels like
someone is drilling my ears.
Krrrrr...
When someone snaps their fingers
it sounds like drums pounding.
- Bam! Bam! Bam!
- What else?
Smell...
This is the most confusing of all.
All foul smells
have turned into fragrances.
The stench of dead animals
smells like perfume.
- What had you put in the injection?
- Painkiller.
Sit down.
Your heartbeat is way too fast.
This is not normal.
- Rabies?
- Rabies...
Yes, it could be.
- Or maybe not.
- Make up your mind.
I mean, I don't know.
But this is really serious.
Then I should consult
a proper human doctor.
Do not make that mistake here.
Hope you haven't told anyone else.
No.
Good! Because the people here
are superstitious.
Anyway, I'll prescribe
some medicines for now.
Take these.
I think you'll be fine.
I think?
Well, I guess I'll be fine.
But I do feel better after meeting you.
I mean, after meeting a doctor...
Um...
When are you going back?
After a few days,
once my job is done.
You never took me sightseeing
around here.
Are you attending the music festival?
Are you?
Pick one.
Are you going, or not?
Don't drink alcohol.
It might react with the medicine.
- Sign or put your thumb-print.
- One by one.
- Your road will be built.
- Get moving.
Come on, put signatures.
- Or put thumb-prints if you like.
- Good!
- Do it quick.
- Come on, next!
Bhaskar sir!
We've got everyone's signatures.
- I'll hand over the papers tomorrow.
- Sure.
- For now, just enjoy!
- Thank you.
"We die everyday!
Every single day!"
"Let me live for tonight!"
"We do as we please!"
"After we get sloshed!"
"We die everyday!
Every single day!"
"Let me live for tonight!"
"We do as we please!"
"After we get sloshed!"
"My timid heart
has gone wild and crazy!"
"It's a rumble in the jungle!"
"Come on! Come on!
Come on! Come on!"
"In the jungle...
In the jungle..."
"It's a rumble in the jungle!"
"Let's soar high..."
Keep the work going.
Don't stop at any cost.
I'm coming.
"Let's soar high
and dance all night!"
"Let's drink the night away
and make merry!"
"Let's soar high
and dance all night!"
"Let's drink the night away
and make merry!"
"Let's soar high
and dance all night!"
"Let's drink the night away
and make merry!"
"It's a rumble in the jungle!"
"O' dangerous, very dangerous!"
"O' the reverie..."
I found my house!
Bhaski!
Where were you last night?
I've got a bad tummy.
We tried calling.
Why didn't you answer?
It must be on silent mode.
I got a little too drunk.
Either way,
the food here doesn't suit me.
They put bamboo in everything.
- Yes, they do.
- Well...
What did you do last night?
Bro, don't you know?
- There was a real rumble in the jungle last night.
- What?
- That timber contractor, Prakash Paja..
- Yes?
He was attacked by a wild animal.
It's really bad.
Everyone was looking for him.
- Finally they found him...
- Is he alive?
He has the land documents
of all the tribals.
Don't know.
They took him to the hospital.
And he's in a serious state.
He lost a lot of blood.
This place isn't safe.
- You never know what's coming...
- Sir! Sir!
- The police are here.
- But why?
They want to see you.
This...
We found it lying in the forest.
Is this yours?
- Is this yours?
- No!
It's mine, sir.
You were dancing
in the festival last night.
Then how did this end up
in the forest?
How did this end up in the forest?
Prakash liked this jacket last night.
So I gifted it to him
in a drunken spur.
- You gifted it to him?
- Yes.
- Buy us gifts too, sometimes.
- Sir!
- Buy him some.
- Officer Tempol!
Officer Tempol...
Hey, Panda!
Don't you see we're in the middle
of an investigation?
Why investigate them, sir?
They can't help you.
Sir, I'm the eye-opener witness!
I saw Prakash's attacker!
Prakash was attacked by an animal.
- It wasn't an animal!
- Then?
- Virus.
- Virus?
It was the virus.
What we had feared the most has started.
Hey, Panda!
Stop spreading rumours.
It'll cause problems.
Sir, the real problem is the one
who is in the hospital right now.
Tell me what you saw exactly.
Sir, last night
when the full moon was shining.
I saw a man approach.
Tap! Tap! Tap!
Then suddenly he went..
Tap-tap! Tap-tap!
Hold on.
How did the rhythm change?
Point to be noted, sir.
He was walking on two feet at first.
Tap! Tap!
Then he went down on all fours!
Then he pounced on Prakash!
He grabbed him by the neck!
Like this...
He sprung upon him
and tore him apart!
Prakash kept struggling on the ground.
It was growling, sir!
I can't even..
What happened then?
Then I literally wet my pants.
What's the deal with Panda?
Must've gotten drunk last night
and watched a cheap B-grade movie.
- The one with the mummy?
- No, the slasher movie...
Where he goes around killing newly-weds.
Or he must have watched
Rahul Roy's movie Junoon.
- The one where he becomes a tiger?
- Exactly!
- A tiger! Seriously...
- You think it's funny.
I still cannot understand
how that man started galloping.
How can a human run
on all fours?
Oh, come on!
I've heard plenty of such urban legends.
By the way, we must go see Prakash.
Bhaski.
- Hey, Bhaski!
- What happened?
- Bhaski! Bhaski!
Pick him up! Pick him up!
Bhaski! Bhaski!
- Yuck!
- Hey!
- Bhaski, this way...
- Let him down.
- Oh!
- It's okay. I'm here.
Daddy! Daddy!
- You'll be fine, Brother. I'm here.
- Doctor..
- See, it hurts here.
- Keep your hand here.
I think it's severe gastritis.
What did you eat last night?
Prakash...
- I had dinner with Prakash.
- Right.
But what did you eat exactly?
Because this happens
when one eats too much red meat.
- Did you?
- No, his ex-girlfriend has turned him vegan.
He hardly drinks milk.
Eating meat is out of question.
Let's get his feces tested.
- Feces what?
- Speak in Hindi.
It is Hindi.
It's called Stool Test in English.
Stop listening to Korean songs
and listen to Hindi songs for once.
- I can talk Hindi.
- As if!
Mind your grammar first...
You wait.
It's I can speak Hindi.
Not Talk Hindi.
You always mess up the grammar.
- This is too much!
- Then speak proper Hindi...
- JD, mind it!
- Guys, I'm dying here!
Guys! Hello!
- He's not well.
- Yes, exactly.
- Please get his stool tested.
- It's not needed yet.
I'll give him an injection.
- Maybe...
- No! No more injections!
- You'll be fine.
- I don't want it!
- I feel better already.
- Grab his legs. Do it!
- Flip him over.
- I'll take digestive pills!
- Please don't do this, guys!
- No...
- What are you doing!
- Easy there..
- I don't want it!
- Bhaski, stop! Hey!
I said, I don't want it!
Was that injection for horses?
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Yes.
Let's get some Chinese take away.
Bhaski must be hungry.
Bhaski's in a world of trouble,
and you want to hog Chinese food!
Focus on what's really happening.
- What?
- Understand the chronology, pal.
1. He was bitten by a wild animal.
2. His wounds healed in no time.
3. He can smell things really far.
4. Back at the Ojha's cottage
he was scared of water.
5. Prakash was attacked.
6. Bhaskar's jacket was found
in the jungle.
7. His stomach got upset the next day
and we both saw that bloody red vomit.
He's become strong as a horse.
How?
Understood?
Not a single word.
- Hydrophobia.
- Right! That must be it.
But what exactly is that?
Rabies!
He's contracted a mystical
form of rabies in this place.
And that's why Prakash...
- Are you suspecting your brother?
- People suspect their wives.
I've witnessed a lot of things.
There's only one way
to confirm our doubts -
What?
'Mal Parikshan'
Stool test.
S**t?
He won't allow it.
If it were money,
we could steal from him.
But how will you extract a stool?
Yes, that's true...
Idea!
Shh!
- Hello, sir!
- Any progress yet?
Yes, there is.
It's just that one project worker
got attacked by an animal.
What's the big deal?
This is common in projects
involving jungles.
But he had all the MOUs
and all the papers.
I'm looking for his replacement now.
I'll wrap up
and leave in a few days.
Sure, leave soon.
By the way, did that worker die
after the attack?
Be careful.
And just finish this damn thing!
Finishing, sir.
- Finish!
- Ah!
Janardan!
There's no water in here!
Hold it in!
The report will come in tomorrow.
Clean this up.
Okay.
Ma'am, where's Prakash Paja admitted?
Over there.
Oh! Mr. Virus!
What nonsense?
I'm not a virus!
You are everything to me!
The ultimate virus!
Have you lost it?
Just give me my papers.
Forget the papers.
Let's hunt as a team from now on.
You be Kohli, I'll be Rohit...
A tag team!
Sir, I've even made a list of rascals
we need to kill!
- I have all the paperwork ready.
- No.
First I'll kill Kaso,
the forest officer.
I used to cut down trees
but he would usurp the money.
Now I'll go after him!
Then comes Suraj, the milkman!
I'll eat up his buffalo!
Let's go, sir!
Let's spread the infestation!
Let's expand our team!
Come on!
Come on! Let's go!
- What are you doing here?
- Well..
I... I came to check on Prakash.
The doctor is here for that.
So leave.
Something isn't right here.
Compared to his morning inspection
half his wounds have healed!
What do you mean?
It's impossible
for wounds to heal so fast.
If the staff gets to know
they'll run away.
I think he's infected.
- Do you mean the virus?
- Shh.
Don't say its name after dark.
We must do something.
Or else, things will go haywire.
Let me think of something.
- Yapum!
Bhaski!
What are you doing here all alone?
- Where were you?
- I went to talk to Neri.
About what?
I lured him with a timber contract.
Now he will help us,
instead of Prakash
and also convince the local folks.
The project won't stop.
But Neri was against the project.
How did you know that
he wanted the timber contract?
This rascal Prakash bribed everyone
and took away the timber contract.
I overheard him say it.
- You're hearing too much lately.
- And even smelling too much.
Bhaski, what are you hiding from us?
- Nothing.
- What do you mean?
You've been acting strange
ever since the animal bit you.
Have you got rabies?
- What do I tell uncle.
- I'm fine, and fully normal.
Normal, my foot!
You vomited blood that day.
Then you started eating chicken, too.
Then during the injection incident
you lifted up the whole bed.
- You snap at us...
- What rubbish! I'm totally fine!
You won't tell us the easy way.
Let me call your dad.
- Put the phone away.
- Why?
- Don't call up dad!
- I won't listen to you!
- I said, I'm fine!
- No, you're not!
- I'm totally fine!
- You're not!
I said, I'm fine!
I told you I'm fine!
Bhaski, let him go!
Bhaski! Bhaski!
Let go of him, please!
JD! Hey, Bhaski!
Hey!
Get away from him! JD!
JD, are you okay?
- JD!
- Help me get up.
Get up!
Hello!
W-What!
They found traces of human hair, nails
and bone fragments in Bhaski's stools.
Are you crazy?
And this is not definitive.
I even spoke to my doctor in Delhi.
Even he confirmed it
that the stool sample belongs to
a man-eating predator.
- Didn't you hear it?
- Yes.
So what are you implying?
- Gangadhar is Shaktimaan.
- What?
Clark Kent is Superman.
Bhaski is our guy.
- What is he saying?
- Speak in Hindi.
Bhaski has caught some mystical disease.
He ate Prakash because of it.
Have you totally lost it?
- Then what about these bones...
- Hello! Hello!
Oh, darn! Not him again.
Such rowdy people sitting
with a fine lady...
And where's our jacket guy?
He's not here.
I trusted you as our project colleague.
And you are spreading rumours
about some virus.
I saw it with my own eyes.
It's not a story.
Never mind him, Mr. Panda.
I've always believed you.
And the running man incident
you were telling the cops about...
- Come on, JD.
- Hold on! Tell us more.
If anyone tries to destroy the jungle
the virus will get him.
Then that person becomes a wolf.
- A shape-shifting wolf...
- My foot!
Shape-shifting wolf, it seems.
Yes, this does sound like bulls**t.
- It's snakes who are shape-shifters.
- Why?
Do only snakes have a license
to be shape-shifters?
Can't wolves change form?
What rubbish is this, guys?
It's a disease...
Lycanthropy.
- Lemon what?
- Lycanthropy.
It's a mental disorder
where a human thinks he's a wolf.
Then he starts acting like a wolf.
No, no. It's not just mental.
It's physical.
He changes his body
like he changes clothes
and suddenly turns into a wolf!
Got it?
I don't have time for all this.
I'll check this and get back to you.
- Sure.
- And...
Go ahead, ignore me.
- But you can't ignore the wolf.
- Mr. Panda...
Speaking of a human
transforming into a wolf...
When does he do it?
Poets, newly-wed brides and wolves...
They all love full moon nights.
When they look at the moon
wolves signal each other.
And soon, the infected human
turns into a wolf.
- Jomin.
- Yes?
Hadn't you left the stove on?
- To boil the milk?
- Yes, let's go. It may boil over.
See you, Mr. Panda.
He must be inside.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
Hey, wait!
- Quiet! Stay low!
- Don't go without me.
He's inside.
What was that?!
What the heck was that?!
What was that?
Bhaski..
Come on! Let's follow it!
Straight...
Maybe it went that way.
Where did he go? Where did he go?
There he is! There he is!
Can you even drive?
- There he is! Turn left...
- Okay, okay.
- Go! Go! Go!
- I'm going!
Drive faster!
He's gone.
How do we find him now?
- There is a way.
- What?
- Let's howl like wolves.
- Crap!
Come on.
He will surely respond.
- But we're not wolves.
- Neither is he.
He's still half-human.
Come on, let's try.
- Me?
- Do it.
This isn't helping.
Let's do it together.
- Okay.
- Come on.
You sound like a dying pig.
And you sound like a donkey.
Really? Like a donkey?
Don't you tell me...
"O' my love..."
"You have me mesmerised."
Where is he?
Did he disappear again?
- Roll up the windows!
- "O' my love..."
Turn off the music!
Where did he go?
Hold this!
Jomin! I don't want to die!
Jomin! Save me, buddy!
- No! No!
- Stay away!
- Help!
- Go away!
Mummy!
Papa!
Bhaski's undies!
"Everywhere in the jungle,
the news is spreading like wildfire..."
"A new flower has blossomed,
with undies on"
Hi.
You never took me sightseeing,
so I went on my own.
JD and Jomin told me everything.
Hop on.
Try not to bite me.
"One little bird seemed so embarrassed,"
"Because, it was all bare..."
"It was so much better there,"
"Inside the shell (egg)"
"Now the bird is wondering,"
"Why am I really out of the shell?"
"A new flower has blossomed,
with undies on"
"Everywhere in the jungle,"
"A new flower has blossomed,
with undies on"
- "Everywhere in the jungle,"
- Where did you find him?
"A new flower has blossomed,
with undies on"
Yes! That's the one!
He was wearing the same undies last night!
And so was that wolf!
I bet it's ripped from behind.
What do I tell his father now?
That his son became a wolf?
No, drink water first.
Or do you prefer drinking blood?
He was clawing at me!
So you're a big wolf now?
- And doctor...
- Yes?
You kept saying it's lycanthropy.
That it's impossible!
A guy who was barely fit to be called
a human is now a damn wolf!
You stand right there!
I came here from Delhi just for you!
And you hid this from me?
Guys, that's not important now.
What's more important than a brother?
Last night, what...
I mean, whom did he eat?
Speak up.
Answer her!
Speak up!
Whom did you chomp down last night?
- Burp later! Answer me first!
- What do I say?
I don't know.
We found Prakash in your stools
and you know nothing?
No, I don't!
I don't know what I do every night.
I don't know if I attacked Prakash,
or not.
One feels miserable even
if a fly gets inside his nose.
But a fully grown wolf
has gotten into my body!
It's as if my body is hijacked
by a terrorist!
We always joke about
our pants ripping apart.
My a** literally tears apart
and a tail springs out!
I sprout dagger-like claws
and fangs like Dracula!
Then I wake up next morning
all naked
with blood on my body
and a snake inside my pants!
But one good thing
came out of all this.
My muscles are so ripped now.
But my life is ruined!
And one more thing,
I can now understand animal language.
Dogs tease me; Calling out
'Uncle! Uncle!'.
- Bluff!
- What bluff?
Sorry, Bhaski...
- Bhaskar!
- Sorry, Bhaski...
Tabaa, why isn't he eating?
Don't know, sir.
Did his girlfriend leave him
or something?
Yes, sir. Minty is missing
since last night.
How do you know?
Did you...
I can understand animals easily
but have no idea about myself...
Where I went last night,
or whom I ate!
Guys, last night some animal ate
a farmer's Mithun.
What!
You ate a mithun!
You could've eaten a pig, or a goat
or a chicken!
Or even a rabbit!
I was a wolf last night!
Hey! How would he know?
- Let him be.
- No way.
Maybe it's fine for you folks,
but not to us!
JD, why do you always say
this 'you folks' s**t!
- Why?
Because we don't want
to bruise a mithun's ego, again.
Guys, stop it!
What are you even saying!
- Ask him to stop!
- Sorry! Hi!
What?
I heard the locals here
hold you in high regard.
Please reassure them
that there's no such virus.
Prakash was a hunter.
He went hunting
and became a prey, himself.
That's no big deal.
I'll pacify the local folks.
But the transaction...
I genuinely thought you were against
cutting down the jungle.
You spoke so much about nature
and ecology the other day.
Everyone talks.
This place has 83 percent forest area.
Cutting down some trees
is no big deal.
Sir, the CCTV footage!
It's wearing undies!
Which animal wears undies?
What happened to him?
Excuse me.
Bhaski... Well...
He's a little sensitive.
The sight of blood makes him queasy.
Bhaski...
Bhaski, thank God
you didn't puke there.
Had you thrown up a finger or two,
you'd be exposed.
- Yes. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- The virus is here!
- Come on!
Let's go! The virus is here!
Rumours will spread
like wildfire now.
Listen, go and get an injection
from Anika.
Meanwhile I'll dispose
of your controversial undies.
I got your back.
Let's go.
We need to do something!
Everyone will know!
The ensuing panic
will shut down this project!
I saw it for myself.
I was on top of Neri tearing him apart!
- This will go viral now...
- Calm down, Bhaskar!
- Bhaskar, calm down!
- How can I?
If I don't get treated
I'll go around eating people!
There must be a cure for this!
In UK, US, Canada, Australia, Uganda...
I don't think it will help.
- Be positive. You're a doctor...
- I'm a doctor for pets.
I know nothing about diseases spread
by wild animals.
AIDS, Ebola, SARS, bird flu
and even Covid...
All these viruses came from wild animals.
It takes years to find vaccines for them
and some still don't have one.
Maybe this virus is a rare strain
from the forest.
All cursed things come from the forest.
Cursed things?
Forests don't send cursed things.
Cursed people like you tamper
with forests and get into trouble.
Nature has a balance.
If you ruin that
it'll be a problem for you, too.
The jungles you wish to cut down
are India's lungs.
Whatever oxygen is left in your cities
comes from here.
If you cut these down, too,
you'll choke to death someday!
- Why are you blaming me?
- What else do I do then?
Come on. I'm not some villain.
I'm here to do my job.
All these talks about nature
belong on twitter and Instagram.
But in real life,
only one greenery matters.
The greenery of bills!
Money!
And I'm fighting for
a big house and a big car!
To move into a better neighbourhood.
Your forest doesn't fit in anywhere
amid all this.
This is how I am.
And you know what?
The whole world is such.
Bhaskar, let's stop the project
and leave.
I cannot do that now.
My house and all my money
is at stake here.
I'll go bankrupt.
It's all the same.
- Even I...
- Just shut up, man.
Bhaski, staying alive is our top priority.
It's dangerous here. Let's go.
I am the danger.
I am the one who knocks people out.
And technically,
I've committed two murders.
No, you're just a human.
What's murder for a human
is dinner for a wolf.
Forget all this.
Let's leave.
I can't run away from myself.
The wolf is still inside me.
It's taken control of my mind.
It's listening to us right now
as we speak.
The people I fix during the day
are the ones I kill after
I transform into a wolf.
At this rate, I'll never make it.
Just get this out somehow.
Bhaski, if these people find out
- they will kill you.
- What's wrong?
Someone's here.
- Panda!
- I knew it!
It had to be one among you.
Look!
Want to burn undies?
Want to destroy evidence?
Deliver us from evil!
Sir, who smashed the window?
Smashed the window?
- Yes.
- Who?
Rubbish!
I always suspected you.
Now I'll tell everyone.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
The virus!
V... virus!
- Bhaski...
- I don't want this!
I want no evidence!
- Bhaski...
- No! Hey!
- Hold him!
- Bhaski, he will die!
- Please, hold him!
- But how!
- Bhaski!
- Please!
- How do we stop him!
- No!
You scared the crap out of him.
He's traumatised.
Mr. Panda?
No, he won't bite you.
- He's the virus!
- No, it's not true.
Mr. Panda, I'm not the virus.
I was bitten by another animal.
Sir, I had warned you.
The virus harms anyone
who tries to harm the forest!
I warned you.
Now I need to tell everyone.
I'm going.
Mr. Panda, I'm not the disease,
but a victim of it.
But if you tell people about me
then I'm sorry,
I'll have to bite you.
Then you'll bite someone else.
One by one,
everyone will be infected.
You, your wife, your kids...
And then?
Herd immunity!
- Really!
- Yes.
Herd immunity!
This will infect everyone.
It took us millions of years
to become humans from animals.
A single mistake you make now could turn
us all into animals again.
- Do you realise, Mr. Panda?
- Yes.
- You must not tell anyone!
- No.
I'll lock my lips, sir.
I won't squeak a word.
- Take this. Burn it down.
- Sure.
This is great!
Mr. Panda is on our team now!
Always, sir.
I was always on Mr. Bhaskar's team.
Great!
Mr. Panda, you're from around here.
Do you know the cure to this?
What about the 120 year old Ojha?
He must know about this virus.
- Yes. It's possible.
- Where can we find him?
He keeps roaming the forest.
No one knows where to find him.
We may find him tomorrow,
or even after three months.
Three months?
He will kill the whole city by then.
What do we do until then?
I must do three things until then.
Not die, not kill anyone...
And find a cure.
I'll find that Ojha for you.
- I will start right away.
- Thank you!
Listen, everyone!
An animal has become a man-eater.
Everyone is hereby warned
not to spread rumours
not to panic
and not lurk near the jungle at night.
"He will come..."
"His coming is inevitable."
- "He will come..."
- I need sniffer dogs!
The ones who go like...
"His coming is inevitable."
- "He will come..."
- "Go! Go!"
"Will they let it come again,
I ask you?!"
"And will they let it bite
into my bum again, too?"
"Are we supposed to stay awake
all day and all night too?"
"Are we supposed to worry every day,
I ask you?"
"Tell me!"
"Because now I've got
the whole village backing me."
"Everyone volunteered;
No one was forced by me."
"We're fully prepared with bamboos
and ropes too."
"He won't be able to break away,
I'm telling you."
"He's not German or Husky, I know."
"If we'll go after him,
he'll break all our bones for sure."
"Will we find it before it finds us,
I ask thee?"
"Friends if we're strangers,
enemies should we meet."
- "Make some noise!"
- "Go! Go!"
"Oh yes, I'll continue with it,"
"That too without any drama
or sad bits."
"Hey! I'm so loving this!"
"What do I say,
even this dog here fears it."
No one should panic.
Special hunters have been hired
from Assam.
"How are the moths burning
without a flame?"
- Can you handle it?
- Of course.
"Hey! The virus'
gonna go hounding at night,"
"Someone tell me who's the hunter
and who's being hunted alright!"
"I'll have to risk
my life to stay alive,"
"I'll have to hurry,
or I'll be someone's dinner tonight."
"Come on, I want everyone to participate,"
"Don't be scared,
we've got a village to save."
"I want you to scream just like me,"
"If their throat goes dry,
give them some water, please."
"And of course, something to eat."
"Go! Go! Go Virus!"
Remedies to escape
werewolf attacks.
Romans used the concept of fatigue
for this.
- Fatigue.
- Yes.
A Sicilian belief of Arabic origin states
a werewolf can be cured
by striking its forehead with a knife.
"Go! Go! Go Virus!"
Where have you brought us?
Hurry up, we need to get there
before the moon rises.
Whose place is this?
How does it matter?
It's a safe place.
Panda suggested this.
Unlock it.
The place is indeed good.
But what if I still break out?
- Then?
- That's what the chain is for.
Now we'll chain you up here,
and release you at dawn.
If the chain snaps
it'll be a problem.
Bhaski, you become a wolf,
not the Hulk.
- That was savage.
- Shut up!
- Why are you stripping?
- All my clothes are ripped.
Let me save these.
Chain me up.
Do it!
Do you want a goat or something?
For a midnight snack.
Hey!
What is Kaso doing here?
I guess Panda double-crossed us.
He suggested this place.
Mr. Kaso...
Well...
We're starting the project soon.
So we came to scout a location
for the timber mill.
Wearing undies?
- This is just...
- Sure! Check the place out.
Sir...
- Hey! What are you doing!
- Sir, please!
- Open it!
- Do you know who we are?
You're just a forest officer.
We're the Lutyens'. You'll be hearing
from the Minister himself!
I suspected you right from the start.
- What?
- Today I will prove it.
- What! Are you crazy?
- What doubts?
Kaso, unlock this.
Let's talk it out.
The mystery of this virus
will be solved today.
- The virus!
- What virus?
This entire fiasco is about money, right?
There's a lot of money in this project.
Neri and Prakash are gone.
You'll get the entire cut for the timber.
Let's do the deal!
Do you outsiders think
we locals are fools?
- No.
- I will seal the deal with Bagga, himself.
Hey, mister! Please unlock us!
Oh, man!
Jomin, talk to him!
Sir, it's not what you think!
Sir, please unlock it...
And now he's singing!
- Let him try. His arms are longer.
- Sir, open it.
- No! No!
- What are you doing!
- He's shooting a video!
- We gotta go. We'll go viral!
- But where do we go?
- We must get out.
- How?
- Jomin, help us out.
- You must know this place!
- Look there!
- Look upstairs!
- Call up Panda!
- I'm on it.
There's nothing here.
Nothing here either!
- Anything?
- No!
- There's no signal here.
- What!
- Stop it!
- Just keep looking.
Hey!
Bhaski, no! You'll get hurt.
There's no exit!
Bhaski!
Hey! Did you hear that?
- Hey!
- Bhaski, don't look.
Don't look, Bhaski.
- Hey, Bhaski.
- Bhaski, look here.
- Look at me. His stomach is hurting.
- Bhaski! Bhaski!
- Bhaski, listen!
- Help me!
- Brother!
- Let's go!
Brother?
- Get the chain!
- What!
- Please control!
Jomin, pull!
You pull!
- This way!
- Okay!
Tightly! Tightly!
Go that way!
Breathe in, breathe out...
Breathe in...
Very good!
- I can't do it! No way!
- You can! Try harder!
Bhaski, mind over matter...
Easy! Hang in there!
Lord, deliver us from all evil!
- Lord, deliver us from...
- Get a hold of yourself.
Where the hell are you going?
Mister! Mister!
He might kill us!
Please, mister!
- Open the gate! Please!
- Please, mister!
I'm still a bachelor!
I don't want to die!
- Please, mister!
- I'll do anything you say!
- Sir! Sir!
Please be human, for God's sake!
Let us go, sir.
- Get away!
- Please...
- Let us go...
A live werewolf transformation.
His bones are snapping!
Look! Look, the tail!
Bhaski...
Jomin!
This is your last chance to do Kung-Fu.
Bhaski!
Shoo! Shoo! Get away!
- Jomin! Help!
- Get over here! Hurry, JD!
- No!
- Look!
- Bhaskar!
- Bhaski!
Bhaski!
I know you're in there!
It's me! Your cousin JD!
Will you really eat me?
Bhaski, stay!
No!
Mr. Wolf, are you hungry?
There's lots to eat outside.
Deer, pigs...
Even those Mithuns.
Please let me go.
Stand back, you heartless animal!
Do you recognise me, Brother?
No...
I'm an idiot!
I'm a stupid a**hole
for coming here with you!
Take all my money and let me go!
I'm your uncle's son!
Eat Jomin if you're hungry.
Shut up, JD!
Are you crazy?
Mummy!
Hey! Hey! No, Bhaski!
I'm your partner!
Don't listen to him, Bhaski!
No, Bhaski...
Please!
I want to live, Bhaski!
Hallelujah! Praise the Lord!
Praise the Lord!
Are you okay, buddy?
Get lost!
Janardan!
That rascal Panda
must've tipped off Kaso.
- Jo, what are you doing?
- He's leaving.
What happened?
I'm talking to you.
I tried, bro. Your turn.
Hey, Jo!
Just look at me!
- Jo, please stop!
- Why should I?
Why?
You almost ate me last night!
- Last night...
- Stop it, pal!
The local folks are right!
You outsiders are the virus.
You are leeching off the local folks.
You were about to do
the same to me last night.
Animals don't know if their prey
belongs to Delhi or Arunachal.
- You know that I have no ill feelings.
- You do, Bhaski.
Not just you, even he does.
Even everyone out there feel the same way.
JD discriminates against me casually
over every little thing!
Even you laugh at his jokes.
Do you think I don't feel bad?
He's been pestering me
to show him Kung-Fu.
Want to see Kung-Fu now?
I don't know Kung-Fu.
For you folks, all of North East
is a Shaolin temple
and we are Jackie Chan
and Bruce Lee's children!
- Right?
- No...
When people call us Chinese
in our own country
it feels so bad!
It really hurts!
Brother...
And JD, if one's Hindi is weak
it doesn't make him any less Indian!
- Come on, pal.
- Jo, please don't...
Jo, please hear me out.
Stop him.
Jo! Jo, please wait!
Jo, please hear me out once.
That was some lecture!
Do you know what the truth is?
People have this insecurity.
When someone looks different,
or has a weakness
or is from a different community
people pick on them.
Even I was called many names.
Stupid, nerd, foolish...
People used to bully me a lot.
But hearing you today
made me feel like a bully, myself.
But you know what matters ultimately?
Friendship.
I have two close friends.
They instilled me with confidence.
They said I'm not stupid.
And today, I'm preparing
for IAS exams.
I don't know if I'll be able to crack it.
Please forgive me.
Bhaski needs us.
Slap me if you want.
- No.
- Yes, go ahead. Slap him.
Slap me, too, bro.
- No, Bhaski..
- Sorry, Jo.
And if I really had to pick between
the two of you.
I would always eat you.
Because animals don't eat trash.
What crap!
So I'm trash?
Don't hug me. No, thanks!
- Come on.
- Mr. JD!
Mr. Bhaskar...
Do you remember the Ojha?
- What happened to him?
- Well...
I found him.
What is he saying?
He asked you to shut up.
He says that...
Humans and forests have shared
a special pact since centuries.
That neither would harm the other.
But when humans break that pact
and cut down the forests
the virus infects them.
The jungle will always live
in some part of the human mind.
The virus unleashes that part.
Then that person forgets
all civilised behaviour
manners and inhibitions
and turns into a wild beast.
The virus is the chief of the jungle.
It infects others
and creates soldiers for itself.
And when the time comes
he chooses one among the soldiers
to be the new guardian.
How can a person infected
by the virus return to normal?
- Ask him that.
- Yes, we better.
On a moon-less night,
the main virus visits the spot
where it infected its prey.
If it bites its prey again
at the same part of the body
he can be cured.
- What!
Grandpa here is asking him
to get bitten again?
So you'll voluntarily
get your head bitten off?
More like my butt.
- Are you crazy?
- Haven't you seen it in movies?
When one gets a head injury
he loses memory.
But when he's hit again
at the same spot it comes back.
- It's the same idea.
- I don't believe you guys.
No, you have to believe us.
Fine. Let's assume the Ojha is right.
Still what's the guarantee
that the animal will show up?
And what's the guarantee
that it will only bite his bum?
I agree, there's no guarantee.
So should I just quit?
Don't my feelings matter?
Am I supposed to go on eating people
I don't want any of this!
I want to be free of this curse.
Do you understand?
And we must create an arm our such that
the wolf bites only his bum.
- And he stays alive.
- Yeah.
Where can we find such an arm our?
You're the animal expert.
Anika, aren't you one?
Will you help us or not?
Please.
"Faith is a strange thing,"
"Why do I trust you blindly?"
"What is this bond forming between us?"
"I don't know."
"You don't belong to me..."
"Yet you mean the world to me."
What are you thinking?
What do you think?
Why me?
Why did this virus infect only me?
Maybe it has never seen
such a handsome young man before.
No, seriously.
Why me?
I mean, you wanted to cut down the forest.
So maybe that wolf wanted to kill you
and you escaped accidentally.
Or maybe it wants to turn the destroyer
into the saviour.
You wanted to go sightseeing with me,
right?
I have a favourite spot.
Let's go there before the big bite?
"You don't belong to me..."
"Yet you mean the world to me."
"How did you do this?"
"You've managed to steal my heart away."
"I know, but yet I don't get it."
"You are my sunshine."
"You don't belong to me..."
"Yet you mean the world to me."
"Let me belong to you, my love."
"I want you to dwell in my heart,
my love."
"Your touch has made my dull life"
"Bright and colourful."
"When I move towards you..."
"I feel like I am soaring."
"This world holds no meaning anymore,"
"You are the only one I want."
"I am in so deep that I
don't know how to uncomplicate it."
"I find truth in your
words even when they're false."
"You don't belong to me..."
"Yet you mean the world to me."
"Let me belong to you, my love."
"Let me belong to you."
- Isn't it beautiful?
- It is indeed.
"Let me belong to you."
This place makes me want to turn
into an animal and stay here forever.
Then stay.
No.
I need to go back.
After getting rid of this virus
I'll go home.
If I survive, we'll meet at the clinic.
Take care of yourself.
Hmm. Come on.
You are the best hunters.
We must nab that animal at any cost.
And most important,
unless you are in lethal danger
do not shoot it dead.
Hey! Hurry up!
The virus is done for!
I bet on it!
Your account does not have
sufficient balance.
To avoid low balance...
Brother, is this the place?
Smell it.
Yes, this is the wretched place.
- Jo, is everything set?
- Everything is set.
- Come on!
- Keep walking...
Keep walking...
- Hurry up! It'll be dark soon.
- Keep walking...
- What are you doing?
- No, let me check.
The neck is more important than the bum.
I have the power!
The number you have dialed
is unreachable.
What's wrong, Bhaski?
This doesn't feel right.
No, everything is right.
The arm our is proper.
The rope is ready.
Even our outpost is ready.
It's all good.
No, bro.
So far I thought I was the hero
in this story
and the wolf was the villain.
But it's the other way.
Between the wolf and I
the wolf is the hero.
I don't care who's the hero.
I just want my cousin back!
- This isn't the time for sentiment.
- I'm not...
- How will I face your dad?
- JD, hold on.
Bhaski, you and the wolf were doing
your respective jobs.
We just want you to become
a normal human again.
We'll debate about the morality later.
Just focus on this for now. Okay?
- Come on, hang.
- JD, we don't have much time.
- Yes, let's go soon. Come on.
- Come on.
- Hurry up!
- There's the rope.
Pull! Pull!
Pull...
- Okay.
- It's fine.
Okay, Bhaski?
Pass me the knife.
- Here.
- Get a smaller one.
- Take this.
- Hurry up!
One, two, three!
Give me your hand.
Crazy!
- Bhaski!
- Shh! Shh!
I see something over there.
Go to him! Go to him!
Lord, deliver us from all evil!
As soon as it bites him, shoot it!
- Why did you shoot?
- It wasn't me.
- Jo! JD!
- Bhaski!
- Hurry up!
- Come here.
- Come on.
- Hold it...
Hold it! Come on!
Take this off quick!
Who fired the shot?
- It wasn't us.
- Not us.
It's over there.
Then you better follow it.
You must get bitten
before they kill you.
Come on.
This is your last chance.
Go, Bhaski!
Just go for it, Bhaski.
Anika!
You!
It is me.
The virus, Yapum...
Whatever you call it...
JD! Jo! Help me!
So it was you who bit me?
I wanted to kill you,
but you escaped.
And became like me even though
I didn't want it.
But what had I ever done to you?
I was just...
The forest was going to be cut down
because of you.
And I couldn't let that happen.
I've been protecting these forests
for a 100 years.
I could've killed you
if I wanted to.
But for some reason
I felt you were changing.
I cannot stay in one place for long.
So I thought maybe
I could leave you here in my stead
and go elsewhere.
But I was wrong.
- Why didn't you tell me sooner?
- I wanted to.
But you were not ready for it.
You still aren't.
Because Bhaskar,
what you think of as a curse
is a great responsibility.
You're better off as human.
You're not worthy of being an animal.
You want freedom from this curse, right?
You wanted to get bitten, right?
Come, let me bite you.
- No...
- Bhaski!
Bhaski! Bhaski!
Could he have gone there?
Bhaski!
Bhaski! Bhaski!
Are you okay?
Did you get bitten?
- What?
- Anika...
Anika is the virus.
- He's gone mad.
- Come on!
It was Anika who bit me
in the jungle.
Dr. Anika?
I suspected only men so far.
But we missed the fact that females
are the stronger sex in every specie.
Oh!
So she's been guarding these forests
for a 100 years?
Yes.
And now, we must save her.
We must stop all of them.
But how?
There are so many of them.
In order to stop them
he must transform into a wolf.
Yes, bro.
Cities have enough heroes.
This time a jungle needs a hero.
Turn into a wolf, Brother.
I'll handle your dad.
Come on, do it.
- Do it.
- Bhaski, you must do it.
- Come on.
- Just go for it!
- Attaboy!
- Yes.
Come on! Come on!
I can't do it.
- What happened?
- It's a moon-less night.
You are too demanding sometimes.
Here, a picture of the moon,
for inspiration.
Stop all this.
What do you need the moon for?
To break the Karva-Chauth fast?
No.
You're a shape-shifting wolf.
Okay?
Go within and bring out the wolf.
Like this...
- You don't depend on the moon.
- True.
- Bring it from within.
- Yes.
- You're a self-reliant wolf.
- True.
Bhaski, you must do it.
Focus. Focus.
Good! Bravo!
Excellent, Bhaski!
Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Come on, Bhaski!
- I still can't do it.
- Shame on your existence!
- Can't even transform.
- Make him angry.
- Come on, make him angry.
- Sorry, Bhaski!
- Hey! Easy there..
- Bhaski! Bhaski!
Look here...
Grab him! Become a wolf!
Become a wolf, you...
Don't you want to save the jungle?
Become a wolf!
Hit him! Hit him! Get angry!
Stop it, guys!
Enough! Enough!
- He needs this!
- Hey stop!
Stop this Royal Rumble!
Enough!
Remember what the Ojha had said?
The jungle is still alive
in some part of your brain.
Unlock that.
Awaken your primal instincts.
Feel them.
You and the jungle are one and the same.
Become one with it.
Realise it.
Smell it.
Wake up and smell the jungle.
This is yours.
It's all inside you.
This entire forest is yours.
Draw strength from the jungle.
This jungle is your house.
Claim it today.
Find it.
It's yours and yours alone.
The virus!
Instead of building this highway
through the forest
we will now build
it along the forest boundary.
And we heartily welcome
this new decision.
Because there can be no development
at the cost of nature.
And we all have understood it.
A wise man had rightly said once...
If there's nature, there's progress.
'The ridge project is currently shut down'
'because many people working on
it suffered animal attacks.'
'Even Babanjeet Bagga,
the company chairman of this project'
'died in a terrible animal attack.'
It's fresh pork, especially for you.
Eat only this.
No more wandering outside
and eating people.
- But this is hardly enough.
- You need to stop overeating.
You ate Bagga yesterday.
He was a whole buffet in himself.
I can only spare one more piece.
Here.
- Okay?
- Yes.
South Delhi Ridge's forested areas act as
the lungs of Delhi city among others.'
Who is it?
'In spite of protests,
they want to cut down the forest, '
Stay right here.
'And build an industrial plant.'
What are you staring at?
Don't you recognise us?
It's me!
Vicky.
We've been looking for you more
than people look up things on Google.
Janna! Janna! Janna!
- I missed you guys so much!
- Stop your drama.
- We called you so many times.
- Sorry, guys.
I used to get seizures.
People thought I was cursed.
So mom sent me here
and made me delete all contacts.
She made me block your numbers.
You forget your friends for a woman?
She's my mother, pal.
- Sorry.
- Janna..
Try and be a good friend at least now.
Okay?
Only you can find her now.
Who?
Stree!
Her effect still lingers inside you.
You still get seizures, right?
Yes?
But how will I find her?
Why is it always up to me to find her?!
But how do I, Vicky...
- Did you hear that?
- No.
- Someone's in here!
- What sound?
Are you enjoying in private?
- Who is it?
- A special friend, huh?
- No...
- Introduce us, too.
We want to meet her.
Where is she?
Not here! It's coming from over there.
- Wow, Janna!
- No, pal.
- Tinted room!
- Hear me out...
- Vicky! Here's his lady...
- Don't go in there!
It's my uncle's room.
Please don't...
They're my friends.