Thank God.
Congratulations. It's a boy.
Thank you for the good news.
If you are looking for a reward,
then you may head to the special ward.
Maybe a prince is being born there.
Go.
Sister, clean the baby
and keep him in the crib next to his mom.
I will inform Mr. Jindal and his family.
I can't understand a word, Pandit Ji.
Is it a good or a bad sign
to be born during a deluge?
- Sir.
- Okay.
- So...
- Sir, I need to make an urgent call.
Can't you see I am on a call?
Sir, it's an emergency. Please!
What happened?
A baby was born in
the special ward some time ago.
The boy was stable
when the doctor checked him.
But now he is not breathing.
The baby belongs to the Jindal family.
I will call you back, Pandit Ji.
The doctor has already informed
the family that their son is healthy.
They are powerful people.
I am afraid they might blame me.
Let's exchange their son with mine.
Even we were blessed with a son today.
And who would understand
this joy better than me?
I've been working for them for years.
I owe them everything I have.
This sacrifice is too small compared
to their favors.
What about your wife?
How will you convince her?
God will bless us with another child.
We cannot do this. It's wrong!
No.
A good deed can never go wrong.
Never.
Let's go.
Pick him up.
Pick up the child.
We are doing a good deed.
Don't be afraid. Pick him up.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Come on.
He is alive.
Thank God!
Look, sir.
Give him to me.
Now he is mine.
No, sir.
It was supposed to be a sacrifice.
But you are being deceitful now!
Deceitful?
His father and I joined
the company together.
We drove to the office together
on my scooter.
But somehow he was able
to charm Jindal's daughter.
From an assistant,
he became their son-in-law.
And I remained an employee.
Now, while he rides in luxury,
I still get soaking wet
riding my old scooter.
Because he was lucky.
But this child…
He could have cried
when we exchanged him with my son.
But he cried after we exited the room.
Why?
Because he is unlucky, like me.
Now he will lead an ordinary life,
and my son will live like a king.
This is worse than betrayal.
- It's a sin.
- Shut up.
Don't snatch a child from his mother.
I won't let you do it.
- Give me the child.
- Let go. Don't make a scene.
I will tell everyone.
- I will tell everyone.
- Who will believe you?
Valmiki. I've been blessed with a son.
- What about you?
- Me too.
Great. Congratulations.
Congratulations.
All okay?
Yes. I just sprained my leg.
- Take care.
- Yes.
Sulochana! Lift her!
My son.
Our son.
I am running out of patience.
What's the name of my future successor?
Raj.
Raj Nanda.
Raj!
Raj Steels.
Raj Cargo.
A true prince!
Raj…
Do you like the name, Valmiki?
Absolutely, sir.
Perfect name for
the successor of this empire.
Have you decided
what you will call your son?
Are you serious?
What kind of name is that?
It's absurd.
I will never allow you to call him this.
Poor kid will become a laughingstock.
And it also damages my reputation.
Goodbye!
- But…
- Pandit Ji!
Listen, Pandit Ji…
Pandit Ji!
Bantu?
It sounds like the clanging of dishes.
- Bantu.
- Why?
Lord Ram calls Lord Hanuman "Bantu"
and still he is worshipped.
Don't try to use this logic with me.
Lord Ram and Lord Hanuman are different.
Who will this boy serve?
What is this?
Only nine marks in math?
So what if madam gave you less marks,
I'll make up for it.
And uncle Valmiki has a similar pen.
What are you doing, Valmiki?
Looking at Raj's report card.
How much did he score in math?
Take a look.
97.
Bravo, son.
Well done.
Can you guess Bantu's score in math?
- How much?
- Ninety-eight!
Gosh, lost out by two marks.
You should have scored 100 out of 100.
Don't be so mean.
He has scored such good marks.
Nobody remembers the guy
who gets out in his nineties.
Only centuries count.
Some are just born unlucky.
Very sad.
The prince
What are you doing here?
Don't worry.
This is just a dream.
Also known as nightmares in English.
Do you remember everything?
Of course.
Twenty-five years ago you changed
this little guy's fortune!
I was destined to be a king.
Instead, I became a miser like you.
Time for you to wake up.
Stop watching these fancy dreams
and go make tea.
Bloody child swapper!
The prince
Dad, your tea.
Keep it downstairs.
Thank God!
If he is busy snoring here,
that means my son's living like
a king in his palace!
Unbelievable.
How can he look so happy
for a guy who lost everything?
Hey!
Get up.
Grandma sent pickles.
Go collect it from the station.
Go on.
Not fair, Mom.
You are so warm and loving in my dreams.
But in reality,
I've to endure his sarcasm.
How could you leave me alone
with this grouch?
Miss you, Mom.
Hey.
I guess that's Kumar here for his money.
Tell him I am not at home.
Is your daddy at home?
Daddy?
Daddy, Poppa, father, pop…
Is any of them at home?
Oh, that guy.
He said to tell you
that he's not at home.
You are a disgusting man!
Asking your son to lie!
Shameless.
I'll be back in the evening
for the rest of the money.
Why didn't you make
him sit on my lap instead?
All you had to say was
"Daddy is not at home".
Call your dad.
Daddy is not at home.
And he's definitely not behind
the wall or under the table.
And that's final.
You are such a lowlife!
We are middle-class people.
Being completely honest and moralistic
will make us misfits in society.
Your simplicity will get
us all killed someday.
If I tell the truth,
I'll be afraid only once.
But if I lie,
I'll be afraid till I don't get caught.
Bravo, Bantu.
Thanks, sis.
Here. Coconut and camphor.
And where is the garland?
We don't have it.
You guys forgot to get the garland.
He's returning from America
after completing his graduation.
Useless.
He didn't win any medals.
It took him six years
to complete a four-year course.
No need to glorify his blunders.
It's okay, sir.
Dad. Seven years.
Seven?
Embarrassing!
- Hello.
- Are you at the station?
Grandma sent pickles
for the entire neighborhood.
Keep it aside.
And get a garland immediately
to Jindal sir's residence.
Is Jindal sir getting married at this age?
Stupid. I just want a garland.
- Garland.
- Who is getting married?
Your dad!
Stop, uncle. I have arrived
at my destination.
Hey.
- Where do you think you are going?
- Relax.
It's heavy.
Not your cup of tea.
I've been carrying you around for ages.
This is child's play. Hand it over.
I've been observing since childhood.
You never let me in.
What is the problem?
Son, this is heaven!
The only way to gain access
is to earn merits or die trying.
Some are just born unlucky.
Very sad.
Raj has arrived!
Raj has arrived.
He has a place for everyone
in his heart except for me.
Thanks, Val.
Welcome, home.
Grandpa.
Hey, Dad.
Welcome back.
I made your favorite kheer.
I hope it's made of almond milk, Mom.
Master Raj, the kheer
is made from the milk
- of our in-house cow, Elizabeth.
- Elizabeth?
We moved heaven and earth
to get her here from the Swiss mountains.
Even he's traveled 12,000 kilometers.
Yes, I am extremely tired.
CP, please.
Listen…
All the best, brother.
Hope you get the job this time.
Focus on your studies.
Let's go.
Did you not see what happened?
I would understand if they were girls.
But what will those boys do
with your pink veil?
People should steal stuff they can use.
Someone misbehaved with your sister,
and that didn't make you mad.
Relax.
You are expecting too much from me.
I am getting late. Bye.
Next year on Raksha Bandhan,
we can switch roles,
so, I can protect you.
Because clearly, you couldn't!
That hurt my ego.
If you ever want
to get a job done by a man,
just hurt his ego.
Where will I find them now?
Everyone says
My sister is one in a million
Hello, Nisha.
Sorry for overreacting, brother.
Doesn't matter.
I found your veil.
How?
We haven't decided yet.
Brother, that pink veil
belongs to my sister.
Your sister is damn hot, man.
Thanks, man.
Please return the veil.
We'll return the veil,
in exchange for your sister.
The prince
Veil.
No…
When you said,
"Your sister is damn hot.",
I wasn't upset at all.
She is a beautiful girl.
In fact, I was happy that we will have
to spend less on her wedding.
That's how we think.
Middle-class mentality.
But then he interrupted
like an '80s villain.
"My sister in exchange for the veil."
Who talks like that?
He broke my heart.
I lost my mind when I realized
You entered the lanes of my heart
Which floor?
- Your floor.
- Sorry…
Thirteenth… floor.
13.
Legal Eagle.
Fooled you too, right?
I am 21 plus.
I am an adult.
The office is called Legal Eagle.
All the best.
Best. Best. Best.
I am madly in love
I can't stop loving you
Are you applying for
the post of paralegal?
Yes, ma'am.
Bantu.
Government Law College, Amritsar.
Most of our applicants are Howard
and Cambridge graduates.
You don't stand a chance here.
I am sorry.
Rejecting me without seeing my merit.
Not fair.
Okay. Come in.
This is Harmeet. My client.
He wants to divorce his wife Simran.
You can defend Simran,
and see if you can get us some alimony.
You have five minutes
to showcase your merit.
What?
Our life cannot be his audition.
Relax.
If he is any good, I will hire him.
Back to the case.
My client Harmeet has
accused his wife Simran,
she was a simple girl
when they got married.
But Harmeet's lifestyle
and fortune changed Simran's personality.
She calls herself a "socialite" now.
She uses me like an ATM.
Gold digger.
Who else will spend
the husband's fortune if not the wife?
The neighbor?
Until now,
Rashmi has never asked me for anything.
Then why do you like, share, and comment
on every Insta-post from her?
Like a stray dog.
Excuse me. Just mind your language.
So, there is still some hope.
Sister-in-law is suspicious about him,
which means she loves him.
You have complaints
because you still have hope.
Even I have complaints.
I wanted to continue working
after marriage.
But his father has a rule.
Chadda family women
never go out to work.
Ms. Samara.
Will you continue working after marriage?
Of course.
If an educated, talented, disciplined,
cute, hot, gorgeous, long-legged…
I kick pretty hard.
Sorry.
You see…
Women today like to work
even after tying the knot.
So get with it, Harmeet.
Let her be self-reliant.
Can't work, can't have kids.
How can we be happy?
By trying.
First, take care of each other,
and then the baby.
And the thing about babies is,
they are like love.
Never plan it,
let it be natural.
Love each other so madly,
that the child comes naturally.
If you have any other problems,
you can write to me.
Bantuka4@gmail.com
Now go and reproduce.
Brother, thank you for this.
So, what time should I come tomorrow?
You don't have to.
Being a lawyer you acted
like a relationship counselor.
You just lost me a client.
I am rejecting you based on your merit.
You have no future here.
Get out.
What are you doing?
Bag.
It's nearly a week since Raj came back.
I haven't seen him.
Where is he?
Master Raj left his room ten minutes ago.
Master Raj has arrived.
Master Raj.
Your avocado on sourdough toast.
There's a guy called Sarang.
Sarang deals in toys.
And uses our cargo planes to export them.
One day our hangars were raided.
And Sarang's real business
was exposed.
So we banned their company.
And his business shut down.
He is sending his brother
to get the ban lifted.
And your dad is sending you to say no.
Sir. Tea?
No.
It's easy to say no to a waiter.
But equally difficult to a powerful man.
Son, if you can pull this off...
Then you will earn respect.
This is your test.
My son doesn't need to give any tests.
Just be yourself, Raj.
That's all I want.
Uncle Kailash,
I am feeling a little uneasy.
Don't worry.
Your dad is with us.
- Where?
- In the coffee shop, at the back.
Hi.
You guys have banned our business.
Innocent children don't have toys.
Ask him what was in those toys.
We just need a signature.
Lift the ban,
so my men can resume work.
Impossible.
Tell him.
So, what have you decided?
Say no, Raj.
Why are you mum?
Why think so hard?
We have much to do together.
We are the future of these companies.
Sign it, man.
What are you doing?
Keep the pen down.
Raj, say no.
Say no, Raj.
Stop laughing.
Say no, goddamnit.
Sarang.
The answer is no.
And no means no.
I will not let you use
my cargo or anyone else's.
The ban will never be lifted.
Get out of my office.
Your father is a stubborn man,
but not more than me.
I will see you again.
Let's go, Vikrant.
- One cappuccino. Take away.
- Okay, sir.
Good afternoon.
Samara.
Why meet here?
I could have come down to your office.
By the way, thank you
for taking up this case.
Mr. Kakkad,
I cannot take your brother's case.
- Why?
- Because he is guilty.
How does that matter?
You can always twist the truth.
We have evidence that
he assaulted a woman.
What if I double your fee?
Our firm does not
defend clients like him.
You must have a price.
I don't.
And please don't upset me.
Or I will prosecute your brother.
Have a good day.
Say yes…
Or we have other means of persuasion.
Although I have no business here,
but you are breaking the law.
Section 268, committing public nuisance.
Don't stick your nose in this.
Let her go, mister,
or you'll be charged with section 354.
Misbehaving with a female is eve teasing.
Bloody Justice Chaudhury!
Take that.
Oh, God!
You will never learn!
Section 503, physical intimidation.
Which means, threatening.
Threatening?
Take that…
Great… Section 425.
Vandalizing public property.
I think you are hungry.
Rascal, you will teach me the law!
Take this!
Guys, where is the security?
You are going in for good.
Section 307, attempt to murder.
Leave me. Let's take this outside!
Bantu, right?
Government Law College, Amritsar.
You don't need a foreign degree
to learn justice.
I used every bit of my learnings today.
I will teach you the rest.
You are hired.
Thank you, madam.
Thank you.
Hey, stop!
Oh my God!
Stop it, silly.
Don't make me emotional.
Section 309, attempt to suicide.
Sorry, madam.
Now listen carefully.
Be it a good offer or bad,
when someone says no, it means…
No!
And when a girl says no, then it's a…
definite no!
Madam, we cannot hang around
after that legal class.
When the energy is high,
we should take an exit.
Good morning, madam.
What are you doing here?
Working out on my way to work.
In a suit?
While trying to keep up
with the pace of life,
I've no time to keep pace with myself.
And I also save some travel money.
- I read your file.
- Yes.
- People dream of going to Paris.
- Yes, yes.
- Driving a Ferrari.
You wrote you never dream
because you are afraid
they will be second-hand dreams.
What does that even mean?
- Do you have time?
- Move aside.
Two more rounds.
Six… not done.
Dad. College starts tomorrow.
I need some money to buy new clothes.
I told Randeep's son that
Bantu starts college tomorrow.
He gave me all his used clothes
without saying a word.
And that's not all, Nisha!
See…
He even gave me his perfume.
Smell it.
- Wow.
- Yes.
I will even smell second-hand now.
A whiff of it
and it feels like Raj is right here.
Do you want it or not?
Dad,
my shoes are torn.
Can you buy me these?
What is your shoe size?
Nine.
Mine is eight.
It will soften up once
you start wearing it.
The shoe and your brains.
You are worse than an enemy!
Giving me his shoes!
My legs will bleed.
Dad, Bantu wants a new bike.
Bantu.
I inherited this from your grandfather.
Take good care of it.
Bantu. No need to be so emotional.
Enough. Let me go.
No.
You are safe like this.
If I let go, it can be painful for you.
Madam, I never had
an amazing day in my life.
I am here now.
Expect a miracle.
I lost my mind when I realized
You entered the lanes of my heart
You are the answer to my prayers
You are the answer
To my prayers
That's the dream I had
Can't take my eyes
Off you when you smile
You even made the sun blush
I lost my mind when I realized
You entered the lanes of my heart
I feel lost
It's so quiet
How did I let you convince me?
You are the answer to my prayers
That's the dream I had
I seek the one
Who understands my feelings
Doesn't have to take me to the moon
But has a heart of gold
Doesn't have to be a prince
But someone who can make me laugh
Takes me in his arms when I come home
Makes me feel like his queen
I am just an ordinary girl
But love always brings a twist
I wish there's a guy out there
Who does what I say
If I ever find him
Never gonna let go
I am madly in love
I can't stop loving you
I steal a glance…
At you
I steal a glance at you
Your face dwells in my eyes
You are the answer to my prayers
That's the dream I had
I need you
I need…
I bring 24 apples for you every year.
Two apples every month.
I bought 600 apples for you in 25 years.
As the saying goes,
an apple a day keeps the doctor away.
Only if you can eat it.
But you don't wake up.
And the apples are wasted.
You are luckier than me.
You have been lying
in a coma for years.
And Randeep is paying
for your treatment.
Because you delivered his baby.
Hey.
Do you understand Hindi?
I don't know.
Is there anything I can do?
We will do, we will fight, we will win
We will win We will win
The Gita says the body is perishable,
not the soul.
Forsake this body.
Be free.
It will bring peace to you and me.
Doctor!
Anybody there?
- Doctor!
- Oh no.
Doc…
- Sister, hurry up.
- Yes, doctor.
Oxygen.
Check her blood pressure and heart rate.
Okay, doctor.
- Keep a check on her vitals.
- Yes, doctor.
- Is she going to wake up?
- Can't say.
But this has never happened before.
- Can she see?
- It's complicated.
- Can she hear?
- I'm not sure.
- Can she speak?
- Impossible.
- Thank God.
- What?
I mean, thank you.
Thank you.
Why did I have to wear
a sari for this lunch, Dad?
They are the Jindals, child.
I would have worn regular clothes
for any other occasion.
And if they ask you if you can cook,
tell them that you were
selected for Master Chef,
but you said no.
But why will they ask
me whether I can cook…
Wait!
Are we here to meet their son?
What would you prefer?
I would prefer a drink.
But that would upset Samara.
Dad, it's noon.
It must be nighttime
somewhere in the world.
Scotch, Gin. Glass of rosé.
What would you like to have?
- How about a black rum with soda...
- Tea.
We will have tea.
Tea?
So, are we gonna see the boy,
or should we elders decide?
Where is Raj?
Master Raj has arrived.
Park it.
Hello, uncle.
Wow! Swag with culture.
Not to mention the car.
Great.
The children might feel awkward
in front of us.
Raj. Take Samara for a walk.
Come.
Do you have a cigarette?
No. No smoking, no drinking, pure vegan.
How sweet.
Do you have a cigarette?
I only have the local brand, madam.
Marblo Nights.
Great.
Tell me more about your family.
Just the three of us.
But the third member keeps changing.
Dad is naughty.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
Me, my dad, and a new bottle every day.
Since mom's death, only alcohol
and sad songs could keep us company.
You know,
I had a girlfriend at the University.
But things didn't work out.
Have you ever been in a relationship?
Several.
Sometimes boys! Sometimes girls!
What?
Love doesn't care about gender.
Don't mind.
But even I don't want
to keep secrets from you.
Do you even believe in marriage?
I have only one problem.
Why should I leave my house
and my dad?
Girls have shed too many tears.
It's the guy's turn
to sit in the palanquin now,
and I will come riding on a horse!
Shall we?
Mom. Dad. Grandpa.
Samara is not a woman.
What nonsense is this?
She's a wonder woman!
I am ready to be the damsel in distress.
What?
Guys, I am ready for this marriage.
Wow, madam, you're getting married
in such a wealthy family.
He said yes.
How can anyone say no to you?
But I am not happy.
They are filthy rich.
Their home looks like a palace.
Even if you two fight,
the husband, and wife can
sleep in separate rooms.
Where there is love,
the size of the house
doesn't matter, Bantu.
I do have a small house.
Do you love me?
You belong in my dreams.
In reality, you are way beyond my reach.
One needs the heart to love not a house.
You will change your mind
when you see my house.
Bantu, I really like you.
I don't believe in all that.
I believe in love.
Okay.
Then let's fall in love.
Will you be able to?
Of course.
Now I feel embarrassed, madam.
Madam...
Can you stop calling me madam?
Why don't you ever wear a pant?
Sorry.
Did I hit too hard?
Yes.
But I am enjoying it now.
Madam…
Baby. Babe. BooBoo…
Call me anything you like.
Just don't call me madam.
I'll need some time, madam.
I'll need some time…
Boo Boo.
I wonder what spell you have cast on me
I am ready to follow you
Wherever you take me
Since the day I met you
I don't need any friends
You are so cute
I would rather call you cuteness
I will take care of you
You are responsibility
Tell your family, now it's my turn
You are going to be all mine now
I've taken a detour towards your lane
I am cute and you're one in a million
For you, I dumped my other girlfriend
You're so cute
And I'm one in a million
I am cute and you're one in a million
For you, I dumped my other girlfriend
I wonder what spell you have cast on me
Let's start this love story
Come tease me, beloved
I don't say yes to everyone
But I said yes to you
I will go with you, beloved
- There is no lover like me
- Is there anyone?
- I am a classic
- Is there anyone tall and dark like me?
- Is there anyone?
- A crazy maniac
- Someone to challenge your dad
- Is there anyone?
And beg him if need be
Is there anyone?
No fat fat, left to right
Like dhoom chak chak
Dhoom dhoom chak
Last night I told my friends
I've stolen the moon from the stars
I am going to keep you away
From prying eyes
I've taken a detour towards your lane
I am cute and you're one in a million
For you, I dumped my other girlfriend
You're so cute
And I'm one in a million
I am cute and you're one in a million
For you, I dumped my other girlfriend
I wonder what spell you have cast on me
I am ready to follow you
Wherever you take me
Yes, sir.
Okay, sir.
Excuse me.
He is ready to see you.
Hello, Mr. Randeep.
Since the children couldn't agree,
I thought I should come
to meet the father.
My decision won't change at any cost.
Randeep!
I keep extending my hand in friendship,
and you keep ignoring it.
I am not scared of you.
Next time get an appointment.
Not fair, Mr. Randeep.
I've incurred far too many losses
because of you.
Sarang, your toys are stealing
the children's innocence.
And you, my business.
My principles are far more important
than business.
Isn't there any solution?
There is.
Shut down your business.
So you won't lift the ban?
Then I must get rid of you.
My dad will never agree to this.
That's why we came to meet Raj's dad.
We will tell him the truth about us.
Worst case scenario,
he will give one tight slap!
It's the least you can do for love.
There is no one here.
He is a busy man.
Must be in a meeting.
Sir.
Sir. Sir.
- Sir.
Somebody help!
- I'll call an ambulance.
- No, call his driver.
Okay.
Sir. Sir.
Shit!
Where are the stairs?
Bantu, he is losing blood.
We must inform his family.
Sir. Sir.
Hey…
Sir.
Open it.
That's our car.
And we stabbed him.
Let him go.
Sir. Sir.
I will inform the family.
Don't worry. I'll call someone.
Who was that?
Ran…
- What?
- Ran…
Ran…
- Randeep?
- Yes.
Do you know him?
Wha…
What happened to him?
Someone…
He met with a small accident.
Don't worry.
He will be fine.
Is he…
Is he your father…
Unfortunately, he's not my father.
That's my father.
There.
- Tell me.
- He is not…
Your father…
Ran…
Your words won't alter the truth.
- No.
- Take rest.
Please sit, sir.
I'll check where madam is.
He is not your father.
He isn't.
I think you are not feeling well.
I will call the doctor.
Wait… listen…
- I'll be right back.
- Hear me out.
- Please, calm down.
- Listen to me…
He is not your father!
He is Valmiki.
How do you know my father?
Valmiki is not your father.
Randeep.
Randeep is your father.
I don't understand what you are saying.
I exchanged you with my own hands.
You weren't breathing
after you were born.
You are the Jindal family prince.
The real prince.
I took the silver spoon from you
and changed your destiny.
My sin doesn't let me live or die.
We must tell your father the truth.
I owe this to him.
Go call your father.
I must tell him the truth.
I want to tell him that you are his son.
Call your father.
Call Randeep.
Call him. I want to tell him
that you are his son.
Call, Randeep. Call him.
I want to tell him.
- Call him. Call him.
- He is inside...
Why is this patient here?
- Sister.
- Yes, doctor.
What are you doing?
Why is this patient here?
- Let's shift her to critical care.
- Okay, doctor.
Kailash, how is Randeep?
I spoke with the doctors.
His heart is intact,
but he's lost blood.
Everything else is fine.
I don't think so, Kailash.
What about security?
What happened?
Who is he?
That's Bantu.
He works in my office.
If it wasn't for him,
Uncle would have never
made it to the hospital.
Thank you.
Kailash, give him some money
and tell him to leave.
It's okay, Bantu.
Don't mind her.
Thank you, son.
Come.
Just give me a minute.
I've been working for them for 25 years.
But they don't even
let me stay in the same room.
All rich people are the same.
They will keep reminding
you of your place.
We are not their family.
We should stay away.
That's how the world works!
He is the king
and we are his servants.
She is no more.
Peace be with her.
- I will tell everyone.
- Who will believe you?
- Did you know her?
- No.
Look at her lying like an orphan.
No family, nor any friends.
This is definitely
because of her bad karma.
As the saying goes…
God sees all.
What are you staring at?
Do you have anything to say?
Shut up!
Out of all days,
this scooter had to break down today!
Not only did you slap your father,
but you are also keeping mum.
Don't you have anything to say?
You are not my real father.
I am not your real father!
If I am not your father,
then where did you come from?
Did you fall from the sky?
No.
You pulled me down from heaven
and slammed me on the ground.
That nurse was in a coma for 25 years.
Are you going to believe
the nonsense she says?
I never mentioned any nurse.
I am the Jindal family heir.
Randeep is my father.
Yes or no?
I've been hearing
your bullshit all my life.
Speak up!
Now!
I just wanted to see my son happy.
And see Randeep's son unhappy.
So, you were punishing
me for the last 25 years.
What harm did I ever cause you?
Will you tell
the Jindal family everything?
Please.
Don't tell anyone.
Are you crazy?
What will I get by telling them?
Money? Wealth? Car?
Screw that!
What's interesting is,
you know that I know.
What did you get
from learning the truth?
Freedom.
I always wondered,
that no matter what I do,
I can never impress my father.
But now I have my answer.
Now I am free.
Free.
Valmiki.
I used to cringe seeing you.
But now I feel pity for you.
Because you can't
tell him he's your son,
and I won't acknowledge
you as my father!
It's the end of my exile.
Time to return home.
The prince
- Valmiki.
- Yes.
I want to meet your son.
I want to hug him and say thank you.
Excuse me.
This nurse and I treated your son-in-law!
You should be hugging and thanking us.
Who are you?
Hello, I am an open-heart surgeon, okay?
For an open heart surgeon,
you have a not-so-open heart.
- This is no way to speak.
- Sir. Sir.
Is he crazy? Bloody oldies!
Never upset your doctor or driver.
If they twist the injection
or steering wheel to the wrong side,
then it's game over.
So, calm down.
You should have been here yesterday.
Where were you?
No one called me.
Your father is in the hospital.
Do you need an invitation
to come and see him?
And why did you bring
a bouquet like a foreigner?
Master Raj, balloons were a better idea.
We should have gone with the balloons.
What is the billed amount?
1,20,000, sir.
Round it up to one million.
Sir, 1,20,000 can be
rounded off to 1,50,000.
- Not one million.
- Don't forget our old deal.
You get five percent.
I get the rest.
God bless you.
Plus GST.
You're too much, sir.
Consider it done.
Sir, avoid t-shirts for some time.
- Shirts will be more comfortable.
- Why?
God. There he goes again.
My son-in-law looks handsome in t-shirts.
That has nothing to do with this.
And this is not fashion advice,
it's medical advice.
Sir, shirt…
T-shirt.
Muscle strain.
Get it?
Anyway, he needs positivity around him.
Not negative people like us.
Like that boy who brought him
to the hospital.
Call him.
- Sister.
- Yes, doctor.
Here.
Great.
Your son-in-law's
blood pressure has become normal,
as soon as I mentioned that boy.
See, 120/80. Perfect.
Sir.
How will his presence affect his health?
See for yourself.
But never believe an MBBS,
M.D, FRCS doctor like me.
You guys keep questioning my abilities!
- Doctor...
- Don't touch.
Last time you were against him.
Now you want me to call him here.
- Answer him.
- Go ahead.
Sir, just give me a chance.
Even we doctors have children.
My son?
His BP will spike at this rate.
Go, get him.
He's at work.
Tell him to take a few hours off.
It's not a government job.
Tell him to take the whole day off.
They will fire him.
Tell him to quit then.
It's his bread and butter.
Send him over to my house.
I will take care of his needs.
- He's talking rubbish!
- Whenever I call him,
you always make some excuse.
What is your problem?
No problem, sir.
- Then what's the problem?
- No problem.
Then call him.
- Call him.
- Call him quickly, please.
The battery is down.
Give me his number.
I will call him.
I'll call him.
Listen, Jindal sir wants to meet you.
But I won't let you set foot in here.
Like the gully boys say,
"My time will come."
But your time will never come.
As soon as you hang up,
the doctor will call me.
How do you know the doctor is inside?
Where are you?
Check outside the gate.
I am here to stay for good
I will be everyone's favorite
What did you do with the doctor?
He didn't want to look at you earlier,
and now he's asking for an appointment.
Relax.
When you kidnap someone's child,
he's bound to react like that.
Did you kidnap his son?
Yes. That's him.
SUPERHERO
- Hello.
- Is he coming?
Yes, sir. He is.
You have been seeing
your son for 25 years.
Now I will meet my father
for the first time.
With little dreams
And years of accounts
Everyone's friend is here
Take a good look, make some noise
I am here now
From rags to riches
Like a spear of destruction
He is reaching for the sky
Shining so bright
Put your glasses on
Witness his glory now
I am here to stay for good
I will be everyone's favorite
I am not innocent nor naive
But I am your best friend forever
I promise, I will be…
The prince
I am the… prince
I've longed to be back home
It's been a decade now
I can feel the love shower
On me as they open their hearts
I can hear laughter on one side
and sighs coming from another
This is where I played my games
I can feel the blessings of my mother
Someone will finally feed me
My childhood will return
One with a true and kind heart
With the key to your destiny
He is called
The prince
I am not innocent nor naive
But I am your best friend forever
I promise
I will be…
The prince
I am the… prince
My son is here.
Where is my son?
- Relax.
- I cannot.
He is at the ice cream parlor.
I'll leave in a jiffy.
I didn't pay for the ice cream.
I will.
He also has my headphones.
I'll buy you new ones.
Who kidnaps a fat kid?
Bloody criminal.
Your father kept you
away like some treasure.
We never met.
Come here.
You have strong arms.
That day, you didn't just
save my son-in-law,
you saved this family's honor,
the Jindal empire,
and our pride.
You work for Raj's fiancée, don't you?
- Yes, sir.
- Does she pay well?
The contract said 25,000.
But after deducting taxes
I get 3000 in hand, sir.
I will give you 50,000. Tax-free.
Come work for me.
Sir, you are spoiling
him with more money.
He will get spoilt if you give him,
but I will make him someone worthwhile.
Will you come to work for me?
Of course, sir.
Choose any room,
with a desk and computer.
But what will be my job?
Exactly, what can he do?
He will hang out with me.
I am a lonely old man.
Right, buddy?
Yes, buddy.
Buddy?
You don't know what you are saying!
I have a lot to do.
I have to meet the other rich people.
Share a cup of green
tea with Jindal sir.
I am busy, Valmiki. Get lost.
Rascal.
Can't believe all this is mine.
You know I am a simple man.
I don't like to lie or cheat people.
Unbelievable, sir.
Preaching what you don't practice.
I have a lot to learn from you.
Who are you?
Bantu, with love.
And in hatred,
still Bantu!
- What is this?
- Eggs Benedict for master Raj.
Master Raj's eggs.
Make the same for me, starting tomorrow.
But I will have ten eggs.
Okay.
He looks like the scrambled egg type.
Get me a cup of tea!
Excuse me.
I am not a servant.
I am Arun.
A family member of this family since 1990.
Why didn't I see you earlier?
Because I am the busy type.
I have my pilates classes.
Can I? Thank you.
These rich people are so weird.
Butlers dressed in suits,
owners dressed in shorts.
- Sir.
- Hey, how did you like the house?
Like paradise.
It's so beautiful that I feel I am dead.
But I didn't like one thing.
You guys are not united,
that's why he was attacked.
By the way, what did the police say?
We filed a complaint,
but Sarang is an unpredictable guy.
I don't deal with guys like him.
But I can.
What?
Let's go talk to him.
Shall we?
Didn't you say you wanted to hang out?
Right, buddy?
Sir!
- Who are you?
- Grandpa.
I mean, he's as old as your grandpa.
You use his planes to
smuggle your goods around.
But you don't know who he is.
The founder. Aditya Jindal.
- Show some respect.
- How did you guys get to Mauritius?
We flew.
I flew business class,
and my buddy was in first.
Though we had a smooth landing
but faced some turbulence
when we got here.
Get the car.
Let's go back.
No, sir. We came all the way.
How…
Same feeling.
The hand print.
Who pushed him?
That boy saved Randeep.
But who will save you?
"The prince."
The prince
Pick up the crates. Hurry up.
Who pushed him?
Where did he come from?
Who pushed him? Who?
Who touched him? Tell me.
- Was it you? Did you touch him?
- No.
- Did you push him?
- No, I didn't push him.
Did you push him?
How dare you!
Who touched him?
How dare you touch him?
Yes?
Gather uncle's stuff.
Hurry up. Give it to me.
The prince
Chilled coconut water.
Especially for you, sir.
Eau de cologne towel, sir.
It will calm you down.
Who was it? Who pushed him?
What do you think, sir?
We all pushed him?
You already punched
the guy who pushed him.
There he is.
Folded up like a new Samsung phone.
Where is your boss?
He is inside.
But you need to yell to call him.
Sir!
It's very clear.
He says your brother is a scoundrel!
But his case is weak
because he doesn't have evidence.
I came here and threw
your men around like ping-pong balls.
There's no proof of that, as well.
So, henceforth no more violence.
That's all we had to say.
Buddy, that's the end of our hangout.
Let's go or we'll miss our flight.
Are you going to say something
or just stare, son?
You can write if you don't want to say it.
Bantuka4@gmail.com
Shouldn't this boat be in the water?
It's a car, Bantu. Not a boat!
What is this model called?
RR.
Looks like it's Rajamouli's car.
Wow.
The tuxedo and the car look rented.
Can we take a selfie
before I give you my two cents?
Nice umbrella.
Don't let me get my hands on it.
I can be reckless with it.
Let's go, we'll miss our flight.
This car is a beauty.
You should get a couple of these, buddy.
You called, sir?
Bantu, come.
We haven't spoken since you got here.
Tell me, sir.
What you did for
a total stranger is commendable.
Thank you.
If not me then who else?
But I am no one to you.
You are.
What?
Boss.
You know, Bantu.
The most difficult battles in life,
are the ones against your own family.
What did my son-in-law say?
A lot.
He's mad about the
dispute with my daughter, isn't he?
He's bound to be.
They haven't spoken for seven years.
Did he say anything else?
He didn't, but you just did.
Buddy, this family has issues.
During tough times,
your family is your strength.
But when your own family
leaves you stranded,
who do you turn to?
Hey, Dad.
Morning, uncle J.
They are beyond help.
And he will never understand.
He is a weird guy.
No one knows what's on his mind.
Just for once, I want to see him
explode with anger.
Then I can die peacefully.
He will explode,
and you don't have to die.
You know, buddy.
Poor had only one thing.
Grief.
And the rich took over that as well.
Hey, you have work to do,
and you are out here smoking.
Don't do that.
These people are naive.
So naive that you swapped their baby.
Valmiki, I am the owner of
this building, this garden, and you.
Talking in English feels better
when you are dressed like this.
Now get out!
Otherwise, I will deduct your salary!
- Hey!
Get lost.
Come on.
Rascal.
Dad first brought Randeep
and gave him the entire business.
And he's been torturing us ever since.
Now he's got this new guy…
Who will screw us sooner or later!
There is something about him.
We should offer him our friendship.
Nice boy.
An everyday expenditure worth 1,50,000?
Twenty-five thousand on fuel.
There are several cars in the office.
Twenty-five thousand for snacks.
We have several poor employees.
Fifty thousand for coffee.
Are we buying Starbucks?!
I am discussing accounts,
and you are winking at me.
They did.
And I forwarded it to you
like a WhatsApp text.
Why did they wink at you?
Because 1,00,000 goes
to their personal account.
But why did they wink at you?
They made an offer to me, as well.
A cut in the home expenditure.
Hand me my cane.
Why?
So, I can beat them up!
- Let's chase them.
- Uncle please, trust me…
- What are you doing?
- Yashu…
- What's going on here?
Uncle is beating us up
because of this outsider.
What happened, Dad?
These two are siphoning money
from the company account.
They have a share.
Who told you this?
- Him.
- And how do you know he's not lying?
Because he never lies.
I see.
So, you only speak the truth?
Why will my brother
steal from his own company?
He earns two million every month.
He spends two million
at the bat of an eyelid on IJL.
IJL?
"Indian Jua League."
He's the Chris Gayle of IJL.
Do you gamble?
Only on weekends.
- Only on weekends.
- Yeah.
Because he's busy
with Sheena on weekdays.
Who is Sheena?
I don't know.
Are you guys going
to believe everything he says?
Sheena sent a text on your phone.
"Call me once free."
You dropped it while trying to escape.
So what? I'll call her when I am free.
He's creating unwanted controversy.
I see. In the end, it says,
"Miss you baby."
- Baby?
- Yes.
And she also sent a kiss emoji.
Show me.
Don't, sir.
These pictures are too explicit.
- Really?
- Yes, his.
Kiss and heart emojis are so common.
In fact, uncle,
I even send it to my driver.
Why are you people overreacting?
Where were you when
he was doing all this?
Normally you are always glued to him.
Are women ever going to change?
When she couldn't slap her husband,
she slapped her younger brother.
So outdated, man.
Bloody leech.
Oh no. Time's up.
Goodnight, sir.
Goodnight, madam.
Look, child.
Don't ask any stupid questions.
I mean, how did you
get stabbed or where?
How big was the knife?
They won't tolerate such small talk.
- They are rich people.
- Hey, Samara.
Long time, short skirt. Cute.
Who is he?
Dad, this is Bantu.
My assistant.
Personal assistant.
But, why is he getting
so personal with you?
He was looking for the key.
Here it is. Park the car.
Haven't told your family yet?
Told me what?
Your daughter has no interest in Raj.
- What?
- Actually, we are deeply in love.
How deep?
So deep,
that someday you might have
to get us married, Dad.
Why is he calling me dad?
Samara's dad is my dad, as well.
Come on, Samara.
Always embarrassing me!
Let's go.
- Blessings?
- Move…
Keep walking, and don't look back.
Morning, Inspector.
Is Jindal sir at home?
He's gone out.
Anything urgent?
The Commissioner wants to know
whether Randeep needs security?
He doesn't need any security
as long as I am here.
Who are you?
Bantu. I work here.
What work?
The usual. Bantuka4…
Netflix and chill on free wifi.
But who are you to make decisions
about his personal security?
Actually, I am Randeep's real son.
It's true, sir.
If he's Dhirubhai, I am his Mukesh.
If he's Mufasa, then I am Simba.
If he's Amrinder, I am Mahinder.
- Dhoni?
- Bahubali.
Morning, Officer.
Hello.
Who is he now?
For the last 25 years,
they believe that he is their son.
25 years?
And when did you find out?
- Recently.
- How?
The nurse told me.
She and the guy hiding behind
the pillar who looks like a pickpocket,
who's eavesdropping on our conversation…
Together they swapped me with Raj.
I got this pathetic life,
and that avocado became their heir.
And you saw this with your own eyes?
No, sir. I was only six hours old then.
- The nurse told me.
- When?
Just now.
Why didn't she tell you this 25 years ago?
- Because she was in a coma.
- Then why tell you now?
Because now she woke up from her coma.
Why did she tell you?
Who else could she tell?
Why not tell Mr. Randeep?
She was going to.
Then why didn't she?
Because the poor soul died
before she could.
Wait a minute.
Does anyone else know
about this except for you?
Yes, sir. You do.
But I will keep this a secret.
I will sacrifice.
If you are so big-hearted,
why come here?
This is my house.
If I don't look out for them,
then who will?
Bantu, give me the keys.
I've to get to the office urgently.
See you in the evening. Bye.
Who is she?
His fiancée.
If you're happy
And you know it clap your hands
Why was she kissing you?
We are in love!
Does that avocado know about this?
Come on, sir.
If he knew, why would he marry her?
If you're happy
And you know it clap your hands
Does Mr. Randeep know
what's going on in his house?
We were going to tell him,
but then this happened.
And because of which, now you are here.
Good morning, Inspector Yadav.
Sir, do you run background checks
on your employees?
Of course, we do.
Then why did you hire him?
Yadav, this family has everything,
except for one thing which this boy has.
What?
Brains of a businessman,
the courage of a warrior.
Hope to never see you again.
This is not your car.
Okay.
I guess I will have to resign.
Thanks for coming in last minute.
Sir, I know all
the romantic spots in Delhi.
If madam and you want to go?
Maybe after dinner. What say, Samara?
Don't mind,
but you two look cute as a couple.
Thanks, Bunty.
Bantu.
But since you're my boss,
you can call me anything.
Where do you plan
to stay after the wedding?
Home or abroad?
Anywhere except for Wuhan!
- Sir…
- What are you trying to do?
You want me to get married to him?
That's what you want?
Bantu, I am tired now.
Why are we hiding it
if we haven't done anything wrong?
Do you both know each other?
Yeah.
We used to secretly
hold hands in the office.
We played footsie.
Actually, we are madly in love.
Aren't we?
Footsie.
Where did you all play footsie together?
- When did this happen?
- Wait for a second.
I am talking to you.
Why don't you say something?
- How?
- Like this.
What?
It's a good thing
the driver didn't show up,
or I would have never found out.
I am so sorry, Raj.
We should have told you earlier.
Actually, we tried to tell you,
but, other things came up.
I really didn't mean to hurt you.
Hey, it's alright.
These things happen.
I have dropped a text to Cadbury.
He said he's gonna make me
a chocolate milkshake.
Always makes me feel better.
And you two look nice together.
I am happy for you guys.
All the best.
Is that it?
You are convinced?
Pardon me.
You are so easily convinced?
Doesn't this make you mad?
I don't know.
How could you not know
if you are mad or not?
That's the problem with rich kids.
Everyone's confused.
Either about love, career, or emotions.
But you cannot be blamed for this,
it's your family.
When you were supposed to ride a cycle,
they flew you in airplanes.
Other children went abroad to study,
you went there for vacations.
Look at yourself.
At home, you're a mama's boy,
your uncles, and your servants
accompany you to work.
Your father has no confidence in you.
And you have nothing in common
with your grandpa except for his surname.
You use a dinky car to go from one room
to another in your own home.
But you cannot be blamed for this.
You demanded one toy,
and you got an entire shop.
You asked for change,
and they gave you a credit card.
You asked for milk, they gave you Kheer,
that too, with almond milk.
Now that's nepotism.
Who are you?
Don't you have dreams of your own?
Your fiancée kissed me,
and you're confused about
whether you are mad or not.
I am.
I am getting mad.
Then fight for your identity.
Attack your family. Take charge.
Won't look nice if I attack my family.
Not a real fight.
Show him who the real Raj is.
- Mom.
- Are you asking for chocolate?
- Dad!
- Think bigger.
- Granddad!
- Lose respect.
Grandpa!
- Little more.
- Jindal.
You are Sunny not Bobby.
- Jindal…
- Now you are Dharmendra.
Bloody Jindal!
- What happened, my son?
- This…
This love is how you
snatched away my personality.
Life is so comfortable
that I hardly have any problems.
So, what is the problem?
- What's the name of your grandfather?
- Kishenchand.
Bloody Kishenchand's son.
Hey, Kishenchand's grandson!
How would you feel
if someone addressed you like this?
What rude behavior is this?
I has been facing this all my life.
"I have."
Funny.
See? Even my Hindi is bad.
My immunity is low.
All I have is virtual friends.
And this is your fault.
What is wrong with you?
My eyes have opened, Mom.
Thanks to Bunty.
Grandpa was the only one
who asked me what I want to be.
When I said I want to be a chef,
you guys said "Aww, so cute"
and laughed at me.
I wanted to try photography,
and be a pilot.
But son, you can't be everything.
But I can try.
But you guys are so rich,
you didn't give me a chance to struggle.
Because if I failed,
you guys would be embarrassed.
Mom, if I had topped the university,
what would I be?
The Jindal Group's CEO.
And what if I had returned
without a degree?
- The Jindal Group's CEO.
- Exactly.
I've been noticing all my life.
You guys know how to give orders, not ask.
No one asked Samara if she wants
to even marry me or not.
You just said she should
be happy with my decision.
My decision!
Hello! She loves Bunty.
Samara and Bantu?
Yes, they have been having an affair,
and you know what, honestly,
I am happy for them.
I was sinning.
I am not a love breaker, Mom.
From now on I'll make my own decisions!
Hope that's okay.
Cadbury, get me your finest scotch.
Yes, master Raj.
Your Raj has grown up.
You're smoking cigarettes in the garden
after canceling my son's wedding!
They were all mine, to begin with.
As for your son,
if I tell everyone the truth,
he will be kicked out.
Kicked out.
His mother will become his boss,
his father his CEO,
and an ordinary servant
like you will become his father.
Rascal!
Me?
You are a rascal, Valmiki.
Bloody child swapper!
Don't spoil my mood. Get lost.
Out. Out.
Your beauty is going
to peak in the next two years.
Oh, stop it!
Is that what you see here?
Do you go to the gym?
Yes? True Fitness.
You are going to find
true love in True Fitness.
Do you know anyone with
a big heart and bigger biceps?
Yes.
Jatin.
My trainer.
He was Mr. Vasant Vihar.
Very soon he will pop the question.
- What?
- Shall we go…
away from this Mount Kailash?
In the valley of my biceps.
Are you blushing?
Stop this nonsense!
- This Bantu will ruin my marriage.
- No!
He is a home breaker.
No, that's not it.
And who is Jatin?
Jatin is my trainer…
Read.
That's all for today. Come with me.
No, Dad. Go ahead.
I don't need to see your hand.
- It's all written on your face.
- What?
You don't get along with your husband.
Come, Bantu. Get up.
Come.
Wait, Dad.
Why do you feel that way?
The doors of your room are always closed.
Why are you so interested?
Whether their doors are closed or not?
How does it matter to you?
When the couple is newly married,
one can understand.
There is much to talk about.
But if the doors remain
closed after 30 years of marriage.
That means there is silence inside.
Regardless of how busy sir is,
he makes it a point to return by 6.
To prove that this family
means everything to him.
But he does this, not by will,
but out of guilt.
What guilt?
Ayesha.
He had an affair seven years ago.
And since then you two
have been living like this.
You don't want to fix
the relationship or part ways.
Unfortunately, everyone knows about it,
but no one wants to talk about it.
Why? Because you fear society.
Buddy, you could have said something.
Or at least get them divorced.
What do you think?
Telling the truth will make you great!
If a lie can save someone's life,
it's better than the truth.
If you ever love someone,
you will know how important a lie is.
The true strength
of love lies in honesty.
Try telling the truth, sir.
It will be painful,
but it will fortify your relationship.
It's six o'clock, sir.
My time is up.
Goodnight.
It wasn't her fault.
It was yours.
You were married.
You had a family.
And what was my fault?
That I always gave my best
to this relationship?
For the sake of our love,
I went against my father.
I fought against the entire world.
And you broke my heart in return.
Guilt alone doesn't pardon your mistake.
You have to apologize for that.
Randeep,
you couldn't even
say sorry in seven years.
Don't you think I deserve that?
I was ashamed to look you in the eye.
To talk to you.
I was ashamed of myself.
It took me long enough, isn't it Yashu?
Forgive me.
I am sorry.
Hello.
Why isn't my daughter reacting?
They fought for seven years.
Give them five minutes.
I am sorry.
I am so sorry.
I am sorry, Yashu.
They are hugging, buddy.
Congratulations, buddy.
Get some rest
and let me have my dinner in peace.
Cadbury, what brings you here?
Good morning, Bantu.
All good?
Jindal sir sent this for you.
Said he'll be very glad
if you can attend.
Don't be late.
COME HOME
The things you do tickle my heart
Your mischiefs bring me joy
Everyone's here
Looking elegant
Make every heart skip a beat
Oh, yes
Climbing over the walls
The boys are here
Glow like the moon
And light up the night
Every moment
I don't spend with you is a waste
When you held my hand
Leaving the world behind
It gave me an overwhelming feeling
The things you do tickle my heart
Your mischiefs bring me joy
The things you do
Tickle my heart
Your mischiefs
Bring me joy
Believe me when I say
That I prayed
The dreams of my loved ones to come true
Every breath I take,
Is another praise for you
There is no dearth of it
Since I've been blessed with your love
It gave me an overwhelming feeling
The things you do tickle my heart
Your mischiefs bring me joy
I want to ward off the evil eyes
Of the apple of my eyes
I can't stand it
If any harm comes to them
The things you do tickle my heart
Your mischiefs bring me joy
The auspicious evening has arrived
But I am a little scared
If this evening comes to an end
I will die
Hello, aunty.
Shall we?
I am fed up now.
All I wanted was a simple signature
so that my men could return to work.
Now sign the documents,
and send your son over
to the location I sent you.
Along with shares worth 50 billion.
This is an old cliched threat.
But if you call the police,
you will never see your wife again.
Raj, you won't go.
This is risky.
I will deal with him.
- Give it to me.
- Dad, I will go!
I can do this.
Raj,
he is right.
A man like Sarang cannot be trusted.
You are naive, son.
You know nothing about the real world.
All I know is when it's about my mother,
we don't discuss, we act.
Where is my mother?
What happened here?
The breeze was blowing slowly.
Old songs were playing on the radio.
My boss was preparing
to leave the country.
His brother was drinking on the rocks.
The guys were busy playing cards.
With great expectations,
we were looking at the gate.
Everything was going as planned.
In the next 15 minutes,
we were supposed
to receive shares worth 50 billion.
And then…
The wind turned violent.
Songs became muffled.
We were hit by a storm.
A hurricane!
I am worried.
We shouldn't have let Raj go alone.
He will be fine.
The prince
So silky.
Which shampoo do you use?
You little back alley rodent.
You always show up to defend this family.
What is your relationship
with this woman?
A child's first home,
a boy's first love.
The most pious relationship
in the whole world.
What?
Don't ask questions
in the middle of the action.
Oh no, just missed it.
Why do you carry an umbrella
all the time, brother?
Now you made a mess.
Who is this, Bantu?
Where did he come from?
No one knows.
He blew away the guys
and our expectations!
I brought him home
because I knew the truth.
He is your son
and the heir to Aditya Jindal.
I thought he will tell the truth
to get this house,
the money, and the business.
But no…
he doesn't want anything.
Valmiki,
do you have anything to say?
Nothing, sir.
In case my son has unintentionally
made any mistakes,
please forgive him.
That's all.
Is that all?
Yes, sir.
That's all?
Is that all, Valmiki?
Is it?
He is my grandson.
My blood.
He is my successor!
You took him away from us
and now you're choosing to keep mum.
I heard the nurse talking
to him in the hospital.
Ever since I found out what you did,
I have controlled myself.
Why didn't you get mad?
I pity him.
He has two sons,
but no one to call him father.
The joy of swapping
the children soon turned into fear.
He hasn't slept peacefully
for last 25 years.
Let him go, sir.
You aren't upset with any of us.
You have no greed.
Then why come here?
Parents are not the only ones
who wish happiness for their children.
Children want to see
their parents happy, as well.
But when a mother
has been deprived of joy,
how can a son be happy?
As long as I am here,
how can I see my father weak?
How can I see my grandpa in pain?
When I realized that you guys
are going through a difficult time,
I couldn't just stand by.
Those who abused my
father behind his back
will fall at his feet.
My mother will be his best friend.
Randeep can never lose
and I won't let him.
I came here
to turn this place into a real paradise.
My job here is done.
I don't want anything else, sir.
I told you…
I told you how my son will be.
Just like him.
Exactly like him.
Sir, please calm down.
Calm down.
Calm down, Dad.
Say that again.
Dad.
Calm down, please.
Come on, let's go see Yashu.
- Let's tell Yashu.
- No.
Don't do that.
What about Raj?
What will you tell him?
Twenty-five years ago he separated
two children from their mother.
Rectifying this mistake will
separate another mother and son again.
As your son, I request you.
Please don't break my mother's heart.
Bantu,
you are one reality I don't like.
Because you are better than my son.
Women can accept
a stranger as their husband.
But their children can only
be the ones they give birth to.
Today
when you arrived instead of Raj,
you not only saved me…
but him, as well.
And anyone who protects
and defends my family
is just like a son to me.
Thank you, Bunty.
Did I do the right thing?
You always do the right thing.
What happened, Valmiki?
Why do you look stressed?
You should be happy.
Your son has made you proud.
What years of foreign education
couldn't teach Raj,
you taught it to Bantu
in the old alleys of Delhi.
Make my Raj just like your Bantu.
Let him start from scratch.
In fact, let him stay with you.
And, in the next five years,
transform him from a clerk to the CEO.
It hasn't arrived yet?
I guess the bus is running late.
When I was a kid,
you frenziedly told me stories.
But your lap was the only place
I could fall asleep.
You can't walk properly,
but you taught me to sprint.
My grandpa simply loves
my rude personality,
and it's all thanks to you.
They may have brought me
into this world,
but you raised me.
Was it a compliment or sarcasm?
I learned that from you, as well.
Compliment wrapped in sarcasm.
The Jindal family grandson's
riding a scooter.
It's 125cc. Gives the best mileage.
And one doesn't have to worry about
changing gears. What else can one ask for?
Good for you!
It's not mine.
It's yours.
Mister, can I get a lift?
We are headed to the same place.
Wait.
Valmiki take a left and right
and stop at the food stall.
We'll have an egg wrap
on our way home.
The chickens are going to curse you.
How many eggs are you going to eat?
Wow! You swapped their son,
and didn't get cursed,
why will I get cursed for eating eggs?