Once upon a time many years ago,
there was a prosperous kingdom
whose ruler was the brave
Vikramaditya.
A terrible drought fell upon
the land.
People were dying of hunger
and thirst.
Vikramaditya was deeply upset
by his people's plight.
A sorcerer then came to the King
and said:
"Vikramaditya, in the Vindhyachal caves,
a body hangs from a banyan tree.
"The great Betaal lives within the tree.
"Bring Betaal to me so I shall burn him
and make your kingdom drought free."
Hearing this, the King set off
on his journey.
The journey was long and filled
with treacherous obstacles.
"Beware! Betaal will narrate stories
to you.
"And ask you questions about the story.
"If you stay silent, yet know
the answer,
"your head will explode
into thousand pieces.
"And if you answer correctly,
"Betaal with escape again."
Vikramaditya, there is only
one way out of this dilemma.
Don't get taken in by Betaal's stories.
Shall I tell you a story?
Pappu, is this the place?
- Don't be shy.
- Yes, sir. This is it.
I've done my job,
now it's over to you.
If they're not there,
you've had it.
Don't worry, sir. Believe me,
they're in there.
Pappu, here. Keep this.
- Lie low for a few weeks.
- OK, sir.
Can we trust Pappu?
Do we go in?
Who knows how many they are.
Shall we wait for backup?
I hate hanging around.
- Is this the time to show up?
- Sorry, sir.
We were held up sorting out
the mess at KKC College.
- Who's the raw meat?
- He just got posted here. Totally raw!
Sir, my name is Deepak.
- Welcome to UP Police STF, Deepak.
- Thank you, sir.
- Married?
- No, sir.
- Girlfriend? Boyfriend?
Prabhakar sir, he has a lonely life, and
you're not taking care of your teammate.
- He won't like our methods.
- Why?
Deepak looks weak.
Had any experience, Deepak?
Or...
No, sir. Never got the chance.
You'll get lucky today, Deepak,
if you make it out alive.
- Stay at the back.
- Yes, sir.
So, both brothers are late.
Forgive us, sir. We had to deal
with a property loan.
Father borrowed money against some land,
we paid it back in full today.
Two worthy sons.
How much did you lose on your bet
this time?
Everything, sir! But I'll win big
on the next cricket match.
Wow!
- Informed the local police?
- Done, sir.
Ansari, tuck your belly in.
Or else they'll see your belly
before they see your gun.
Ready?
You first.
You'd be dead, Deepak.
Sorry, sir.
Prabhakar-ji!
Sir, please...I surrender.
Too late for that.
You run out of hiding places,
then you decide to surrender.
I wasn't thinking straight, sir.
Where is Vedha?
I swear. I don't know.
- Where is Vedha?
- Don't shoot!
I'll give you whatever you want.
Such as?
Money, sir. Just name your price.
Money is so overrated, Muni.
It can change lives,
but it can't buy one.
Tell me a joke!
Huh?
Know any jokes?
I remember a joke.
Sir, how much is two plus two?
Four.
Six.
- How?
- By mistake.
Not funny.
I'll tell you another.
An elephant and an ant...
Don't be a wise guy.
They're new gang members.
Take them to hospital.
Yes, sir.
Abbas, why the hell did you stop?
Deepak, this is a crime scene,
not the Nimbu Park.
- Stop strolling about.
- Sorry, sir. Sorry.
Wasn't that the shooter Muni
upstairs?
Yes, sir.
He's been charged with
5 murders and 8 assaults.
And him?
No information on him, sir.
He got sifted out,
like chaff from wheat.
Sir, he's unarmed.
Unarmed?
If the CP finds out,
he'll order an inquiry.
Where are the arms we seized
at the Naka Hindola encounter?
In the jeep. I'll get them.
Who's got 38 bullets?
Sir, I do.
Deepak.
Now your fingerprints will be
all over the cartridges.
You'll land up in Central Jail.
Learn from Prabhakar.
- Who took it last time?
- I did, sir.
So, Prabhakar, it's your turn.
If Prabhakar-ji gets hurt, the red-light
district will have to shut down.
In the arm, please.
- Deepak, hold his arm.
- Sir.
- No trembling, Deepak.
- Yes, sir.
- Prabhakar.
- Yes.
- Ready?
On three. One...
- Why are you screaming?
- Sorry, sir.
Deepak, is he a lefty or a righty?
- Don't know, sir.
- Which wrist did he wear his watch on?
Right...no, left, sir.
- Meaning?
- He's right-handed, sir.
This is the story.
We came in following these thugs.
He opened fire first.
Abbas ducked; the bullet hit
the wall behind him.
He fired again, grazing
Prabhakar's arm.
We returned fire.
They ran outside, still shooting.
We chased them.
- Raja Babu got killed in the encounter.
- Yes, sir.
Muni ran in that direction.
We ran after him, he fired at us.
We fired back.
He died at our hands. We had to fire
in self-defence.
- Understood?
- Yes, sir.
- Any doubts?
- No, sir.
Good.
Yeah, I know, sir...
The cops arrested
the wrong guy again.
I did a complete background check.
He's a college student, sir.
Squeaky clean.
Madam Lawyer, my wife is missing.
What?
No, no, no, of course, I know.
His father came to our office
the other day.
Near Moti Lake, sir,
that'll be safe.
Who?
OK.
Why fear the police, sir?
Will you devour me with
your eyes?
Do you have eyes in the back
of your head?
That's why I hate cops.
I hate lawyers too.
Am I complaining?
Look over there.
We moved to Lucknow
6 months ago,
and you still haven't
unpacked.
OK.
Hey!
Trading hearts is far from easy
- What is it that you do?
- I'm a lawyer.
I hate cops.
A whisky on ice.
A large whisky with ice, please.
But your magic has cast over me
I surrender my heart to you
O beloved
I'm all yours, now it's your call
I surrender my heart to you,
O beloved
I'm all yours, now it's your call
You do all these things to me.
Then give me a gift.
I feel so used.
Plucking the stars from the sky
I can't promise you that
My love is simple, without frills
I lack the words to explain it
Shall we go to bed?
Please...let's sleep.
Thank you.
I surrender my heart to you,
O beloved
I'm all yours, now it's your call
Sohail.
Stay calm. It's OK. It's OK.
What! Your son's school fees
are 150,000 rupees!
- Do they inject him with knowledge?
- No, my friend.
It's not for the knowledge.
I send him there for the prestige.
Many rich kids study there.
Prabhakar, our CP sir's
daughter studies there too.
She's my son's classmate.
Is that why you send him
to that school?
Want them to marry some day?
You'll be invited!
Here he comes.
Why do you look so scared?
Imagine your plight if you had
to face Vedha for real.
Vedha?
Vedha who?
Vedha Betal.
Mithilesh Tiwari ruled Aminabad.
He was a big shot.
He had 12 armed bodyguards
following him, full-time.
Vedha killed him in a crowded
marketplace. Ask me how.
How?
He jumped from the third floor
with a sword.
And whoosh!
Tiwari was in two pieces.
Imagine how horrified we were
at the post-mortem.
Kidney, liver, all mixed up.
- Hey, Ranjan.
- Sir.
- New bike?
- Yes, sir.
155 cc. Liquid-cooled engine.
What's the torque?
Don't know.
But my wife said
when she rides pillion,
we must look the same height.
So I bought it.
14.1 n.m. at 8500 RPM.
You don't deserve it, man.
- How is your arm?
- Good morning.
Good morning, sir.
- Deepak-ji.
- Sir.
Why are you in uniform?
He doesn't like it here.
He wants a transfer.
I thought as much.
My sister Gita's wedding date
has been fixed. You must come.
Wonderful, Giri!
- Congrats!
- Thank you, sir.
- Head Constable.
- Yes, sir.
- Where's the IG?
- Outside.
Morning, sir.
Vikram, the forensics report
is here.
Ballistic and gunfire residue
are a 100% match.
- Good job.
- Thank you, sir.
- Didn't Abbas show up?
- He's taking his son to the hospital.
- Hospital?
- Chronic inflammation.
Any news, sir?
According to our sources, Vedha was
at Muni's house for the memorial.
I thought Abbas should
check it out.
- I'll go, sir.
- OK.
Sir, they all go silent when I ask
about Vedha.
Sir, I have some info on
Raja and Muni's families.
Raja Babu has no family,
but Muni has a son.
Name 18, age Dilip.
Sorry, sir.
Name: Dilip. Age: 18.
Where is he?
You didn't get the good stuff.
- That's why I'm drinking this.
- The cops. Run!
Did you kill my father?
Come to apologise?
No.
He was a criminal.
"As you sow, so shall you reap."
Good, the lowlife is dead.
He'd get drunk every day
and beat me.
Familiar story.
You too?
With a belt.
Father skinned me alive for
the smallest mistake.
Ever seen a police belt?
I learned one thing from him.
It's either right or wrong.
Nothing in between.
My father had nothing
to teach me.
Throw it down!
Deepak, put the gun down!
If they hear I faced
my father's killer
and did nothing,
do you know what they'll say?
Let go.
Vikram, Sonu's been selected
for the district cricket team.
Want to meet him?
No, sir. Some other time.
And Sattu's son?
He's a problem, but he'll reform.
OK, sir. I'll be off.
Sir, was I wrong to draw my gun?
He could've killed you.
He's just a kid. How could
he hurt me?
- Mister!
- Coming, sir, two minutes.
We're cops.
We should know by looking into
someone's eyes
whether he's a criminal or not.
Look at him.
His eyes tell me he's an imposter.
He'll say he couldn't find
the chain sprocket.
I tried very hard, sir.
I found everything, sir,
but not the chain sprocket.
It's a 1985 model. Hard to find.
Can I replace it with a new housing unit?
Only 8000 rupees.
Shall we shoot him now?
Have you heard the engine sound?
Dupu...dupu...
That's the sound I want.
Find that chain sprocket.
OK, sir.
Did you get it, Deepak?
Know why we sleep peacefully
after every encounter?
Because we know we did not
kill an innocent man.
- You'll learn slowly.
- Sir.
They've been breaking
the law for six months.
22 encounters to their names,
but no sign of Vedha.
Sir, he's the reason Vedha
had to go underground.
We must not forget why this unit
was created.
We had no other way
of stopping Vedha.
What's the difference between
cops and gangsters?
- Sir...
- Wait there.
Do you believe in police procedure?
Or protocol?
Of course, sir.
We believe it's better
if two gangsters die,
rather than four cops.
- Vikram!
- We...
I'm in charge of the Shivgadh operation.
I take full responsibility.
Take action against me. Please.
Abbas, I lost my mind.
Let them investigate me.
What's the worst the scumbag can do?
I didn't mean to abuse him, sir.
I meant, sir...
All right boys, goodnight.
Sir!
I'm OK. I'm OK.
I'm fine. You guys carry on.
The place where we were sitting
was in a worse condition.
This house belonged
to my ancestors.
It's in ruins now.
And the night you hid a snake
in the instructor's room?
When he entered...
Remember when we got caught?
You took all the blame.
Like you did today.
Never mind. Forget that old story.
- But those Academy days were...
- The best.
Those were the days...
Don't start again, please.
Vicky, there's blood on my hands,
I've committed many crimes.
- I can't remember...
- Hey, hey!
We're doing nothing wrong.
To clean filth, someone's hands
must get dirty.
If no one does it, we must.
Someday we'll have to pay
the price.
Or our families will end up
paying for our sins.
The son must pay for
the father's sins.
Stop this nonsense, Abbas.
You don't understand, Vicky.
You can sleep well.
Sameera and I...
I can't remember when we last
slept peacefully.
We spend every night fearing
my son Sohail will have
another attack.
It's all your fault.
I told you a dozen times, don't get me
emotional when we're drinking.
Who kept saying "on the rocks?"
According to our sources
Vedha was seen in Mirza Mandi.
This is it, boys.
Close Vedha's file today.
Vedha was spotted in this building
in Mirza Mandi.
We'll position the riot control teams
on these three junctions.
Yeshwant, Giri, Deepak, Anthony.
You monitor these points.
- Make sure no one enters.
- Sir.
- Ansari, cover these three points...
- Yes, sir.
Prabhakar, Ranjan and Martin
will be here.
Don't let the local police enter,
or our operation will be compromised.
Abbas and I will go into
the building alone.
Sir.
Remember, this is Vedha's territory.
There are plenty of people
who'd kill or die for him.
Be alert. Be safe.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
He's Vedha Betal.
Vedha, we hear you don't like
people talking loudly.
I'll speak quietly for your sake.
Confess to all your illegal deals
and murders.
We'll try and get you
a minimum sentence.
This offer is valid only for today.
So, start talking.
Won't you talk?
Well, I'll give you three options.
A: We pull your nails out with pliers.
B: Strip you naked and lie you on ice.
Or C: Hang you upside down
and tie a bag full of mice
over your face.
Talk! What is it?
Cat got your tongue?
We were interrogating Vedha.
He pushed us aside and tried to escape.
We fired in the air to stop him.
Unfortunately, we blew
his head off, sir.
That's what I'll tell the Commissioner.
Medal guaranteed.
He's not talking.
There's one thing though,
he did turn himself in.
He has a jackal's mind.
A criminal mind, sir.
And the question isn't
why he surrendered,
the question is...
if he was safe underground,
why did he come out?
Shall I tell you a story, sir?
I thought you'd taken
a vow of silence.
I learned long ago who to talk to,
when, and how much to say.
I learned long ago how to make
people talk when I want them to.
I'd like to see this same smile once
you've tasted police hospitality.
A guest is like a God.
Will you mistreat a guest?
Why surrender?
I came to tell you a story, sir.
Your story is all too familiar.
"I come from a poor family.
They all depended on me.
"It started with pickpocketing.
"Then circumstances forced me
to become who I am."
Your story, right?
Shall I tell you more?
If I offered you 100 million rupees
and said: "Vedha, take it.
Turn your back on crime."
You'd refuse me point blank
and go home.
Then you'd start plotting how
to rob that 100 million from me.
That's your nature.
If I offered you this same 100 million
and asked you to let me go,
you would not.
You'd kill me the first chance
you got.
That's your nature.
Nice.
You and I are so alike, sir.
We only exist because of each other.
They both might have tails,
but does that make a cat
and a mouse alike?
A cat exists because
the mouse exists, sir.
But the mouse has walked
into a trap.
Would the mouse do so willingly?
This is no ordinary mouse.
He's committed 16 murders.
You're no ordinary cat. You have
15 encounters to your name.
18.
Were you behind the
Shivgadh encounter?
That was Abbas Ali.
Oh, yes? The encounter ended with
three dead men?
They fired first.
We fired back in self-defence.
No choice.
I've killed 16,
you've killed 18.
- You're ahead of me, sir.
- No.
The question isn't about
who's ahead,
it's about right and wrong.
This side of the line is right,
the other is wrong.
I believe you, sir.
You're Ram and I'm Raavan.
You forget Lord Ram played a vital role
in making Raavan who he was.
You're wondering
if Vedha was safe underground,
why did he come out?
To tell you a story.
It's important you hear it.
Thief! Thief!
Bye.
Is that Parihar's son?
The PWD contractor?
Who took him?
He was kidnapped from my territory.
They want 10 million in ransom.
Find out who they are.
Boss.
Boss, I think they're outsiders.
No one in Kanpur would dare
cross you.
Your reputation is at stake.
If news gets out
that an outsider abducted a kid
in Parshuram's territory,
then it's all over for you.
Get my spittoon.
Boss, may I say something?
Put it over there.
- Boss, I think...
- Go!
- Who is he?
- He's new.
If he interrupts you again,
I'll give him a hard slap.
They abducted the kid
from under our noses.
Everyone was stunned.
Why be a hero?
Why poke your nose in?
Don't push it.
We're foot soldiers.
This is our life.
Why fight destiny?
You think destiny will help you
if you fight it?
Destiny can be made.
- Wow!
- Such pearls of wisdom.
Greetings, uncle.
One man less.
- Ask who.
- Who?
My father.
He spent his whole life
sitting around.
You talk as if he ended up
living in France.
If he had only tried a little,
he would've been successful.
You're so right.
Where would they hide
a kidnapped kid?
Get it?
- The Ganga stretches for miles here.
- So?
Who knows?
How will you find the kid here?
It's vast.
To fly you need to see the sky,
not the land.
Look over there.
An eagle can see both
the hunter and the hunted.
That's the Ghansa gang.
You thought it was your old aunt?
- Uncle, listen to me.
- Quiet.
Let's plan.
No plan, let's attack.
No. I get out of breath very easily.
Why did you come?
Sacrifice your life for a smile
Share the pain of others
Love someone from the bottom
of your heart
What a song!
When I was a kid, it was
my favourite song.
- It's a Raj Kapoor song.
- Who are you?
- Anwar, my gun.
- What are you doing?
What, man? I came for some action.
You can see my knife.
But let me hear the song first.
Hey.
Cool it! What's the hurry?
We can start later.
Oh man!
Sacrifice your life for a smile
Share the pain of others
Love someone from the bottom
of your heart
That's what life is all about
I admit my pocket is like
a pauper's
Yet my heart is like
a rich man's
Your choice of music is cool,
but you're a moron.
This is Parshuram's territory.
Nothing personal.
But I'm on his side.
How can I thank you?
No need.
Consider it Parshuram's gift.
Your efforts,
and I get the credit.
To whom do I owe the favour?
Speak!
I've been trying to, sir.
But you didn't let me.
What did you want to say?
Kanpur's getting crowded, sir.
Lucknow is calling.
But you turned a deaf ear.
From now on,
Vedha will look after
the contracting business.
Boss, I won't spare Vedha.
That scum doesn't know he's
stuck his hand in a beehive.
I'll bury him alive.
It's not as easy as you think, Ravi.
Parshuram's protecting him.
Stay calm and focus
on our heroin business.
Everyone's here. Great!
Children, listen carefully.
I'll say it again.
It's all about keeping eyes
and ears open.
Tell me. How can you tell
if it's the police?
Their sirens.
Their shoes and truncheons.
Their uniforms.
Bravo!
Remember what I told you.
They don't always wear uniforms.
They dress casually, too.
Then how will you recognise them?
Their short haircuts.
Bravo, son.
Short haircuts, chiselled moustaches,
and super clean shaven.
- Understand?
- Yes.
Yes.
- What's your name?
- Shatak.
Mr. Shatak, in case you
get caught with heroin,
what will you tell the police?
I found it lying on the road.
Bravo! You know your lines.
You've earned a round of applause.
Bravo!
Bablu gang is ready now.
Bravo. Well done!
Shatak, what are you doing here?
Bablu called me.
He calls and you come.
Chanda, you're older.
Why are you so stupid?
Now go.
Where are you taking them?
Bablu, he's my kid brother.
No wonder he's so sharp.
He'll outsmart you, Vedha.
I'll hit you with a pan,
you'll end up in Japan.
Don't taunt me.
Tell Shiv Prasad.
He told me to put the kids to work.
You said if the police arrest us kids,
they won't harm us.
- You have a sharp tongue.
- Yes, and so?
- I'll show you...
- Bablu!
Does it look good getting
beaten up by a girl?
Watch your step, Vedha.
Shiv Prasad is very close
to Parshuram. And if we start...
Oh man!
My hands are shaking from fear.
Idiot.
Shut up!
Why do you keep watching
Shaktiman?
He's a great guy.
How so?
He's a hero.
What's a hero?
Someone who helps the weak.
Someone who helps the weak?
I see.
Is that easy?
No, it's tough.
I see.
Who are you?
What do they call you at school?
- Shatak.
- How come?
I scored 100 marks in maths.
A century, that's why.
Was it easy?
No. It was hard work.
Why do you work so hard?
To become a hero.
Someone who helps the weak?
Like Shaktiman?
Yes.
I see.
Someone wants to be like Shaktiman.
But he's wasting time
with worthless people.
Why beat around the bush?
Come to the point.
Don't waste my time.
I'm going to Lucknow
for three days.
What will my hero do?
Study and stay away
from worthless people.
Come, my hero! Great.
Bablu's gang! The packets must be
the same size. Got it?
What will you say if
the police catch you?
We found it lying on the road.
Not a word more. No matter
what they ask.
Now run. Quickly. Run!
There's only one packet left.
It'll get you arrested.
Get rid of it.
Shaktiman smashed all the thugs
yesterday.
- Shatak, take this.
- No.
- Give it to Chajju the confectioner.
- Don't want it.
- I'll give you 100 rupees.
- 100 rupees?
Chanda, stay out of it.
You and your brother...go!
Chanda, what are you doing?
If my brother finds out,
we'll both get whacked.
Nothing will happen, Shatak.
The police!
Run, Chanda, run!
No, no. This way.
Come on, Chanda.
Search me! Strip me. Want me
to take off my underwear too?
Madam, he's clean.
I told you; I've mended my ways.
Can I go?
Madam, I found this packet
in her bag.
Why are you looking at me?
She's the one with the bag.
Who gave it to you?
No one. I found it lying
on the road.
Why are you hitting her?
Bablu gave it to her.
He said: "Dodge the police,
I'll give you 100 rupees."
Look at this.
- Why are you lying?
- We're not lying.
Madam, he's lying...
We lost 50,000.
And the business was shut down.
- What was the boy's name?
- Shatak, boss.
We thrive on fear, Bablu.
This boy will set a bad example
for the other kids.
He's Vedha's brother.
So what?
Scar him.
Humpty Dumpty sat on the wall.
Shatak, run.
Where do you think you're going?
- Come on.
- Let go!
Where are you taking him?
Let go.
- I'll tell Vedha.
- Get lost!
He's just a child.
Let me go.
It's nothing, brother.
It won't affect my studies.
I'll be more careful next time.
It won't happen again.
No, it won't.
Never again.
Now tell me, sir.
Who will Vedha punish?
Bablu who stabbed his brother's hand?
Or Shiv Prasad whose orders
he followed?
Bravo.
You save a child, but you shoot a guy
in the back,
and become a don overnight,
Vedha Betal.
When your days are numbered,
you start talking in riddles.
Do you believe you're the hero
of your story?
The question isn't about me, sir.
The question is about the moral dilemma
I'm facing.
Moral dilemma?
It's easy to choose
between good and evil, sir.
But in this story,
they're both evil.
That's the dilemma.
Who will you punish?
The guy who did it?
Or the one who instigated it?
Don't hold back. Punish the evil.
Kill them both.
I didn't expect that from you, sir.
You know rules of punishment?
One crime, one punishment.
Right.
If I punish the doer,
then the instigator escapes.
And if I punish the instigator,
then the doer escapes.
Who would you punish, sir?
Shiv Prasad or Bablu?
Shiv Prasad ordered the attack,
Bablu committed the crime.
Bablu is just the trigger,
Shiv Prasad's finger was on
the trigger.
The finger is to blame.
Shiv Prasad should be punished.
Did you act out of love
for your brother?
Or to rule the world of crime?
- What was it?
- Someone to see you, sir.
Priya?
Mr. Vedha is our client.
He's our senior lawyer.
And this is Mr. Vedha's bail order.
If you were in a hurry to get bail,
then why surrender?
Check the bail orders.
Is everything OK?
Damn...
Sir, you'd better talk
to my lawyer. He's outside.
Vedha, did they mistreat you?
No, Bablu.
In fact, we've become friends.
I'm leaving, sir.
What's your game?
You have to figure that out, sir.
Bablu, let's go.
How could I know it was
your case?
You never tell me anything.
Now you know.
He's using you to escape the law.
You're overreacting, Vikram.
Mr. Vedha is our client.
Mister? Bloody imposter criminal.
Imposter criminal,
but he has rights too.
Come on, this is my biggest case.
And Vedha turned himself in,
didn't he ?
You talk as if you'd risked your life
arresting him,
and I freed him.
Priya!
Sh***
It's OK. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Think about it, Priya.
How can we work on the same case,
living under the same roof?
What about our private life?
We'll have to go to different rooms
to take calls.
Husband and wife working on the same
case is a conflict of interest.
My department will never approve,
nor will the court.
You're right. So what shall we do?
- Drop the case.
- You quit your job.
Your job is real. My job is a waste
of time?
He's been accused of 16 murders.
A special police task force has been
chasing Mr. Vedha
and his gang for six months,
and you had him released
in six minutes.
Are you doing something noble
by defending this criminal?
No, your department is, in the name
of law and order...those encounters.
Priya must know there's a
difference between us and them.
Why marry me to a lawyer?
Can I call you back? I'm driving.
All OK?
I'm going to the Old Mill.
Got a tip off.
Some Chanda says she has info
about a drug deal.
Shall I come?
No, I'll handle it.
Let me go.
Shatak?
What's wrong?
I'm going to the Old Mill.
Got a tip off.
Some Chanda says she has info
about a drug deal.
Chanda, you're older now.
Vikram?
Who will you punish?
The doer, or the instigator?
- It was Abbas Ali's operation...
- Really?
Vedha's brother Shatak died
in the Shivgadh operation.
Vedha resurfaced to get revenge.
But he wants the finger,
not the trigger.
I took Abbas's name by accident.
Abbas.
Abbas!
Did you inform Abbas's family?
Sir.
I'll do it.
Vikram.
You leaving without uttering
a word
O friend, why turn your back on me?
You stood by me in all my loneliness
So much is left unheard
So much is left unspoken
Come back. Make your way back to me
O friend, is this the way to depart?
The night SSP Abbas Ali
was murdered,
Mr. Vedha was attending
a wedding in Agra.
His travel and hotel details.
Here are the photos and the footage
confirming his alibi.
Priya, Abbas was murdered.
Our Abbas.
Where's your conscience?
I'll see you in court, sir.
Thank you for your time.
OK.
Sir, Vedha killed Abbas.
I hope you don't have
any doubts about that.
The bullets retrieved from Abbas's body
were fired from Chanda's gun.
- But sir...
- Don't jump to conclusions, Vikram.
CB CID is handling the case.
They'll deal with it.
If anyone interferes in Abbas's case,
our unit will be suspended.
Commissioner's orders.
So, what do we do till
the CB CID solves the case?
Sit and stare at each other?
What else can we do!
Our unit will be the loser.
The CB CID will conduct the inquiry.
They think we can't do it.
Are we that pathetic?
We cannot let Abbas's death
be in vain.
Vedha.
Let's kill that rat.
But no one knows where
the lowlife is hiding.
His lawyer must know.
Hello. Yes, sir.
They'll charge him with something
and arrest him.
File for anticipatory
bail immediately.
Yes.
I'll get the documents ready.
We need Mr. Vedha's signature.
Call him and...
Sir, I can't call him.
His phone must be tapped.
So how do we get his signature?
I'll get it, sir.
Forgotten how to drive over 40?
- Sir, madam is ahead of us.
- She's his lawyer.
She knows where Vedha is.
A text.
Who sent the message to Priya?
Trace the number.
Yes, sir.
- Tell Prabhakar to overtake us.
- Yes, sir.
- Tell Giri to follow her.
- Yes.
Sir, madam is heading home.
The phone's switched off now.
The last location was right here.
- Sir, I think...
- Hang on.
A black SUV overtook us back there.
That's where they exchanged
documents.
Their car can't be far.
- Find it. Quick.
- Yes, sir.
Yes, Prabhakar?
Sir, we've found the car.
He's buying biriyani
in Mirza Market.
Follow him.
- Mirza Market.
- Yes, sir.
Sir, he just came out
of Murgiwali lane.
He has the file your wife
gave him.
OK, sir.
This is the right place, sir.
But which house?
Which lane did he go down?
Search every lane.
There are over 250 houses here, sir.
If we ask anyone here,
Vedha will find out.
Exactly.
Move it!
- Come on, go. Go!
- Yes, sir.
Where is Vedha?
Sir, the police have surrounded
the neighbourhood.
If you stay here,
the police will arrest you.
The scum.
Brother, want to fly kites?
I'm playing hide n seek now.
See you later.
- Found him?
- No.
Brother Vedha.
- Love you, Vedha.
- Love you too, aunt.
- He must've gone this way.
- How to find him in this maze?
What are you doing here?
You bloody...
Ansari, you go there.
Yashwant, come with me.
Over there.
So this is police work.
I underestimated you guys.
I was sad to hear about
your friend Abbas's death.
Why did you kill Abbas?
Why?
Why did you kill Shatak?
Abbas was a good officer.
Shatak was a criminal.
How can you compare the two?
It's traumatic to lose
a loved one.
Damn it! It's the same emotion!
It's the right time!
And the right weather.
Shall I tell you a story?
Hey brother, look where you're going
Not just ahead, not just back
Not just left, not just right
Not just up, down too
Hey brother!
Hey brother, look where you're going
Is the job done?
I'm heading towards Faizabad, sir.
Why?
I'll stop on the way.
You should've killed him
back there, Vikram.
A crowd was watching, sir.
No problem. I'll finish him off
and call you sir.
OK! End it soon.
Sir, can I have a drag?
Smoking is injurious to health.
You will know in 10 mins
what that really means!
Here.
Life too is like a cigarette, sir!
One day it'll turn to ash.
Till then take as many drags as you can.
I've seen many lose their cool
once they step out of their vehicle.
Those guys give our profession
a bad name.
Wasn't your father a cop too?
Didn't he die in the line of duty?
Thanks to a criminal like you
who fired before my father could.
No wonder you don't believe
in long conversations.
Sir, why are you looking for your
father's 1985 bullet chain sprocket?
It's been 36-years.
You won't find one now.
Have you been spying on me?
Is that why you used my wife?
Sir...
You don't show it, sir,
but you're an emotional guy.
Or else why try fixing
an old motorcycle?
That's not it.
It was rotting in my garage,
I thought I'd have it fixed.
And Muni, sir?
The man you killed in the encounter.
You pay for his son's education, right?
- You're an emotional guy.
- Balls to emotions!
I don't want one criminal to die
and be replaced by another.
How are you so sure, sir,
that a cop's son will be a cop,
a criminal's son will be a criminal?
Then Einstein's father and son
would be like Einstein.
Do you even know their names?
Cut the crap!
Get up and run!
I will run, sir. I will.
But first hear my story.
Aren't you very emotional
about Abbas?
My story has the same emotion.
Think of it as my last wish
and hear me out, sir.
Thief! Thief!
Only two people can save you
when you're in trouble,
Lord Bajrangbali or Vedha Betal.
Where have you kept all the MLAs?
Never question good fortune.
Tell Parshuram I said hello.
We'll be late getting
to Aminabad.
So I'll step on it. Full speed.
Oh man!
The traffic won't ease up
if you keep honking.
It's never so crowded
in the afternoons.
What did you say?
Brother, tissues?
Kill him!
Vedha.
Don't stare at me! Run.
Brother!
Your Mother...!
I'll fix you.
Why help me?
Should I have just stood by?
What are you doing?
Why are you screaming, brother?
It's his day for screaming.
I don't want you mixed up
in this mess.
Why did you get into this mess?
Why not?
We had nothing.
This is how I earned my swag?
Lucknow's famous for two things:
Tunday kebab and Vedha's swag.
How did you earn your swag?
Powerful men bowed to me.
- How did that happen?
- Through my own power.
And how did you get it?
Money.
If money could be earned honestly,
then why bother with this mess?
What are you talking about?
Look here.
Aunt used to sell poppadums
on the street.
Now people line up at her shop.
They wait hours to buy them.
And here.
Baiju Biryani Centre?
It started as a street stall.
Now they have branches
all over Lucknow.
They even export biryani to Dubai.
How did that happen?
The 500,000 you gave me
for expenses,
I invested it in their business,
in their hard work and honesty.
Small loan, big smile, brother!
Things looked up for them,
and we made big profits.
All legal, after-tax.
Brother,
give me a chance.
Make a big investment
in my company.
So you can keep your reputation
and I can keep my word.
Brother...
Why make up such a long story?
Come to the point.
Don't waste my time.
Small loan, big smile.
Thank you, brother.
No mention. I know that much
English.
Chanda, we'll make Vedha brother
stop all his illegal business.
From tomorrow we'll lead
a white-collar life.
You listening?
Isn't it great news?
You're always carrying on about Vedha.
Vedha will never give up
the world of crime.
Nor will you stop praising
your brother.
You know what? Get out!
Go live with your brother.
He'll pamper you like a child.
Shut up!
You've always been on his side.
I still don't mean anything to you.
I know what you think of me.
I'm older than you. So why would you
marry me?
You're grown up,
but you still cling onto Vedha.
You're an idiot.
Chanda,
I work 18-hours a day.
Who is it for? It's for you!
You're my life.
Oh? You forgot to wish me
happy birthday too!
It slipped my mind.
It's no big deal...
You never admit your mistakes.
Shut up!
Another word from you
and I'll strangle you.
You remembered.
Your mother...
- What language is that?
- Marathi, I guess.
Why is the Mumbai gang after us?
We have nothing against them.
Why rob from a robber?
What has the world come to!
You fool, we're not thieves,
we're gangsters.
There's a difference.
What's the difference?
Thieves and ruffians work alone.
We're a gang. The Vedha gang.
Therefore...gangsters.
- The Vedha gang.
- Exactly.
Show me your tongue.
All your sucking up has shrunk it.
You know nothing,
but you act so smart.
I would've known if they were
local goons.
I watch everyone.
The Mumbai gang has made
big trouble...
Every problem has a solution.
Just look for it.
I see nothing, bro.
One of us ratted.
Who gains from our defeat? Think!
- Boss.
- Vedha.
Vedha Betal.
An advance from Mithilesh.
10 million.
Ravi.
Count it and put it in the car, Muni.
Ravi, have we ever counted
the cash Vedha gives us?
I've ordered something special
for you today.
Really?
You get the best 'kulcha-nihari' here.
- I see.
- Gajju's famous Dhaba. That's Gajju.
Vedha, I hear you've started
a new business.
You can double the money.
Nothing escapes you.
The business is called Shatak.
He invests money and earns
three times its value.
Cricket betting? The police are
cracking down on gambling.
Be careful.
Shatak stays away from anything illegal,
everything he does is totally legal.
Boss...try it.
What are you doing?
Let me show you.
First wrap the bread around
the nihari.
Then dip it in the gravy
three times.
One, two, three...
Straight into your mouth.
Close your eyes and enjoy.
What do we say in Kanpur?
Delicious! That's what this is.
Brother has a point, boss.
Ravi, put the money in Vedha's car.
Tell Shatak to invest my money,
and double it.
Shatak, we have our investment!
Yes!
Brother is flying high!
Senseless since dawn.
Glowing since dawn
Blood flowing since dawn
My senses swaying senselessly.
Even nomads would lose control
I promised not to drink,
but drank too much
Your eyes are like drops of wine
The season has turned Alcoholiya!
I dipped my face in wine.
The thirsty come swinging by
No counting drinks today,
but today will count for me
Fill those glasses and pass them here
I stand at your doorway,
longing to see you
Fill me with love
The season has turned Alcoholiya!
Oh those grapes of wine
Oh my helpless heart
Rob me, but I'll keep smiling
Stop drinking!
Unbearable thought
If the bottle is Laila,
the heart is Majnu. So, sing!
Alcoholiya, Alcoholiya
Pull that towel between your legs
and dance!
Alcoholiya! Alcoholiya!
Drinking turns Lucknow into Mangolia!
Don't hesitate
Keep dancing
Wash shyness away
The season has turned...
...Alcoholiya!
Alcoholiya!
Shatak.
What is it?
It's called the ultimate pleasure, Shatak.
Marijuana.
It looks like a cigarette
on the outside.
Filled with the good stuff
on the inside.
My side business. Big profits.
Here.
Have a drag.
- Brother...
- So early in the morning?
Bablu, how are things?
- Business good?
- Absolutely, brother.
Thanks to you and to Lord Shiva's grace,
I paid last month's 20% on time.
- Are you a devotee of Lord Shiva?
- Yes.
Can I ask you a question
about Lord Shiva?
Go ahead.
The snake around His neck?
Why is it there?
Is it for Lord Shiva's protection?
Or for the snake's?
What do you think?
Shall I tell you what I think?
If the snake slips away
from Lord Shiva,
will it make any difference
to the Lord?
What happens to the snake?
An eagle or crow will grab it
and fly away.
The snake will become
someone's breakfast.
You're right!
You're that snake.
Treat me as your Lord.
You're safe as long as you're
wrapped around my neck.
So shouldn't my share be at least 50%?
- 50%.
- 50?
50?
I'm making you my partner.
Gajju, time to celebrate.
Sure.
- Bablu...
- A celebration!
Cheers, partner.
Cheers... partner.
Have you thought about
Parshuram's money?
- How will you invest it?
- I have a plan...
Brother Sanki, where did you keep
the money?
At Chanda's.
- You messed up again.
- Why?
I'll be right back.
Go. Run.
Chanda's granny! Want a kulfi?
Chanda!
Hello? Brother?
The money was taken,
I understand...
But why take Chanda?
It must be the Mumbai gang.
Who's the traitor amongst us?
Vedha. Why are you hitting me?
Why lose your cool?
Vedha!
Boss, see how he manhandles me
in your presence.
He took the money.
He's rotten. Now he's grabbing
my collar.
I always knew that he
and his young brother...
Enough, Vedha. Stop!
I don't doubt Ravi.
I gave you the money.
So you are responsible.
Until the money is returned,
Ravi will handle
MLA Mithilesh's work.
Where will we get so much money?
If Mithilesh finds out,
we're done for.
How did it all this happen?
All roads are now closed to us.
What do we do?
Brother, will anyone help us?
Brother.
It's been two days!
Chanda!
Chanda, where are you?
Shatak.
I've been waiting for your call.
Where are you?
Who abducted you?
Who should I name?
It was me.
When I saw the money, I thought
I could make my dreams come true.
But when I was on the run,
I realised,
I was leaving behind my most
precious dream.
Brother, forget about why she ran,
think about what brought her back.
Bravo, Vedha!
You want to defeat the man
who taught you the game.
And where did you choose to strike?
In brother's house!
Ravi!
The money's back.
Vedha.
We thrive on fear.
When people hear what that
two-bit woman did to us,
and that we did nothing,
then who'll fear us?
If my reign of terror is over,
then I'm done.
We must stick to the ethics
of our trade.
You know what our ethics demand.
Finish the girl.
Vikram sir! Another moral dilemma.
What will Vedha do?
If he upholds our ethics, Chanda
is dead. If she's dead, so is Shatak.
If I'm loyal to blood ties, it means
turning against Parshuram.
What will Vedha choose?
Ethics? Or emotion?
Let me explain it like you do.
Hey...
This...
Remember the line?
This is it. The line of control.
This side of the line is good,
that side is evil.
In the earlier story,
both were wrong.
But in this story,
they're both right.
Who will you side with, sir?
Parshuram? Or Shatak?
Ethics? Or emotion?
Parshuram is powerful.
And Shatak's only strength
is his brother.
Rebelling against Parshuram
means fighting the world.
But Shatak's world is only made up
of you and Chanda.
If I was in your place,
I'd side with Shatak.
Because Shatak is innocent.
There's goodness in him.
You're right, sir.
Shatak was innocent.
Vedha did as you would have.
I chose emotion, too.
Sent Chanda and Shatak to Mumbai.
Paid the full price for her actions.
Full gang war!
I didn't kill Abbas, sir.
You want to know why Abbas died?
First find out why Shatak
was killed.
As the law dictates, sir,
first investigate, then judge.
Don't announce the verdict
without investigation, sir.
We should know by looking
into someone's eyes
whether he's a criminal or not.
Do you know why we sleep peacefully
after every encounter?
Because we know we didn't kill
an innocent person.
This...
- Priya...
- Don't touch me.
Priya, I did what I thought
was right at that time.
I was just doing...my job.
You used me for your job,
and you thought that was right.
You tapped my phone.
Show me.
Don't move.
I can't figure out if
I'm living with my husband,
or a police officer.
I've warned you once.
Now move!
Must I do everything for you?
The car keys.
Where were you, brother?
The police have issued orders
to shoot on sight.
I've made all the arrangements
at the Kursi Road warehouse.
Go underground immediately.
Give me the car keys.
I don't know your game, brother.
Vikram is not like
the other officers.
Please be careful.
Of all the lawyers in the state,
you had to appoint his wife
to defend you?
Because of her...
- Vikram...
- That's enough, Mr. Vedha.
I'll inform my seniors
that I cannot work for you.
You've crossed a line.
Sometimes for the greater goal
you must cross that line.
I've been watching you.
I've noticed you've been riding
on Vikram's back for a while.
But why Vikram?
There are 285,000 police officers
in this state.
Why him?
I only ask questions of people
who can find answers.
What are you looking for?
What do you want?
I once wanted...
my aunt to sell poppadums
all over the world.
And movie stars would wear
Sikander's shoes.
And Baiju's biryani would sell out.
I wanted to help others
realise their dreams.
Small loan, big smile.
He wanted to change me.
My younger brother Shatak.
He was no criminal, madam.
But he was murdered
in an encounter.
I asked Vikram sir a question.
He will be at a loss
looking for the answer.
That's when he'll need your help.
I've sent Chanda and Shatak to Mumbai.
Vedha sent Chanda and Shatak to Mumbai.
Why would they risk their lives
by returning?
Abbas and Shatak.
Their deaths must be connected
somehow.
We must find out why Shatak died.
You guys went after Muni,
and found Shatak by coincidence.
Sorry, sir.
I don't believe in coincidence.
Everything has a reason.
The enquiry led us to believe
Chanda returned to Lucknow
for her grandmother's funeral.
Right, Vikram?
Where are the other photos?
Look at this, sir.
Ligature marks.
Chanda was held captive.
She was tied up. It means
she was abducted.
But why?
- Where are Shatak's phone records?
- Here, sir.
It's clear, sir.
The dates match.
Shatak landed in Lucknow
a day before the encounter.
He went looking for Chanda.
Vedha was underground.
There was only one way
of finding Chanda.
Shatak had to ask Muni
and his gang for help.
That's why they were meeting, and the
info was leaked to us on purpose.
So we'd get there and Shatak
would be killed in an encounter.
This is no coincidence, sir.
We're being used as pawns
in someone's game.
Hey...who tipped us off about Muni?
One of Abbas's guys...Pappu.
Yes, sir. This is it.
I've done my job.
Where can we find Pappu?
It's Muni and Raja Babu's
memorial service.
Next left, sir.
Since Vedha went underground,
all the mice are out to play.
Why is Parshuram here?
Sir, Pappu was last seen heading towards
the condemned bogies in the railway yard.
Let's go. Let's go.
Prabhakar, check all the bogies.
Pappu has been murdered.
The killer must still be in
the vicinity. Come on!
Someone wants us to not talk to Pappu.
You two, over there.
Lower your guns!
I want him alive.
The place is full of people.
Who are we looking for?
Sir, there's no one here.
I'll check the main yard.
Find him. He cannot escape.
What are we looking for?
As if I knew!
Your Mother...!
Why is the Mumbai gang after me?
Slimeball!
How do we get out of here?
Who sent you?
Bloody Lilliput.
Sir...
It just went off.
He would've killed you.
You said we should know by looking
into someone's eyes
whether he's a criminal or not.
- Did I do something wrong, sir?
- No.
You did the right thing.
If you hadn't fired,
I would've been fried.
- Was that your first kill?
- Yes, sir.
Tell Prabhakar to complete
the formalities.
Yes, sir.
Priya.
Listen to me.
Won't you even look at me?
Hear my argument before
you announce the verdict.
What is your argument?
This is not between a cop and
a lawyer, it's between you and me.
Can I suggest something?
From now on, lawyer and cop
stay outside the house.
Only Vikram and Priya
are allowed in. OK?
So you won't follow me
into the house?
No way.
OK.
- Well?
- I said the house, not the bedroom.
What's wrong? Can't sleep?
Seriously?
You said work stays out
of our home.
Tell me.
Priya, I won't beat around the bush.
I must talk to Vedha urgently.
No wonder you were in a hurry
to sweet-talk me.
No.
That's not it.
I don't know where he is.
- Priya...
- Vikram, I really don't...
He'll be at a loss
looking for the answer.
That's when he'll need your help.
So am I a courier service
between you two?
What?
Vedha told me if you're at a loss,
I must remind you of...
'Kulcha-nihari'.
Why 'kulcha-nihari'?
- Thank you, sir!
- Take it away carefully.
Please, sir.
What can I serve you, sir?
One 'kulcha-nihari' and Vedha.
Yes, sir.
Let me show you.
First wrap the bread around
the nihari.
Then dip it into the gravy
three times.
One, two, three...
Straight into your mouth.
Close your eyes and enjoy.
Sir.
Vikram sir, did you enjoy it?
I have a gift for you.
Get it from shop no. 16,
next to Sharma's tea stall.
I have a gift for you, too.
Who tipped off the Mumbai gang
about you, Vedha?
I mean the Shivgadh encounter
where Shatak died.
Do you want to know
who tipped us off?
It looks like a cigarette
on the outside.
Filled with good stuff
on the inside.
Babloo.
The Mumbai gang was
working for your Babloo.
O Man, there is no difference
between black and white?
It's all perception
O Man, good and bad aren't
different things
The concept of heaven and hell,
sin and virtue - all worthless
What you've gained, what you've lost,
just let it go
It's all illusion, just let it go
What's right? What is not?
Who can figure out these nuances?
Who is god here? Tell me
Who is without mistakes? Tell me
There are stains of crime on you too,
just check
There is blood on your hands,
wash it off if you can
What a trap it is!
It's all deception, O Man
Look for the truth
behind the curtains
Are you blind, O Man?
Vedha and Babloo are in
the Old Mill...
They're dangerous.
Don't risk your life, Vikram.
I can't afford to lose another man.
Wait outside. I'm coming
with backup.
Don't worry, sir. I'll deal with them
before you get here.
Scum! You were the finger!
I was 7 years old,
I was in short pants
when I entered this business.
I slogged day and night,
hoping to see the fruits
of my labour.
I saw the fruits.
But when they were in my reach,
a dirty dog snatched them away.
See the irony? I've had to lick
that dirty dog's feet.
That's when I decided,
I would kill you
and all your men, one by one.
You're going to die.
Only after I do.
Brother Vedha!
Welcome, sir.
Was it tough finding me?
I liked your gift.
Thank you.
No mention.
Nice, huh?
Everyone is having fun.
Me with you, you with me.
And life is having fun
with the pair of us.
This is my 20-year-old long friend.
Brother Babloo.
I even spared the scoundrel's life.
You'd be stunned if you
heard his story.
He has a story, too?
You all are so alike.
You're all the same.
Him. You.
No, sir.
What are you doing?
Don't you want to know
why Abbas was killed?
No more stories. Tell me straight.
A friend dropped his wallet
on the street.
He came home and looked
for it everywhere.
I asked him: "What are you doing?
"You dropped it on the street,
and you're looking for it at home?
"You crazy?"
He said: "How do I look for it outside?
It's so dark there."
You need to shift your gaze, sir.
Enter the darkness.
Meaning?
Why was Abbas killed?
The answer is in my final story, sir.
Listen patiently and carefully.
This time you won't just enjoy it,
it'll astound you!
"Thief. Police."
In the war, Parshuram was the king
and his elephant was Mithilesh Tiwari.
I got the audition.
What if I get rejected?
No one could ever reject you.
Look! You're a lefty,
aren't you?
You eat with your left hand.
That's it! She's a born star.
You're right.
See. This is my love story.
I'll need another piece.
It's all my fault.
What is?
I forced you into this gang war,
otherwise...
A wise man never cries
over spilt milk.
He curdles it into cheese
and eats it.
Did you think I could work for
a man like Parshuram forever?
Why don't you move to Mumbai
and start a business?
You promised me. Remember?
OK. Don't sulk.
It's time to go.
How could I've known it was the
last time I'd see my Shatak and Chanda.
There's a new twist in Lucknow's
mafia story.
AK47.
We need something to challenge
his AK47.
We'll find something.
I'll create a gangster
greater than he is,
or my name isn't Babloo.
The people of Lucknow live under
the trauma of gang war.
The police have created a special
task force to deal with the problem.
The team leader is SSP Abbas.
And in their team, they have brought in
an encounter specialist, SSP Vikram.
I'm a big shot now!
I'll have to escape to London
or somewhere.
Who's that?
The police.
Hey...
No, no...
Kill me!
Just imagine they killed Kallu.
He was too young to die.
We're a target.
You must go underground, Vedha.
You stupid?
I say we go with all guns blazing,
and take revenge.
They kill 4, we kill 40.
Stop provoking him.
One of our boys was killed.
The cops should've shot you instead.
Always provoking him.
Can I say something?
We've seen enough wins and losses.
Been on the run for too long.
Time to stop.
You should take Shatak's advice
and move to Mumbai.
- You'd send me there alone?
- Not alone!
You go first, I'll be close behind.
Bloody scum!
- Where is Vedha?
- You said he was in the car.
He was.
He's escaped again.
Five million.
These scumbags have brought
an AK47 from Mumbai.
But I was true to my word.
Look, Sanki!
I got a rogue cop of my own.
Slaughtered them like swine.
Abbas sir,
only Vedha is left.
I'll tip you off. You kill him.
Double the money.
Yes, sir.
Your friend. Abbas.
Good...evil. Police...criminal.
Truth...lies.
You love drawing lines, right?
Now which side are you on?
On that side, or this?
Or is the line no longer visible?
It's turned into a circle.
We're all going around in circles.
Round and round.
What do you think?
You'd tell me stories
and I'd believe you.
Abbas was taking money from Babloo
to carry out encounters.
Do you know how long
I've known Abbas?
Do I look stupid to you?
Vikram sir.
Blinkers cover a horse's eyes,
so it cannot see left or right.
Blinkers covered your eyes.
Abbas's son was ill.
How much was the treatment?
How did Abbas pay?
With his police salary?
The blinkers are slipping.
No.
If that was true, then Abbas...
Abbas would come to me.
How could he, sir?
Your honesty scares everyone.
Abbas.
He's dead, sir.
If Abbas was working for Babloo,
then why did Babloo kill him?
He didn't kill Abbas, sir.
Then who did?
I had to first find out
why Shatak died.
And I've found that out, sir.
Abbas is your riddle.
You solve it.
How could you let Vedha go?
You fell for his nonsense.
What do you think?
The illiterate Babloo masterminded
this whole game?
There's one thing I don't
understand, sir.
If Babloo didn't kill Abbas,
who did?
Abbas came here to meet Chanda
about the drug deal.
They argued about something.
Shots were fired from both sides.
Abbas died at Chanda's hands, right?
Maybe we're seeing things
from the wrong angle, sir.
The son must pay for
the father's sins.
Abbas was aware of his crimes.
He thought his son was paying
for his sins.
And even on that day
he couldn't shoot Shatak.
Because he knew Shatak
was innocent.
Abbas didn't come here
to meet Chanda,
he came here to rescue her.
To atone for his sins.
The Mumbai gang held Chanda.
Right here.
This is where she was tortured.
They heard this sound.
And started shooting
from over there.
Chanda!
Vikram!
Chanda didn't know that
Abbas had come to save her.
Maybe she shot him out of fear,
or maybe to avenge Shatak.
Forensics have confirmed the bullet
that killed Abbas
was fired from Chanda's gun.
Blinkers cover a horse's eyes,
so it cannot see left or right.
Blinkers covered your eyes.
Abbas's son was ill.
How much was the treatment?
How did Abbas pay?
With his police salary?
The blinkers are slipping.
Giri, you had a grand wedding
for your sister.
Ranjan, new bike, single payment.
Ansari.
Your son's annual school fees
are 150,000.
You're a good father.
And you two. You're good sons.
Martin and Anthony.
You paid off your father's loan.
Prabhakar!
You take 14 days casual leave,
but never miss visiting
the red-light district.
You have expensive taste.
Head constable.
You bet 200,000 on a sixer?
Where did you get so much cash?
And you, sir. Your ruins,
sorry, your ancestral mansion.
You must return it
to its former glory, sir.
My eyes were wide open,
but I could not see.
I've killed people, framed them
by planting guns on them.
But you forgot that the devil
is in the detail.
You placed the gun in
Chanda's right hand, sir.
That was a small mistake.
Chanda was left-handed.
You're a lefty, aren't you?
You eat with your left hand.
That's it! She's a born star.
We made no mistakes, Vikram.
We did our duty by killing them.
Drawing salaries from two places.
What use is the department's
salary, Vikram?
Your father died in the line
of duty.
What did he get?
A medal and a bike.
Is that what he left you?
It was a simple plan.
We'll abduct Chanda.
Shatak will come to free her.
We'll kill Shatak.
Vedha will come out of hiding
to avenge Shatak's death.
We'll kill him and collect
our money from Babloo.
But suddenly Abbas developed
a conscience.
He decided he didn't want
to be any part of it.
He became a threat.
He would've taken us all down.
We had to silence him.
We've carried out 18 encounters, sir.
But I always believed justice
was on our side.
Where's the line that
separates us from them?
What's the difference
between us and them?
Right and wrong?
Police...criminal!
You've turned it all to dust.
Sir.
Drop your guns.
Drop them!
Drop it. Drop it.
Kick them away.
And move back.
Anthony.
Back.
Sir.
Deepak, give me cover.
- Deepak, cover me.
- Yes, sir.
Move back.
Deepak...
Move back!
Pick up your guns.
Don't let him escape.
Seal all the exits.
Go, go, go!
Bloody hell! He doesn't have a gun.
Don't kill them!
Let's kill this one, sir.
Sir, I haven't done anything.
- I was only following orders.
- You're not a full-fledged cop yet,
but already a criminal.
It's tough killing your colleagues,
isn't it?
Trigger or finger.
I have no doubts, sir.
You killed the IG, sir.
That's serious.
I know a lawyer.
Priya madam. Shall I give you
her number?
She'll never defend me.
I'll put in a good word.
Love marriage?
One often faces such problems
in love marriages, sir.
I have a solution.
My own love story.
- Do you want to hear it?
- Enough!
No more stories.
Sure?
Look at these two, Vikram sir.
They could never be honest.
Not to their own people.
Or to their profession.
All their lives they've chased
greed and illusions.
People forget.
You're born empty-handed,
you die empty-handed.
Born from the earth.
Only to go back into the earth.
Lying there like cockroaches.
What did I gain, sir?
Balls!
Life is a joke, sir.
Yes!
Police.
Vedha sir, now you tell me,
what should Vikram do?
Should he let Vedha go?
Spare Vedha because he saved his life
and fought alongside him?
Or should he kill Vedha?
Because Vedha is a criminal
who has murdered 16 men.
Another dilemma.
What should Vikram do?