Sister Is The Place God Would Wake Me Now
God
Is My Sister Studies Last Year
Let Him Pass.
I Have No One In This World Except My Sister
I Do Not Care About Me
Day And Night Living In The Same Thing
I'll Do My Sister Read A Lot Of Progress
Is Just A Prayer.
Lalita
Moving On
Up In The Morning
Those Who Get Up Early To Study
Get Up Early What Are All The Pass In Exam?
Why That Is The Case
According To Principles Of Twilight..
Starting Studies,
The First Mind Machine Should Rest
This Machine Is Cold
And Then The New One
Enough
Dont Make Me Fool This Utptang Telling Stories.
It's Brush, Quickly Brush
Hot Water Is Ready, Quickly Take A Bath
And Breakfast Is Perfectly Formed
Ohh Ohhh Puri..??
Colgate Dental Cream,
To Bright And Sharp Teeth Use Colgate Dental Cream.
Sister Just Do Comb My Hair
You Has Grown So
You Combed Your Hands Up
Sister Never Before Did I Ever Have To Comb,
And Let Some Get Anything Only What Comb.
If You Wash My Clothes
Even The Bed At Bedtime
I Have To Say You Do From Morning Till Evening.
Take Only What You Do To Me
Except Studies, Studies, Studies, Studies.
Yes, Yes, You Just Studying
And My Life's Greatest Wish
You Have Do College B.Sc. Or C.Sc
What Is The Name Of? You Passed It.
Sister
What's The Use Of My Bsc Passed?
If You Will Passed,
You Will Have To Be Decked Thy Life
Every Mother, To Improve The Lives Of Their Children
Is Putting Her Life.
So What? That Child, That Hard Work,
The Love, Wants Any Advantage?
And Then
There Is Only A Older Sister Is Like Mother
So Silly, You Read A Lot Of Your Studies
And Studying My Part, Take Thou
Your Share Of The Household Work
And My Share Of Domestic Work, I Will Do.
Oh Silly, Why Are You Silent?
Hey, Your Eyes In Tears.
Sister, You Do Not Have To Tell Her Mother
But The Mother-To-Be Great For Me
But, Rather
To Be Like God.
Enough, Enough
Let, Be Ready Soon, And The Right College
Me To Go Home Of Parvati.
Oh Yes, Two Rs Are Placed On Top Of The Wardrobe,
Hey, What Happened,
Now Is Thy Harvest, The Money Was Sent,
Hey, That Cry, I'm Crying.
All That Money, Stripped Grandson Took
Stripped Away?
Yes, My Son Is The Enemy Of Money,
Hey, I Was Born In The House Of Ravana, Ravana.
Hey You, Why Does The Worry,
This Time Not Come To Ask For Money,
So To Say, As Well As Taking Care Of The Land
The Money Transaction Has Raghuveer.
Send Him To Me
I Will Show The Way, Never Forget
Too, Will Not Be On The Wrong Track
Go, Go.
Hi Uncle, Hello Grandma,
Hey It's Standing As A Match Then The Storm
Uncle Quick Rose,
He Decided To Do Something With You About
Well, Then Said, Come In Half An Hour,
You Will Reach It?
Otherwise, My Nose Will Be Cut Off.
Hey, Your Nose Is
The Nose Of The Whole Village
Never Cut It I Can Give?
Yes, I Can Give? No Right.
Aunt, Aunt
Oh That Toofan Mail, Come, Come
And He Has Been To The Temple, Where
If You Tell Him, I'll S Grind Chilies Tomorrow.
Because Today I Have A Lot Of Work
Seema Aunts Home The Spice Grind
And The Sheela Aunts At Homes Marraige,
Here's Aunt Fatima..
Enough, Enough, Engouh,
I Will All Speak.
You Said That I Will Speak, And Who Did Not,
Hey, I Will Speak All, My Grandmother, Now U Go
What Girl?
Work Each Understands His Religion
His Family Understands All The Village
I Do Not Deny It Ever Heard.
I Pray That, God, Who Sends All His Life In
The Way Of Happiness Flower
Gangu, Gangu, Ram Babu Coming
Go Early And Bring A Basket Red Carrots
And Take Also Mangoes
Come Back Soon, It's Time For Him To Return.
Yes
I'd Make Them Carrot Cake,
And Mango Juice'm Ready, They Will Love
Thank You, Thank You, Janaki
What I Like?
Do You Remember It More Than Me.
You, I Mean You.
Janaki, The 6 Years I Have Inside
You, How You Been?
Hey, I'm Just The Same Old Ram, Ram Only.
Come On, You Were. Be Happy, How Much Is Lean?
Oh Mother, It Was Above
All In The Eye Of A Mother Has A Specs
So Whenever He Sees Her Child
, She Only Looks Lean.
Well Tell Me, How Is Your Health
My Health, And In The Home,
Both Monitoring Janaki,
Pudding, We Shall Flower Girls,
If The Flowers Instead Of Trying To Kill Us
Then Kill Us To Avoid Eating
This Is A Short New?
We Throw The Bud Chanpakli At
Hey, Big Oh Man Some Sense And Not?
Wisdom, Only To Hit The Flower
If Not Kills Stone
How's My This Dialog?
Your Dialog, So Ugly, As Thy Mouth.
Look Hare, Has Been A Little Thicker,
It Will Not Be Satisfied With Small Flowers,
It Should Have A Huge Bouquet
Hey Punk Somewhere
, I Will Break The Teeth
Teeth Fall
Let Me Just Pick Up Their Steely Arms.
How's My Dialog?
Absolutely Ridiculous
The Queen Is Coming To Our Village,
We Will Garland.
Oh, What? Are You In Your Senses
Not Feeling Well
Oh, Your Love Is My Health.
If Your Love Is My Love To Find,
So This Is My Destiny
Hows My Dialog?
I Have A Strong Slap In The Face Do Not Crash
Then You Will Feel That Slap
Idiot.
You've Insulted Kamesh
Now You See How I Changed The Insult He Said.
What Will?
Just Come To The Village
So Beating Wasim Said
Over The Year Was In
So I Will Not Attack You
My Disciple, With Kalu Kalan Calcuttewala.
He Will Attack You
The Small Pieces Of Your Body
And I Will Eat The Fry Fry
So, He Will Be Seen Later.
Well, Now You Have Your Convince
Girls, Come Quickly, Hit, Hit It, Hit
We, The Village, The Village Dwellers,
Oh Boy, This Is The First Village,
Otherwise Everything Else Is Evil Rogues.
The Village Will Always Be Proud Of You.
Uncle,
You Probably Do Not Know
To Complete My Studies
I Become A Lawyer,
Is A Human Being Behind The Move
And That Janaki.
If The She Does Not Care Mother
So In My Mind How To Find Studies
Trying Desperately To Study Day And Night I Could
All That Is The Result Of Your Vagaries, Janaki
What Are You Saying
Your Mother Sent You The City
, Taught, Joined
You Have To Work Hard
It Appeared In My Favor?
You Said Right Son
In Your Absence
He Served Me A Lot
More Than Children
Morning And Evening
To Take Care Of Me
He Is, It Seems
God, To Serve The World, To Care, Create Her
Now See
It All On One Side Of The Village Is Served
On The Other Hand Teaches Her Sister.
She Also Teaches City Sent For College
And That Girl From The City Alone,
And Comes Back Alone.
Some Courage?
Good!
Lalita Has Grown So Large
And City Also,
It Is Awesome!
Listen, Miss
What Is The Time
Look, Do Not Show Much Finesse,
I Know Everything
You Just Have To Leave The Path Of Moving Girl
Them Secluded Foolish Sing Song
Hey, I Do Not Sing It, You Are Mistaken
Yes, The Song Of Kishore Kumar
Is Known,
And Is Stacked On The Wrist,
No, Its Mine.
But Is Off. Look At 12:00 Pm
He Is Also On Your Face,
Look, I Know Who You Are, Mister?
You, The Kalu Calan Calcutta, Hooligan, Butcher
That Nerd, Sent To You Following Me
But You Do Not Know
If You Give Me A Hand Slapped, Either
Kalu The Calan Calcutta, Hooligan, Butcher,.
The Wench Seems Loose Screw
Look, A Punk Is Following Me
Help Me,
Hey, What Are You Doing?
Leave Me.
Dattu Voice Is Dhoodum Dhoodum
Just See.
The Game Was Upside Down.
He Is Killing, Beating Our Man.
We Must Work Quickly To A Metal Part
Should, Run, Run
Hey Ram Babu You?
When Did You Come From City
I Came Yesterday.
Your Mother, Parvati's Feeling?
It Is Good, Will Leave.
Ram, Parvati Aunt's Boy. O God.
What? You Abused Ram Babu
How Dare You
So What Could I Do
So The Length Of Time After
They Saw Could Not Identify
I Must Admit Did Not Recognize
But What Was Needed To Abuses
They Punk, Loafer Came In
Went Up Thy Mind?
Sister Made A Mistake On There?
What I Do Now?
I Say That, Do The Same
What?
Let Them Come Home Right Now
Grab Their Feet, They Say Sorry.
No, I Will Not Come, Their Home
Too Ashamed To Face Them Now
Ashamed, When Abuses Were Not So Shy
When Abuses Were Not Ashamed
Work Apology Be Ashamed Of
go
Sister, Please, I Will Not Come.
Hey, How Come There?
Sister, Listen.
No One Around To See.,
How Do You Come In?
It Is The Home Of Gunday.
Along The Way You Can Power A Punk
Punk In Your Home, You Do Not Know
Sorry Sir
I Have Been A Big Mistake
Hey You Made A Mistake?
How You Think That I Am Punk?
Clean Dressed
Appearance Is Also Good
Guys Say, Can Be A Hero Still Try
And You Got A Punk Hero
So, You Can Have The Real Hero
A Real Hero?
Then What Was The Need To Vilify
Then What Was The Need To Vilify?
That Is Why I Am Apologizing
Stop Sobbing.
You Would Not Forgive So Easily.
First I Say, Do That
Can Be Forgiven Again
Say, What Would I Do?
Come Here
Come Here,
Come Here Oh
The Place
To Be Looking
Yes
Here Are Give Kiss.
Oh
Grandmother,
oh
Hey, What Happened?
Grandma,
Vedas And Puranas Sabari Said Of
The Man Who Was Very Current
You Like Him Is Very Current.
Hey, How's Things
Sabari Where? Mi Where?
In Her And Me What I Compete?
What Grandma Talk?
Sabari And In How Many Things
She Used To Gather Fruit For Sabari Your RAM
And This Is My Grandmother Raise
Grandmother, Is Not It
Oh, My Devil, My Grandson
I Understand Everything.
Sabari Was Collecting Fruit.
You Have To Feed Food. Eat And Go.
Do Not Tease Me Like, I Have No Money
Raghu Is Close To All The Money Transactions And Custody
Go To Them, Demanded From Him
Old Women, You Not Old Woman, You Are Rotten Bird
If You Wish
I Will Fight For The Money, And He Went To Raghuvir
Attack To Beat Me Remove
Old Woman
And I Will Take Money From You And Now.
Will Not Give Me,
So Much So Smite,
Leave,
Come On.
What Are You Doing?
Daughter, He Wants To Kill Me.
No
This Old Women Is Lying
I Was Just Looking At
My Staff Is Strong? Or Old Womens Head
Are You Not Ashamed At My Grandmother Raising Hand
One Day Do Loiter.
And Do Not Bring A Dime To Earn.
And Up On The Julum Do Old Woman.
I Would Like To Report You To Uncle Raghuveer,
And He Report You To The Police, Will Send You To Jail.
Do Not Do It.
I Realized My Mistake,
My Grandmother-Be Like God.
Grandmother,
If Such A Thing Again, Then I Will Not Spare You.
Grandma, I'm Hungry.
So Let's Give You Food. Running,
Forgot To Tell You One Thing.
My Grandfather Came In The Night Visions.
Yes, And He Said He Used To Eat Food In Silver Plate
Which Is Planted In The Middle And Gold
He Spoke Today With
The Food You Eat Into The Silver Platter
Spoke Today With The Food You Eat Into The Silver Platter.
Today I Would Like To Tell
Hail Silver Platter.
Grandmother,
When I Am Ready To Eat
And I Do Not Like Grandpa
Oh Dear, What Are You Saying?
Just Look At All Identically Like Him.
He Would Sit Like Dead Quartet,
So I Have Made Many Things Of Their Choice.
He Has Made A Lot Like They Own Potatoes.
He Made Like Eggplant Brinjals
He Also Created And Loved Mountain Lentils.
I'd Also Like To Bring Them Yogurt.
Take It.
Grandmother,
What?
And I'm Going To Sell It.
Hey What's Up?
What's Going On?
Hey, Hey, What Are You Doing?
You Owe Me,
I Will Not Pay The Debt, I Not Return Kalash.
What Which Borrow?
Oh So Soon Forgotten?
Which Is Not To Say, However, Borrowed?
You Come Back To Me,
Unless You Have Give Me A Sweet
Until Then I Will Not Return
But I Will Throw In A Little River
Please
Give Me My Kalash Back.
Otherwise My Sister Would Shouted Me.
If You Want
Give Me My Puppy
And If I Should Not Have?
Then Went Into A River.
Hurry Up
To Me And Much Work To Do.
Hurry Up.
Hey, my kalash?
'Oh, forget it.
Which you have given me, for that,
I will give you thousands of kalash.
Thousands kalash?
O Fair Maiden
In your body
In your adornments
Are decorated
Urns
Yes Urns
In your body
In your adornments
Are decorated
Urns
Yes Urns
Youth
Tornado
Will mislead
Then settle
Watch its antics
Humming
My sight is a killer
Your sight is worth watching
Humming
My sight is a killer
Your sight is worth watching
You will be injured
My anklets will dance
And bracelet will sing
Your style is
Sweet mischief
Will echo in my home
You will be injured
My anklets will dance
And bracelet will sing
Your style is
Sweet mischief
Will echo in my home
Firstly dont come in my heart
If you come then dont leave my heart
Stop teasing me
O Fair Maiden
In your body
In your adornments
Are decorated
Urns
Yes Urns
Youth
Tornado
Will mislead
Then settle
Watch its antics
Humming
My sight is a killer
your sight is worth watching
you are that untouched flower
that has not been touched by a bee
I was drawn to you
In such a way I reached your lane
you are that untouched flower
that has not been touched by a bee
I was drawn to you
In such a way I reached your lane
Im for you on the way
You can hug me anytime you want
ou are the only one in my view
O Fair Maiden
In your body
In your adornments
Are decorated
Urns
Yes Urns
Youth
Tornado
Will mislead
Then settle
Watch its antics
Humming
My sight is a killer
your sight is worth watching
Humming
My sight is a killer
Well mom I will go.
Hey, Wait a minute son
the new job
and scooter also new purchased
At this auspicious moment to pass
Me? Me? Why mother?
Yes yes, you.
You have the whole village that tells
you that the good omen
I will profit from the you front passing out me.
You're right, son.
Janaki passing through the front of u
What, do you find the greatest treasure of life
If that is the caseif i hit the jackpot
I will give it to janaki all.
Come to the passing through the front of me.
Got it, got it,
hit the jackpot.
Hit the jackpot?
Yes,
today said a goddess
you are going to get huge treasure
Where is the treasure?
The Treasury looks just get rest.
Where you going?
College? How will you go on?
How will you go on?
Today's bus strike.
Every girl has to seek to lift his fellow boy.
Ohhh?
I am not saying it
it was in the paper today.
Special radio news came today.
Yes, I know everything, you're lying?
Talking lie, what I will get the Padma Shri award?
If you do not believe, ask the jaggu.
Jaggu,
Jaggu to ask what you need?
I have truth and lie machine
Just know that the bus will come or not.
Ohh its tell.
I think the bus has problem.
If bus will nt come today then todays
Come sit on the scooter.
I do not sit on the scoote
I will go away on foot.
If you go away on foot,
you will be late in reaching college.
And if you arrive late in college
your class necessary will be missed
And if you have to miss a class
then you will fail.
Lets go.
Scooter is my new
very fast runs
Hence the fear of falling.
Just do hold me tight.
And, and, a little closer
If you do that
then I will go off the scooter
Oh, no, no, hold it up.
Otherwise you will fall.
Let's go.
My God, thank you a million
you have come.
I was waiting for.
Why?
Why not?
I had gone to the front
If anything happens to you
and all the blame falls on me
Oh how that could be?
Today was a very good omen
too cute benefited,
Tell me what happened?
Tell me
You promised that
whatever will give all I get.
Whatever I have
all that
belongs to you
whatever I have
all that
belongs to you
paravati aunt's house I am going
there too work on me today.
Maybe I'll come late, you stay at home.
Yes Yes Yes
Il be at home,
and will call Raghuveer uncle
And talk to your wedding.
What will?
About my marriage?
Oh God, which has been written
and will remain in coincidences
Do not think such stupid things
Sit and read.
Use your body to shine
forever
liril liril liril.
What, Kamesh has been arrested
Yes son
You can go city at any sitiuation
and son bring him to somehow bail
i Also agree he is dirty and
But looking his grandmother face
something will have to do for him.
Go son.
The sergeant to release me, right?
I knew
because the freedom fighters
Bhagat Singh, Chandrashekhar, , Mahatma Gandhi
was in jail
Then came the revolution in the country.
People were eating chestnuts on
Government had created panic among the tents.
So when
you do not have the freedom of the city
in the country and the revolution comes
Spherical moving,
dump bodies
fire, strike, neither, not knowing what is happened
Nothing happened.
Come on
your bail by Ram Babu
so you are being left
Rambabu,
the police inspector
after today
should remember one thing,
the country's central Madan is not alone.
The lawyers of the line is
Rambabu
We both belong to the same village
You did very well that, today
If God willing
God would surely
tomorrow I will come to rescue you on bail
No.
A great favor to me and the villagers.
It is true.
But Ram Babu
what it case on me
, I am going to Bajaru woman
police terrible mistake.
How?
Such that,
I'd just damage good girls
Which is poorly bad, i never touch them.
How's my this dialog?
Raghu uncle you recite the dialog
you will repair the poles.
Raghuveer?
You are the name of your family to be a stigma.
Did you just spit on the face of his family and the entire village is not.
Black mouth reaches notoriety.
If that's the case, I put away out of the village
to give me a share of property
I go out of the village rushed to
You get nothing until your grandmother is alive
All his life he had this old heart and flesh is real butter
Very strong
not easily going to die so soon
Easy Rider is somewhere waiting for my death.
Remember you will not be penniless.
How would not?
Within a week
if the property has not been decided and I did not get my share,
I am outraged at this village,
Sataunga people, lift up sleeping
People will cry
and then he moved to take my complaint come to you
Will you be forced to give my share
If it was, I do not sit in peace
What do you think about this drama?
Do not you ever forget this again.
You know
I was so nervous?
Hey I just wanted to see that
if something happens to me
it would have some effect on you or not.
What do you think if something happens to you
will be alive Lalita
If I died,
I will die.
If I fell into the river,
So I will go with you fall into the river.
If I committed suicide,
So I'll take himself.
If I may take the puppy to hold you tight.
I'll take the puppy grabs.
So why the delay has hurry
Be very mannered
Go, from today I will come closer to you not.
50 feet away, standing there being to speak.
Let me go, please.
OK OK you will go on one condition.
First tell me when you will meet me tomorrow?
Now rub off yesterday Meet nothing.
I have to prepare my coming exams.
Otherwise my sister will kill me.
Hey you, do not worry about your sister.
I am your sister that teaches
he will send you to me
Do not increase or hit the Go.
It will not do everything in front of my sister
Tomorrow, I shall assume that you own
Ram Babu is the brain, the mind of a lawyer
Yes yes see.
Is it what are you saying?
Janaki, a teacher of Lalita was
Well, he told me
he is good in every subject
expect botany.
What Botany?
He will fail if he dont have
Oh you do not know about Botany?,
Botany is a Botany
if she has failed in botany
she want homework again from children's class
How many years will be wasted.
And will lose money.
So my friend advised to me
why do not you teach her Botany
You teach her Botany? You get?
I was the champion of Botany,
When I was in college
people would say to me
Look at him
him he his botany's king
look at him there is botany's king.
Then start teaching her tomorrow
You will very much favor.
What is kindness?
I am forced to,
I have not the time to head scratching.
No, no,
do not say that
when given a little time to teach her
Well, when you're doing such a recommendation
then i have to do something.
But first ask her that
she teaching from me that is approved
because he does not even
What needs to ask her?
If Fly not sit on her nose,
Please Sister, Sister, please,
NO
I will not listen
sister why are dont understand
He can teach me how?
Their subject and my
So do not try to be too clever.
I know everything
He studied in college for 5 years and
you are still in the third year
What do you think
I have not gone
so I do not know anything about college
Sister, Sister, they studied arts.
And i studied science.
Maybe they do not know
Do not know a word
hey people in college used to say to
And you say, they do nothing.
Sit down.
Clearfully heared Ram what speaking?
What teach?
My acquaintance is no more
I raise it seriously and diligently try to
Why it considers wrong?
If she does not give attention you do not
Hey you can belive or not believe.
Your sister is you.
Complete freedom of with you anything
i can do it.
You admit momentum
Show speed teach Botany then bangs it
Hey what's Botany?
Botany, Botany is Botany
botany is a brinjal.
Brinjal's the last leg
of the thumb
is to have his nails
he says Botany.
If I wink with one eye
When I wink the other eye
If I wink both eyes then
The girl is won over
Trash talk
If I wink one eye
If I wink the other eye
If I wink both eyes then
The boy is won over
Trash talk
Some sweet, Some sour
Naughty Naughty
Your youth is like chillies
Taste this chilly just once
And you will want it everytime
Youth is not under control
We will be playing with fire
If I wink one eye
If I wink the other eye
If I wink both eyes then
The boy is won over
If you get water on the seeds
We will meet you and I similarly
In the sugarcane fields the both of us
Will listen to the cooing of the cuckoo
You and me together there
Will do a lot of talking
If I wink with one eye
When I wink the other eye
If I wink both eyes then
The girl is won over
The boy is won over
gulgule,
Yes sir.
We decided to property issue raghuveer uncle
gives one week braether has been
Crooked finger until sin-bin in the decency
No
Now we start our action as the earthquake
many villages have drowned in a sea of ruin.
How?
As used in mythology monster,
He did what?
Brahmins did make life miserable for the move
the goddess of sin decent
Young, virgin girls were robbed respect.
It mean?
Means rape.
Not found a virgin girl of the village survived.
He is coming out jasmine.
Look, now I am a youth, how Lutta?
Hey, jasmine I will rape you, rape.
Which car is it, babu?
Car No, I will hold you firmly in my arms.
I will love you,
I will smash your youth.
I will suck your soft lips.
I will drown in your eyes.
Truly I say that fortune?
You, you are so happy, as
Hey stupid girl I will ruin you.
Will spoil your reputation.
So do it
was waiting for this day long limitation.
When you were at my eyes
Let's go over there,
no one will come.
It seems the girl did not understand anything
Hey I have understood everything
and now i also understood you
Hey dattu, dattu, Save me
Come come to my King.
Oh save me dattu,
Oh save me, Leave me.
Lets go.
Come fast.
Let's hurry up.
Aunt take it, it will nothing happen to him
will be fine in 2 days.
The whole village knows daughter
Kumkum after worship facilitates
That is very important.
Hey Lalita is studying very,
Preparing to test what?
Yes, aunt is working hard day and night.
Then passed the exam this year will be good.
I have many things aunt
Lalita, examination fees are
yes
How many?
300 to Rs.
300 bucks?
Hey HH
redress of grievance to the sun god
Lord, give me the freedom to
Look he is worshiped head priests
If you go to his hips kick strike.
Do not misconstrue this.
Cumbrous, dreadful colossus General
silent,
if I am not wrong
then raghuvir uncle will not tight
And I will not share my property.
So Guru, do not delay, hurry, hurry.
Handmade god forgive me.
Two essays liberation liberation Do Dham.
Wicked, vile, thy holocaust.
Will be in Hell.
There is the go.
Hey, that was i wrong with you for
Your hips kick is my duty
I will do it every day.
I will reprove its to raghuveer uncle.
That's what I want, do it.
What kicked you, what kicked you,
Worms will.
The village of priests of sarpanch's
What kicked masters such as
Now he will hear my uncle Julum
Has sparked outcry in the village priests.
And raghuveer uncle will be coming to give
He is coming out in the village priest.
Seems to me some abuses are in Sanskrit
do it. come, come,
Lord, you are God, not man.
The earth is the Lord's second form.
14 years of back pain I was suffering
Great, quack, doctors, physician lost.
But you kick me in the
I like Dnushy was awry
Was straight like arrows
Milk tribute stages are devoted to your Lord
No no.
Accept.
Pries
I kicked your hips
though you abuses me rather
You mean
you are not my complaints toraghuveer uncle
oh god
I complaint against you.
My mouth will have bugs
you are Gurudev, you are great,
Look around
and see the corn stalk Shastri
is also suffering from the disease, like me
Your Holiness leg to kick on his hips do it too well
Do redeem it, Beat Kick
No,
Everything was up down,
Hit, Hit,
I am kicked, do not worry, ohh god.
Janaki
has received wages for the first time
2 brought saris
for a mother, for you,
take it.
Why me?
Hey, for wearing and what
You will to wear this sari and
Hey That is to say
if you wear a sari then sari will look beautiful
So come tomorrow, come to wear it
I will go.
Gift.. Gift.. Gift.. Gift..
Brought Brought Brought
My My My My
Heart is aflutter
Your gift of Love
Has become my life
if now support for my heart
What more do I need in life
Your gift of Love
Has become my life
if now support for my heart
What more do I need in life
Gift.. Gift.. Gift.. Gift..
Brought Brought Brought
Like the body is without soul
I am the same without you my love
Your body is like musk
Your fragrance fills the air
Like the body is without soul
I am the same without you my love
Your body is like musk
Your fragrance fills the air
The deer inside runs
To touch your youth
Your gift of Love
Has become my life
Is now support for my heart
What more do I need in life
Gift.. Gift.. Gift.. Gift..
Brought Brought Brought
It is a message of my heart
Its not just a Saree, its your love
Its the adornment of a married woman
It is a message of my heart
Its not just a Saree, its your love
Its the adornment of a married woman
In the guise of Silk
On my body it is draped like you soul
It is a message of my heart
if now support for my heart
What more do I need in life
Gift.. Gift.. Gift.. Gift..
Brought Brought Brought
Oh how nice sari.
The day before yesterday my birthday
thankyou sister,
The day after my sister's birthday,
Gift is to take him to my sister sari.
I have no money
if you can give 100 rupees
So what you need to work, Janaki.
The part of the world going here and there
but on her birthday you never
Take this.
Siste
what have you bought a sari,
I saw mad.
Think
we both liked the same time,
Sari sight, I remembered my birthday
How much is?
It is a sign of my love.
And do not ask the price of a token of love.
Correct,
the sari like my sister's love
priceless.
Raghu Ji I was sleeping on bed at night.
Kamesh grabbed me by the leg dropped cot.
That loafer is also me.
Uncle
also my two children, in the river, has driven by him
that brave is also me.
It's my house ate yogurt and
that is also me an incarnation of
He is flirting with the girls at
here's all girls are gopiya and
Do something Raghu Ji all the
Abe shy bastard to the devil,
This is why many movements?
The samples were all small.
If you still have not given me my share.
I am wrong then all the village
he would wrong the world map of the
The Devil and the witch too,
Grandmother, quickly divided the property
and give me my share
Hey You shut up.
Raghuveer his grandfather is very respectful person,
The villagers used to worship them.
And he is unworthy, he's got all
Do that two property division,
I also spent economize.
Its such foolish acts to close for a few days
give me one week time for thinking.
After that, the house Vkan, Vmin ground,
Well, give me a house, gave it Vkan,
Give me ground, give her to the Vmin,
Give me property, give her Waydad.
How's my this dialog?
You mean, in your eyes Vmin land, house property,
Well then, the property of the Waydad
Vkan of houses and
ground of vameen,
I give you
rest what are left i give to them
How's my this dialog?
All this sounds like a dream to me.
Our wedding could
turn this dream into reality
Listen
I'm going on tour a few days
Before I return
you to your sister
hear your love story
she immediately confirmed
And when I would have to return
the wedding preparations.
Conical oboes are ringing at the door.
And I'm waiting for you in bridal wear.
Yes, Lilta,
Now only one desire
when I come back
so I see it as the bride
Wow! Its voice is so melodious and sweet,
It is her Lila
poverty feeds such beautiful lotus artemisia
Brother,
now I would like to
, the morning and evening the voice
singing the same song heard in the house.
I shall always keep.
To this point
I have called you by harassing it.
You mean that,
I want to make your daughter in Janki
what do you think about how are u thinking?
Remember,
I can not find words for joy
Janki will come to this house,
So I take it in the house
But the law,
once ask Rama
Hey, ask him for what?
There can be no objection to this,
I know.
She also likes her.
What if late
the wedding date, take immediately
I will handle everything else is responsible.
I will handle all the work.
Janaki I want to say one good news.
We are a marriage of Rama.
How many relationships have come from
And what people are willing to pay dowry,
real estate wealth jewelry.
However, I am not greedy of all these things.
I have a daughter that
take care of my son.
Bless our family's
respect forever
The girl is the only one in the village
and she is you Janaki.
If you say yes
then my life will be full of the largest duty.
Janaki dont refused.
Mother
mother, in if i am poor, so canl am lucky
It's not your luck,
But we are lucky.
We are getting such Daughter
who is coming to our house with
Sister,
Sister, you wanted to say something.
She said I could not sleep.
Amazing is not even I sleep.
Sister, I,
This is a very nice thing
to say, two people together to try
then a new guy comes into the house.
Sister, you want to say something,
speak up.
Yes
You also want to say something, you tell me.
Before you say,
you speak,
You first, you first.
You, I would not speak.
Before You Say.
You are younger
you should get the first chance to
What book are written in large and small before you speak.
You do speak.
What is the matter
sister
arm ye-ye-in in the night would pass on in.
Rupee tosses a work,
if rupees will be tell then you speak first
if first is head then i will speak first, ok
Approve.
Didi, it is rupee?
Yes.
1 2
Hey wait.
Now what happened?
Looking
If I had to say, i cant speak looking to you,
So you have to close your eyes.
And, if I had to speak
so you have to shut your eyes to you
otherwise I will not even speak.
Hey where is this money?
It has stuck anywhere?
I do not know where did it go?
Look
we do one thing you're
older you have to speak first.
No, not, say.
My eyes closed, speak.
Lalita I
am getting married.
Very good luck Oh wow
He is Ram Babu
Yes Lalita
Parvati aunt asked me about this relationship
How could I deny?
I said yes.
I love him,
By heart I love him
worship him
And their attitude seems to me he too.
Truly speaking after seeing them in
It is often used to think
if alive, I could not become her,
I can not become someone
I will give my life.
Just now they will soon fix the
I gave my heart to hear
what you want to say now
We had bet it sister
my heart shall then
have to close your eyes to the other
say,
Have you had your eyes closed?
Yes
got off, so to speak.
After hearing your the good news of sister
I'm not understand,
what to say
there is no voice for joy.
Sister, you're very lucky
you heard God.
Having in mind whom you ask
Wishes in the world born in
Sister you're lucky
you get your choice of a husband
ovner a good person and good heart
If you're married
settle your home
your life and you just be happy
That is my wish.
First tell me
what you wanted to say?
That, I was saying
Principal sir promised me
after result i worked as a
truth
Lalita, you are teaching in collage.
Today I am so happy
that God made me worthy
I educated my sister
I could be sitting on a good stage,
Lalita.
He could not be alive if I could
I can not become that begins of I shaved
I will give up my life
No it can not.
That can not be.
What should I do?
What do I do?
Lalita, see it
You ? 1 night which was tossed.
She have had here, in front of
And he also have a tell.
First your turn to speak,
You forced me first speak forcefully.
Tell Who am I to force you?
Sister It is the fate of Joy and restraints.
God gave you a chance to speak first.
Because,
He is with you.
Wants to see you happy.
Ok Sister, I just go to college
bring the certificate
Go slowly, in Kityn Bvra
Lalita
you here? I'm awake?
This is not dream this is reality.
You come into the city, going from village
to my house for me, why??
Want to ask you something.
Ask me, ask, ask,
Will you marry me?
Wedding?
Yes
with me? wedding?
Lalita
might think I'm stupid to see,
Not much on stupid
what you say i will not admit.
I bastard, pig man.
Do not try to play me.
Fate is playing me, kamesh.
The hands of fate to become a toy,
He will play the what?
Just tell you that
will you marry me or?
Not speak a word further.
Me, I'm ready to marry you.
Lalita,
you say I should die in the river
You speak so I jumped down
Do you know, I went inside to give soda bottle.
Am ready to marry you, Lalita.
But on the condition.
I accept all your conditions.
Listen first, kamesh.
I will not ask you anything about your past today.
Neither you ask me about my past tomorrow
I want only flowers smell
i dont want to know Who hit plant?
Who gave the water, who is the gardener?
That means nothing to me, Lalita.
I just care about the future,
which was not your past.
We both got married.
No
It can not be.
That's a lie.
It's a lie, right?, Lalita.
No
It is true, sister.
Today, we are husband and wife.
Beware, which again came the
It can not be your husband.
You can not wear this necklace.
It's a lie, is false.
I am not ready to accept.
Dont accept Janaki
your accept or reject our relationship
We both have the wedding i front of God.
Keep quiet.
If you say that God is witness.
I will tell you this, he is not God.
Lalita, to take off the necklace
and hit it on the mouth,
or I'll throw this scrape.
No sister
so it can not be.
If you wear one necklace in life
when he becomes married
And takes off once
when her husband dies
and she becomes a widow
The necklace has remove
noone right given
No, Lalita.
Why the yelling?
What is the right to admonish this?
This is my wife, wife.
In this world, however lowly girl
she will not get married with you.
I can not be so alive.
I bullied you to Lalita will be forced.
That you get married.
Say, Say, Say What was the point?
Sister
you can not insult my husband
anything What happened to all my wish.
He is wearing to me necklace.
I accepted the husband.
But how did it come to be
Wanted to marry you
then tell me
Or do you think that I am permitted will
Or, or he better than, for you could
I, what was I dead?
Why did it?
Tell me what?
I want an answer, I want an answer?
So are you crying
you did not stand my pleasure.
Are you jealous
that before you i got married, right?
But marriage is not a crib
It is every man's own personal matter
And also the right to decide
And nobody anyone.
No matter who you are and
what?
What did you say?
You say to me, 'Who am I?
Lalita, do not you know who I am?
Lalita, I'm the one
who you never feel short of your
Lit up every single day of my life,
Every dream of life, all desires
all you had used Wish
And asks me who I am?
Okay.
Today, I do not even know that,
Get out there
Get out of here
Lalita meets your face.
Spirit have brought someone else.
She whom I loved Lalita,
My sister,.
You're not her
died Lalita.
Get out of here,
get out of here,
I have shed tears over the death
No, I will not ask you any questions.
Ask nothing.
Because, when you do not
So even though I am a non-person.
But one thing is clear Listen, Lalita.
I your place if I had a daughter
, I would be dead by now to know him.
And i would have even finished.
Kamesh,
am responsible for all waste.
I long ago gave you your share of
so that the child's life should be spared.
But too late.
Still wants to, and that your blood, you
The villagers say that I raghuveer uncle.
They want to know, Raghuvir uncle is at the heart of the village
how much passion, so much love.
But could not do so.
I am forced to
because even the girl's like godesses,
So before i attempting your murder and
Go away from here,
You will get a share of property.
Tomorrow morning to leave the village.
And do not come back.
Get out of here,
Listen one more
you ever co-incidentally be passing
Just move it out before bringing
Raghuveer alive or died.
And inform you of the death of Raghubir
got to step on the earth of the village,
Lalita,
open the door
I am the Ram.
Whom do you want to meet?
I have come to meet Lalita,
I have loved.
Then you've come to the wrong door.
This is Lalita, who is kamesh wife.
It's impossible.
How lalita became the wife of Ramesh?
Why can not?
Of course that could become
Witnesses believe God, we both got married.
I dont beleave
and not beleave even at death.
You will tell me only
he scared you to Lalita,
you forced by him,
or took advantage of my absence
Which you may be forced to marry her.
Tell Lalita
what she did this to you?
please tell me
Want to hear, listen
, I loved the kamesh
so I have to marry him.
No it can not.
You are lying.
In human life, loves only once
not repeatedly.
I also loved only one time
the same man
and that
kamesh.
ANd me
Who loved me and he had deceived me?
He promised to marry me, that was a lie?
The time spent with me, who spent lousy,
yes, Ram Babu
is with you, which I loved,
he was betrayed
So forget me.
Falsely promising to marry
you so hate me do it.
So the time spent with you was just pretending,
so Damn to me
Lalita?
Do you remember
what you said when you go from village?
When you come back
then I come see you as a bride.
Look, look, I am at the
Bless me.
I bless you
whose hearts have been Waters,
He can bless anyone?
Law of the universe
that emerged as a bride
it is blessed,
it is even an enemy.
You're just bless my wife.
Blessing with both husband and
Since you have made my wife Lalita,
people are jealous of us.
No
Let us not be among these burning
Let's move away from here.
Lalita, often a bride adorned for her
Or spend a large hotel on the soft bed.
But their honeymoon is some wacky style.
We have been living in
Lalita Lalita my honeymoon and have
So listen,
When love comes, we will
Golconda station arrive,
I will take you, I kiss your soft Otaen
Nikatpur station so
we both will very close of each other
Jirakpur station soon we will
Dariyapur station arrived
We both love each other will like to be
Say how's my dialog?
The station is coming,
I am going, you will be sitting.
I brought the fruit, the fruit I did.
I went.
Bastard, some ****,
I will not leave you alive.
Where the **** is going to run away?
**** I will not leave you alive a despicable.
I will not leave you
to kill thee, Where I have come to follow you
You ruined my sister's life
False love him trapped
betrayed, and fled.
He had committed suicide
**** The **** out of you
, I will revege my sister's
will give thee in pieces, got it the dog.
Kamesh murdered Suresh for
But murder is a crime,
Do it by kamesh.
Therefore, the court sentenced him to
Lalita
I know, you are very sorry.
After the wedding, we could not spend
But you do not worry.
It's a matter of just 7 years.
And it will fly away like 7 years 7 minutes.
Janaki,
No, leave me.
No, leave me
, let me die,
Janaki,
Not
Janaki what you want it to
for whom?
Who was kicked out of your
We explained the million,
she not her sister Skege forgotten.
You like her mother,
Handled it
or else it will die in suffocation.
I, ? What do I do?
Let's make her your daughter in low
When you like the girl, like son,
What are we waiting for?
And at the head of the house will
If the heart's workload automatically'
Yes.
What?
Yes dear
I thought you come back
I supposed to talk to you about it
But never got the chance.
But son
Lalita when the day he was
1 day ago
i talk with janki about your wedding.
And they had agreed happily.
Janaki
nothing you said Lalita before marriage?
No
If I would have said if i does
never.
Tell me something good,
promiscuous before marriage,
or any incident that you recall.
On the night before she was married,
also with me.
We talked for a long time.
Such a long time has passed.
Bus,
and the next day
she married kamesh
I did not understand until now,
Lalita why doing it?
But I have understood,
you are thinking absolately right, Ram.
Your idea is absolutely correct.
Lalita when she know
about janki love you
So she, her sister's wedding to
that married kamesh Jalil. And
herself, in the eyes of the world has dropped.
She had sacrificed so much.
And could not understand any
But uncle, how can I live without her
What is left in my life?
Janaki was the same question,
What you're doing.
He also wanted to finish her life.
Lalita but not such a big compromise
You guys were disappointed with life have committed suicide
But because of that,
You get another one.
Be each other's support.
You have to respect the sacrifice of Lalita,
For which he killed himself alive,
Cancer deaths do not desire and rejected.
Son, you Marry Janki,
is the only way for you
Wow wow! Wow! Broke the record,
5 years in practice all cases won.
Not even beat a lawsuit.
Lawyers are proud to be your advocate.
Your clerk as a clerk and I was proud.
Biscuit bring two,
I should Barfi, should Peda
Oh shut up, children eat.
Look,
Hey where are all of them?
Come early,
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon,
Janaki,
Look,
I am in love with the children,
Would like to bring everything
But the mother heard a voice, all escape.
Yes, Janaki.
Because your not mother
in the world there are kids only his mother
could not be anyone else.
Okay.
I love kids so much,
But God does not give me children, why?
I am daily worships,
I beg to children.
Why do I still not have children?
You should not kid Atma Ram, yet
yet God has given,
This is how they justified?
Janaki,
our marriage was so limitation?
7 years
if there is still some 70 years.
The child is full of chance.
Right?
You just sound like the bride of the first night
and the brightness of God's
mercy had not even matter
I think today like hero.
Not this point,
youth heve safe then child
Am i right?
Yes.
And if crop farming have to start so early.
The weather is good,
what do you think?
What do you think?
Monday, why you kill Tuesday
Dad, Wednesday killed yesterday
if your not trust then ask saturday,
Saturday what are ...?
Hey Ray Ray Ray's calendar of son,
Do not fight.
Listen, God has give us 6 children.
We have their names placed on
Just short of a Sunday,
By the grace of God to be the girl, we
Sunday is a holiday
the name of a child in the house
6 children, 6 years ago,
like calendars are hanging
hey Listen,
killed. Sunday I should
Please give, me
the girl want, give me.
Also like the girl,
But outside,
Hey,
my God, how is stupid husband give me
Sir said,
children should arrive half an hour before
I know
you do not talk.
But, keep in mind that
go out and you have to do?
You got to try and take the first prize?
Just 1 minute first prize win
hey its head,
Then I'll tell you mom
your son will get the first prize
And could not find anyone.
Yaronar,
today your criminal law
one person is saying to you criminal.
Today is the person whom you stayed
Who made the perpetrator?
The condition, his poverty
his helplessness
and society by increasing unemployment.
If he is a criminal,
your society is also criminal.
Only give the punishment crime will not be over.
Crime is a poisonous tree
its root begins on biting. cutting
accept it and I would dont say anything.
That solve yaronar.
Well done son,
lawyer acting was very nice, God bless you.
Sir, the record is break
about to making a child,
Who you?
Yes, me, my wife.
Hey sister, you have said many times
the children do not fast-worship,
But you did not listen.
The Look
What I slept that night,
today morning she eating Carrie.
And saying that's going to happen
Really Sundari? You are so lucky.
Lucky?
Oh my bad luck started.
Atmaram you're saying is like
it's full blame of her
all blame of her
night calling me sound like shhhhshhh
And so I say, baby, drop,
drop the child.
I die
I will go to even though it will keep the baby.
And I will be bulldozed child
I'll be the cause,
I will be bulldozed.
Sir, the decision to terminate, and you're generating.
Wait,
I will decide.
I will tell of the evening
Sundari whart should do?
Well, let's go
Atmaram not want to child
But his wife want
the child will remain in any case
What have you decided?
I? Can not fight fate therefore,
I have decided
We will adopt the child
we'll take it.
Oh wow that looks like the
I talk to not Janki
have any smart lawyer sensible
Janaki
I am very happy with this decision
Sister-in-law, what you are saying?
Yes're right.
You will give birth to my children,
But the child will adopt.
But in return we give you this ? 10000.
10000?
Oh God, it looks like today, you have the
Ray my Dhanlakshmi
so I think today was
You did nothing but damage the stomach
Today, I feel that after finding ? 10000,
not a Baby in your womb, its lottery ticket.
Sister-in-law, sister-in-law,
let's get you booked on the next year.
What rubbish that you do not feel ashamed to live?
Sister, I understand your feelings.
You want a child in your lap empty.
And I'm glad that my child would
Sister-in-low, I'm moving market.
Not today you will not market,
No household will work,
Despite such a big lawyer
took the trouble to come here and for him
thank you very much
It's All Right,
Anandpur which is your real estate
you have the papers?
May i come in sir?
When she works here?
In the past 5 years this branch of Mumbai
was very smart and hardworking girl
We've got here is the transfer.
It is fortunate that
as soon as it has found a place in
But as far as, its own life is concerned,
Poor very unlucky.
Why?
The day got married
her husband was arrested the same night
Before the wedding
the husband had cheated on a girl.
Her life was ruined,
The girl's brother attacked him
and killed him by her husband in
Gopi Hey, you here?
We live here,
Today we are going to leave the house
Then I thought
I meet my friends.
You saw me today after long years
And after see decided the
Once the storms and hurricanes that
she changed back to the home before
before you go
Get answers only one question,
I only love you have for life,
obsessed with love.
And you have murdered the love,
And by making the blood vermilion blood
filled her sister in demand.
Who gave you the right?
Came out of my own life,
And your sister were left in my life.
Who gave you that right?
Without asking me
my dreams shattered,
Killed my hopes,
who gave you this freedom?
Right, Authority, freedom,
when something in my life has been
The right to decide about his
Right, Authority, freedom
Your love and your innocence
I was convinced.
And in that moment
What, it was my fault
My sister is in love with you,
Even
if you do not meet him,
she is giving up her life so
I was forced,
I felt my sister's funeral
how could your wedding vows?
My sister is a goddess and goddess
like you that only God can give all
So I love you in the light of his life filling
went into a different world.
You brought light into the lives
But got lost in the oblivion.
A fallen human being married skunk variety.
And then,
it has undergone a life of loneliness
Like this, to be alone in the world
No one in this world of yours.
No Lalita, there is a limit to everything.
Now I will not let you spend this life.
Come with me
now and at this time, come to my house.
No, it's impossible,
And this home
not mine, my sister is right.
If she know that,
I did everything for her happiness,
So,
then, it will bear the shock.
Yourself will end
It is not alive and I'll never,
He never knew that
I am here in this city,
Therefore, I am going to leave this house
and go away from here, Ram Babu.
So you want us to leave,
By now that movement we were
are leading a peaceful life
If the mind was understood,
Now
after knowing what your reality will
And in my situation to see
what your sister will not get in Happiness
So what did you sacrifice?
That was the purpose of what
No
I do not I will not
I will never be.
Well
I'll be here on a bet,
The Sister, never know, I am here
He thinks that Lalita was dead years ago.
Tell me, will you be able to keep this secret.
Well, Lalita, I never tell Janaki,
But, to me, is a prerequisite, So let me do that,
can come to you in your pain
just on humanitarian grounds.
One two Three.
The meeting
Of waves with waves
Convergence
Of clouds with clouds
The love of centuries
To be done in moments
Not knowing about the future
The meeting
Of waves with waves
If a thirsty person doesnt drink water
The river levels will drop
If someone doesnt pick the flowers
Its fragrance will spread
The gifts of nature are for the whole world
The showers of love
The love of centuries
To be done in moments
Not knowing about the future
The meeting
Of waves with waves
The winds do not have enough power
To blow away a butterfly from a flower
Even tornados cannot stop
The determination of love
The seasons are singing
The music of happiness
Then why is there loneliness in the heart
The love of centuries
To be done in moments
Not knowing about the future
The meeting
Of waves with waves
Convergence
Of clouds with clouds
Rambabu, Rambabu help me
Lalita?
Rambabu,
In those stormy Waves deep water flowing
I was scared,
I think
You will not be saved.
If I would have died by drowning?
Who stays here alive?
I would have died by drowning in the same Waves.
Lalita Yes, now is sworn,
You are alive, then I am.
You do not, then I can not.
Rambabu
I want to ask you one thing?
What?
Who is Gopi's father?
Why not speak? why are you quiet?
This is not the time these things.
If you will wait here for long
in the minds of those who doubt the
So do not mind
then please, go away from here, go away.
Dantenge
killed 7-year sentence was cut.
Happy independence,
You are my true
My Wife, Indian Women did not take me,
But you come,
Boss, Lalita is working in an office.
Lalita here, then pull the rickshaw to her
You,
What you have current
Whan free from prison?
You probably forgot the date of
but police did not forget,
Let's go home.
This is office
Look, you go, I will come later
Let me work
you do it Work?
7 years after come your husband is
His wife says, instead of welcoming
I do it Work?
Look Lalita,
Come home straight away,
Otherwise if the beast has awakened in me then,
I, I, will come, Boss by informing,
you do not riot.
Learn from me to be a husband,
If your wife is to keep under control
Sometimes Scolding, Hit, abused it
Whether it be a mistake or not.
Soda only soda
Lalita,
What is the fate
7Years ago, you came to me himself
married me But before I could have
The bloodthirsty God, I was in prison, police
I made unusable,
not Peanut
i want like you Bud,
I want your hunger
today I will eat, I will Drink
Today we celebrate this moment
Mummy, Mummy, Mummy,
Mummy? Interrupts,
Son, when a neighbor's house's going
do not speak Mummy Mummy Mummy
I speak uncle, they speak aunt.
The aunt's bell, speak,
Mother, Who is he?
Then the mother
uncle speaking, aunts speaking
monkey somewhere?
In my house, scolding me that, who are you?
You monkey?
Broke out.
Why he is saying to you mother?
What's the matter?
Look at the moment is finished with me,
Speak directly Otherwise,
I'm like a dog barking
You are standing up like satute
Why he called you mother?
Who do you have it?
This is my son,
Son
You lap it
No
I gave birth to it.
How can you be born?
7 years, I was in prison,
We have not celebrated a honeymoon
I was wearing a necklace just for you,
You just became my wife,
Say, How you have become a mother?
After I leave, With whom you spent
You're mistaken
when wear your necklace after
That means wearing necklace,
perhaps you will remember
Before marriage, I had promised you
you do not ever ask me about
and I will not ask you about it.
Therefore not entitled to ask
Silent,
in the absence of the Husband, his Wife, child up to
I've wasted my life many virgin girls
But not touch the girl,
who already destroyed
And appeared as a girl in my house
so what shall I do Quit..
Say, what have you done with the sin?
Kamesh,
Ram Bapu?
Welcome, Welcome
You've come to the right Time.
In the past, you had saved Me As a lawyer
Today I was on the need to do justice,
Now solve the issue,
The day I got married
that day I had to go to jail for
After 7 years in the rest came back,
It was my wife who is no child,
kid who is 3-foot stand that
How this Happen?
Now do you justice,
Ram Babu, the husband and wife's race matter
You please not to interfere in it,
would be better.
Please, get out of here right now
Shut up, Why should quiet he go?
This is my lawyer, my side it will
As far as fees are concerned
Of your salary and I will give it to them
Lawyer to investigate fully.
Ssuri made whole bottle
Have all passed,
I was just able to come,
mother Mother,
Do not cry, son,
do not cry,
Who is this man?
The scolded you you struck out,
Why do I refuse, I will not call you mummy?
What I do not speak my mother?
NO son, speak, you speak to me,
you speak to Mother.
Lalita,
you will be doing is harassing the innocent.
Do not know him, who is the father?
He is afraid to say Mother of his Mother
How long will it?
If the pain and suffering will come to life,
But the burden of pain and suffering
not only to crush the life of a child is wrong,
But the sheer crime.
Laying hands on his head is a must
Why do not you tell who his?
Let me, Gopi is a sign of our love,
Tomorrow is the picture of our past
I know,.
Was already known,
But wanted to hear from your mouth
Our son, who is a symbol of our love
Which proceed in life,
It is in this way, can not live in fear.
To this day happened, happened,
However, after today it will not be in
I will take it with me to My home.
No, it can not,
I, I can not live without him
and he can not live without me
So for this I am alive
that is an excuse of my life.
Neither of these would I when I died.
Do not disassemble him, me.
Leave him with me.
You swear by its head,
This rule will be two of us.
If anyone got to know about it,
Then the day will be the last day of my life,
Okay
What you do not like
it will never come on the tongue of RAM
I will not disclose this secret to
Uncle, uncle, do not go.
Do not go.
Will come back, he will beat me, Uncle,
do not go, do not go, Uncle
please, He beat me. P
fear
No son, After today, he will not touch you,
I am with you, Let's turn to come
Sweat baby
Janki, the son of my friend.
He Live in a Londan
and He is doing business there
what son? How did the aunt?
Uncle-aunty is very good.
My God, how well that speaks English.
Oh God! How good talks aunt.
Sit, I'd take you sweet.
Your house is very nice uncle.
Uncle, uncle who is she?
I come from, is being eats on eats on..
Gopi Son, your aunt no one child
And she who have another aunt,
Which is eating an apple, it's having a baby.
She will give birth to the baby
and then we'll take the baby
For this we are from morning to evening feeding
Uncle, aunt to having her own child.
And that too very soon.
Hey, how do you know that?
Tell Ya Ya,
When if the tell then have boy and see
Tell?
This will come Head, Hey Girl,
Aunt will be the girl.
Janaki,
it avowedly is saying that,
Emerging out of the tongue may be true
The elders say,
Child's tongue is the language of God.
Please God, it's true.
Mummy, Mummy, Aunty is so good,
He loved me so much,
Sweet feed, food feed, was not coming
How many of you are also praised,
My compliments?
Mummy, she said you are so lucky
but the goddess,
who gave birth to children like you
Yes, but mother I was a great laugh,
Was very difficult to stop,
On everything that she say,
You do not blow their jokes or laugh
No, I can never do that,
Rather, the opposite I also Laugh them
I also, my God, O Krishna, said.
The doctor, a little too fast,
SUndari to bless her baby to be comfortable,
Went up the mountain will come to
Have mercy on him, God.
Doctor, Doctor it's boy born
No boy
So the girl is born
No Girl
Infact, your wife is not pregnant.
Ammunition is in her stomach,
doctor, the doctor what happened her?
I did not want kids, then you put the kids line.
When I want a baby, then you have
What is my fault in it
Hey, is not your fault, its my fault ..
Hey, today You have to create ball
Later, football proliferate.
Then, volleyball proliferate
Then, to create a cricket ball.
Then we put on the road to store balls,
Take ball, four Ane, Ane four Geden take.
Atma Ram,
Yes,
Is good news, Janaki Devi is pregnant.
Truly, O Lord, is thy thank you a million
You're talking right spirit
Hey sir, lie in the hell put this divine soul,
The doctor told me that, Janaki's
Aunty,
madam Happy
Are you happy now?
Your wish has been fulfilled in your life,
Very quickly, a little doll-like little Munni
The boy made the gesture
which said the same thing happened
It came to me as an incarnation of Krishna
He said and I became a mother
Why are the roads fragrant?
Why are the flowers blooming?
What is the wind saying?
Why are the roads fragrant?
Why are the flowers blooming?
What is the wind saying?
You get every joy
You get a long life
This is my blessing
The beautiful season says welcome
Ring-a-ring o'roses,
A pocket full of posies,
Husha
Which is the flower which
When you have your kid,
Which are the lamps
Your beautiful eyes
The beautiful season says welcome
Why is vermilion applied after prayers?
As we pray for the long life of our husband
What is the only wish
I have thought that I leave this
We will meet again in the next birth,
Thats a promise
The beautiful season says welcome
Having the desire to smoke, go and bring the Sigarate
go
What is your name?
Ram
Your
Janki.
So Ram babu is the husband of Janaki Devi.
That is my Sadu, When one a Sadu, is Rich
The second can turn the broom
What is it?
Oh my Gul kulcha, you, you are my earning spouse
I, over alcohol, I need the money.
Is the last day of the month,
I have no money.
So what happened?
You Sister a lot of money to do so,
sister?
Demand for her and take
How do you know, my sister,
I know everything.
I am a little bit punk,
Many times I have been in prison
and came out of jail several times.
That's my job is to keep people
I know that your sister is here.
Her husband is a lawyer and has a lot of money
But you did not tell me yet?
Anyway, leave it,
You, you go to your sister,
And bring me the money
No
Are you or I go to your sister
No, not even my sister to run that,
for God's
You do not go there.
Why?
Ram Babu knows that, Lalita is here,
However, she should not know that her sister,
But why?
No, you're lying, it can never be.
I have these stupid things,
Ram Kali, the personification of this
And that the worship of Ram Avatar also do
I understand my wife Devi
and the Devi temple
which means that her home is here,
In the same city, you do not know
No,
I unite my heart, my sister
I do not want to meet me but
You lie
go away from here,
No
Your eyes to see, and so
So lets go my house
and see with your own eyes
Your god Ram And My Godesss
Come with me,
My God, it's not true, do lie out, God.
I can not afford that,
You live a life terrified with him
Come on, you leave the house today.
No, do not rush,
Everything slowly comes automatically
itself in front of the world, the better
you have a request
you did not come here every day
Otherwise it would be wrong
Sister finds out,
Your built home will be consumed
Well done, very good drama is going on
Janaki, how come you here?
Why, I came to become clogged in the
I destroy to be here, ruined or environment?
I just had to know the truth,
And it was known,
I, I always thought your goodness
Oh, God was worshiped
then never asked for anything
Just been praying for happiness
And instead of you
trying to ruin my own home continued,
My only demand is to devour dreaming
No Sister,
Beware ever told me sister,
Shameless
your tongue protruding from it was
And now
now I have grown to hate this term.
While your husband is
my husband wants to snatch the
Enough, enough
you have to give a lot of abuses, to Lalita,
You do not know your sister, Janki
It is a goddess
who give you pleasure yourself
It has the gives you life
which God did not want to give you.
How are Lalita
To learn is very important to know the truth.
Lalita,
Rambabu,
What is the truth?
I said
to you this day in the city kept hidden from me
this is the reality,
Shut up here to visit you everyday,
it is truth
If you are raising a son
And bringing our house kept lying to me,
The big businessman's son,
it is the truth
And if it is false
then why not tell me till now?
That she is here, in this city
in-tell me what's happened?
Say, why be silent?
Silent,
This time you will not understand.
But one day come that
Truth will automatically come to your self,
And then you will repent on their behavior
Come on, Let's go here,
Do not try to trap me into things
Today I shall be decided
only by, Either it will remain in this world,
I will.
Brillian
What is Finishing Touch by husband
So you wanted, your sister will don't
What is squat drama?
I'm your husband,
and he is your sister's husband,
in front of you, your sister's husband
So thathat s why husband went to his
Have to pray.
Otherwise the wife will not get the
and this husband will not get his wife..
How are drama?
Meanwhile, here's husband have to go
If all couples the right outfit, so do not
Wow wow! Kamesh brother,
We also have a similar, good,
We want to take her to our country
The same? Good girl?
This is the best? It is so raw
It is also true girl I have,
Yes, but the problem is
he has a younger brother,
Which always stays put behind him,
You do one thing;
You have both calf and cow,
No, no,
I do not want the child.
We only if the girl is good,
We will then you a lakh
one lakh?
Damn, at 100,000 rupees
the city will carry all the girls.
By separating the child, the girl put in
You keep the money ready
I went and came, I want and come
Which place that I want to take
where Gopi can not come
I, I, will come not without Gopi
No more intelligently,
for you than Husband
other children began to lovable?
You must admit that my orders,
The pups have been admitted
Otherwise I will soft-soft throat
Oh Where is my wife
Leave it,
and come with me directly
Haram of pups, will turn Mundi,
Open the door, open open.
I never imagined that,
One day I will see you in this condition,
how the Life has changes its colors
Lalita she was naughty girl in the village
who had been impressed my mind
and she started liking me,
I love her sank.
And after that I visited Lalita another,
As my wife
went to a desolate world.
I was outraged that,
And then
I saw the true face of Lalita,
That Lalita, who lives quietly
And who sacrificed herself for.
Then she appeared as a
and now,
And now the same as Lalita who are
Who murdered her husband and
Standing in front of you in the
My death is waiting.
Lalita No, I will not let you die.
I will fight your case,
You help me, just so,
These two papers signed
No Ram Babu,
Now I do not want to live,
Because if I'm alive,
Then my Life set lamp will be fire to
So let me hang,
let me die.
If your life was extinguished lamp
So is the life and the darkness,
and he is your son, Gopi.
You have to live for him.
Right now I have it, but also get
Asks the same question, where is
And he will know
that she will never come
then what would become of him
he would be crazy,
Please do not be obstinate
and sign two papers.
Well,
I would like to sign.
But on one condition, however
say,
I was released from prison,
Then I and Gopi will go away from here
You Will not you try to stop us,
Will happily go.
People in the world
have seen the statue of deities,
If anyone to see the statue of sacrifice
see Lalita.
Yaaronar, was assassinated in circumstances
I request the court that,
Keeping an eye on the mid those circumstances,
the case should be decided
Aunty,
What is it?
Mummy will be released from prison
what i know realeased?
What do I know?
I'll tell you if, it will come head
Heads come, head come and it will, it will
I hear what's going on?
Go away from here,
Gopi
Mummy,
has happened to you?
Have you gone mad
What was the child done your damage?
Do hurting him, hating him,
what you'll get
Only I'm give hurt?
You're hurting
giving Lalita, it is to give
all the people hurting me and
Why does not God let me die?
Janaki you become animal,
Rather than animal Battar
who are taking revenge on the little kid,
Today you pushed off
tomorrow than you you can kill him
Better, I take it from here
I am the very dengerious than an
The man is dead within me
What to do?
I do not understand,
For all this only responsible of Lalita.
Truth is thst
Lalita burned her dreams
And she brought light into the world,
And you're saying the same Lalita vile,
But first, know the truth
in this house not you but should
Ram not yours,
Lalita has killed her husband,
But She,
And to save her child's life, forcing
Therefore, in the eyes of the law
not the murderer,
Baizzt it is released and the court
You will sacrifice your sister do?
Your sleep will be bad,
Their blood shall be burned,
But the poor girl for you, burn his life cast
Her love to, sacrificed you
Otherwise, life is what you are spending
you would not even dream of luck
Before your marriage
Rama and Lalita loved each other,
Wanted to marry,
Wanted to settle,
But for your sakes he became
Were reduced to ruin.
Hey Janki,
Otherwise, my heart, my conscience
that I let you go,
This is the life, the Ram Babu.
Sometimes human heart,
has to live even after losing everything.
You kill yourself have got used to
But what should I do?
Even after Die, I, you, your sacrifice
your love shall never forget.
You spoke of love
one thing to say,
My sister used to love me,
She said that,
I will also do my share of work
you Just Study
also studying their part, my part too.
I have a request to you today that
You go home
and my love is in your heart
and love that he deserves it,
Lalita, okay,
as you wish.
Uncle, uncle, the whistles, the
Yes son
the train is going to leave you
God bless you.
Lalita, was my last wishes,
you
So tell Gopi, he once told
Gopi son call him to dad
But his my uncle
no son
You always ask?
He is your Father
Papa
Son
Bye, Bye
We are searching yor from long time
Janki is very serious
mental condition is not ok
just repeating the same thing over and
Lalita?
I was forced to hear the whole story,
You relax,
Mr. Ram
try to convince she soon,
Janaki,
I have sinned greatly,
Me, my sins, let
I, I, on my Lalita's atrocities.
Once you got a call from her
Or else I will die
my child will die before birth.
He has cerebral palsy,
whom she is missing,
May be some difference in
Hello Mr. Ram Babu
Hey Mukherjee?
I'm just in a hurry
you give me your bike, take my car
Lalita, Lalita
Lalita
Janaki is very critical,
Look, otherwise you will not have to meet her,
let's hurry
DR.?
Janaki Devi, the girl arose.
Baby girl so safe,
Elder Sister
Look Janaki, who has come to meet you?
I, I, yours, Lalita
Lalita?
Elder sister
Lalita
you have come
I do not deserve this
But can you forgive me?
Sorry, for what?
Do not cry, do not talk.
No Lalita
I did not recognize my sister
She loved me
and I doubt her
Forgive me
Listen
Bring My child
Give to Lalita
Lalita
we have spent a childhood without a mother.
We know that
do not mother's lap
then fashioned childhood sun burns
I do not want that
That my daughter
So again it's do not Happened,
Give my child the edge of the Support,
Understand that
it's not my,
To diverge from your sister,
Starting today, you're her mother,
Yes Lalita
earth was created for the
Unneccesory I came in,
This story upset,
So
So I am leaving in the middle of the story
But Lalita
be with him till the end of this story
Listen
who Devi is being mother of our child
who is not widow
So
So Lalita
as you have come to light
Which is daylight the Gopi,
the house will find
I am lucky,
Going, going by the
What is the only wish
I have thought that I leave this
We will meet again in the next birth,
Thats a promise