At least you could have told me that
you wouldn't be having dinner!
How can one know about meetings
fixed at the last moment?
What happens during these
meetings and discussions?
Only talks, right'?
And that too on a subject that
has been discussed repeatedly!
Slowly!
If you aren't very tired"
"read this letter!
So that explains it! - It's a
very important letter, lnder!
Read it, please!
What must have been written is that..
"The job is gone, right'? Good!
Why should you be upset?
We'll have to vacate this flat in 3
months! Isn't that reason to be upset?
No! - After 3 months we will
once again be on the streets!
Maybe, that too isn't
a matter of concern!
Till when will this go on, lnder'?
From the time we've married,
wherever we've stayed"
...we had this perennial fear!
Where to, from here'?
In all these years, we don't even
have a house to call our own!
I promise, Pooja, very soon you'll
have a house of your choice..
...your very own house!
DreamsL. Dreams, once again, lnder'?
Pooja, whenever there's any
problem related to the house"
...you think that the world has ended!
Don't talk like lnder, Aparna!
You're my childhood friend, know very
well what a house means to me!
I've not been brought up in
the laps of luxury like you!
I'm an orphan! Stayed in an orphanage!
Since childhood all that
I've dreamt of is my own house.
After marrying lnder I thought
that he would fulfill my dream!
But, he can't work anywhere
for more than 6 months!
Keeps on picking up
fights all the time.
Due to this house problem I
haven't become a mother yet!
What'?
Listen. As long as you two love
each other, it doesn't matter!
Is my lunch ready?
- I'll just lay the table.
How's your cough?
- Better than before!
What's the matter, Pooja, you
look worried'? - Nothing!
She has to find a new
house in 3 months time!
In 3 months? Well, in 3 months
I'll find 300 houses for you!
I'm jealous of you! - Why'?
Why don't we trade places?
- Pooja, please agree!
Well, I'm not at home!
Hello, lnder, how are you'?
You have a long life!
We were talking about you.
No, actually I was defending you!
Yes, she's here. Well, you
don't trouble my friend!
Well, here, talk to her.
Tell. Yes" What'?
But how is this possible, lnder'?
But?" Where are you'?
Okay, I'm coming.
What's the matter, Pooja'? - We'll
have to vacate the house today!
Wh at n ow'?
Take this.
You think it's a joke, lnder'?
I feel that you're turning mad!
No place to stay and you're giving
me these books on interiors!
Who told you that there's no house?
There is a house! - lnder, please!
Your house!
You don't believe it, even now, right'?
Can you read English?
See this, what's written in it'?
Mad!
28 years!" After 28 years, my own
house..l just can't believe it!
Hey Pooja, have you gone mad'?
I havant gone mad! I can't
believe it as yet!
Tell me, how did you manage
to buy such a big flat'?
From where did you get so much money'?
Robbed the bank!
Tell me the truth!
This is a perfect example of
underestimating your own!
I'm your husband and that's why
you underestimated this genius"
...but the world spotted the
diamond among the stones!
What do you mean?
It means that I've got a partner!
He'll invest his money and
I'll use my brains!
We will be making films. We have
started our own film company too!
Henceforth I won't be
working for anybody else"
"but for my ownself!
This is for you!
Don't try to cut out on expenses
to furnish this house..
...no compromises, please!
Whatever you had wished for,
Make all your dreams come true!
And when I return" - Return!'?
Where are you going?
Goa! - Why?
I have to work on three
films out there.
Film star, Kavita is working
in one of the films!
When are you going? - Today!
No, not today!
To gain something, one has to
lose something too!
You wanted a house, right.
You've got it!
Now in the bargain you'll have to
stay away from me for a few days!
And then, you'd be involved
in doing up the house!
Curtains, beds, cupboards"
all these things won't give you..
"Any time to think about me!
Inder, the bedroom is small, but
I'll put up a very big bed!
The walls will be of cream color!
Curtains too of the same color!
How will a red carpet look'?
All the furniture would be of cane!
I'll put a lot of plants
all around the hall..
"As if the greenery from outside
has found it's way inside!
Is Mrs. Malhotra in'? - Yes, speaking.
Please hold. There's a call from Goa.
Pooja! How are you! - I'm fine,
when are you coming back?
May be tomorrow evening. What can
I do, Pooja, work isn't over!
Pooja, are you listening?
Inder, I was just having a dream!
Our child! Just like you!
Inder, you're alone there, right'?
Wh.. what do you mean? - I mean, is
there anybody else in the room'?
Yes" Me and my solitude!
Inder, is Harish there? - Who'?
- Harish! Your assistant.
No. Why'?
You tell him to get me some
plants from there.
I'll get them!
I'm hanging up. Bye Pooja! - Bye!
Don't forget to get my plants!
The water in the tub is
getting cold. You..
Inder.. lnder!
What will happen, Kavita'?
What will happen? - I don't know!
lnder, I love you!
You're stinking! Go and have a bath.
Go!
A forehead like yours" my eyes"
...your nose" and this, my nose!
My lips! Your skin color and mine!
That's some comparison!
Your brains and"
...your hearL. just like you!
Inder, I want a child!
I wish we'd met earlier!
We would have been married by now!
And we would have had a lot of kids!
Inder, we'll have
our children, right'?
We'll have them, right'?
We'll have!
Hey.. how will we look
when we grow old'?
Kavita, how are you'? - lnder!
I'm very tired! - I'm tired too!
Hey.. madam is here!
The watchman informed that you
were on the lookout for a maid!
Come!
What work can you do'?
Utensils, clothes, sweeping
and swabbing. Anything!
I'm not afraid of work!
We're just two of us,
me and my husband!
There's work in the morning
for a couple of hours and"
...in the evening too for a
couple of hours. That's all!
There's house work in the
afternoon. will do!
What would be your salary?
- You tell me!
I'll give 5O now, will increase
it later on seeing your work.
Will do! - What's happened
to your eyes?
Husband beat me! - Why'?
From the time he's involved
with the other woman"
"creates some problem everyday!
Has he remarried? - Not married,
madam.. just kept her!
Had a good job in the municipality"
"lost that due to
his drinking habits!
I've been looking after the
house for the past one year!
Gives him money for his drinks too!
Beats me inspite of that!
How many children do
you have'? - Just this one!
Madam, she'll be with me..
won't trouble you!
I don't want to keep her
alone with my husband!
All right.. take your thumb out of
the mouth, you'll spoil your teeth!
No one would marry you then!
Let me have a drag!
Harish, these past few days, have
you met Pooja by any chance?
Inder, I'm your assistant! Just
come back from Goa alongwith you!
For the past few days, lying
for you, I've become an expert!
What's the harm if you lie for
your friend at some times?
Why do you feel so bad'?
Inder, I respect Pooja and
I don't like this relationship"
"that you share with Kavita!
Inder, what I fear is the day
when Pooja finds out the truth!
If I was in your place,
I'd have left him and gone!
How can you tolerate all this?
What'? Leave" that thought
never crossed my mind!
It's a bond for a lifetime!
Can't snap off just like that!
He beats me, thrashes me..l scream"
but he's my husband after all!
And that other woman, she's amazing!
Doesn't she know that
he's your husband?
She's aware of it, madam"
but she too has problems!
Last night, in a drunken state,
he beat her too! Beat her a lot!
That's our story! Work whole day
and then get beaten up at night!
Move aside!
I'm not afraid of work, madam!
My mom has been working alongwith
her mother since childhood!
And I've been working with
my mother since my childhood!
This has been going on!
But I've decided that my daughter
won't continue this tradition!
She'll study, go to an English
school" be like you!
Madam, you do me a favor!
You keep my salary in the
bank, in my daughter's name!
I've not told my husband
that I work over here.
He only knows about the other
two places that I work.
Will you do that for me'?
Well, will you go
to an English school!'?
Just find out who's come.
- I'll check up.
Shameless! - There's madam inside!
Who are you'? - I'm her husband!
This bitch lies to me,
lies to her husband!
Told me that she works
only at two places"
"and is the earnings of the third
house for some lover of yours?
You go inside.
Why have you come here'?
- I'm her husband, madam!
So what? - What do you mean, this
bitch eats at three houses..
"And I'm hungry since
yesterday night!
Give me 1O rupees advance.
- I won't give you a single penny!
You go from here or
I'll call the watchman.
You go home, I'll come at night.
If you don't give the wife's
earnings to the husband"
...who would you give it to'?
Give me the money! - Are you
leaving or should I..
What would you do'?
- Hey, you leave!
What do you think?
Inder, see this man,
he's drunk and misbehaving.
Hey, what's happening? Who are you'?
Don't catch me, Sir, I'm
asking my wife for 1O rupees.
So what are you doing here'?
Inder, I'll take care of
him, you go in.
I didn't ask you for it!
Hey, you misbehave after
having a drink!
Don't touch me! - Will you
beat me'? - I can hit too!
Throw him down!
You move in, I'm coming.
Hey, you, take him away.
You come home.. - Yeah, I'm coming.
Get lost!
You go too! - Well.. she's innocent!
You shouldn't keep such
people in the house!
It was her husband who was drunk
and beating her up. You go in.
Scolding her for no reason!
Do you know, that lady he'd
come with, that's his mistress!
Inspite of her, she tolerates him!
If it was my husband, I would
have left him a long time back!
Let it be, Pooja. By the way
I should appreciate your taste!
You've done up the house
beautifully, isn't it, lnder'?
By the way, lnder, we'll
shoot our next film here!
Beware if you.. - I was joking!
Don't you ever think about it.
Some of your books are
still locked in the suitcase.
I'm leaving, Pooja.
Well, you just came and
are leaving so soon?
I've got a lot of work, Pooja.
Have to show the film
to the client tomorrow.
That's why I'll have to
work overtime tonight!
I've invited Anil and Aparna for
dinner! - Work has to be done!
How bad would they feel? They're
coming to our house for the first time"
"and you wouldn't be at home.
All right, I'll try to come early!
Inder, mom will be
very happy to see you!
Madam, talk to your mom!
Mom, hello mom, this is Kavita!
How are you'? I'm fine, how are you'?
Health? What?"
Pickle.. Yes I got it.
You listen to me first.
Listen, you used to pester
me to get married, right'?
I'm about to get married!
Yes! He's good, very good!
No, he's not an actor. She
thinks that you're an actor.
Not at all, well, you talk to him.
Talk to him at least!
Fast!
Greetings, mother!
Well, my name" didn't
even tell her my name?
Talk, please!
Well, lnder!
That's right! Why don't you come here'?
To meet Kavita.
What's left over there?
Well, she seems to be
very happy these days!
You don't worry, I'll take care of her!
I promise you that
I'll take care of Kavita.
Well, talk to Kavita.
No, I don't get scared now!
Being with lnder I feel just like I
used to feel when I was with dad!
You don't worry at all!
You come fast. come fast!
Mom?
What's the time'?
2:30!
I'm leaving! - Why'?
You leave at 4 everyday?
I'm very tired today!
And there's lots of work
in the morning too!
Won't you come with me to the door?
Seeing you go out of this house"
...l feel scared of
the vaccum created!
Pooja has got a house now, right'?
You had told me that
whenever she gets a house"
...you'll stay here!
You must have not told
Pooja about me as yet!
And neither will you tell!
If, by tomorrow morning you
don't tell her about me..
...I'll call her up and tell her!
All the money is over and the middle
room still needs to be done up!
Your writing table itself
will cost Rs. 1000!
What are you thinking about?
I want to talk to you!
What'?.. What's the matter, lnder'?
Madam, I'll get the wheat flour.
The flour-mill will be closing!
What's the matter, lnder'?
Pooja, I was thinking of letting
the middle room be as it is.
For work, I have the office!
Was that all you
wanted to talk about?
Yes! Why'?
See this! How fast
my heart is beating?
I thought you'd tell
me something bad!
What bad things can
I talk to you about?
I can't understand.
But, Sir, I had informed
you about today's show!
Maybe you've forgotten!
Forgotten? So what" can't
I forget, that you remind me'?
Which movie are you
watching? - lnder's film.
That movie which stars Kavita Sanyal'?
Madam, don't go in, please!
Fantastic! Fantastic! Very good!
But.. where is the product?
Where is our product?
I want the product!
Dilip, this film has Kavita, who'll
remind the viewer of the product!
We have given Kavita Sanyal
80,000 rupees for this film..
"It's the costliest film in
the world of advertising!
But, we have made this film, not for
Kavita Sanyal but for our product!
Something which isn't there!
- Dilip, you don't understand!
Inder, this film publicises your
romance and not our product!
I invested for my product and
not for your extravagance!
Inder, you leave, you have my oath!
Harish, stop him!
Come on!
Bloody swine"
Madam, did you call me'?
Gulshan, call up at lnder's
place, I want to talk to Pooja.
Sorry, madam, I think" - Do exactly
as I tell you to! - Yes, madam.
Don't know who it was!
How is this nameplate of ours'?
Put it up!
Here! A bit here!
Not there!.. Just a nail here!
Why don't you take a leave for a
few days'? Anil was saying that if..
You could get a leave for a week,
all four of us could go to Goa.
Would be good for you!
I'm telling! I'm telling!
Pooja, I love somebody else!
I love Kavita Sanyal!
Well, Pooja, please try to understand.
Initially, we were very
good friends and then"
"what happened, how it happened,
nothing was in control!
It's necessary to tell you all this.
This is pricking my conscience!
Neither can I work, nor can I sleep"
"stay awake the whole night like mad!
I'll burst open.. I can't bear
it any more! Can't bear it!
Nothing!
Don't touch me!
Come! - Well, I just wanted a minute"
Come in, buddie.. come in!
Sit. What is it, you look worried!
Madam walked out of the shooting.
"Seemed very scared
after talking to you!
So what's new'? it happens
all the time! You know it!
Where is she now'?
Down in the car. Wants to
see you for a minute.
I'll just be back.
Where have you been'? - Aparna,
you come over immediately.
This very moment! - What's
the matter, Pooja'?
You come over, I'll tell you!
Yes, I'm coming.
I can't believe it!
Can lnder do that'?
Nothing's gonna happen if
you take things lightly!
Pack up your belongings
and move out with us.
He'll come to his senses
in a couple of days.
"Then he'll come searching for you!
No, Aparna, she shouldn't
do that! - Why'?
Because this is her own house!
That's why she shouldn't do it!
Pooja, these relations
don't last long!
Give lnder some time!
I'm sure.. he'll
come to his senses!
And he'll come back home!
He.. will he come back?
Pooja, the walls of the
house aren't so brittle..
"They don't break so easily!
This relationship between the
two of you is seven years old!
Have faith!
But Anil, I can't leave
Pooja alone like this!
Madam, I'll stay with her!
I'll leave!
Inder, please, let me apply the
medicine, you may leave after that.
What's happened to me'? it's just
a minor cut! You're simply"
You have my oath, please"
Take, do whatever you want to do!
Do you want anything, madam?
Did the doorbell ring'? - No!
Does she suck her
thumb in her sleep too'?
Don't worry madam, God will
take care of everything!
Go to sleep!
Get up! It's 4!
No, PoojaL. No, no Pooja!
Inder, you go.. you 9°-
In spite of being with me,
you were with your wife!
Only your body was lying over here!
I don't want it! I don't
want your body alone!
You go!
This two-faceted life!
No! Not any more!
Kavita, I'll stay here.. with you!
Maybe, this decision"
...would be best for all of us!
Take me to Kavita SanyaPs house.
I want to meet lnder!
You too, kept this fact
hidden from me! You too!
Shall we go'?
Pooja, why do you want
to affront yourself?
You stay here, I'll call lnder.
I don't want your false sympathies!
I want to meet my husband!
I was trying to tell you
right from the beginning..
...only if you had listened to me..
I feared this day,
lnder.. this very day!
Where's Pooja'?
Outside in the taxi!
What hae you done'?
Why did you get her here'?
What else could I do'? Have
you seen her state? She"
She would have come up!
What do you expect of me'?
What can I do'?
Inder, get over this
madness and come home!
Please, it's too much!
No, Harish, I've made a decision!
You go and tell Pooja
about your decision!
Harish, take Pooja to the office.
I'm coming there. Please!
Harish, Dilip will be coming.
Discuss it out with him.
These daily nuances should be over!
What was my fault,
lnder'? Where did I err'?
I had never thought that one
fine day you'd stop loving me!
I've not stopped loving you, Pooja..
...the only difference is
that I love Kavita too!
Suddenly I felt as if I was
back to the orphanage!
I'm feeling very scared, lnder!
Pooja, you're not alone,
I'm with you!
You have a house,
money in the bank"
"and then we' re still
friends and will be, always!
Inspite of Kavita our
friendship won't suffer!
Inder, forget whatever
has happened!
Let's go away from
here, somewhere far"
"start our life in a new way!
Whatever I lacked in,
whatever my drawbacks"
...I'll try to eliminate them!
Give me one more chance, lnder!
No, Pooja, I've made up my mind.
I'll stay with Kavita. That
would be ideal for all of us!
Kavita, this is Pooja.
Don't hang up.
I want to talk to you!
Don't tell lnder that I'd called up.
You're listening, aren't you'?
- Yes, go ahead.
Well, you're a woman, would
understand what I've to say!
Kavita, I'm all alone.
Other than lnder,
I don't have anybody.
You' re listening, right'?
Kavita, please, don't
snatch my lnder from me..
"Without him, what will
I do, where will I go'?
You're listening, aren't you'?
Kavita, I beg of you,
please leave lnder for me!
He's all that I have.
Without him I'll..
It's been 2 weeks, lnder hasn't
come home, hasn't phoned up too..
...l feel very lonely!
Pooja don't brood over it so much!
You should be relaxed sometimes"
"living like this, all hassled
you'll..- I've tried a lot but..
"Nothing is in my control!
Pooja, it's impossible to try within
the confines of that house..
"Everything in that house
will remind you of lnder!
Why don't you decide to go out
for a few days, meet new people!
Try to be cheerful!
That's right, Pooja. We've an
invitation to a party tonight..
...there'll be very good
people out there too..
...will be some change for you.
No, Aparna. - Yes, Pooja,
you're going for this party!
That's decided. What you
do is, go home by our car..
"Have a change of dress
and reach the party.
We have to go to the
airport to receive someone"
...will come over for
the party from there.
Yes, Pooja!
Where have we met before?
As a matter of fact,
we've never met before!
Aparna and Anil..
Mr. and Mrs. Mehra have"
So, you're Mrs. Pooja Malhotra!
Mrs. Mehra just called,
should be here any moment.
Have you come alone? Where's lnder'?
Inder is busy with some editing!
Come, have a seat!
She's lnder Malhotrds wife, one
who's having an affair with Kavita!
Yes, the same guy's wife!
If you're tired, you may stop
smiling" anyway no one is watching!
Discard this smile from your face to
find out the relief that you get!
My name is Raj" and what's yours?
Poojaji, I've a problem..
...do you think all these people
would appreciate my 'ghazal"?
I'm a professional singer"
don't believe it, right'?
Poojaji, an artist has to
struggle a lot in life!
A talented singer like me has to
sing at such places!" for money!
Yesterday, I sang at
a tonsure ceremony!
Poojaji, if I don't
raise this hand"
"can this blemish in
my dress be seen?
Well, drinks would be
after the song, all right'?
That was fantastic!
Come on, I'll introduce
you to Kavita!
You sang very well!
Hello, you sing well!
What happened?
How did you like the tune'?
Can't you even face me'?
When you have the courage to
brazenly walk into a crowded..
"Gathering, hand in hand
with your mistress"
...you should also have a little
courage to say hello to your wife!
Why did you run away after seeing me'?
My name is Pooja Malhotra..
Mrs. Pooja Malhotra!
The wife of your lover!
Please, I'll come to meet you!
Inder, what is it that
Kavita has that I lack?"
"that you were forced to desert me!
Yes, there is.. Kavita, you
do have something special!
According to our preachings, a wife,
while serving her husband"
"has to sometimes assume
the role of a mother"
"sometimes that of a sister"
"and in bed, has to assume
the role of a prostitute.
"Something that she's
taking care of!
Give me one more chance, lnder,
I'll try to make up for that too!
Why are you running away?
Why don't you face the truth?
These things do happen.
Please leave her alone!
You go and sing!
I told you to leave her alone.
You raise your hand on me.. you swine!
Leave me.. I'll take care of him..
I'm all right now, thank you!
Left me..
In bed, has to assume
the role of a prostitute"
"something that she's
taking care of!
In bed, has to assume
the role of a prostitute"
"something that she's
taking care of!
What happened to you'?
Who are you calling up'?
Doctor, this is Kavita. - Yes,
Kavita, what's the matter?
I'm feeling scared, once
again. I feel very scared.
Who are you afraid of'?
Who are you afraid of'? Tell me!
- I'm afraid of myself"
...of everybody, I'm afraid
of everything!
Where's lnder'?
Inder can't do anything!
He himself is scared.
You come over please! - Kavita,
what has happened to you'?
Kavita, give the phone to lnder.
You come over, please.
Inder, this is Dr. Puri.
Give Kavita two sleeping pills.
Not more than that, it could be fatal.
And.. don't leave her alone at all!
I'll be there as soon as possible.
Kavita, take this, have these pills.
Sit while I get the water.
In bed, has to assume
the role of a prostitute"
"something that she's taking care of!
In bed, has to assume
the role of a prostitute"
"something that she's taking care of!
Kavita, what's this madness!
Spit them out!
Kavita, stop this madness!
Last night, due to your
disgusting behaviour"
...do you know what happened?
Kavita.. that poor girl
tried to commit suicide!
If anything had happened to Kavita,
I would have never forgiven you!
Wouldn't have looked at your face!
What is her fault in this?
Just that she loves me..
much more than you!
If, by mistake I've married you,
it doesn't mean that you..
...go around insulting Kavita!
That would be enough!
Don't mention your mistress
repeatedly in my presence!
This is my house. At least
respect my house!
House! Your house!
Do you want to know the truth?
The house that you call your
own, is due to Kavita!
These things, all of them,
are all due to her.
The very Kavita whose name
you don't want to hear"
...all this has happened
with her money!
Feel like listening
to something more'?
That's a lie.. a lie..
Sir,
Don't ever try to meet me again"
"and if you need money,
send a message through Harish.
Come on, we' re going..
- ls this any time to go'?
What' s the matter?
Madam has given this!
Inder, I apologize for
whatever happened yesterday.
Something like this never
happened in 7 years.
I can't understand how
I stooped so low.
I'm sending the chequebook, the
keys and whatever cash I had.
Your Kavita wants to have a
clear conscience by favoring me..
"But I'll not give her that chance.
Let her live with that guilt.
The 2000 rupees that were in
the account before our marriage"
...I've kept that.
I'm going.
Will try to live a respectful life!
I'm going from your Kavita's
house" not from your life!
Living away from you.. that's
something I've never learnt!
As and when you feel
that you need me..
...I'm there! Will be
always there. Pooja!
Tell your madam to
stop this nonsense.
A lone woman doesn't get
shelter so easily in this world!
Sir, madam wouldn't come
to that house now!
All right, you go!
What type of a woman are you'?
Steal the house, the
clothes or the food"
"but why do you steal the man.
Beware of what you speak!
God will never forgive you!
Over here, only those girls get
accomodation who are into service!
Do you work'? - Yes, I do!
Do you have any certificate or
your company's appointment letter?
Well, I don't have
it right now, but..
No problem, you may give
it in a couple of days.
Write your name and
sign over here.
Are you Pooja Malhotra'? - Yes!
Well, I don't like
this at all'? - What'?
Don't leave your suitcase
open in the room..
You may say that your bra is robbed
or that your pantie is robbed..
...or that your costly saree is
robbed and then you'll blame me.
If you want to stay in my room,
learn to keep everything locked..
"The way I keep it, do
you understand? - Yes!
Brinjal vegetable once again
today! Eeks, who wants it'?
Who's Pooja Malhotra'?
Yes!
You work, right'? - Yes!
So, why haven't you given
the certificate till now'?
I should get the
certificate by tomorrow.
Or else you will be expelled.
Mrs. Bhalla! - Yes!
You shouldn't be giving
rooms to anyone like this!
This is against the rules.
I need her certificate by tomorrow.
All right!
You don't have a job, right'?
I have! - You're lying!
I'm telling you the truth!
No, you don't work. I know it!
Don't be afraid. I won't rat on you!
Fact of the matter is that..
even I don't work!
But I had given the
appointment letter!
HOW!
I have a lot of rich friends,
one of them gave me a letter.
Tonight, I'm going to meet him.
If you wish, I can talk to
him about a job for you.
Now tell me the truth, is
there, or isn't there a job'?
Well, get ready. The job
will be taken care of.
5.. 6.. 7..
8.. 9.. 10..
Open your eyes! - You're so good!
And this!
Did you see that.
He's not stingy like you.
I asked you for your Walkman for
some time and you didn't give.
The day you fulfil my wishes,
whatever you want.
...you'll get all of it
without even asking for it!
Can you arrange for a job
for my friend Pooja'?
She's quite upset!
She's told the hostel people that
she's working but she isn't!
At least arrange for an
appointment letter from somewhere.
Yes, sure, why not! I'll arrange
for it tomorrow itself.
I'll go and get the cigarettes.
Can I take your vehicle'? - Why not'?
Come, I'll take you for a ride!
- No, I won't come.
You want the Walkman, right'? Come!
Pooja, we' re just coming.
You may discuss things with
him in the meantime.
You'll get the letter" by the way,
what type of a job do you want'?
Something in the office!
Leave me!
You're awake'?
How was your meetiing'?
ls the job taken care of'?
What do you think I'm'? Am
I something that can be bought?
Something for the purpose
of an exhibition?
What do you think? I thought
you were a good girl!
That you wanted to help me..
"But you're a dirty and sick woman
and consider others to be the same!
How dare you took me over there?
Don't you feel ashamed of yourself?
How pure you try to be'?
You feel great, right'?
You consider yourself
to be great, right'?
By calling me bad you
consider yourself good!
But how did you get the
right to call me bad'?
You didn't do me a favor
by coming with me.
I went out of the way
because you needed it.
If you can't take care of
yourself, why blame me'?
It's not as if some major
calamity has befallen you!
What must he have done'?
Must have wanted to kiss you!
Must have asked you
to sleep with him!
So, what's the big deal?
Nothing comes free in this world!
Be it desire or need, to get
something you have to lose something!
And then, what do we women
have besides our body to offer'?
Even in a pure relation like
marriage, what is in it'?
The same give and take business!
The day the husband is tired of the
same old skin, he stops giving!
Goes far away in search of a new body!
Who else would know this better
than you, Mrs. Pooja Malhotra'?
Give me some more jam.
Will you give me so little?
Last night, when I was
in bed with Uday..
Please, I don't want to
know about your nights.
Well, listen. Last night,
when I was in bed with Uday..
...he spoke about a girl he
had bedded many times.
She is a receptionist
in a record company.
She's going to Australia.
Before the company guys release
an ad in the papers"
...why don't you go and try'?
Don't think that I'm staying
idle and giving you this job.
I'm not so great!
9 to 6 every day, 6 days a
week and just 900 Rs]?
I want a lot more from life!
And to get this lot more..
I'm ready to give a lot more!
This is the address of
the record company.
Go, try for the job.
This is my first class pass,
your money will be saved!
Others may not meet
but we will meeL.
"Maybe that's what is
written in our destiny!
Have you come for an interview?
I have an audition here.
How are you'?
You're smiling again!
I'm sorry for the scene
I made the other night!
No need to be sorry.
Whatever you did the other night
requires lots of guts!
I was floored! Really!
By the way, you owe me
Rs. 11.40 - What'?
That's because I had to
reach you home that night".
"Had to take a cab.
Instead of paying back the
money and repaying me..
...why don't you treat me for lunch'?
That's if you get a job!
I'll be waiting outside
for you after the interview.
Is it Miss or Mrs.
- I beg your pardon!
I mean, are you married?
We don't hire married woman for
the job of a receptionist over here.
One who is a wife today would
be a mother in the future!
We don't have provision
for maternity leave.
But Sir, I promise you that
nothing of the sorL.
How can you guarantee that'?
One look at you tells me
that there's no lunch for me!
These unmelodious chaps failed
me in the audition too!
Didn't like my songs! Ignorant
lot! All of them!
But, Pooja, there's no law that says
that one can't celebrate defeat!
I'll treat you to lunch! - No, I..
Come along, my house is nearby.
You must be wondering as to
how a person like me..
"Can afford a house like this!
As a matter of fact,
this house doesn't belong to me.
It belongs to Pestonji Ghodewala!
- Who's he'?
A person whose first love is
racing and second love is music!
What an amazing combination!
He's the owner of 6O horses!
This is your grand lunch!
Once at a party, at the request
of some drunkards, I sang"
...he happened to be there,
went crazy over my voice..
...he was drunk and getting emotional
handed over the house keys.
But I've heard that this would
be broken down to make way"
...for stables for the horses.
Eat it!.. I'll be homeless very soon!
What are you thinking about?
I was thinking about where I would
go tonight after leaving the hostel.
You have a house, right'?
- I had a house! Don't have now!
That's funny. You had a house
which you don't have now..
"And I have one which I wouldn't
be having in the future!
Our problems are so similar!
Eat it!
So you want an appointment letter?
- Yes!
Today itself? - Yes!
You have your coffee. I'll be
back in 2O minutes and 13 seconds.
But where are you going?
- To solve your problem.
But how can I give this fake
appointment letter to them?
Besides us, who else knows
that this letter is fake'?
But this is illegal!
- A lie which helps someone isn't a lie..
"And neither is it illegal!
Think of a nice name!
- What'? - Name!
What could be the name of your boss'?
I can't think of anything!
Take this!
You won't agree!
This is really illegal!
If it is illegal,
I will be handcuffed, not you!
Shall we go'? I have to
return this typewriter!
One more drink!
Well, it's your birthday today,
it's not everyday that"
How was the party, lnder'?
- Good! Very good!
We were five of us.
Today is Harish's birthday!
How is Pooja, lnder'?
Who'? - Your wife, Pooja!
Wasn't she at the party'?
Do you think that all the time
that I'm out of this house I'm with Pooja'?
What has happened to you'?
Ask Harish if you want.
Why should I ask him'? He would be
very happy if you go back to Pooja!
That's some style of
dealing with guests!
I should thank you for affronting
my friend! Thanks a lot!
You're sick and slowly but
surely you're turning mad!
You've gone mad!
You're right lnder, I've gone mad!
Do you know why'?
That's because inspite of being mine..
...you don't belong to me!
Inspite of leaving Pooja,
you haven't left her!
No, Kavita, that's not the truth!
That's a fact, lnder!
That's why you haven't
divorced her yet!
Neither will you marry me
nor will you divorce her!
This is a game you're playing lnder!
Inspite of staying in this house,
you'd leave the doors of that..
"House open for you!
So that when you're through with
me you can go back to that house!
Kavita, you know very well
that I haven't come here to return!
No, lnder! - Yes" Yes, Kavita!
So divorce her.
Divorce her and marry me!
Marry me!..
Marry me!.. Marry me!
I'll do that!
Pooja, what was it
in the morning? - What'?
Didn't you see'?
- What didn't I see'?
What time did you get up'?
- 7 o'clock! Why'?
That's the reason why
you didn't see it!
What didn't I see'?
Pooja, this morning I
accidentally got up at 6..
...l saw that there was a lot of
light in the room, I was afraid"
...l opened the window and saw
that a big sun was shining"
...opened the other window and
saw that there was another sun"
...when I opened the door,
there was a third sun.
Why were there three suns
in the sky today?
Why'? - That's because today's
18th September! Your birthday!
How did you know'?
- ls the answer yes or no'?
But, how did you know'?
- Tell me, yes or no!
Yes, but who told you'?
The other day when you
were filling up the form..
I read your birthdate.
Well, Pooja, we get very less
opportunities to smile in life!
This life is full of tears,
sorrows and sadness!
That's why, whenever one
gets a chance to be cheerful"
...one should make the most of it,
laugh to his heart's content!
What do you want'?
I'd like to celebrate your birthday
at my place, at my cost!
So if you could come at around 7..
No! - At 7.30! - No!
8 o'clock!
How are you'?
Fine! How are you'?
I'm fine!
Sit!
How come you came'?
Kavit isn't well! - Who'?
Kavita!
What happened?
She's afraid that..
She thinks that once I leave
the house, I wouldn't return!
Her insecurity is the
cause of her sickness!
She thinks that
when I'm not with her..
...I'm with you!
With me'?
Acts like a child!
She's sick!
What do you want from me'?
What is this?
Request for a divorce!
This is just an excuse to
allay Kavita's fears!
She'll feel relieved when
she sees your signatures on these.
She's very sad, sick.
This is just a game,
a pretence put on for Kavita..
...believe me there's
nothing between us thaL.
Where should I sign?
Here!
Will the signature be in the
name of Mrs. Pooja Malhotra'?
Yes! The date would be 18th September!
18th September?
- It's 18th September, right'?
Your COPY!
Your house is as it is!
If you.. - If I..
If you need money..
Poor Kavita! Wants to be tied to
you by the holy sacrament of matrimony"
...which can be broken
by a mere signature!
Pooja, I want to tell you something!
There's not much of a change, Pooja!
Just by striking off Malhotra
from the name Pooja Malhotra..
...Pooja isn't incomplete!
She is complete by herself!
That's the real Pooja!
That real Pooja is born today!
In future, Pooja will
be standing on her own feet!
She herself will make a
place for herself in this world!
On this, your new birth,
here's a small gift from me.
No, what's the" - Keep it with you,
there's a big surprise in it!
Open it only when I leave!
But this is sheer childishness!
Inder came with the divorce
papers and you signed them!
What else could I do'?
I have told you before too!
You wait and watch"
...lnder will come to you one fine day!
Inspite of signing on
the divorce papers? - Yes!
Is he going to get
his divorce tomorrow?
Will take at least 6 months!
Pooja, I've handled many cases.
In 6 months"
...there is always a compromise
between the husband and the wife!
And the same will happen in your case!
Yes Pooja!
What's the matter, Raj'?
But the fear refuses to leave, Pooja!
- What fear'?
What fear'?
Pooja, do you know that my
first record is being made today!
In some days, this record will
reach all the shops in this city.
People will hear me
for the first time!
If they happen to like my voice
and songs and if my records sell"
...I'd be a star or else
back it's back to square one!
I'm sure that your records
will definitely sell!
Really, Pooja?
Pooja, pray that my records
sell and that I become a star!
I pray that success touches
your feet and that you become..
...a very famous singer!
And don't forget to get that perfume!
Can you call Pooja'?
Quick please, my name is Raj!
She's just gone to the
dining room to eat! - Food!
No, Pooja! - What happened?
You can't eat this food! You can't
eat this, haven't I told you'?
Come!
You will get me expelled from this hostel!
Barged into the dining room! Don't you
know that this is a ladies' hostel?
What's the reason for this madness?
See this! - What'?
This is my car! Mine! - Means?
This is the reason for the madness!
And today, your lunch partner would
be the new star on the horizon, Raj!
Achieving so much success in such
a short time, how do you feel?
Success is an amazing
thing, Pooja! - Why'?
The success of just one record
changes the life of the singer!
Suddenly a lot of people want to
do a lot of things, give many things"
"see this, someone gave the car keys
for a mere stage performance!
Another guy wants to take
me on a tour of Europe..
"And he'll give me a big,
well furnished room in return!
And two rival record
companies are fighting"
...for the rights of my records!
Doesn't all this give you happiness?
I feel very happy, Pooja but..
...for the past few days,
the heart is longing for something else!
And it looks like this success,
wealth and fame may not live up..
...to the demands of my heart!
After getting all this what
else does your heart long for'?
Who says that I can't
get drinks? Call the manager.
Get the bar opened.
Can't get the drinks!
Leave me. I'm all right!
How are you'? - I'm fine!
You're fine! Happy!
Inder, this is Raj!
We've met before!
Yes, at the party!
You sing very well!
Shall we go'?
Aparna will be waiting!
Inder, have you gone mad'?
Pooja, give my love
to Aparna and Anil!
Harish was getting
so embarrased!
You two will you
stop your whispering?
Do you know
that we' re about to record'?
Pooja was telling me that she
bumped into lnder at the restaurant!
How is he'?
Was drunk! Tiredness and worries
writ large on his face!
On seeing Raj with me, might
have thought that he's my lover!
Pooja, how do you know that
what he thought isn't true?
L.\ \ \ \, I?' \ > \ K \ k - \ !
Pooja, I didn't mean to
disturb you! I spoke the fact!
Pooja, I.. - Raj, you're a very
good man, gentle and honest but..
...l can't give you anything!
I'm not asking anything
from you, Pooja..
"Just want to make you
realize that I love you!
Love! I don't know the
meaning of this word!
It's not necessary to know
and understand love, PoojaL.
...It needs to be felt!
But I don't want to feel anything!
I'd like to live
without any feelings!
Let me live, Raj!
Henceforth, we'll not meet!
Hey, you, here'?
You haven't stopped sucking
your thumb till now'?
How are you'?
Madam, you're strong-hearted!
You live alone here'?
Is everything all right'?
- I'm fine! Very fine!
I tried to find you
for quite some time.
Got your address from Aparna
madam. I used to worry about you!
She used to inquire
about you everyday!
Used to pester me to
take her to your house!
Where would I search for you'?
Has she got admission
in an English school?
I've come for that
very reason, madam!
The admissions have
started today.
You please come with me.
People over there talk in English!
I can't understand anything!
And then there are all rich
people's children over there.
They might not admit
her after seeing me!
There wouldn't be
any problems if you come!
Which school? - The one next
to the old house" which one'?
All right, let's go!
Is the child's mother a maid?
- How does it matter?
She has passed all
the tests for admission!
That's fine but our new building
wing is taking shape in our school!
And the requirement of admission
is a donataion of Rs. 1000.
She wouldn't be able to give that!
- I'll give it, madam!
I'll give a 1000 Rs.!
As soon as we get the 1000 Rs.
we'll admit her child.
Why are you troubling me'?
What do you want'?
Pooja, I want to talk to you.
I can't do so here!
What do you want to talk'?
Tell me, what do you want to say'?
Well, Pooja, any relation,
no matter how big, how deep..
...It's a part of life!
Life isn't a part of any relation that..
"The end of one relation
means the end of life!
By grieving for the lost relation,
you can't stop living!
Where have I stopped living?
I'm working, living well!
You may think that way in spite
of not being able to look..
"Yourself in the eye, not me!
Why don't you have the
courage to ask yourself"
"as to what you want'?
Why are you lying to yourself?
I'm lying to myself because"
...I'm tired of the truths of life!
I've heard some bitter truths, Raj!
I know, Pooja, but all the
truths of life aren't bitter!
It is a fact that I love you a lot!
It is a fact that your heart
too has a lot of love for me!
And it is also a fact that
life can't be spent imprisoned"
.by one's sorrows!
Pooja, whether there is any meaning
in your life, your very being..
"That's not for me
but for you to decide!
Don't misunderstand me.
The gap between our friendship won't.
"Lessen till such time
that you decide for yourself!
I can't promise you anything, Raj!
I don't expect any promise
from you, I only wish that..
...you give yourself
one more chance!
Maybe you'll once again
start believing in life!
Well, Raj, maybe,
what you say is right.
"But it's not so easy
for me to agree to all this!
I'll think over it!
- Will you'?
I'll leave!
Pooja, this is Kavita's mother!
I'm Dr. Puri, her psychiatrist!
What' s the matter?
Well, Kavita is very sick and
the sickness is of the mind!
The patient has a
variety of hallucinations"
"and a lot of unfounded fears!
Whatever medicine we've given
her till now has had no effect!
Electric shock is
the only treatment left!
very painful, child!
Only you can save her from that pain!
What Kavita did to you wasn't right!
She destroyed your well-settled life!
She's suffering because of that!
Forgive her, child!
She's only afraid of you!
Inspite of separating lnder
from you she isn't at peace!
Her conscience pricks
her all the time!
She's not mad, child!
You meet her once,
she'll get rid of all her fears!
She'll be at peace!
Will you come with me'?
She wants to meet you too!
Sit!
How is your health now'?
Health? What's happened to me'?
Do I look sick? Do I look mad'?
No! - Now what have you
thought of to frighten me'?
What'?
What game would you play
at night to frighten me'?
Are you afraid of me'?
Why, Kavita'?
For the past few days,
you have made life miserable for me!
You come over every night and cry!
And cry so very cleverly
that only I can hear!
What do you get by coming
to my house and crying?
Does crying lessen sadness?
Are you trying to
nullify your deeds?
Trying to tell me that
it's my imagination!
It could be so! Could be!
So how do I get your
smell from my bedsheets'?
Why do you sleep between
lnder and me like a wall?
Aren't you ashamed?
Inder is now mine!
He was your husband sometimes!
And now he has divorced you too!
Well, Pooja, we' re getting married!
How can you sleep with
some other woman's husband?
Aren't you ashamed?
And why did you throw your
marriage ritual chain here?
So that the small black beads
pierce into my legs all the time!
I get tired cleaning this
floor from morn to night!
Don't know how they manage
to come under my feet even then!
Don't know!
See this!
Do you recognize this?
This isn't my imagination, right'?
Pooja, I'm tired!
I can't bear it any more!
You take my life
if you so desire!
But don't take your revenge
by frightening me like this!
Please, Pooja, forgive me!
Do I still look like mad to you'?
No, Kavita!
You're not mad!
- So leave! Go from here!
I'm going, and I'd like you
to be safe in the knowledge that..
...l will never come here again.
Pooja, I never wished ill for you!
I liked lnder, not your husband!
I wanted to settle my house,
not destroy yours!
Forget it, Kavita.
I never had a house"!
So you never destroyed anything!
Take care of yourself.
I'll leave!
Inder, don't leave me alone!
Pooja, your phone!
You leave, I'll join you!
Tell him I'm coming.
Anil, this is Pooja.
That maid of mine..
"She has murdered her husband!
You come to Khar Police
Station immediately.
Is this her own statement?
- Yes!
She has written in her
statement that her husband"
"stole the money she'd kept
aside for her child's education.
In the morning when she found
the money missing she went in search"
...of her husband and found
him at his mistress' place.
He was inebriated.
They had a fight.
And then, she has written that
she killed her husband with a knife.
You may meet her.
Madam!
I toiled to save that money!
He spoilt my life..
didn't even think about his daughter!
What will happen of her, madam?
She hasn't got anyone of her own!
Now it's sweeping and cleaning
utensils in her destiny too!
I haven't taught her that too!
What all had I dreamt of!
Can't do anything!
What will happen of
my daughter, madam?
Don't worry, I'm there!
Harish, you know that the court
has accepted my divorce request!
I'm getting married to Kavita.
I'll get some cards from the house.
As you're going to the city,
distribute them among our clients.
Inder, I want to tell
you something! - What'?
Inder, 7 years back, I had
decorated your marriage venue!
The one where your marriage
to Pooja took place!
So?
Inder, these hands haven't
changed as much as you've changed!
That's why..
"Take this! - What's this?
My resignation letter.
Who tore these wedding cards'?
Me! - But why'?
What has happened to you'?
I came to my senses!
After tearing the first card"
...l felt a different
sense of satisfaction.
After meeting Pooja,
a question cropped up in my mind!
A marriage which couldn't give
her any security in 7 years"
"what security will it give me'?
What have you decided to do now'?
What do you want Kavita'?
What I want is something
I haven't found out till now.
But today I've found out
what I don't want!
Inder, I don't want to live
this life of lies and deceit!
I don't want to live off the
alms given to me by Pooja!
Don't want a married life
living in the shadows of the curses"
...of a married woman!
Inder, you left Pooja for me!
You may desert me for somebody else!
No, Kavita!
I can't live with this new fear!
What has happened to you
all of a sudden?
I've noticed the flaws
in this relationship!
You leave!
No! No, Kavita!
- lnder, you leave!
You can't do this to me!
- You go!
You can't do this to me, Kavita!
Inder, you leave!
Ma, is Kavita all right'?
She's all right. For the first
time she's made the right decision!
Let her go! - Ma!
You go to Pooja,
that would benefit everybody!
It isn't your right any more but chances
are that Pooja will forgive you!
Please go! Go!
Why are you standing outside?
Come in!
I want to talk to Pooja!
Aparna, you go!
- Come, child!
She'll just come!
Say!
Pooja, I..
There's nothing between
Kavita and me now!
Really!
Just consider that
she has rejected me!
Pooja, anyway she could
never get me away from you!
I'm very sorry, lnder,
but I can't help you in any way!
Pooja, I've not come
to you for any help.
What then?
I've lost, I'm tired, Pooja.
It's true that I've given
you a lot of troubles"
"and it's also a fact that
I will never ever go back to Kavita.
I want to start
life all over again!
Wilh you!
I promise, Pooja, assure you
that I will never ever..
...give you any reason for complaints!
Really, POOP!
Tell me one more truth, lnder!
- What?
Whatever you did to me,
if I had done the same thing"
"and had come back to you like this,
would you have accepted me'?
No!
I met Aparna and Anil.
They told me about this child.
Pooja, by supporting this
child you have" - No, Raj.
I haven't given her support
but have got something from her!
A chance to be a mother!
A chance to share my solitude!
And now'?
Raj, legally Malhotra isn't
a part of my name any more.
I'm fully aware of my own self today!
- I can see that!
I can feel that too!
One day you had said that
I'm complete by myself"
...I'd like to separate my name
from all other names and live as Pooja!
Don't misunderstand me, Raj.
I'm grateful to you that
you have always helped me!
You've supported me but today
your support will weaken me!
Very weak!
I will never forget you, Raj!
If ever I have to return
I'll come back to you!
But, let me go today!
Go, Pooja!
The courage that
has awakened within you..
"That's the true
meaning of life!
Now you will never
need any Malhotra or Raj!
I'll not stop you
for my selfish motives!
Go!
Don't turn around to see, Pooja,
look in front! Go!