'Praise and disgrace are the result
of your own deeds.'
'Your shadow will always follow you.'
"Days, months and..
..years will pass."
"But my love will.."
"..never ebb."
Abdul!
Start the car.
You're terrific!
It's not the flush of youth
that works here. But of experience.
Guy's a wizard!
Forget touching any car, he goes
close and they sway like lovers!
You are right, friend.
- Good day sir.
- Good day.
- Good news for you.
- Good news?
Your overtime for today is sure.
he is Sitaram.
He's Laxminarayan's driver.
Their car is not working.
Go with him to their house.
You'll get the price you quote.
I won't work overtime today.
What? You're the king of overtime.
And you're refusing a party.
Are you feeling well?
I sell my time everyday.
But I've kept this evening for myself.
I want to live for myself.
Excuse me for today.
I'll be there in the morning.
Okay!
Radha.
Congratulations on our
25 years of marriage.
To you too.
What's in this?
What are you doing?
The children are watching.
Children?
- Where's everybody?
- Gone for a film.
Film?
So only the two of us are at home?
This auspicious day...
And this solitude.
Good God you are great!
- What are you looking at?
- The lines of your destiny.
...which have grown dull thanks
to mundane household chores.
They are more deeply etched.
My destiny is shining
on your forehead.
25 years have gone by.
But it feels like yesterday.
"Day, months and years...
...will pass...
...but my love will never ebb."
- "We'll see that.
- Sure, do so!"
"Day, months and years will pass...
...but my love will never ebb."
- "We'll see that.
- Sure, do so!"
"Day, months and years will pass...
...but my love will never ebb."
- "We'll see that.
- Sure, do so!"
"Day, months and years will pass."
"Know one thing that
I consider you as God..."
"...I don't know anything
other than this."
"You have to know what
to tell and what not to."
"Now you know it."
"I'll do whatever you tell."
"But my love will never ebb."
- "We'll see that.
- Sure, do so!"
"I want to share all
my joys and sorrows with you."
"I've accepted you as my life-partner."
"You are my anchor."
"Our love will only grow."
"But my love will never ebb."
- "We'll see that.
- Sure, do so!"
Rascal! Scoundrel!
Despite so many warnings,
you haven't learnt a lesson!
- Daddy.
- Shut up!
He has forgotten his position
because you encourage him!
A pauper mechanic.
Who looks at our cars for his bread.
He dare do this! Rascal!
Do you know the consequences
of playing with my reputation?
I will wipe you out completely!
Come!
Open the door!
Sir...
...where is my Radha?
I've come to take her.
Don't be foolish. Talk sense.
You can write your
own destiny if you wish.
I haven't understood.
Come with me.
Money can buy every feeling,
every moment of life.
This little scrap of paper can
buy humans not Just love.
It's a blank cheque.
Fill whatever you desire.
Can I fill in whatever I wish?
Yes, whatever you desire.
Jugal Kishore's cheque
is never dishonoured.
Here. Sir, honour your cheque.
Scoundrel! How dare you?
You said I could write
whatever I desired.
Honour your cheque now!
Give me my Radha!
Veeru.
Throw this dog out of the house!
Radha!
You...
You've come here?
I've left everything and come to you!
I've come home.
I've come to my own house!
You serve me like a devotee.
Silly boy, people don't give
so much respect to God these days!
You are my God.
What was our relationship?
I was an orphan.
In this crowd of unknown faces,
you held my hand.
Or I'd be lost long ago.
If I can spend my life at these feet,
who can be luckier than me?
Me!
Sewak...
...God knows what relation we share.
Father.
Get my towel.
Mother, make cauliflower
stuffed pancakes today.
- I'll have brunch not breakfast
before I leave for college. - Okay.
Towel.
- Sewak.
- Yes mistress?
- Put some oil in the stove.
- Okay.
Ramesh. Daughter-in-law!
Are you still sleeping?
- Get my sari from the laundry.
- Sure.
- Good morning.
- Live long.
- Sewak.
- Coming!
- What is it?
- Iron these quickly.
I only see Sewak in this house.
he too has limited
horse power like any car.
If you put too much load,
it will suffer a breakdown.
If he is laid up in bed,
nobody will get anything done!
That is why I sleep on
the floor not on the cot!
- Chander.
- Yes.
How was the movie last night?
Very good till the interval!
After that she fell flat.
Fell flat? That's where the
directors of today lose out.
Take this!
In these times of inflation,
I somehow buy almonds for you.
And you give them to the boys!
It's their time to
eat almonds not mine!
Open your mouth! Eat this.
- Ramesh.
- Yes.
- When is your Job interview?
- At 11 this morning.
My blessings are with you.
God will give you success.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Found anything? Mr...
Avtaar Kishen.
It packs up every other day.
I've checked it out and
understood the problem.
- Hi, Daddy. Very good morning to you.
- Good morning, dear.
Come. Let's have some breakfast.
Have breakfast alone.
I'm very late for college.
- Get the car out.
- Your car is ready.
Wow! My car is ready.
That's nice.
Thank you very much, mechanic.
No need to thank me. It's my duty.
Hello Chander.
What's wrong with my sleep
that it keeps me awake?
And your memory that never goes away!
"Betel from Banaras,
Pune, Mandwa or Bengal,"
"Which one will you have?"
"Apply some more lime."
Here you are.
Good day brother.
Good day. Add it to my account.
I certainly will.
- Good day to you.
- Good day Rashid!
Quickly give me some betel leaf.
Where are you these days?
You're like the elusive moon!
Even forgotten your friends!
I can forget myself not you!
As regards meeting you,
I have no time to breathe!
No point hiding from you.
Remember my son, Anwar?
- The one who is abroad?
- Yes.
He hardly writes letters
but sends draft after draft!
2000, 5000, 10000!
Meaning you're having a ball daily!
That is fine. May the Lord
grant him more prosperity!
But my life is miserable!
So much of running around!
Bank accounts, household expenses,
house rent, groceries...
Everything is on my head!
- And your daughter-in-law?
- She's one of God's creations!
She won't spend a penny
without asking me!
If she goes shopping, it's with me!
If she wants to go out, it's with me!
You'll be shocked to hear this.
Even her Jewelry is of my choice!
By the grace of God,
I've got a good daughter-in-law!
What else do you need?
Your old age is great!
You maybe old! I am still young!
I was passing by the confectioner's
he was frying piping hot sweetmeats.
My mouth watered, so I bought
the whole lot. Everybody start!
- What's in this?
- Just a minute.
This is for my daughter-in-law.
Thank you, father.
- This is for Ramesh.
- And me?
Be patient.
This pant piece is for you
And this shirt piece for Sewak.
Thank you.
And this is for my only wife.
At least say thanks.
- Where's yours?
- That's a surprise.
When I wear it on Diwali,
people will watch agape.
Dad, these are great!
Let's have tea.
- Chander...
- So you'll wear this for Diwali?
I wait for your new clothes.
Get something for yourself too.
I spend the day in uniform
and night in a night suit.
It's their time. They go places.
They are Avtaar Kishen's sons
not some nincompoop's!
Mother!
Mother! Dad! I've got a Job!
Congratulations!
Congratulations, brother!
- When do you Join?
- On the first.
But we'll have to pay 5000 rupees
as security deposit within 2 days.
Five thousand rupees!
Where will we get so much money?
Why do you worry? God is with us.
Everything will work out fine.
Good day! how did you come by today?
- I have some work.
- Command your slave.
I need 5000 rupees.
Ramesh has got a Job.
he has to pay security deposit.
- By which date?
- Tomorrow.
Rustom has gone to Ahmedabad.
I'll return it soon as he comes.
You're a little late.
By God, 10000 rupees
were lying in the house.
Then Amjadbhai came,
my brother-in-law...
...he needed it so I gave it.
This is very difficult.
Look there's only one solution.
I'll go to Amjad and
get the money back.
Let him arrange from elsewhere.
But your Job must be done!
No way! he's your relative.
Don't worry about me.
Lord will make some
arrangements for me.
Okay, I'll take leave.
At least have tea.
Some other time. Good bye.
Oh Lord!
Dad!
- What is it daughter-in-law?
- What is this you've picked up?
Vegetables that resemble you!
And that mince...!
how often have I told you
to get fine mince!
The mince is quite fine.
Is that fine? God what a shame!
While eating eye sight is sharp
but weakens when buying groceries!
You do one odd Job but ruin 10 others!
Where are you going?
One rupee is short in the account.
I got some betel leaf
and tobacco for myself.
Lord bless us!
he's got the world's vices!
What expenses you pile up!
I'm fed up! Your son
is sitting cool in Dubai.
And tied this pain round my neck!
I'm so stupid!
I forgot to tell you the good news.
- Good news?
- I've got a whole month's leave.
Start preparations.
First we'll go to Shimla.
Then Red Fort in Delhi, Taj Mahal
in Agra and Charminar in Hyderabad!
I've been watching them from here.
Whenever you need something,
you take me on a tour of India!
What is it?
Actually...
Give me these bangles.
- Bangles?
- Yes, I'll return them in a month.
No, I won't give these.
- Listen...
- Absolutely not!
These are mother's bangles.
Ramesh too is our child.
Silly woman! For whom do I need this?
Remember his condition?
That little baby was
almost breathing his last.
How terrifying that night was!
Doctor.
I am sorry. I can do nothing.
No. This can't be true!
My baby! You can't leave me!
Do anything but save my child!
If anything happens to him,
I'll never forgive you!
What haven't I done?
Consulted doctors, physicians.
I went everywhere.
Where do I go now?
- Knock at mother's door.
- Mother's door?
Knock at Vaishnodevi's door.
Take him to her refuge without
eating or drinking anything.
Nobody returned
disheartened from her temple.
"Whom the Goddess invites...
...different are those people."
...lucky are those."
"Let's go, the Goddess' call has come."
"Let's go, call has come."
"Glories to the Goddess!"
"Let's go, the Goddess' call has come."
"Sitting on high mountains,
the Goddess beckons."
"Let's go, the Goddess' call has come."
"Glories to the Goddess!"
"This is the only place in the world...
...where all sorrows are forgotten."
"The Goddess is waiting
for her dear ones."
"The cool breeze is blowing
carrying her message."
"Let's go, the Goddess' call has come."
"Glories to the Goddess!"
- "Keep saying...
- Glories to the Goddess!"
- "Glories to the Goddess!"
"Keep saying...
- Glories to the Goddess!"
"Keep saying Glories to the Goddess!"
"Keep walking and don't see
the blisters on your feet."
"The one who has
endured so much pain...
...gets that much of happiness too."
"Let's go, the Goddess' call has come."
"Glories to the Goddess!"
"In Vaishnodevi's temple..."
"...prayers are answered."
"Devotees come in tears but
go back with a smile on their lips."
"Let me also ask for a boon,
all prayers are answered."
"Let's go, the Goddess' call has come."
"Glories to the Goddess!"
"I am also a mother, Goddess."
"Only a mother can
recognize another mother."
"I am also a mother, Goddess."
"Only a mother can
recognize another mother."
"Nobody else can understand
a child's suffering."
"How can I see the one in
trouble whom I've given birth to?"
"Let's go, the Goddess' call has come."
- "With love say...
- Glories to the Goddess!"
- "All of you say...
"Glories to the Goddess!"
- "Queen of mountains.
- Glories to the Goddess."
- "Merciful.
- "Naïve.
- Glories to the Goddess."
- "Queen of lions.
- "Gives you boon.
- Glories to the Goddess."
- "Eases the pain.
- "Glories to the Goddess."
Mr. Ramesh, hearty congratulations.
- You are appointed.
- Thank you so much, sir.
I am confident you will do your
duty with honesty and dedication.
I will try my best, sir.
- Carry on.
- Thank you, sir.
Dear friend, my landlord.
here's the rent for this month.
The same 80 bucks
for the past 15 years!
Neither can I throw you out of
the house nor from my heart!
Why don't you buy this house?
- Buy it?
- Yes.
- Why do you pull my leg?
- No Jokes. I'll sell it dirt cheap.
Give me 30000 and become a landlord.
I was born a landlord.
The country was divided. Land got
left behind and the lord came here.
Now I have but one desire.
To make Radha a landlady.
God willing!
The moment I win a lottery,
I'll come over with the cash.
Till then my friend,
make do with the rent.
Good day.
Goodbye, sister-in-law!
Whose telegram is it?
From him. he is coming.
Anwar is coming? When?
- Around Eid.
- Good gracious!
I'll see my son after a whole year!
First see the condition of the house!
What will he say? Stains on the
walls and cobwebs hanging too!
Don't worry. I'll get a labourer.
You want an excuse to splurge!
A two room house and
you can't clean it!
By God you eat like a horse!
Get a broom not a labourer!
Why are you standing? If the mill
closes, you'll have to sleep hungry!
As if she feeds me a proper meal!
- Hi, dad.
- Hi.
- Hello, father!
- Seeing you after very long.
He's always studying.
Brilliant boy! Sit!
I've often told you to
introduce us to your family.
In a day or two.
You always say this.
Scold him hard Dad.
Meeting each other
will strengthen bonds.
Now go home and tell your Dad...
...that he and his family will
eat dinner with us tomorrow.
This is my request and order too!
Understand?
Come!
This is my mother.
- Greetings!
- Bless you!
That is my Dad.
And she is Laxminarayan's
only daughter.
- How is sir?
- He is fine.
My Dad told Chander
and Chander told me.
And I'm telling you, my Dad has
invited all of you for dinner.
Tell Renu to tell her Dad...
...Avtaar Kishen said to tell her Dad...
...that he will come with his
family for dinner tomorrow night!
- The meal was delicious.
- Sit.
The effort with which you've educated
your sons and made them capable...
It's really your courage.
You may call it courage.
You may call it duty.
But I call it love.
I appreciate this love.
You've done a lot.
Now let me do something.
I want to take over all of
Chandar's responsibilities.
His management course.
Training, business.
Leave it all to me.
Assume you're free from his side.
I haven't understood.
I don't see any difference
between a son and son-in-law.
Renu is my only child.
Chander can stay here and look
after my house, business, everything.
So you want to make
him a house husband?
I want to make his future.
Thank you very much sir.
Chander's father is alive as yet.
What are you saying?
Avtaar Kishen lives by his own efforts.
Your wealth can never
wield power over his poverty.
In your false pride,
you're losing a good opportunity.
You'll regret it someday.
Sir, it's the needy who regrets!
Avtaar Kishen.
The one you want to buy with wealth,
has this written on his forehead...
'Not for sale.'
Money can buy everything.
But I'll never sell my wealth!
Father!
Understand one thing clearly.
Renu will come to my house
as my daughter-in-law.
My son won't stay here
as a house husband!
Goodbye!
Yes, I know wealth is great.
But relations and feelings that
aren't sold in the market are greater!
Laxminarayan must be thinking
what a man he has encountered!
But you did speak a lot.
In a way you insulted him.
Insult?
Whatever it be, he is a big man.
A big man is one who
doesn't consider others small.
You're still a child. The fangs
of these wolves are hidden.
As regards your love,
look at your mother.
Her Dad could buy 10 Laxminarayans!
But she left everything and came to me
If Renu's love is true,
she too will come.
Now all that remains is your studies.
Leave that to me.
What is 15000 rupees?
I'll work night and day, slog my
guts out but you'll do the course!
First I trust the Lord.
Then this hand of mine!
From where did you get this Junk?
From the Junkyard of my destiny!
What will you do with it?
I've got Ramesh fixed up with a Job.
Now I'm only worried about Chander.
he wants to do a course
and I will see that it is done!
This will be the last test of my life.
But son, every bone in this is broken!
I'll fix its' bones with my sweat.
I'll put life into it.
And sell it as brand new.
Just be kind enough to give me
some space in your garage.
I'll do your work during the
day and mine at night.
Who has stopped you? Go right ahead!
Take him to the hospital! Fast!
My hand!
What has happened to my hand?
- Doctor...
- I am sorry...
...this hand will have no sensation.
No.
Good God! What has happened!
Who has cast an evil eye on us?
Our own.
I used to work a lot.
Now I've got a break.
Don't cry silly woman.
So what if I've lost an arm?
I have two arms left.
Ramesh and Chander!
With them around, why should we worry?
Don't cry.
Be brave.
This watch is for you.
Perfumes.
- Saris.
- Nothing for my sister?
- I've bought 2 saris for her.
- And my brother?
This suit length for him.
For whom is this?
I bought this for Dad.
Good you did that.
he will be pleased.
If not you who else
will bring for him?
Anwar. Anwar.
Where are you son?
have some sweets.
I'd asked God to send you.
I'm really relieved you came.
After ages, I'm at peace.
Found peace? So long
you were sleeping on thorns!
Walking on fire! I swear,
complain to your son about me!
Tell him I wouldn't feed you!
Made you work like a
slave day and night!
- Tell him.
- Yes! Yes!
You are right!
You've made me a servant!
Since the day you left,
this woman has made my life hell!
Both father and son slaughter me!
Let your heart be at peace!
God is witness that I considered
him more than my own Dad!
But what did I get in return?
What are you watching?
Throw me out by my hair!
Dad this poor thing
serves you night and day.
And you are maligning her?
It's very sad.
I didn't expect this from you.
Come, Zubeida.
Rice pudding.
I love it.
- Avtaar Kishen!
- Welcome, sir!
- Greetings!
Greetings!
- How are you?
- Everything is fine.
Son, you left the garage
and the life went out of it.
Sir!
People leave the world but
the world still gets by.
But how did you come by?
Good news for you.
Good news.
15000 from your provident fund.
You met with an accident
during working hours.
Compensation for that 20000.
And your Junk car...
...that you repaired and dressed up
I even sold that for 20000.
- Really?
- That accounts for 55000.
Mr. Mehta, give him the money. Take it.
- Is this all mine?
- Yes, yours.
Mother, I may forget you but
you don't forget me for a moment.
You made all my dreams
come true in one flash!
You've made me so rich...
..that there's no worry of the future!
Didn't I say I would see
that you did the course?
Take this and catch hold
of Khan uncle today itself.
And get the papers made for the house.
The house should be registered
in your mother's name, not mine.
Congratulations!
Today you have become a landlady!
I won't let this Joy go unnoticed.
I'll celebrate it grandly!
"Lord..."
"Lord, you are too good!"
"You keep giving!"
"Your benevolence is endless."
"Lord, you are too good!"
"You keep giving!"
"O Lord..."
"You gave me such a loving wife
and such a wonderful family."
"You are happy under
all circumstances."
"And are smiling like
the flowing waters."
"Not you or you,
it's me who is the father of two sons."
"That is my greatest wealth."
"Lord, you are too good!"
"You keep giving!"
"O Lord..."
"If you take away something...
...you compensate for it
in a thousand other ways."
"If you take away something...
...you compensate for it
in a thousand other ways."
"I had so many dreams.
You have been very kind to me."
"Some people crib for shoes."
"But there are some
who don't even have feet."
"I'm not in such a pitiable condition."
"Lord, you are too good!"
"You keep giving!"
"O Lord..."
"What can I say about your glory..."
"...you've given me so much money
in my bad days?"
"What can I say about your glory..."
"...you've given me so
much money in my bad days?"
"You gave me encouragement
and the fruits of my labour."
"Good and bad days are
the two sides of a coin."
"In a garden of blooms..."
....there are thorns
also along with roses."
"Lord, you are too good!"
"You keep giving!"
"Your benevolence is endless."
"Lord, you are too good!"
"You keep giving!"
"O Lord..."
Come on.
Okay kids begin.
"Let's go, the Goddess' call has come."
How time flies.
We took Ramesh when he was tiny
to the Mother Goddess' temple.
And today he is 25 years old.
But you didn't let me
fulfil my promise.
You were involved in
your own running around.
Now there's no running around,
Just time to while away.
We can leave whenever you wish.
- Ramesh.
- Yes, father?
On this Ashtami day, your mother
wishes to go on a pilgrimage.
Looks like Mother has called her.
Today is Saturday. Get 2 tickets
of the Super fast for Monday.
Okay, father!
"Glories to the Goddess!"
"Let's go, call has come."
Despite what you say,
I won't give you a penny.
If they are fond of loafing,
let them arrange it themselves.
Ramesh, how is this set?
It has Just come today.
It is beautiful.
Keep this coat for sir.
It will be very cold there.
You are always worried about him.
Ramesh...
What time is the train?
- I ...
- What is it?
- I couldn't get the tickets.
- Why?
I couldn't arrange money.
You couldn't arrange for the money?
Yes mother I tried a lot.
I asked the bank for advance
but I didn't get it.
We didn't want thousands!
You know Chander is studying.
Dad too is out of work.
The house is running only on my salary.
Why don't you go on the
pilgrimage next year?
By then I'll arrange something.
He is right. We'll go next year.
No. Once you've thought about it
you must definitely go.
By the grace of your kindness, I've
saved some money in the post office.
Rupees 500. I'll get that.
Sewak.
My child! You're offering this...
Our pilgrimage has been successful.
- Mistress!
- My child!
- Hello!
- Hello, Mr. Rashid!
- Hello Uncle!
- Bless you, son!
- All fine?
- Absolutely.
Uncle...
If you could open a little account
with 10000 rupees in my bank...
Why didn't you say so earlier?
Anyway no problem. It will be done.
I don't need to take permission.
- Thank you! Bye.
- Bye.
- Is the betel leaf ready?
- Sure but I won't give it.
All right. Let's hear it.
Who belongs to whom?
It's all fate.
When a dear one thinks of us,
a pain is close to the heart.
Amazing!
This reminds me of one.
Goes like this...
Yes, please.
What does beauty know?
What does love understand?
The world lies at the feet
of us who lick the dust!
- Beautifully spoken!
- Thank you.
- Goodbye!
- See you!
- Radha, where are you?
- What's wrong? I'm here.
What Joy is it that
you can't even see me?
- Chander has got through!
- Chander got through!
After all whose son is he?
Radha-Kishen's!
But where is he?
Daddy! Daddy!
By the grace of your blessings
I have got through!
This is no great news for me.
This is the beginning of your success.
It's my heartfelt desire to send
you to America for higher studies.
America!
But you won't go alone.
Renu will go with you.
Every Joy of life will be at your feet.
Studies and honeymoon,
both together.
I can never forget your obligations.
Young man, one has to lose
something in order to gain something.
What?
The need of today has reduced
the importance of relations.
Nobody thinks about anybody else.
Man has to think for himself.
I haven't understood.
It's plain and simple. On one hand
you have status, position, future.
And on the other side is your family.
You can choose whichever one you want.
The choice is yours.
What? You will leave home?
Mother every man has the right
to think for himself.
What is wrong if I think for myself?
I'm making my future.
But... you are our future, son.
We raised you with our blood and sweat
Made you capable enough
to be noticed by others.
And you will leave us?
Is this how you repay your
Dad for his sacrifices?
Sacrifices?
What have you done for me?
Educated me? Paid my school
and college fees?
This is the duty of every parent!
That is what you have done
What else have you done?
What are you saying?
I am right, mother.
What do you want?
Should I let this opportunity go?
Don't weigh your parents'
love with wealth son.
Love! Wealth is even bigger.
You left everything and came here.
What did you get in return?
Stove, grinding stone, smoke!
Your hair has turned gray
doing the dishes!
You spent your whole life
in Just 2 pairs of clothes!
- Shut up!
- No, Radha.
No, Radha.
He is right.
What have we done?
We have done what every
parent does for their children.
Chander! Chander!
Radha!
Mr. Avtaar Kishen?
A father has come to your door
as a beggar not Avtaar Kishen.
What are you saying?
You seem somewhat upset.
Tell me how I can help you.
Have mercy on this poor man
and give my son back to me.
Say whatever you have to Chander.
I don't want to come
between father and son.
You are already between us.
I'm not one of those rich men
whose wealth lies in banks and lockers
My wealth is my children.
You locked that up in your vault.
Avtaar Kishen!
I faced mountains of difficulties
but never lost courage.
But today the sorrow of
a child broke my back!
I suffered, lived in abject misery
but I never stretched out my hand!
Today I put out my hand before you.
Put my earnings of 22 years
in my lap as charity!
I'll be eternally obliged.
Don't accuse me unjustly.
I haven't tied up your son.
You've come here of your own will.
I haven't forced you.
You may leave with
your Dad if you wish!
Come home son. I've come to take you.
I won't go back to that hell!
Have pity for your mother, if not me.
Come and see how she pines for you.
For me both my parents are dead!
No.
Ramesh has closed your account.
He said if I give you cigarette...
...I must take the money from you.
You went out and the
mistress fell very ill.
- What happened?
- She fainted all of a sudden.
I called the doctor.
He gave an injection. Now she's better.
Radha...
- Now how are you?
- Did you go for the wedding?
Yes, I did.
Why didn't you come for the wedding?
Everybody was waiting for you.
Mr. Laxminarayan has sent
these for both of you.
Sewak!
What happened?
Who broke the lock to my room?
- I broke it.
- Why?
The mistress suddenly fell ill.
Nobody else was at home.
- There was no money at home...
- So you broke the lock for money?
You worthless boy! how dare you!
You have pampered him too much!
Today he stole money.
Tomorrow he may steal ornaments!
He has not stolen anything.
What is breaking a lock
to take money if not theft?
I have taken 50 rupees of yours.
I'll take it out from my savings
and replace it by morning.
Stay in your place, rascal!
Why did you stop? Hit me!
He lifted his hand on his
daughter-in-law for a servant!
- Is this the respect we get?
- Please forgive Sewak.
Whatever he did was for me.
As if you were so sick?
We were on our way.
You wouldn't have died in that time!
Ramesh...
Once the peace of the house
is lost, it will only worsen.
Now you earn your living so make
arrangements to live elsewhere.
Why?
I want you as well as us
to live in peace.
That is why vacate this
house as soon as possible.
Vacate the house?
Who are you to throw us out?
The owner of this house!
I am the owner of this house not you!
What is she saying?
Father, I got the house registered...
...in her name not mother's.
Well done son!
You've done very well.
One son stabbed in the chest
the other in the back!
How does it matter
whose name the house is in?
You can stay here as long as you wish.
I don't want to die before my death!
In fact I want to
live even after I die!
Let's go Radha.
Let's go.
I only have 500 rupees now.
I swear by God I'll pay the
remaining 200 very soon.
Do you think sir is running a charity?
First bring the full amount
Then you'll get the key to the room
Sir, my parents have
no roof over their head.
Have mercy on me.
Give him the key.
Thank you very much sir.
I can never forget your obligation.
What are you thinking of?
What is left to think about?
I don't understand what will happen
So what if our kids deceived us..
My experience will never let me down.
I am a skilled worker.
Once I get the tools...
I will write my own destiny.
But where will you get the tools?
That's what I'm thinking of.
No! No Radha!
I'm already indebted to you.
These things come handy in bad times.
A woman's bad time starts
when her husband is no more.
I am alive!
I'm alive. Don't you worry.
Everything will be fine.
Next.
Your name?
Bahadur Singh.
Got in the line again!
No, I've Just come.
You've already donated once
and you say you've Just come!
Throw him out!
What's the matter?
Why are you beating him?
For them selling blood is business!
he drinks and gambles with the money!
What's this child?
Sir, I...
Sir!
See what I've brought!
Sewak...
Where did you get these from?
I...
Did you steal?
- No, I didn't steal.
- Then where did you get money?
I asked where did you get the money?
I met Chander.
Sewak!
You've begged that rascal,
Chander for charity!
Get out of my sight!
No Avtaar!
He didn't ask Chander for money.
He is lying.
Look at this! And this!
Not once, this poor boy sold
his blood twice to buy these!
Forgive me.
Forgive me my son.
Sewak!
Why didn't you take
birth from my womb?
- Mistress!
- Sewak.
"Life is to be enjoyed."
"Life means youthfulness."
"A drink, a message."
"Life..."
"Life is to be enjoyed."
"Life means youthfulness."
"A drink, a message."
"Life..."
"No, life means hard work."
"Time is short and
there is lot's to do."
"Life..."
"All the joys are within my reach."
"Sorrow is a far fetched thing."
"A drink, a message."
"Life..."
"What tradition is this
in the norms of society?"
"The tree bears the heat of
the sun and people enjoy its shade."
"Life..."
"I feel like showering my love for you
and giving my life for you."
"Life is to sacrifice it for others."
"A drink, a message."
"Life..."
"Man dies and takes birth
for thousand times."
"But only the brave and
courageous survive."
"Life..."
I enjoyed it. The food was great!
We didn't get such food abroad.
Our country is our own after all!
Okay, we'll take leave.
- Okay! Bye.
- Bye. Bye.
Hello, father!
Dad, I've been searching for you.
Finally I found you today.
Why all this? For what?
Mother, why does Dad need
to work when we are here?
You'll stay in a hut when we are alive!
I can't tolerate this!
Instead say, you can't bear to see
this hut near your friends' palace?
And you can't bear to see a crippled
man in the hut because he's your Dad!
A dirty stain on the
pristine sheet of your honour!
- What are you saying?
- The truth!
You're scared to see us.
What will people say?
Mr. Laxminarayan's son-in-law
is the son of this shabby man?
Who is sitting on the footpath
with a screw driver and plier!
That's not right Dad.
It is! Take your fraud
face away from here!
I've seen its' ugliness. Go away!
- 50 rupees, please.
- What?
I've stopped working for free!
Radha! Sewak!
I've reached my aim!
I've achieved what I wanted!
By inventing this new carburetor...
Avtaar has solved the petrol
problem to quite an extent.
A car that ran 10 kilometers
on 1 liter of petrol...
... runs for 15 kilometers
with this new carburetor.
It is a great achievement.
Congratulating you on this invention..
We approve of your carburetor.
And recommend it for registration.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you very much, sir.
Radha.
Wishes on our wedding anniversary.
You too.
I'm very happy to see happiness
on your face after years.
The greatest happiness is...
...with every passing year,
our love too is growing old.
See what I've brought for you.
Bangles! My gold bangles!
I thought there would be
diamonds and pearls in this.
But I never imagined you would
give me such a precious gift!
Time had stolen this.
Today I stole it back from time!
Silly woman! This is your principal.
I have to pay the interest.
On every curve in life,
you have given me something.
You never asked for anything.
The need never arose.
When the time comes, I'll ask.
I'll wait for that time.
But now dinner is waiting for you.
Sewak.
- Yes?
Is the order for Universal
Trading Company ready?
They are working double shift.
It will be completed in 2 days.
And what about the
complain about the radiator?
We've asked for the damaged
ones to be sent back.
And we've replaced them with new ones.
At least eat dinner in peace.
I am eating peacefully.
Sewak, what about Mr. Kapoor's...
That's enough. God has given us
much more than we had desired.
Now take it easy.
Even the government retires men at 55.
Man should retire the day
his call comes from above.
Beautiful, Sudha.
Your taste is exquisite.
You've decorated the house so well
it can't be recognised.
Now we need 2 things.
A video and a car.
They too will come.
- Sir dinner is laid.
- Come on.
Please come.
- Take a seat.
- Come.
Take. Start eating!
Mr. Ramesh.
Excuse me.
Welcome.
What happened to our installment?
It will come to you this month.
Every month you put
me off with promises.
And use our refrigerator,
television and furniture.
- This is not right.
- We had some unforeseen expenses.
I don't like to repeat myself.
You are the son of a wealthy man.
It doesn't speak well of you.
Don't worry, Mr. Taneja.
You won't have reason
to complain henceforth.
Okay!
Dinner is turning cold.
Sir Gopal has come.
Greetings, sir!
Gopal...
I am sorry that you lost a leg
while working in my factory.
If one part is damaged,
the entire machinery is ruined.
I've experienced this.
And so I can sympathise with you.
That you say this is enough for me.
You will get your dues
from the company.
From my side...
I give you 30000.
Thirty thousand!
Are these mine master?
Did you see children
how generous my master is?
What a generous heart he has!
he has made a cripple man wealthy!
This money will be useful in bad times
Keep them carefully.
No Gopal! Don't make this mistake!
Don't ruin your life yourself!
This world is very cruel, unmerciful!
They will cut off your other leg too!
This crutch is more dependable
compared to blood relations!
Sorry Gopal.
I have no right to interfere
in your personal matters.
Forgive me.
I want it done at once.
But sir our products are
much more superior to theirs.
Why do we need to sell them cheap?
We will suffer losses.
Sharma...
What you consider a loss,
is the biggest profit of my life.
Wipe out Laxmi Enterprise and
Chander International from the market
At whatever cost!
Yes, daddy.
Why are our orders getting cancelled?
Ball-bearings,
pistol-rings, clutch plates.
They were in demand till yesterday
Why aren't they being sold today?
That...
What's the matter?
Our competitor, Avtaar Enterprises
is selling its' products very low.
"Kashi, Kolkatta and Patna rock."
"When you dance,
the whole world rocks."
- Good day sir!
- Don't abuse our friendship.
One doesn't make fun of friends.
Not this, my brand.
Write it in my account.
You are great.
You haven't changed one bit.
We always talked about you.
Neither have I forgotten.
I missed you badly today.
So I came to meet you.
- What are you doing?
- Washing grandpa's clothes.
- Grandpa's clothes?
- Yes, he is unwell.
So what if he's unwell?
You'll wash his dirt? Get up!
Stupid! You're washing
his dirty clothes!
But you make him
wash your dirty clothes.
Shameless!
Daughter-in-law, aren't you
ashamed to hit the child?
You should be ashamed!
You made him wash your dirt!
Tomorrow you'll make
him beg and steal!
I won't let his horrible
shadow fall on my child!
I swear by God, either I will
stay in this house or him!
Come inside!
Dad, this is too much!
Let us live in peace.
For God's sake go somewhere else...
Anwar...
Where can I go son?
I have nobody in
this world but for you.
Don't throw me out of the house.
I did everything for this house.
Washed clothes and dishes.
Swept and swapped. Stayed hungry,
listened to your wife's abuses!
But I never let the world
hear about our family problems.
I kept up this false appearance.
Don't throw me out son!
Tomorrow if I wander in the streets
nobody will say this is Rashid.
Everybody will say,
this is Anwar's father!
Don't take the family honour
on to the streets my son.
Anwar...
Whenever you take me
out of this house...
...take me out on your shoulders.
Avtaar.
I had fallen in my eyes.
Today I fell in your eyes too!
Everything is in the open!
Eat something.
No, I can't eat.
Rashid, have a bite or two.
No. I'm not hungry at all.
It won't go down my throat.
- Eat one morsel.
- No.
For the sake of my friendship.
God knows how many Avtaar
Kishens exist on this earth!
How many Rashids!
This is a problem.
An issue.
A problem, an issue!
Friends this is not
an orphanage or an inn.
This is our house, yours and mine.
It's a place of relations
based on feelings.
It's for those who are alone
despite being crowded by relatives.
This house is not for those
whom society has shunned.
But those shunned by their own!
What is this injustice that after
life long hard work and experience..
People retire and are thrown away
like useless, discarded parts.
The oil is present but
the lamp is extinguished!
We will light these lamps again!
Muster up your courage.
Create the desire to live.
And proceed forward.
Friends, get up, walk and run.
Don't give up living before you die!
"Friends..."
"Friends, get up and run..."
"...don't stop living before death."
"Friends..."
"Friends, get up and run..."
"...don't stop living before death."
"Friends..."
"We are no less than these youngsters."
"We are not dependent on them."
"So, shatter their illusion."
"Friends..."
"Friends, get up and run..."
"...don't stop living before death."
"Friends..."
"Why are sitting so listlessly?"
"You are such an experienced man."
"Play your innings;
don't run away from the field."
"Friends..."
"Friends, get up and run..."
"...don't stop living before death."
"Friends..."
"We've made the decision..."
"...not to give in."
"Not to give in."
"Live respectfully
not on their crumbs."
"Friends..."
"Friends, get up and run..."
"...don't stop living before death."
"Friends..."
No problem. You can call everybody.
But how did this happen?
I don't understand a thing.
What's the matter?
Nobody is seen in the factory.
All the workers have left.
Left work? Why?
They have been employed at
double the salary elsewhere.
Double the salary!
Who is paying them double?
Dad.
Why is he out to ruin us?
After all what does he want?
Yes.
No, that's not the case.
I'll be there at sharp 4.
Bye.
Good day sir.
- Miss Amy.
- Yes, sir?
Why do you send anybody
without an appointment to me?
Don't you recognise me?
Mr. Laxminarayan,
how can I ever forget you?
You seem upset.
So how can I help you?
You've taken away everything from me!
You've erased my name from the market
You gave me such a kick in
business, that it broke my back!
Somebody's profit, somebody's loss.
Somebody's loss is somebody's gain.
This is the world!
Today you had my factory shut down.
You grabbed all my workers, my talent.
Talent?
Once you too had
snatched somebody's talent!
Laxminarayan!
I will be ruined Dad.
My blood and sweat too
is mingled in that business.
At least think of my future.
I have no interest in anyone's future!
Mr. Chander Kishen...
...today every man has the
right to think for himself.
If I think about myself,
what's wrong with it?
Don't waste my time. You may go.
After every kind of inquiry,
it has been proved...
..that Ramesh has misappropriated
50000 rupees belonging to the bank!
This is wrong. I did nothing.
I did not misappropriate funds.
I am innocent!
That will be decided by the court.
You are under arrest, Mr. Ramesh.
Sir.
Tukaram.
Daughter-in-law!
You and here?
Mother, I am ruined! A mountain
of difficulties fell on us!
The bank people acted mean with us.
They accused my husband of
misappropriation and had him arrested.
What?
Ramesh arrested!
Did you hear?
I am listening.
What's surprising about it?
He is innocent. He has been framed.
Save him father!
Or he will be imprisoned!
We will be destroyed!
Nobody supports criminals.
You've come to the wrong door.
Mother, please do something.
Pay the bail and save your son.
Come with me.
Radha...
You won't pay the bail.
I bind you by oath!
Sir...
This is between you and me.
Don't worry, I will pay
bail for Ramesh tomorrow morning.
What is the need for money?
There is need.
I don't trust Ramesh at all.
And I'm not paying this bail for
Ramesh but for the sake of Radha.
I can't bear to see my life cry.
Release Ramesh Kishen.
- Okay, sir.
Thank you, inspector.
- It is alright.
Sir...
We are obliged to you
for paying the bail.
We can't forget it all our lives.
Strangers are better than family.
You are an angel.
I've done nothing son.
It's all God's doing.
Come, let's go.
Come.
Is Rashid Anwar at home?
- he doesn't live here.
- Then where does he live?
- What's the matter?
- He has won the Provident Fund case.
That had been going on for 5 years.
His draft for 37500 rupees is with me.
37500!
Why are you standing outside?
Please come inside.
- Did you hear?
- What's the matter?
- Remember Dad's case?
About Provident Fund? - Yes.
He won the case! Lord Almighty
has answered our prayers!
Brother don't feel offended.
Somebody keeps coming to pester Dad
so I said he doesn't live here.
Then call him.
God! he's Just had lunch and gone out
- he'll return by evening.
- Okay, I'll come later.
Why bother cosign again?
You can give the draft to me.
- I'm his only son.
- And I'm his only daughter-in-law.
Sorry its government work.
I can't give the draft to you.
This happened because of you!
I ask, in which house
don't people fight?
It doesn't mean you forget him!
Wasn't it your duty to bring him back?
God forbid! Nobody should
get such a useless son!
God knows what
condition Dad must be in!
- Thanks a lot.
- No problem.
This is the result of the
35 years of service you put in.
You deserve it. I must go.
- Goodbye!
How did you come here?
Dad and Mom are here to meet you.
- Greetings, father!
How did you come here?
Is everything fine?
Dad, you left home and happiness
and prosperity left with you.
If we made a mistake,
please overlook it.
May the Lord punish me!
If one cruel word escapes my lips,
you may pull out my tongue!
For the sake of God, spit out
your anger and come back home!
To grind flour?
To wash clothes? To be scolded?
- I swear by God...
- Don't take false promises.
You'll face the Almighty
with the face of a pig!
Hen-pecked! You ruined
everything for one woman!
Father...
Wipe those crocodile tears!
I understand everything.
This is the miracle of money!
My Provident Fund is
dripping down your eyes!
As if it's a bone not cash,
that you smelt and came here!
Hear this carefully!
You won't get a single penny!
Don't be so cruel-hearted!
Take her away from my sight!
The Rashid who lived off your
leftovers is dead and gone!
Keep one thing in mind, God forbid...
...if your son throws you out of the
house when he grows...
...come here with my name.
You'll get place to stay.
We've interviewed you.
We'll let you know later.
Thank you, sir.
Next.
- Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
Your name?
Ramesh Kishen.
- Age?
- 26 years.
- .Qualifications.
- Cheating, deception.
Swindling, craftiness,
misappropriation.
- Father.
- Mr. Gupta...
We don't want such a qualified
and educated man for this Job!
Father.
Chander!
- What is this?
- He is in difficulty.
I want to help him.
If you want to help them do it
with money earned yourself!
Our money is not for charity!
That you distribute to beggars!
Aren't you ashamed to insult them?
You should be ashamed.
You've started stealing!
- You're crossing all limits!
- You are crossing limits not me!
Don't quarrel because of us.
We came to you as we're family.
I hate family!
Go away from here.
I don't want to see your faces!
- This was very bad!
- No it was good!
Shut your mouth!
I've been tolerating you for long!
If you want to live off us,
you'll have to put up with more!
- Renu!
- Shameless! How dare you!
See how unjustly she behaved me!
- I'm her husband!
- I made the same mistake.
Money can change the
clothes not the body!
You are right.
Your father earned some money
and forgot himself and his place!
he blocked our means of livelihood!
And you're responsible for it!
- What's my fault?
- The fault is of the cheap blood!
The way your scoundrel of a
father behaved with us..
I should have thrown you out
of the house at seeing that!
But I'm not depraved.
I won't do that.
But you may leave if you want to.
The door is open. Come dear.
Two bars of Lux, one cream
and one toothpaste.
Excuse me first clear the old account.
It's been 3 whole months.
You owe me 450 rupees.
I'll clear the debt. Trust me.
The days of trust have gone sir.
These days I'm little hard pressed.
I'm not running a factory.
I have a small business.
If everyone takes credit,
my whole business will flop!
- But...
- I will give no credit now!
Times change a bit and you turn away!
have you forgotten you've taken
thousands of rupees from these hands?
But in return for goods.
That was not charity!
Neither have you done me any favours!
When I don't have money, you stop
giving credit! Is this decency?
I know how decent you are!
Have you forgotten it was you who...
...closed your Dad's cigarette
credit when he fell on bad times?
Ramdulare!
Kishen...
Forgive them.
It is your own who are forgiven.
I have forgotten them.
I can't forget.
My children ...will stay with me.
That's impossible!
Why not? Don't I have any worth,
any respect in your eyes?
Can't I do anything?
Who was your partner in Joy
and sorrow? It was me.
I walked with you with a heavy heart.
I never turned to look at the kids.
Because I had the assurance that
they are happy where they are.
But today they are homeless,
with no support.
They are broken in every way.
Whom are you mourning for? The ones
who're perpetual wounds for parents?
They cannot stay in my house!
This is also my house!
I too have some right over it!
You have a right
over my body and soul.
You are everywhere but I have
no place for your maternal love!
Because today you have name!
You have been blinded by
the glitter of wealth!
So blind that you can't
see your own blood!
Don't be so cruel!
They are repenting for their deeds.
And even God forgives all sins
for one tear of repentance!
I am not God!
Kishen!
One day you said I never
asked you for anything in life.
And I said I will ask for it
when the time comes.
And you said you'd wait for that day.
The day has come.
Give me my children!
- Hello.
- Kishen...
It's quite late.
You're still in the office.
When are you coming home?
I may not be able to come home.
I have an important meeting going on.
Kishen!
You came here in this storm?
No storm could stop me today!
Why aren't you coming home?
There's no time. Work has increased.
Work hasn't increased.
It has got spoilt.
Whom are you making excuses to?
Showing this anger? To me?
You know I don't get angry.
It would be better if you would.
You could hit me and be relieved!
I would be at peace!
But why are you burning me within?
What are you saying?
I know you better than I know myself.
I supported my children
so you left my side!
You are punishing me so severely.
You couldn't spend a minute without me
Today it is 4 days and
I am tossing on live embers.
But you don't give a damn!
You broke all relations, gave up
your rights and came here.
I'm living for you.
You have enough people.
A thorn pricked your heart Just
because motherhood beckoned me!
And you're sulking with it.
Why don't you think of
the cross roads I am at?
Wherever I go, I am incomplete!
Even a stone would melt at my state!
But you are not even a stone!
You are a lifeless soul!
No love, emotions, feelings!
You have no heart!
You are heartless!
Avtaar! Avtaar!
Come, sir!
Where is Avtaar?
What's the matter?
Is everything all right?
When we were with you,
we were really happy.
But now he's not the same.
He has changed totally.
Today he has forgotten me!
No! What are you saying?
He can forget himself not you.
I will always remember that night.
And I'm giving this bail
for Radha not Ramesh.
I can't bear to see my life cry.
What?
Meaning.. the bail was paid by..
Hello.
Mistress! Come fast!
Sir has suffered a stroke!
Forgive me.
Don't cry silly.
I am fine.
Radha.
So far I was on duty.
Looks like it's time for me to retire.
Don't say that!
Radha...
I have only one request.
After me make one Apna Ghar
centre in every city of the country.
Make my dream come true.
From my property...
...I leave 2 lakhs to Ramesh Kishen.
And 2 lakhs to Chander Kishen.
Not because they are my sons.
But because their behaviour gave me
a new direction, showed me a new path.
Sewak, who all his life...
... served me selflessly.
I wish to put one
more burden on him.
If something happens to me..
Then my body should be...
...torched and cremated by Sewak.
Sir!
Sir.
"The world never stops moving."
"The world is a stage."
"Friends, bid me a cheerful farewell."
"Leave my hand and let me go now."
"Don't cry and break my promise."
"Leave my hand, friends."
"Friends."