Return this and my love to him.
Here is your ring! This is
what you wanted. Take it!
Now you must be feeling great!
Shame on you!
The girl who was your life,
your love...
The one you were living for...
You broke off with her!
May l know the reason?
Why dig up the past?
l know you loved her a lot.
Shall l tell you something? She'll
always remember the pain you gave her.
So l've kept both the rules of love.
You were ready to fight
the world and die for her!
l don't understand why you did this.
Do you really want to know?
Because l am shattered.
You know the people in this house.
There's no place
in their hearts for her.
lf there was anyone who
could fight for her it was me.
lf there was anyone who could hold
her hand and stand by her, it was me.
As long as l was on my feet,
l was a shield for her.
But today that shield is broken.
What am l today?
An incomplete cripple!
Who can do nothing without support!
That is all right but
did you have to break her heart?
Till l wouldn't break
her heart, make her suffer...
Till l humiliated her,
she wouldn't have left me!
l didn't want to ruin her life.
And your own life?
What about me?
l lost everything.
A gust of wind took away everything.
Now even Chandni has gone.
You didn't inform us
that you were coming.
- l'd have come to the station.
- l didn't want to bother you.
Aren't you ashamed to say this?
- She will stay with us.
- No need to say that.
Who else does she have in Bombay?
One who doesn't have anyone
has to stay in my house, is it?
This won't do.
l need a little space for shelter.
l will be very grateful.
The rent is 100 bucks.
- Water, electricity separate.
Acceptable? - Yes.
l have no extra room.
Manage here somewhere.
How did this happen?
Just assume somebody
cast an evil eye.
God knows why l couldn't be happy.
Now l can neither
forget nor remember.
Yet whenever l remember,
it brings tears to my eyes.
l'm telling you
today you will get a job!
Pay obeisance to Lord Ganpati
before you leave. You'll get the job
Drink this tea and get ready.
Hey! What are you doing?
This is an emergency.
Don't look at me. Just drive.
- You...? - l've come
from Delhi, new to your city.
l'm looking for a job.
l have an interview.
l'm already late. l'll be obliged
if you could take me to this place.
Do you know where l have to go?
Do you follow?
Why don't you say anything?
- Get off.
- Are you offended?
No l meant get off.
This is the place you have to go to.
Listen...l'm sure you'll get the job.
Go in from this door.
- You... sir?
- Surprised to see me?
l was nervous before l came here.
But seeing you has
given me confidence
This is a travel agency.
We take people around the world.
You mean you fulfill people's dreams.
Nobody ever described this
profession so beautifully.
lt will be done. Not to worry.
We have to complete the
formality of the interview.
My name is Chandni Mathur.
l have completed B.A.
l know shorthand and typing.
l have no experience of work
but l promise that...
lf you employ me, l'll work
with dedication and sincerity.
l believe it if you say so.
Come in.
She is Miss Chandni Mathur.
She'll work in our office.
Explain to her about my personnel
files and ticket reservation.
What is wrong with you?
l'm very happy today. - Why?
By the grace of God l've got a job!
Now l can breath, l can live.
l can be alive.
Some of my clients
are coming this evening.
l am very busy today and
they are our important clients.
l want you to take them out
to dinner and entertain them.
l can't do this.
Can't do it? l don't understand.
This is not my job.
Will you tell me what's your duty?
You promised to do any job given
to you with full dedication.
Every job in this office
is part of your duty!
But l don't consider it good.
She doesn't think it's good!
This is the problem with
you middle class girls!
You decide before hand what is
good and what is not!
The dirt lies in your minds.
lf our clients are happy,
it improves our efficiency.
We get business from them.
This office runs because of them!
You are paid because of it!
This is my order.
- l can't do this.
- Then just get lost!
Madam sir has sent this.
What does he think of himself?
Big reception party.
ls this for me?
The colony was raided today.
lt's a government colony. You can't
keep illegal tenants like us.
- Now what? - Nothing. Spend the
night somewhere and return by morning.
- The raid will finish by then.
- l have never seen Bombay.
So let's see Bombay.
We must have parties like this.
Don't worry. The government is
kind. This will be repeated.
Let's get wet.
l'm already wet.
What are you doing?
Aren't' you ashamed? ln the office
you're the embodiment of decency.
And now alone in the middle
of the night on the footpath!
Come here.
She's my friend Kiran.
And her husband.
- We're paying guests in a colony.
- lt has been raided today.
So we're having a forced picnic.
Tonight we're helpless, constrained.
Then come home with me.
Your house?
My mother will be happy to meet you.
Come in.
Meet my mother. They are..
She is Chandni, works in my office.
And this is her friend. Her husband.
Since when have you become so good?
Feeling sorry for mother's
loneliness, he brought guests.
l am trying to be nice
plus they had a problem.
Thank you very much sir.
Consider this your own house.
l'll change and join you.
- Will you have coffee?
- On one condition.
l'll make it and
everybody will drink.
Brace yourself for the worst
coffee you ever had in your life!
- l'm witness to that!
- don't ruin my reputation.
The kitchen is there.
There's a room here if
you want to wash up.
Tell me don't you feel as if
we own this place.
- And you're the guest.
- Absolutely.
- Come here.
- Will you beat me?
Yes l will! Come here.
Such a dear child.
Sir, may l say something
if it would offend you?
You are something in the office
and another at home.
One form is for the world
but one is for yourself.
Do you like the rain?
l love the rains!
l'm enjoying myself!
Let's go. Goodbye.
Couldn't sleep or l woke you?
lf l'd slept tonight,
l'd have lost something.
Even l have lost something.
And l'm searching for it.
Do you stay awake like this?
Staying awake is in my stars.
lt sounds as if you
asked for this sorrow.
When there's no cure for the pain
one must consider pain the cure.
Do you believe that sorrow
is reduced by sharing?
To share pain one has to
undertake a long journey.
Every moment has to be relived.
lt's very difficult to embark
on a journey filled with pain.
From where do l begin?
What are you talking about?
What do you think?
- Let's play a game.
- What game?
l'll make 3 guesses about you
and you do the same with me.
The first, you've
never fallen in love.
You've taken over a huge
business at a young age.
Are you a detective
or an astrologer?
Some terrific incident is
going to occur in your life.
That has already happened.
Now you make 3 guesses about me.
One guess out of the three
is that my life is stark.
Fill it with the colors
of your love.
l want to see this world
with you, through your eyes.
For how long will you be away?
- Why do you ask?
- We've just met and you're going!
lt's just a few days.
What should l get for you?
One condition.
His name is Lalit.
Tell him life is
terrible without him.
Bring him back with you
as soon as possible.
You don't worry about that.
lf he's careless about you...
l'll carry him on my shoulders
and drop him at your feet!
His place is in my heart not feet!
Will you do one thing for me?
- Why do you ask?
- First promise me.
l promise.
Promise to take care of yourself.
And when the time comes,
you'll marry a beautiful girl.
More beautiful than me.
Why are you punishing me?
Life is very beautiful and
l don't have the time.
For me, my love.
Yes l promise. For the sake
of your love and you...
Now l want nothing from life.
Now my life is fulfilled.
And in a flash she had
left my hand and gone forever.
l still feel the warmth of her
palm in mine, her breath on mine.
Whenever l recall her smiling
face vibrating with life...
The burden of the pain increases.
ls this any life?
ls this life worth living?
Just think it's a habit to live.
And nothing else.
And nothing at all.
l like Chandni very much.
Mother you like every girl.
Seeing her has raised
some hope in my heart.
l liked her very much.
ls there any point in this?
People who have to die do die
but the others have to live.
l accept this.
One has to live whether
one wants to or not.
Look at me. Your Dad is no more.
Am l not alive?
Son, now l live only for you.
Even l only live for you mother.
And after me?
Don't say this early in the morning!
Okay. You are sensible.
You're also my son.
lf you live for me
then listen to me.
lsn't it?
Come here.
Book a first class ticket to
Zurich and prepare the visa papers.
This should be done soon.
ln which name should the ticket be?
Are you going out?
There's a conference.
Have to go for 10-12 days.
Can you answer one question?
After seeing you home last night
why did l feel you were no stranger?
There can be one reason for that.
When you meet the first time,
you are strangers.
Sometimes l see the shadows of
my sorrow in your eyes.
l feel in today's world,
every man is lonely.
He wants a companion, a destination.
Yesterday this town was new to me
And after spending some time
in your house l felt...
That l have somebody in this city.
l know nothing about your life.
My name is Chandni Mathur.
l have completed B.A.
l work in Hansa Travel Agency.
After that life has come to a halt.
lt's better if life goes on.
l've been waiting
for you since ages.
We're having our office annual
party l want your contribution.
Here are 100 rupees.
You'll remember me!
How long will you deceive yourself?
You live for her memories.
You still feel warm with her breath!
Her fragrance, the glow in her
still exists within yourself.
Not one moment goes by
when you haven't thought of her!
To hear her voice you call
her up in the nights!
Your heart beats only
because of her memories!
You are right.
She is still my life.
My heart beat, my love.
- But today... - Even today
she'll come running back to you!
Yes!
l remember when l first met her.
l went to call her.
l'd swept her off her feet.
l want to do the same today.
l want to get well.
l want to get better.
Whatever you want will be done.
Don't worry. l'll call the
hospital in Switzerland.
Did you talk to Chandni?
- Not yet.
- Why not?
- What's the hurry?
- l'm in a hurry not you.
l've waited enough.
lf you won't ask her, l will.
Mother these days
you behave like a child.
l tell you l'll ring up
and call her just now.
And ask her when she'll
come here as a bride.
l'll ask her soon as l return
No, today and just now!
- You are blackmailing me!
- So be it.
Okay. l'll ask her as soon as
l get a chance at the party.
Aren't you dancing?
l can't dance.
But why aren't you dancing?
lf l say l too can't dance?
Then l'll believe it.
There's one thing common in us.
Both of us lie well.
Another thing in common.
Both of us talk well.
Then let's go and talk.
l'll win in talking.
How can you say that?
Looking at you l feel
either you don't have a tongue..
Or it has become silent
after talking too much.
- My mother is very fond of you.
- Even l like her a lot.
- Meet her in my absence.
She'll like that. - So would l.
There's a desire in my heart.
- Just name the desire.
- l am frightened.
Why sir?
Because l maybe turned down.
l wish you could come with me.
To the airport. To see me off.
That's all? l was feeling generous
today. You'd have got anything at all.
l'd only want you to be happy.
Because you spread joy
wherever you go.
Don't curse me sir.
l'm frightened of my joys.
lt is said the moonlight
remains for only 4 days.
l wish l could prove
this saying wrong.
l'll change this saying
if l get the opportunity.
lt's time for your flight.
l'll see you to the airport.
Stay here and look after the
staff. Chandni will drop me.
Here one gets the feeling
that everyone is leaving the country
You too come with me.
l mean it.
Why do you think like that?
l've seen life closely.
l have a name.
- l'll have to muster up
some courage. - Then do it.
Without the formality.
That will take some time.
What shall l get for you?
Just get back.
- l don't need anything in life.
- But still...
All right. Eiffel Tower from
Paris, Big Ben from London.
And Statue of Liberty
from New York
There's no place in
my suitcase for all these!
Will you miss me?
l... you...
At least try.
Your flight has been announced.
You still haven't told me your choice
My choice? What can l say?
l want to know your choice.
l am sure your choice
will be the same as my son's.
lf you take so long to buy
one thing, l will...
l have lots of shopping to do.
l want to buy a sari for you.
For me? No, mother...please.
lf you don't listen to me,
you'll get a thrashing.
- On vacation?
- No, business conference.
- And you?
- Treatment.
Hearing one's mother tongue
abroad feels very good.
One misses one's country abroad.
And one's countrymen.
Are you here since long?
lts 4 months and 10 days.
But it feels like a century.
Have you left somebody behind?
Think of it like this,
l've left my life behind.
Let's do one thing. Today we have
the time and the weather is with us.
Let's hear from and tell
each other about ourselves.
From where do l begin?
When l fell in love,
my life was full of happiness!
We broke all shackles,
even got engaged.
- Then?
- The relation ended.
l ended the relation.
l don't understand.
l met with an accident.
l became a cripple.
My life was ruined. Why spoil hers?
That is why l broke the relation.
Now l wait for the moment
when we will confront each other.
Time will stand still.
Tell me about yourself.
My story is of few words.
The first love they say,
can never be forgotten.
Even today when l shut my eyes,
l feel her lashes on my face.
But there were very few moments
of joy destined in my life.
She fell so sick that
she never recovered.
After her, l forgot to smile.
l forgot to live.
l even lost the will to live.
But again the desire
to live has been awakened.
A girl has entered my life.
Life seems good.
How do you feel when you see a ray
of light after ink jet darkness?
l can understand.
Tell me who the girl is.
You started it. First you tell me.
You could say it's the result of
somebody's love and prayers.
- When do you get back?
- Come to Bombay on 28th.
- Don't tell the family.
- Okay, l'll come.
- How far has your love reached?
- l haven't even said l love you.
Live in the jet age
and couldn't do this?
ln the olden days,
flowers did the trick.
But these days ''l love
you'' doesn't work
Buy her a gift.
The more expensive the gift,
the easier it is to say, l love you.
- Take this.
- What is it?
lt's not a tip,
but to say l love you.
There's a pay phone there.
Go and call her up.
Time waits for none my friend.
Before time changes its' mood,
go and tell her you love her.
And call her to the airport.
Let me also see your choice.
Can you guess who this is?
l recognize your voice.
Doesn't my voice convey something?
- Where are you calling from?
- You're evading the topic.
From Geneva airport.
- When will you get back?
- Today. The flight is almost due.
Tell her you love her! Come on!
l have something important to tell you
- We can talk when you return.
- l may not be able to say it then.
- Don't feel shy. Tell her.
- l will.
- Whom are you talking to?
- l've found a friend. Very dear.
- You'll like him.
- l'd be happy to meet your friend.
He wants to partake in our joy.
What are you talking about?
That's why l called you.
- Are you listening?
- Yes.
The flight has been announced.
l want you to meet me at the airport.
- Will you come to the airport?
- Yes.
l told her! l love you!
And do you know she'll be at
the airport to receive me!
So even l get to see
who has made your life!
Your job is done.
But mine is annoyed with me.
lf things go well, we'll make a
foursome. We meet with our dates.
l'm Chandni. l want to talk to Rohit
How dare you call here!
Aren't you satisfied
by ruining our house?
l want to talk to Rohit.
Don't you dare take his name!
You'll deal with me
if you dare call again!
Why didn't you go to the airport?
- Purposely.
- You don't want to forget your past
What has this love
you talk about given you?
Unhappiness, problems.
Has he ever turned round
and asked you... just once...
How are you Chandni?
Are you alive or dead?
How long will you live like a
living corpse for this hollow love?
How long will you live like this?
And his family..!
Do you have that strength?
To go through another
ordeal by fire?
Hear their taunts, abuses!
Learn to look life in the eyes!
Rohit was your past,
Lalit is your present.
Just a minute. Do you have
lndian currency, 50 paise?
Chandni hasn't come.
- Why is nobody picking it up?
- l too will call up.
- What's the matter?
- Nobody is picking the phone.
Mine is engaged.
Won't you say anything?
l've forgotten everything
on seeing you.
l pray to God to give you a
long life and fulfill your dreams.
Meet him. He is Lalit.
Two friends but one heart.
And he's my brother-in-law.
- Mother!
- Felt like seeing you so l came.
This is Rohit. Think of him
as your younger son.
- And this is his brother-in-law.
- Good day.
Okay, l'll take leave.
Don't forget about the meeting.
- How was your trip?
- Very good.
Did you talk to her?
lt's great that you left home.
After this trip you're really flying!
- Chandni was to come?
- Must be feeling shy.
What shame? We'll land up
with our bag and baggage!
Does she know you're coming?
lnforming reduces the romance.
l want to give her a surprise.
- First ask her. - What for?
Just tell her to call her parents.
Before the family lands up,
let's organize the wedding.
l can't wait for the wedding!
What is auspicious day?
Every day is auspicious.
The day Chandni marries you
will be an auspicious day.
The day she'll be mine is auspicious!
- Did she come to meet you?
- Everyday.
- How is she?
- See for yourself.
We've done a lot
of shopping for you.
- Shopped a lot?
- What else did l do?
l've even bought the
ring she'd returned.
This ring is for her.
- Very pretty.
- Watch and perfumes.
- For me?
- Your daughter-in-law.
First tell me why you
didn't come to the airport?
Just like that.
What's the matter?
l want to talk to you.
You've told me everything
about yourself.
But you know nothing about me.
l don't want to know.
l have a past.
l have also loved somebody.
l don't want to know
about your past.
But ...
l want to tell you something.
Don't know why l'm scared.
What is it?
What my eyes kept telling but
my tongue couldn't dare.
l want to marry you.
Are you angry?
- No.
- Are you willing?
Yes.
You don't know how
happy you've made me!
And mother too will be thrilled.
l've never seen Lali so happy.
lt looks as if he's
got the full world!
l gave birth to him but
you've given him a new life!
l've be forever obliged.
l want his life to be
filled with happiness!
And l trust you completely.
You'll keep him very happy!
What will happen to me!
l'm very nervous!
See how l'm sweating!
What will she say on seeing me?
Will l be able to say a word?
l might faint on seeing her!
lt's also probable that she might
faint with joy on seeing you!
What are you staring at? lt's me.
Not a ghost but your
very own live Rohit.
You're looking good.
Dazed? Shall l show you some magic?
Shocked out of your wits?
Extraordinarily amazed?
Look carefully!
l can dance, turn around.
l can do sit-ups, l can dance!
So how is it?
Ask me in.
You've forgotten me.
You never thought about me,
whether l'm alive or not.
This is where you were wrong.
People in love do not die.
lf love exists in their hearts..
No power, no pain can separate them.
Honestly...
Just the thought of seeing you,
the desire to meet you...
Gave me the strength to get well.
lt saved me. l stand before you
only because of your love.
l swear by you if l've ever
been away from you for a moment.
lf a moment went by
without me thinking of you.
l've been cheated once.
But not again. Ramesh and l
have arranged our wedding.
And before there are any other
obstacles let's get married.
Yes or no?
You're not saying anything.
l didn't give you a chance.
Tell me something about yourself.
You must have cried for me.
Cursed and abused me.
Say something.
What do l say?
The phone is ringing.
Not used to attending it?
l kept calling from the airport.
Nobody attended to it.
Lalit here.
You like the rain don't you?
lt's raining outside
so l thought of you.
Look at the rain fall in the lawn,
You'll see the face dearest
to you in every falling drop.
Did you see? Can you see me?
What miracle have you
worked on mother?
She's thrilled to bits!
l told you l'd introduce you to a
pal of mine. We'll meet tomorrow.
The rain here is wonderful.
What's the matter?
l hope in my absence you
haven't found a rival!
There's somebody else in my life.
l am marrying him.
What do you mean?
This is not possible!
You are only mine!
You can't punish me and yourself!
You can't punish our love!
You can't belong to anybody else!
You were mine, you are mine
and you'll always remain mine!
Rohit's Chandni!
Where was your Chandni
when you broke her heart?
When you insulted her love? Did you
ever try to find if l was alive?
How l spent each
moment since that day...
Today again l ask you...
What would you do in my place?
You are right. l have
given you a lot of pain.
l thought l could get you back
whenever l felt ready.
l never thought you would..
l've lost you once again.
This time it is forever.
You be happy.
Tell me what happened.
There's another man.
- Do you know who he is?
- No.
- Does he know about you?
- Don't know. lt's not his fault.
His fault is he's
between both of you.
l feel stifled in this city.
l'll return by the evening train.
What? Won't you
wait for my wedding?
l'm getting married in 2 days.
You have to attend it.
l won't listen to a word.
You will have to stay.
This is my fiancee.
My friend Rohit.
Won't you greet each other?
l asked him to stay for our
wedding. But he doesn't agree.
lt's not his fault. He is sad.
The girl he loved is
marrying somebody else.
But l won't like it if
he doesn't stay for our wedding.
He might listen to you and stay.
We would be happy if you
stayed for your friend's wedding.
lf you want me l will stay.
You're not yet ready?
lt's my friend's wedding. Everybody
will watch when l get dressed!
Everybody will watch the
drunken scene you'll create.
lf we'd get married together,
we'd have a real ball!
lf not mine at least your wedding!
Sometimes l feel you're saying
something but l don't understand.
Even l don't understand.
They must be looking for
the groom downstairs.
- Go ahead.
- Come soon.
Friend you punish me but
not give me the time.
You've become a scene!
- What's wrong? Everybody
is waiting. - Come on.
Save my Rohit!
Save my Rohit! Or l will die!
Go and call the doctor!
Open your eyes! Call the doctor!
ls everything all right?
The blood pressure and ECG are fine
lt's a mild concussion.
He'll be fine in a day or two.
No cause for worry.
People who love don't die.
There's another man.
You are mine, only mine!
You can't belong to anybody else!
l also loved somebody.
l want to marry you.
But you know nothing about me.
Rohit was your past.
Lalit is your present!
l like Chandni a lot.
Seeing her, l have some dreams.
l gave birth to him but
you gave him life!
l'll be grateful forever.
The day Chandni becomes
your wife will be auspicious.
Vermilion adorns
your hair beautifully.
ls the suite booked?
The honeymoon suite?
Decorate the entire room with roses.
There should be nothing lacking.
One gets married just
once in his lifetime.
Two tickets, first class.
What time is the flight?
lt's on time?
l've never seen such a
beautiful bride in my life!
Driver get the car.
Keep the bags in the car.
- Where are you? Not dressed?
- l'm ready since ages.
Where will l go? l am here.
lt's time for the flight.
Where are you leaving me?
l'm also waiting in the flanks.
You take so long
dressing up like girls!
Don't get hot. l'll change slowly.
You're looking beautiful.
Let's go. lt's getting late.
You've given me lots of love.
Live long, be happy.
Mother l'm your other son.
- Don't forget me.
- Can a mother forget her child?
You're my younger son.
Go and be happy.
Why did you do this son?
Mother this was a compromise,
not love.
And one can't live life
with a compromise.
Maybe you're not fated the
joys of a daughter-in-law.
And love is not in my destiny.