Dear.
- Yes.
Come here.
What is this?
A dress for you on
this festival of Eid.
Gorgeous!
You're looking like a newly wed.
Stop it! Wear it for some
more time, mom.
I couldn't see you wearing these
clothes at your wedding,
because I wasn't there.
Let me watch you now.
I'll slap you.
My nephew is absolutely correct.
Why are you scolding him?
Greetings Mr Maruti! Come in.
- Greetings!
You really look wonderful!
Keep it here.
Even your wife is beautiful.
- That's what I'm saying.
Look at my kid.
He looks like his mother.
What are you saying?
- Quiet!
God has tattooed
my complexion on his sole.
If he would've taken my
complexion even by mistake,
we had to mark twice for
removing to prevent bad luck!
A black mark is very auspicious.
Auspicious? His soles have wheels.
He moves so quickly!
I'll always cherish this day.
No one would forget
such an auspicious day.
Maruti, are you in Mumbai now?
I have a good hold over Mumbai.
The train won't move
until I reach the station.
Give brother too.
Have it brother.
It's time to leave for duty.
I'll go with you too.
- Yes! Quickly eat!
Wrap him tight.
You promised to take me.
- I'll take you!
We'll leave to catch our train.
- So early?
I'll drop her at Kolhapur
and leave for Mumbai.
Come along, brother, I'll drop you
at the bus stop. - Let's go.
Bye, dear.
- Bye.
Come son.
Good bye sister!
- Okay.
'CENTRAL JAIL'
Welcome sir.
Congratulations on your
release after 10 long years.
Just one garland?
Where's the second one?
- Second?
The other garland that I was
supposed to offer Salma?
Why are you quiet?
It's too late.
Salma..
- What happened?
Salma got married
after you were jailed.
No!
She can't get married
to someone else.
It would be my defeat and
I've never learnt to accept defeat.
Recognize me?
- Zafar?
Did you think I would
never return from jail?
That you got your daughter
married to someone else.
We learnt your true colours.
You're a murderer!
You've cheated people of millions!
I did all that for your daughter.
And you got her married
to a beggar!
Listen! You still have a chance.
Get her divorced
and married to me.
Divorce?
Impossible!
I prefer my daughter to die,
rather than getting her married
to a devil like you.
I'll kill your son-in-law and
forcefully take Salma away.
No, I won't let that happen.
Move!
- Zafar!
Zafar, it's a crime!
At least fear god.
I am god,
I'm not scared of any other god.
Let's go, Goga.
Allah Rakha...
You have stayed with us for years.
You must look after my family.
It is your responsibility.
Deliver this message to Salma.
Fly away!
You?
Why are you here?
To take Salma
whom I was to marry 10 years ago.
Have some shame.
I'm a married woman.
I don't follow
the rules of society.
The world knows
I acquire what I want.
I'm stubborn by birth.
How many doors will you close?
I'll break open
all the doors of the world.
Be afraid of God and His wrath.
Neither do I believe in God,
nor His wrath.
I'm a disaster for the one
who doesn't listen to me.
Wait, Zafar!
I'll make this fire a pyre for you.
Don't be a fool.
Look at his hut.
I'll keep you in a palace
and bathe you in gems.
For an Indian woman like me,
a husband's house is a palace,
this scarf she wears
is as good as silk
and the dust of my husband's feet
is more than your gems.
Really?
What if I kill your husband?
There'll be
two dead bodies lying here,
one, my husband's and mine.
Get out or I'll call
the entire neighbourhood.
They'll drive you out
after a good thrashing.
Good.
I'm leaving this place right now,
but I'll leave this city
only with my Salma.
What's the matter, Allahrakha?
He's the one.
Dad!
Dad! Let me go.
Oh, lord!
Mom!
Goga!
Mother!
Take us too!
Get lost!
Apply a black mark on him
once you reach Kolhapur.
Stop!
Why did you stop the cart?
Can't you see the water ahead?
It's risky to proceed.
He's correct, let's not go.
Don't get scared by his warnings.
- You don't worry.
We'll miss the bus.
Take Rs. 20 and let's go.
Come on! Move!
- They only want money.
No, please listen to me.
My son! Save my son.
Parvati!
- Save my son.
My son!
Parvati!
- Help!
My son! Help!
Parvati!
No! My son!
My, son! Please someone
save my son.
Parvati!
I'm an orphan now.
I have no one now!
God, despite your presence,
you made me an orphan.
Uncle!
You lost everything,
so did I.
We have to support each other.
Let's go.
The accident
has left her traumatised.
She has lost her speech.
Can she never speak?
Did she have a child?
- Yes, but...
Get him. We can't treat her
unless he's here.
How can we find her child?
- I'm sorry.
It's necessary to get her child.
Doctor!
- Coming!
But doctor...
Why are you worried?
We'll get a kid somehow.
Today's breaking news!
America created a hydrogen bomb!
Aeroplanes are on a 7-day strike.
Today's breaking news!
Uncle Rahim!
It's a one-day journey...
When you reach...
- Hello, Uncle Rahim.
Greetings, son.
Are you going to Ajmer Sharif?
- No.
Today's breaking news. America...
- Hey, paper boy.
Today's...
Are you going to Ajmer Sharif?
- No!
Sir, be seated.
I'll be back with the change. - Okay.
Bob, I've established
a chit fund office
for you in Mumbai too.
- Okay.
But make sure my name
doesn't appear in these matters.
Understand?
Come.
Sir.
Madam, are you going to Ajmer?
Will you offer a sacred sheet
at the shrine?
Pray that I get my mom back.
Mother!
Mom, where were you?
This is my mom!
I'm her son, Iqbal!
- Get out!
Get out!
- Let go of me! Mother!
Nurse, bring the child.
- Yes, sir.
Madam, this is your son.
Get out!
What happened?
Thank God,
Salma lost her memory,
or this boy
would've taken her away.
Do I kill him?
- Kill him.
Mom!
Come on, silly kid!
Stand still.
Bob!
- Let go! Mother!
Mom!
Leave me!
Don't go away, mom,
I'm your son, Iqbal.
Don't leave me!
For God's sake,
don't leave me!
I'm your son!
Stop, mother!
For God's sake, don't leave me!
Don't leave!
I'm your son.
Why don't you speak, mom?
Don't leave me!
Mother!
Leave me!
Uncle!
You scoundrel!
Scoundrel!
Don't worry, uncle,
I'm your right hand from today.
We'll share all our troubles!
Allah Rakha, both of us will
take care of porters from now on.
'415 Express train...'
'arriving by...'
'INDIAN RAILWAYS'
Porter!
Come.
'Brother!'
Hurry up!
Quickly!
You dropped the dog!
You scoundrel! You dropped
my dog.
Bloody fool!
Sir, why are you beating a porter?
What's the matter, uncle?
Hey, he is bleeding!
Sir, you can't
beat them up like this.
You dog! How dare you touch me!
Don't move!
I'll suspend you! I'm a member
of the railway advisory board.
You thrashed our colleague
and we...
Don't you dare move
or else I'll shoot.
What can you do?
What's the matter, Allahrakha?
Really?
Let's see.
Who are you?
Open the window for a while.
My introduction is very lengthy.
I've the blessings of God
right from childhood,
and I've got Allahrakha with me.
I've got badge no. 786,
I smoke cigar no. 20, I'm a porter
and my name is...
- Iqbal!
The one whom I hit on the head,
becomes bald.
What do you want?
A worker should get his wages
before his sweat dries.
But he got a thrashing.
It's better
that you apologize to him.
Never.
No?
Think about it.
If a porter, who lifts others'
burdens becomes a burden on you,
you'll have a tough time.
Seems you'll leave
only after a good fight.
Where will I go?
The railway platform is our home.
What say, brothers? - Yes!
These are the guests.
- Yes.
So house owners will...
- Stay back!
And guests...
- Will leave!
What say, brother?
Would you like to try?
Allarakha, watch the fun.
- Come.
Don't you dare!
Move away!
Police!
- Catch him!
Arrest him.
Sir, please arrest the bearded man.
Leave me!
What have I done?
He did everything!
Me?
- Yes!
One minute!
Leave me.
Sir, our presence
doesn't create a fuss.
But a fuss is created
if we're absent.
Do you want to see how?
Strike!
Hello, sir.
Why did you stop the train?
To register a complaint.
A complaint?
- Yes.
The chairman's son hit an
old porter, he's in the hospital.
We raised a voice, but the
police arrested our leader, Iqbal.
Please give us justice.
PA!
- Yes!
Call a board meeting
and call their leader too.
I'll investigate this.
A board member is the culprit,
how will you investigate?
Spare time for the poor as well.
You have no idea
how we live in pain, in tears.
No one listens to the poor!
They apply bandages to dogs,
but for us, they have no balm,
no bandage, no provident fund
or hospitals.
We shoulder the burden of the world
but no one shoulders our burden.
We have concluded, that
the mistake is yours, Mr Puri.
What?
- You have to apologize to him.
Do I have to say sorry to him?
No!
Well then, please resign.
He has heart trouble.
A person without a heart
can't have heart disease.
It's epilepsy.
Smell my shoes!
Stop that nonsense!
See, it's neither heart disease,
nor epilepsy.
Quiet!
I'd rather resign
than apologize to him!
There he goes.
Mr. Puri has resigned.
Can you call off the strike?
As you wish, sir.
When I say it's over, it's over.
'19483' 'N U D S 4B'
"Porter!"
"We lift the weight
of the entire world."
"We lift it."
"We lift the weight
of the entire world."
"People arrive and depart,"
"but we remain here."
"We lift the weight
of the entire world."
Idiot!
- I'm not an idiot, I'm Iqbal.
Wow!
I think God has created you giving
special instructions to angels.
Shameless!
You ruined my dress!
Your dress is ruined but
your face is blooming like a rose.
Let's go, porter.
"You give a one-time charge
for work by four."
"Don't suck our blood."
"Or take away something else."
"You have paid one rupee less."
"I swear on God
that we work hard."
"We lift the weight
of the entire world."
"We quench our hunger and thirst,
having water and praying to God."
"We work
in every situation."
"We enjoy one holiday,
on the festival of Eid."
"We lift the weight
of the entire world."
"Our life is difficult,"
"even we have a heart."
"We are humans
and we have aspirations too."
"Our life is difficult,"
"even we have a heart."
"We are humans
and we have aspirations too."
"When we are sad, we enjoy."
"When we are sad, we enjoy,"
"smoke a cigar
and eat betel leaves."
"We lift the weight
of the entire world"
"People arrive and depart,"
"but we remain here itself."
"We lift the weight
of the entire world."
Here you go!
Mom, this is
my last application for a job.
If I don't get a reporter's job,
I'll start selling newspapers.
Mr Sunny,
Mr Iyengar is calling you. - Yeah?
I think I got a job!
Look after my belongings.
Come in.
Hello, sir.
- Where?
I'm here!
Greetings! What?
Hello.
- Greetings.
I'm Sunny.
- Okay.
I've studied journalism in London.
- Very good!
I'm a son of a rich man too.
- Really?
My dad can buy such presses
if he wants.
Then do buy them.
- No.
I want to stand on my own two feet,
without my dad's support.
What are you standing on
right now?
If you want to stand on your feet,
make our press stand first,
because our newspapers get printed,
but they don't sell.
Bring front page news,
that our paper gets sold
before it's even printed.
Anna, I'll bring front page news!
- Very good God!
Thank you very much, God!
You're great.
Savitri!
- I'm coming. What's the matter?
Savitri, tomorrow the advocate's
family is coming to see Deepa.
Yes! - I bought
a beautiful sari for her.
Look, it's lovely!
What's the use of a sari
if our daughter is absent?
Where is our daughter?
- She must've gone there.
Catch them!
- Police!
'MUNICIPAL GENERAL HOSPITAL'
I'll provide you news,
but what will I get in return?
Here.
Wow! I saw...
- Speak in Hindi!
Last night, one lady gave birth
to 7 children.
7 children?
The 8th kid is to be born!
Call the doctor!
God!
It's hurting!
No. 7!
It's a fact!
Madam, 7 at a time at one go?
Fantastic!
Congratulations, madam!
Madam, 1 photograph please.
Thank you.
Smile!
Okay!
That's it!
Very good!
This is our daughter Deepa.
Hello.
- Hello!
Deepa, have a seat.
Sit.
- Walk properly!
Get them married
as early as possible.
I'll print the news of
their marriage on the front page.
Like this.
Oh God!
- Oh God!
Why are you so shocked?
I won't charge you for that.
It's my press.
Have a glance at the paper.
No need to see the paper!
Shut up!
Whose daughter is this?
Is she the neighbour's?
She's definitely our daughter!
Whose 7 kids are these?
This girl is ours,
but the 7 kids aren't hers.
See that!
Listen to me!
- Move!
Father!
Mother!
Close the door! Let's go!
Deepa!
Deepa, why are you crying?
Why didn't you tell me
that you're leaving school?
We're going to London for my mom's
treatment and will stay there.
Even my parents
wanted me to go to another school,
but I refused, for you.
And you're leaving me?
I'll return
once I complete studying.
Write to me
and I'll stay in touch too.
Sunny!
Yes, coming.
Keep my photo with you
and I'll keep yours with me.
Let's go.
I'm in this state today
because of you.
Why did you go away?
I haven't been able to forget you.
I haven't forgotten.
Mr Iyengar!
- News reporter! Come here!
Come here!
- I knew you'd go crazy
and you've indeed gone crazy.
I was printing, composing
and developing all night.
I kept on walking back and forth.
I didn't have liquor,
didn't shave and didn't even eat.
You didn't eat.
- No!
Would you like to?
- If you offer with love.
I'll feed you with great love.
Have a seat.
Wow!
Hot food!
Did all your papers sell?
There are a few left.
- Oh no!
Whose picture did you publish
in our newspaper?
That girl's.
And her dad's photo?
- I'll do it!
I'm the father of that girl.
Print my picture!
Congratulations!
You're a grandpa of 7 kids!
Shut up!
That girl is unmarried!
How can she have kids?
You've created a problem,
you broke her engagement.
Now eat this paper up!
Eat this.
How can I eat paper?
I'll add salt and spices to it.
I'll pour curry on it.
Here!
I'll wash my hands.
- Sit!
Eat.
Eat it up!
I've heard that each grain is
destined to be in someone's name.
It seems the one
who has the paper, consumes it.
Have it!
- Eat!
Eat! - Curry and paper!
Never heard of it.
Eat!
It's very tasty!
I can't gulp it.
- You surely can!
Ate it?
He ate it! Now eat this.
- Gulped it?
It'll go down fast!
Eat!
Again!
Kick him and throw him out!
I might as well eat well.
Hurry up! Get out!
- Don't hit me! Let me eat!
Iqbal!
- Yes, uncle!
Look at the beautiful Eid moon.
Happy Eid!
I'll first greet mom on Eid.
Mom, happy Eid.
One should see an auspicious face
after seeing the Eid moon.
For me,
you come after God.
Only you.
But you didn't fulfil
even a single wish of mine.
On every Eid,
mothers get new clothes stitched,
prepare sweets
and hug their children.
But...
But you never blessed me,
for a longer life.
That all my wishes are fulfilled.
You never did.
Well,
may God keep you in good health,
wherever you are.
Enough!
Stop it!
Goga.
- Yes.
When did you last give her a shock?
- 15 days back.
I told you
to give her shock treatment daily!
I'm sorry.
If she gains her memory back,
I'll kill you!
She should forget her past!
Since you've brought her,
she's in the same condition.
She's like a moving dead body,
whom you've kept alive.
Why don't you kill her?
- No!
She is an emblem of my victory,
whom I've brought home like a prey,
just to decorate my house.
And...
This is her punishment.
Sir, she's all right!
- Out!
Salma!
You mustn't think a lot.
The doctor said
that it's bad for your health.
Here's a letter from your son
from India.
Here.
He wrote that he'll soon
get a job as a reporter.
And that
he'll quit drinking forever.
"I am not a drinker."
"I drink to keep worries away."
"To keep away your memories."
"I am not a drinker."
"I drink to keep worries away."
"To keep away your memories."
"I am not a drinker."
"I drink to keep worries away."
Sunny!
"I lost the book,"
"to which this tale belongs."
"One part is with me"
"and one part is with you."
"How do I join these hearts?"
"I am not a drinker."
"I drink to keep worries away."
"If we could have met,"
"water would also
have caught fire."
"If we could have met,"
"water would also
have caught fire."
"The friendship of childhood,"
"blossoms during youth."
"It has turned into a need."
"A need for this friendship."
"I am not a drinker."
"I drink to keep worries away."
Police.
The police will capture me.
You!
The police are after me!
Hide me somewhere.
Hide you?
I published your photo
and your dad fired me!
If I hide you,
the police will arrest me.
You lost the job because of me.
- Yes!
Look at this!
MISSING!
Rs. 5000!
Take me home
and you'll be rewarded Rs. 5000.
We'll split the money.
I'll run away again.
You take me home!
Half will be yours and half, mine.
Next week...
Sir!
Here is your reward.
Good bye! See you again!
- Thank you!
Hey man!
Give my share!
You caught me,
I won't spare you!
I'll get you!
- Shut her in the room!
'MISSING MS DEEPA IYENGAR'
She's 5 feet 2 inches tall
and belongs to an Iyengar family.
Stand straight!
5 feet 2 inches.
She has a wheatish complexion
and her name is Deepa.
Don't you know that Tamilians
are great? - Hurry up.
This time they're going to give
a special reward to a Tamilian.
Oh!
It takes 5 minutes to become
a Punjabi, Gujarati or Marathi.
It takes time
to become a Tamilian.
I'll go there and say,
'Mr Iyengar, hello!'
I risked my life
to save your daughter!
I can win Rs. 5000!
'I belong to the brave
'Kattaboman's royal family.'
'I fought exactly like him
with the sword.'
Oh! So, you are the missing girl!
- That is not me.
Come on!
- No!
Sit!
- Save me!
Where are you?
Save me!
- Where are you taking the girl?
Hey tall guy!
What, shorty?
Why are you taking her?
- For a reward.
I told her dad
that I'm bringing his daughter.
Tell him that a tall guy
is taking her home.
Okay.
Tall guy!
"Hey tall man."
- "Speak shorty."
"Don't block my path."
"Don't touch this girl."
"Hey shorty."
- "Speak tall man."
"Don't block my path."
"Don't touch this girl."
"Hey shorty."
- "Speak tall man."
"You tall man."
- "Speak shorty."
Yeah, boy!
"I saw her first."
"I found her first."
"But she prefers me."
"It's my reward."
"You tall man."
- "Speak shorty."
"Don't try to make me angry."
"Don't touch this girl."
"You tall man."
- "Speak shorty."
Oh, boy!
'Tam dhitam...' 'Tam Dhitam...'
Oh, boy! -Go!
"I have come
to Bombay from Madras".
"So you became tall on the way."
"You are trying to fly high
though you are so short."
"Height doesn't make
any difference".
"You tall man."
- "Speak shorty."
"Don't boast about your height."
"Don't touch this girl."
"You tall man."
- "Speak shorty."
"I have brought her."
"Her father will decide that."
"We should be
sharing the reward."
"We should
split the money equally."
Equally?
- Our reward.
I'm fed up with this girl.
She keeps running away!
We have no money.
One of you marry her as a reward!
Only one! C'mon!
- C'mon!
"You tall man."
- Speak shorty."
"This girl
is not a gold mine at all."
"Don't touch this girl."
- "Don't touch this girl."
"Shorty!"
- "Tall man!"
Hello!
- Yes?
Could I meet Mr. Chopra?
He doesn't work here anymore.
The owner has changed.
But they're giving us houses today.
You can go.
C'mon!
Let's go.
Stand in one place!
Hello, sir.
You?
I'm the owner.
What are you doing here?
The map lying in front of you
shows where our houses stand.
Give us the charge of those houses.
Have you paid the advance?
- Yes! Here is the receipt.
Where is the balance?
Here. You promised us
to give houses at Rs. 5000.
Houses for Rs. 5000!
Nonsense!
Vicky?
- Yes, dad?
Where are the contract papers?
- Here.
Show them.
Houses for Rs. 5000.
Advance of Rs. 1000 and Rs. 49,000
before buying the houses.
49,000?
Rs. 1000 less than Rs. 50,000.
Read this!
(Stamp Paper)
No... No, no!
This is a lie, it's injustice.
We had agreed on Rs. 5000!
You added a zero.
What do you mean?
You can't get
doors and windows with Rs. 5000.
Get the money and then speak!
Get out!
Get him out!
Throw him out!
This isn't right!
Be ready to face the consequences!
We'll surely voice this out.
- Out!
He spoke of Rs. 50,000!
Let's go to Iqbal!
See how we've taken
a hold of her property.
Now the question of
Julie's remaining property...
I remember...
Did you speak to her
about marriage?
Yes, daddy.
- What did she say?
She declined.
Declined?
Greetings, madam.
- Greetings.
We'll have to make her agree,
so that we'll have
half of the share in her property.
How?
Daddy, have water.
What happened, uncle?
Julie, good you're here.
Dad had a heart attack.
I'll call a doctor.
Uncle!
My child, I wanted to talk to you.
Good that you came.
Your father
had promised me something.
Will you fulfil it?
- Yes.
Please marry him.
That's impossible.
I want to avenge
my father's death.
Avenging your dad's death
is your wish.
But your marriage
was your dad's wish.
Uncle, why don't you understand?
I can't get married!
Why don't you get engaged?
- Uncle!
Let me die in peace.
I raised you like my daughter
since you were 5 years old.
With the hope that you would
fulfil my last wish. - Uncle!
Okay.
Bless you!
I will die happy,
seeing my daughter-in-law.
Father, doctor is here.
- Send him back.
Now that you're getting engaged,
I feel perfectly fine.
Julie agreed to get engaged.
Really, Julie?
Print cards!
Invite people for the engagement.
Your engagement has been fixed
for the 2nd of next month.
Where is the department of printing
wedding and engagement cards?
Hey, you!
Hello, sir!
- Interrupting my drinking!
Hey, shorty!
- Tall guy!
Here for the reward?
- No! I'm not here for the reward.
Is the engagement card of
Mr Vicky's son being printed here?
Yes!
Do I print them for you too?
Yes, but not a card!
Listen...
What's the date
printed on the card?
2nd.
- That's it.
Take with this hand
and return with that hand.
What?
Excuse me!
Yes?
Who are you?
Didn't you recognize me?
- No.
Didn't you recognize
the famous reporter of Rigby?
My card?
Move it!
- Okay, sir.
I want to print your picture on
the front page and show the world!
Bad shot!
Good try!
I'll write that
you're a generous person.
Till now, rich people invite
only the rich for the parties,
but you will be the first person to
invite the poor, that too, porters.
Porters?
- Nonsense!
Porters at our party?
The porters who insulted you.
Don't you believe this?
Have a look.
What do you think of the fun
these porters are having?
Shut up!
What are you up to?
Who sent you inside?
That's strange! First, you invite us
and then you forget.
We've got an invitation card
for the engagement.
Look.
- What misbehaviour is this?
Drive them out!
Michael!
You want Michael?
There's Michael and party.
Excuse me.
They're your guests.
You invite them
and then drive them out?
This isn't good.
Bad publicity.
Vicky, call the other people
and ask why they aren't here.
One pose please.
- Of course.
Put your arm around him.
- Why not?
Smile please.
Hello.
- Hello, Uncle Zafar, I'm Vicky.
Vicky, I have an invitation
to your engagement.
What happened?
- What?
Today is the 2nd, my engagement.
Today?
- Today's the 2nd.
'Engagement ceremony
of Shri Vicky with Julie.'
The date printed is the 20th.
- How did it change?
Like 5 changes to 50.
You taught this to us
and we used it on you.
So, you did this?
- Yes.
Thank you.
We did this, thanks to you.
Till you don't give us houses,
we'll stay in your house.
We'll consider it our own.
What do you say?
- Yes!
Excuse me, could you
throw some light on this?
Is this your way to get the houses?
Sir,
you took our money in your way,
we'll get the houses, our way.
You want houses, right?
- Yes.
You'll get them.
Excuse me!
They have a right to the houses
and you've grown pale.
Do you want to say something?
They'll get the houses
that they have a right on. - I see.
You want a house, right?
Here.
Happy?
What happened?
Are they small?
It's bigger than your heart.
We'll provide what's necessary
for rich people like
you in this house.
Move away!
What are you doing?
I'm trying to decrease the size
of this chandelier,
or it won't fit in this house.
Iqbal.
- Yes!
Could you throw some light
on the chandeliers and the houses?
I'm about to throw many things.
Wait and watch.
Do you know how costly that was?
- Excuse me!
What do you think about the
chandelier in pieces? - Shut up!
I will.
Iqbal...
- What?
I use a plate as a mirror.
You want a mirror?
You'll get it.
I would've photographed it,
had I known.
Binbal?
- Yes, Iqbal.
Can you see yourself?
- Yes. It's great.
Excuse me!
It's unlucky for a mirror
to break during an engagement.
What do you think about it?
A clock is necessary
for us to reach on time. - Yes!
Just a moment!
Smile!
Now break it.
- There we go!
Uncle!
- Yes!
Friends, take your share.
Your misbehaviour...
- This pendulum moves,
it keeps moving.
This time belongs to us now. - I...
What's your opinion
about this moving pendulum?
Shut up!
Vicky, call the police!
Wait a minute!
Now break it!
Hello!
I want a fan.
- I want it.
Hold it!
Thank you. Your turn.
'Yeah, so what was I saying?'
What's all this?
Who are these people?
So you've reached here too.
We're guests.
We received the invitation cards.
Uncle Ramu, did you get everything
or is there anything left?
He only wants a wife now.
A wife?
A wife!
- Let go!
Uncle.
Look at yourself and me.
Does this girl suit you?
I'm keeping her for me.
He's holding my hand
and you aren't doing anything.
He's come with so many men.
I would've dealt with him
if he was alone.
Consider me alone.
I need to settle
a few matters with you.
Do I settle them now?
- Sure.
Leave him.
In a minute this iron
will pierce your chest!
We are workers and
our chest is an iron wall!
And these are our tools.
They help us sustain our livelihood
and can destroy you as well.
Hey, excuse me. Hello!
Smile, smile smile.
- No!
Your body is sinking
because of the eagle's weight.
Do you have anything to say?
Oh I forgot.
You can't speak.
Cheers for Iqbal!
What are you doing?
- C'mon!
Just a moment Iqbal, smile!
- Leave me.
Uncle, call the police.
- What are you doing?
She will stay with us
till we get our homes.
Any comments? I'll be back
in a while. Let's go guys! -Uncle!
Uncle! Uncle, call the police.
So, these porters defeated
and embarrased you...
What is your opinion on this?
Shut up!
You shut up!
Leave me! I said leave me!
- Don't move your legs.
Shut up and sit here.
Sit! Lie down!
I'm warning you, let me go!
I'll send you to jail.
I'll handcuff you now.
Next I'll send your partner
to jail.
Leave me!
- Shut up!
Or I'll break you like
I broke your house at the party.
Big talks.
Will you have food?
- No.
Don't eat.
I'm telling you to sing.
Water is leaking!
Look ma'am, you get water through
taps, we get it from the roof.
I can't cook here now.
'Welcome to Akashvani Radio'
'We present Swami Sevanand
on a special programme.'
'We'll now teach you
various methods of doing yoga.'
Oh, yes!
Chef Khan was supposed to teach us
a new recipe with eggs.
What time is it?
Yes!
'Mr. Latif and Mr. Hanif will teach
you how to make a French omelette.'
'Mr. Latif and Mr. Hanif...'
- This is why I'm strong!
'Are you ready
to make an omelette?' - Yes.
'Take clarified butter.'
'Add one teaspoon
of clarified butter...' - Okay.
'Add an onion.'
- An onion!
'Keep all the spices ready.'
'We'll assist you
on the further steps.'
'Stand on one foot and jump.'
'It's necessary for good health.'
'Now stop.'
'Do you have an egg?'
- Yes.
'Sit on it in a yoga position,
on the ground.' - Yoga!
'First sit down.'
I'll sit.
- 'Sit cross-legged.'
'Place your hands on your knees
and close your eyes.'
'Fry it on a low flame.'
'It's moving a lot.'
'Yoga...'
'Slowly...'
'Listen carefully.'
Where did this
chick come from?
'Now take a green chilli.'
Yes.
'Open your mouth
and hang your tongue out.'
'Add the chilli to it.'
'It's necessary for a good taste.'
Chilli!
'Now lie down, slowly.'
Lie down!
'Lift your left leg.'
- Left leg!
'Then the right leg.'
- Right!
Both legs!
- 'With both legs...'
'Get an onion.'
Yes.
- 'Yes, an onion.'
'Hanif will tell you
what has to be done next.'
'Keep it on the ground
and punch it.'
Break it!
- 'After that...'
'Add it to the pan
and wait till it turns red.'
'Now stand up.'
'Place your hands on your knees'
- What?
'tuck your tummy in,
and inhale.'
'Don't move.'
'Moving isn't good
- 1 2...
for the health.'
'Take another egg.'
'Break it and put it in the pan.'
Break it...
'Now do a headstand.'
'A headstand. Slowly!'
- Headstand.
Okay.
- Slowly, slowly...
'Look at the omelette cooking.'
Madam, can you see it?
How is it?
Great!
It's good, right? After so much
hard work it has to be good!
'Keep your legs down.'
'Now slowly stand up.
Slowly.'
'Be seated'
- Again!
'and place your right leg
on your neck.'
Right leg.
- 'Slowly.'
'Don't do it in a hurry.'
'Place your right leg
on your neck.'
Oh God!
The spices used in the omelette
are wonderful. - What's happening?
I'm stuck! I'm locked!
Let me go!
The keys!
No!
Madam, please unlock me too.
Please!
Oh, God!
Sir, your neck is trapped
with your legs. - Yes.
What is your opinion on this?
- Very bad.
Hey! Hey!
Thank you.
- Okay.
Please help me!
Help!
Allahrakha...
Don't try to run away!
Or Allahrakha
will gouge your eyes out!
Come here and help me
get rid of this situation.
Come!
My neck!
My body is aching!
'Your French omelette is ready.'
'Eat it and...'
- I'll show it! I'll hit it!
Hey girl!
Hold this!
I'm going to the railway station.
When I return,
keep the French omelette ready.
Understood?!
Keep a watch on her, Allahrakha.
Don't be afraid, dear.
Whenever the train passes,
the houses of the poor shake.
I'm returning
from a pilgrimage to Shirdi.
I heard that
Iqbal brought you here forcefully.
The donkey!
No decision
can be taken in a hurry.
You can go.
It...
- Shut up.
You have troubled me a lot.
I won't spare you.
You wanted
a French omelette, right?
Why are you killing
a dead person?
He wished to have
a French omelette made by you.
When he was
walking towards the station,
the train broke him
into little pieces.
Every piece
was yelling out your name.
'IQBAL COOLIE MEETS WITH AN ACCIDENT'
- Why did you leave us like this, Iqbal?
But there was no such news
in today's paper.
No one prints news
of a poor person like him.
If a person like your uncle had
died, they would've printed it.
If you don't believe me,
check for yourself.
Porters have erected a statue
in his memory at Rani Baug.
He died for you.
So you can express your love...
- What?
Tell his statue
what you feel for him.
So that at least his statue
will rest in peace.
I can't stand to know of the death
of such a great young man.
I shiver with fear
when I think of this.
Will you come?
Iqbal!
'What are you thinking about?'
'If you have feelings for him, go.'
'If you don't, don't go.'
How long
should I hold you like this?
Hold me until the girl comes.
Here she is!
Jump!
- Hold this.
Umbrella!
She's also carrying two candles.
Candles? For whom?
Only she knows.
Come.
The craftsman has created
such a lovely statue.
Feels like he will speak any time.
He's unable to speak right now,
as it's just a statue.
I wish you had waited
for a few days.
We could've got to know
each other better.
The moment I saw you
on the railway station,
my heart started beating.
What happened?
- What?
No need to be shy.
I thought you would reach my home
in my search.
I didn't know the address.
- What?
He didn't have the address.
How could he reach your place?
You troubled me a lot.
You carried me away like luggage
in front of many people.
I liked that attitude,
your bravery.
You should've said that before.
You should've said it before.
Why are you interrupting?
- I am not!
I cried a lot
seeing your photo in the newspaper
and I didn't know
whether it was sympathy or love.
They say that love can make
a dead person alive with its power,
I wish my love had that power.
See, here I turn alive!
Are you alive?
Was it an act?
- It wasn't an act.
The power of your love did this.
- Who said I love you?
When I was a statue,
you loved me.
As I turned alive,
you started hating me.
I don't care about you!
I don't have any feelings for you.
You're a cheap person!
She's gone.
Hey, Sunny!
Hey, Sunny...
Where have you escaped?
The train has lost its track!
You?
Don't keep staring.
Clear the water.
You?
What are you doing?
Can't you see?
I'm clearing the water.
How will I cook
the special omelette?
What are you doing here
at this hour?
I'm here of my own will.
I've also decided that,
I won't move
until the porters get their houses.
Hey, hey, hey!
Such heavy rainfall...
Water-logging...
Are you here
to give us the houses?
No, I'm here
to create my own home.
Oh Lord.
"Allahrakha!"
"Two souls
are heartily celebrating."
"It's neither your mistake,
nor mine."
"Neither did you see a signal,
nor did I."
"It led to an accident, oh God!"
"Two souls
are heartily celebrating."
"It's neither your mistake,
nor mine."
"Neither did you see a signal,
nor did I."
"It led to an accident, oh God!"
"It led to an accident..."
"We made an agreement
and it was permanent, oh God!"
"Two crazy people,
we didn't look back or forward."
"We placed the train of our heart
on the track."
"Two crazy people,
we didn't look back or forward."
"We placed the train of our heart
on the track."
"Neither did you see the signal,
nor did I see the flag."
"It led to an accident, oh God!"
"It led to an accident..."
"We made an agreement
and it was permanent, oh God!"
"Allahrakha!"
"The paths were misty,
youth blossomed."
"You were unveiled."
"The ambience was playful."
"Neither did you notice
the danger?" - "Nor did I."
"It led to an accident, oh God!"
"It led to an accident."
- "We made an agreement."
"It was permanent, oh God!"
"We'll have to
make up for the loss."
"We have to fall in love."
"We'll have to
make up for the loss."
"We have to fall in love."
"Neither did you whistle,
nor did I."
"It led to an accident, oh God!"
"Two souls
are heartily celebrating."
"It's neither your mistake,
nor mine."
"Neither did you see a signal?"
- "Nor did I."
"It led to an accident, oh God!"
"It led to an accident."
- "We made an agreement."
"It's permanent, oh God!"
"Allahrakha!"
Do I offer them houses
at Rs. 5000?
They should get them at Rs. 5000
or I won't marry.
Why do you care?
Because the way they live,
they should get houses for free.
But the houses...
- Just a minute.
If we agree
to offer them houses at Rs. 5000,
will you agree to get married?
Yes, but keep in mind,
I'll get married only when
the porters get their houses.
Listen, all my brothers!
Keep your money ready!
We'll be getting our houses soon!
Yes!
Let's go to the chit fund
to withdraw the money.
'BOB CHIT FUND'
Welcome, Goga.
The police has raided
our Madras Fund. - What?
Zafar told us to vacate this place
before the police reach here!
Hurry up Bob,
we should leave as soon as possible
and burn all the documents!
So the police won't get
any evidence when they arrive...
You're a spy?
Take him inside! Quiet!
Sunny?
- Be ready to go to jail.
You, dad and his followers!
Take him upstairs!
- Tie him!
We'll decide about him
when Zafar comes.
You won't decide!
I'll show you!
I was on this case for a while!
Now I have proof!
All your bad deeds
will soon be exposed.
Thief! Do you think
it's your money?!
Come on, boys!
The goods seem to be heavy.
Do you need a porter?
Will you stop us?
- Yes.
Because the money is ours.
C'mon!
You have no place to run.
We've surrounded the place!
One hand of Maruti
is enough for you.
I made a mistake
by cutting only one hand.
I will cut the second one too.
Give me the axe!
How dare you shed
the blood of porters in my absence?
You burnt all the documents and
tried to run away with the fund?
Iqbal!
Did you see that, Iqbal?
My dad's acquaintances
tried to kill me
but my mom saved me.
That's why I always carry
my mom's photo with me.
That's what a mother is.
Whenever I'm sad,
I pour out my heart
sitting in front of my mom's photo.
When I am happy, I go to
my mom's photo to express my joy.
You're fortunate
to have a mother and her picture.
I am so unfortunate
that I only have my mom's picture.
I don't have a mother.
- Why?
We were separated.
How?
A long time ago,
when I was eight years old,
there was a flood
that destroyed the entire village.
Mom and dad...
They all drowned.
After a while,
I saw my mom on the train.
I was telling her
that I'm her son.
But she was looking at me
with clueless eyes.
It was like
she didn't recognize me!
I'll write about her in the paper.
We'll find her!
What's her name?
Salma.
Salma?
My mother's name is Salma.
Where is she?
I've heard that she was abroad.
Abroad?
Mom!
I am Iqbal, your son.
I'm here to take you along.
Try to remember mom,
we were so happy!
A flood
took all the happiness away.
Once...
Just once address me as your son
and embrace me.
Or else I'll die at your feet.
Right from childhood,
not one day has passed
when I didn't miss you
and didn't cry.
Today...
After years,
fate is on my side.
Now, with a mother,
my life's goal is achieved.
Let's go, mom.
Come with me.
I've come to take you with me.
Hey mister, you're under arrest.
For what offence?
Trying to kidnap this lady.
She's my mom.
- He's lying.
She isn't his mom
nor is he, her son.
You can ask the lady!
Is he your son?
She can't speak.
She's lost her memory.
What's the proof
that she's your mother?
If you look into my heart,
you'll find my mother's image.
The law doesn't accept this!
Then even I don't believe
in your law.
She's my mother!
I'm taking my mom
and no one can stop me.
Come.
Leave my hand!
Mom!
Stay there.
Hit him!
Don't talk nonsense.
He isn't Salma's son.
He wanted to run away
with our wealth.
You stole his biggest wealth,
his mom.
Stealing at a thief's place
can't be called stealing.
Sunny!
- Don't shout!
I know what you do
and what your business is!
How you cheated the poor of
their money through the chit fund.
This film contains all that stuff.
If you don't get
my brother released
and if you don't return
all the money to the poor porters,
I'll publish all your deeds
in tomorrow's newspaper. Get it?
What if I agree with what you say?
Then I won't publish it.
Fine.
I'll be back with a cheque.
Mom, I'll take you
to my brother, Iqbal.
Here.
This is your cheque.
'INDIAN BANK' 'PAY MODERN CONSTRUCTIONS'
Hello.
Zafar here.
- Yes, sir.
Sunny knows too much about us,
so kill him.
Slow!
Stop the car!
Salma.
Salma, we have
so many business rivals.
They couldn't stand our progress
and wanted to kill our son.
I'll take you to the shrine today.
You can read the holy book
and thank God
for saving our son's life.
I'll get the signatures
on a few papers.
He'll get released from jail
after 14 years.
And you are
taking her to the shrine?
Where is the shrine?
In front of the jail.
Then, after he leaves jail...
She's here to thank God
for saving her son's life.
May God give your son a long life.
May He keep you and your husband
in good health.
May He protect him
from all the perils.
'CENTRAL JAIL'
'DONATE BLOOD' 'SAVE A LIFE'
Where will you go now?
Brother,
I'll go to the shrine and ask him,
where my lost ones are.
Goodbye, Aslam.
- Goodbye.
'CENTRAL JAIL'
Oh, God!
'IN LOVING MEMORY OF JOHN D'COSTA'
Do you recognize this sepulchre?
It's my master's.
And you are responsible
for his death.
Me? No!
But who are you?
I'm Julie.
The daughter of the same master.
Dear Julie!
I was waiting for this opportunity
for 14 long years.
To kill you
the day you stepped out of jail.
My child, I swear
that I didn't murder your father.
That'll be decided right away.
I'll pray to God before dying.
You had 5 chances
to prove yourself innocent.
I think you're innocent.
I said the same thing
insistently in the courtroom,
that I am innocent.
But this wealthy world
didn't allow me to speak.
Who is the murderer of my dad?
When I was drowning,
there was one gentleman
who saved me.
That gentleman was your dad.
I had parted from my wife and son.
If it wasn't for his support...
He gave me a job in his mill.
Once the workers
got a bonus of 6 months,
but his partner
gave us a bonus of 1 month.
He got the documents
signed by us.
When my master found out,
he called his partner
and talked to him.
He denied the accusations.
Then he said, that whatever
has to be done, will be done.
When my master tried to
call the police, he shot him!
Before I could do something,
he threw the gun at me.
When I rushed to inform the police,
I bumped into his partner Mr. Puri.
I was pleading
that I was innocent.
Suddenly you came down
on hearing the sound of the pistol.
And, found your father's dead body.
That mean partner picked up a gun
lying on the ground as evidence
and started saying
that I had killed your dad.
Even you considered me
to be a murderer.
What's the name of the partner?
His name is Zafar.
Zafar.
'YOUR CANDIDATE' 'ZAFAR KHAN'
What do you think of this?
Zafar, friendship and business
are two different matters.
We'll have to incur a loss
of 5-6 million for your victory.
What's the use?
I tried doing many businesses
and I lost.
This was the only business left,
so I tried it.
If I win, I'll issue
all the tenders in your name.
What say?
But uncle,
who will vote for you?
He's right, Zafar.
You remember what I said?
Give houses to porters and they'll
be of help during the election.
Here are the papers
of the new houses.
Listen!
What's his name...
Iqbal.
- Iqbal.
Tell him
that I've kept my promise.
Congratulations.
Julie, are you happy now?
Let's go.
I'm doing this for you.
I've kept my promise.
You have to fulfil my promise.
Promise?
Which one?
That of getting married.
Marriage! Sure.
How nice!
But I won't marry you,
I'll marry Iqbal.
What?
Did Julie say that?
Yes, dad!
- Vicky.
Follow my method
and you'll always benefit.
Either get the one
whom you want, or kill her.
No!
I'll surely kill, not Julie,
but that porter Iqbal.
'Iqbal!'
'COOLIE NAGAR'
"We have fallen in love."
"Ask how we are doing."
"Our eyes met in the market"
"We have fallen in love."
"Ask how we are doing."
"Our eyes met
at such an early age."
"We have fallen in love."
"Ask how we are doing."
"Whenever young souls meet,
it leads to a beautiful story."
"When clouds touch the mountains,
rain falls."
"The sound of the raindrops..."
- "The raindrops..."
"The raindrops..."
- "The sound of the raindrops..."
"Lightning
fell in the monsoon..."
"We have fallen in love."
"Ask how we are doing."
"God, hurry up
and make me a groom."
"We can't trust you guys."
"Bring a pen, paper
and agreement."
"We can't trust you guys."
"Bring a pen, paper
and agreement."
"I'll bequeath my life to you
if you want."
"We have fallen in love."
"Ask how we are doing."
Mom!
Mother!
- Mom!
'I.C.U' 'INTENSIVE CARE UNIT'
Doctor. - We operated on her
and removed the bullet,
but the poison
has spread throughout her body.
Her condition is very critical.
I can't predict anything.
How's mom? - It's difficult
to predict anything.
Sunny!
Iqbal, save my mother!
Please save my mother.
I'm taking an oath.
Once my mother is saved,
I'll never have liquor again.
I'll never drink!
Don't be afraid, Sunny.
God is great
and listens to everybody.
What's the matter, Allahrakha?
"O my Lord,
here I am at Your service."
I got it.
I got it, Allahrakha.
You're telling me
to go for the pilgrimage.
Maybe God created you for this.
Now obeying your orders,
I'll go for the pilgrimage.
On behalf of the committee,
we welcome those who are
proceeding for the pilgrimage.
We request you all to keep
your passports, tickets
and doctor's certificate ready,
to get them checked
at the entrance.
You have fever.
Proceed for a medical check-up.
You have high fever.
Don't worry, let me go.
We'll have to do a blood test.
You might be suffering
from malaria, typhoid etc.
You can't travel until we're done
with the medical test.
Even major diseases fade away
during the pilgrimage.
You're right, sir,
but I'm helpless.
We need to take care of formalities
in two countries.
I'm sorry.
Where is the priest?
- There.
Greetings.
Hello.
- Greetings.
What's the matter?
Please tell them to let me go.
My mother is critically ill.
I'm going on this pilgrimage
with great hope.
I'm ready
to knock the doors of God.
I'll pray a lot for my mom.
Please tell them to allow me,
it's the last boat.
My child, it's God's wish.
No one can go there
until He calls.
Look at that old man
who has been
lying there for 15 days.
He says that he wants to go,
or he'll kill himself.
All his documents are ready.
But he doesn't have money
for a ticket.
You've got a ticket,
but you can't go.
Why don't you make an exchange?
Exchange?
Send him on your behalf.
Your pleas
will reach there through him,
and your mom will get a new life.
Bless you.
Uncle...
Uncle.
- Who's that? Oh, God.
What's wrong?
Do you want to
go on the pilgrimage?
Yes.
He keeps testing all of us.
Now even I need to test Him.
Let's see if He wants to
shower his favours on the poor
and whether He wants to call us.
He has called you, uncle.
You'll surely go.
Me?
Yes, uncle.
I want to send you in my place.
But you'll have to ask God
for a favour on my behalf.
Tell him to save my mom's life.
Pray to Him to save my mother!
Many years back,
my son promised to take me
on the pilgrimage.
Today, I feel as if
he's fulfilling that promise.
Praise...
- The Lord!
Happy pilgrimage.
May God keep you
and your mother happy.
"My eyes keep searching,"
"for God every day."
"With Your grace,
I'm searching for God."
"Happy Hajj pilgrimage to you all."
"I wasn't fortunate enough
to see Madina."
"Convey my prayers to Him."
"Even the sea cried
seeing my agony."
"I wasn't fortunate enough
to see Madina."
"Convey my prayers to Him."
"O my Lord,
here I am at Your service."
"Everyone is equal over there."
"All possess equal status."
"The one who goes
on the pilgrimage..."
"The one who goes on the pilgrimage
achieves victory."
"He achieves victory."
"I wasn't fortunate enough
to see Madina."
"Convey my prayers to Him."
"O my Lord,
here I am at Your service."
"I'm far away from the holy land."
"Bless me here itself."
"Forgive me
as I'm fighting with time."
"I am helpless in my agony."
"Everyone
was blessed with fortune,"
"but I just got thorns."
"I need not speak,
as You already know everything."
"Send me a sign of mercy."
"I understand that the stars
don't favour me right now."
"But don't separate
a son from his mother."
"If death is destined,"
"take my life but spare my mother."
"Oh king of heavens
and king of Madina..."
Mother!
Nurse!
Iqbal,
mom has regained consciousness.
Your mom is fine now.
Don't talk too much, let her rest.
Just a moment.
Drinking has ruined
both his kidneys.
One kidney is enough to survive.
But he needs a kidney
of a living person
and I suppose as a father,
you'll donate one kidney to him.
Doctor,
never ever talk about this,
in front of him or my wife.
Even if he had been my son,
I wouldn't have donated my kidney.
Isn't he your son?
- No.
My wife was ill at that time,
a doctor like you advised me that,
if she had to recover, let
her embrace any child as her own,
so I brought an orphan
from an orphanage.
Neither is he, my child,
nor am I his father.
C'mon.
Sunny?
Where did he go?
Take everything,
my hat, coat and shoes.
This bottle has gone empty.
Sunny, what are you doing?
I went to the hospital
and I found that you escaped.
You're sick, let's go.
Who are you to take me away?
- Your elder brother!
Did you listen?
He's my elder brother.
I don't know who my parents are
and he says he's my elder brother.
What's bothering you? Tell me,
I'll drink your sorrows away.
But don't ever say
I'm not your brother.
Our fortune has been written
by some inauspicious pen.
Don't say that.
- Let go!
You have a mom,
still, you didn't get her.
I lost her although I have her.
Mother!
Sunny!
Let go!
Even the bond of brotherhood
that we had, has been broken.
Go away, my brother.
Sunny!
I promise that
I'll break all my relations,
but I'll never
break our brotherhood. - Let go!
An orphan has no relations.
I'm an orphan brought
from an orphanage in Kanpur!
Sunny!
Go away!
- No, I won't leave!
Leave at once!
Sunny!
Uncle, call a taxi.
- Taxi!
I was right.
He was drinking inside.
We need to take him
to the hospital.
Careful!
Why does he drink so much?
He found out that Mr Zafar brought
him from an orphanage in Kanpur,
he started drinking.
My son!
Iqbal, he's my son!
I recognize the mark on his foot.
He's my lost child.
Your child?
- Yes!
We need to rush to the hospital.
I'll donate my kidney!
What's this in your hand?
You can't take that with you
to the operation theatre.
What's the matter?
Sunny.
- Iqbal.
This is the girl I love.
I lost her in childhood.
If something happens to me...
You keep saying foolish things!
You'll be back shortly.
Go.
'OPERATION THEATRE'
Sunny!
Where is Sunny?
In the operation theatre.
Why are you crying?
What's wrong?
- He's crazy.
He said that I should burn this
photo if something happens to him.
Nothing will go wrong.
This...
This is my photograph!
Your photo?
- Yes.
Sunny and I used to
study in the same school.
Look!
And...
And we parted...
'OPERATION THEATRE'
Congratulations!
The operation is successful.
Sunny!
There's going to be a programme
held for the minister.
Shall we also get married
on the same day?
Nice idea.
But I need to
get revenge on someone.
You have an entire life
to do that.
But we just have
a short span of time,
or else we'll never
be able to get married.
And we'll lose our chance.
'KRISHNAGIRI'
What are you thinking?
"We shouldn't be
losing out on love."
"The heart shouldn't break
in the game of love."
"No thief should steal..."
"No thief should steal"
"our tickets."
"We shouldn't be
losing out on love."
"The heart shouldn't break
in the game of love."
"No thief should steal..."
"No thief should steal,"
"our tickets. And run off!"
"I'm the engine
and you are the train."
"The train starts
only with the help of an engine."
"We shouldn't be
losing a connection."
"No thief should steal,"
"our tickets."
"We shouldn't be
losing out on love."
"The well is so deep..."
"The well is so deep,"
"my back is aching a lot."
"I don't want this pot to break."
"We don't want anyone else
to come between us."
"We shouldn't be
losing out on love."
"Climb up to the terrace."
"Come here and open the door."
"We shouldn't lose out
on this beautiful night."
"We don't want anyone else..."
"We don't want anyone else,"
"to come between us."
"We shouldn't be
losing out on love."
"The heart shouldn't break
in the game of love."
Parvati, bless him. I have strong
support for my old age now.
Parvati, if you were here...
- I'm here, father!
You offered me a new life
by donating a part of your body.
From now on, I'll shoulder
all your responsibilities.
No, you're a journalist!
We need you to write about
the atrocities being committed on us.
to voice the problems of the poor.
Iqbal, ready!
Why are you taking photos?
We'll be able to print posters.
Posters?
- Yes.
You're contesting the elections.
- I...
Elections? - Yes, Iqbal,
you'll contest the elections!
Have you gone nuts?
Leadership requires education.
I'm not educated!
Who told you
that all politicians are educated?
Sit on the chair once,
then you'll realize.
Sit!
- Sit down!
The rich will never know
how the poor suffer.
Only a hungry person
can understand hunger.
Homeless people
know the value of a house.
Only a porter
will understand porters' problems.
Yes, that's right.
I don't know how to give a speech.
- Right!
He keeps chatting
and says he can't give one.
But it requires money.
Where will we get that?
We don't need to buy votes.
Porters will support you
nationwide. What say?
Yes!
What say, Allahrakha?
You'll be the emblem of our party.
And we'll have to defeat Zafar
who gets votes by bribing people.
'Drive away poverty
and vote for a bolt of fire.'
'If you want a raise,'
'vote for the greatest.'
'This man will bring light
into your lives!'
'We promise
to resolve all your problems.'
'We'll install taps and lights
in your colonies.'
'The party leader is Zafar Khan,'
'the well-known owner
of D'costa Mills.'
'Vote for Zafar Khan!'
'Vote for the greatest!
He is great!'
Zafar! You...
Aslam! You?
Come!
I am...
- Aslam!
I've been looking for you
since you were released...
To apologize for my ill deeds.
I've got good news.
- What?
Your wife and son are alive.
Alive?
- Yes.
Where are they?
- Let's meet them.
Iqbal!
Oh, God!
'YOUR CANDIDATE, ZAFAR KHAN'
Zafar!
I won't let you
reach the election platform.
Stop!
Three cheers for Iqbal!
Three cheers for you!
Because you,
in order to show the rich people,
took me to an election platform
from a railway platform!
You can ask any question
that you wish to ask.
Can an uneducated poor person
fulfil the needs of poor people?
Can you solve their grievances?
Can you provide them
food and shelter?
No one can do that,
because it's God who does that.
He has given us two hands
to earn our livelihoods.
You rich people...
You rich people
take away our share of food too!
You suck our blood!
If you could,
you'd sell our souls too.
Do you think you're the ones who
shoulder all the responsibilities?
You need the rich to fulfil
the needs of so many people!
You'll have to agree,
nothing can happen
without rich people.
How's that possible?
Have you ever heard of rich people
sacrificing their lives at war?
It's the poor man
who sacrifices his life
and makes his nation proud.
The world keeps moving
because of us.
Right from the Taj Mahal
to the smallest hut...
Every building has been
created by people like us.
The rich have created everything
by resorting to corruption.
These people buy votes for Rs 10...
Get approvals for Rs. 100...
Pay thousands to pass an exam...
Shell out millions
to get tenders passed.
Only if the corrupt fail
will the nation progress.
Stop him
or I'll get a heart attack!
Where is Zafar?
- Dad!
Do I have to answer that?
- No!
I'll answer this question.
Move!
Brothers...
This blood and injuries,
were caused by this porter!
He didn't want me to come here,
so he shot me
by sending his girlfriend.
Lies!
Then check who's arrested
at the police station!
But I'll shower flowers on the one
who tried to do this.
Don't look there.
Listen to me first
and then look over there.
Your father, Mr. Aslam is alive
and he's in my custody.
My father?
- Yes.
The person
who's coming to that platform.
Your father's life
is in danger right now.
So you better quit
the elections, or...
What's the matter, son?
Uncle.
Is the person standing there,
my dad?
Aslam!
Yes, he is your dad!
Welcome, Mr. Zafar.
Zafar has done great work
while offering a garland to me,
that I can't say anything,
nor defeat him.
My...
The answer to my prayers
is with him.
I withdraw my name
from the election
and apologize to all.
No...
He hasn't decided to step down
because of good work by Zafar.
Zafar must have blackmailed him!
This woman will voice out
all his bad deeds.
My husband,
Iqbal's father,
greetings to you!
Greetings to you, dear!
My brothers...
- How did she speak?
Mom, don't say anything
against Zafar.
Father's life is in danger.
The Almighty who united
both of us,
will save his life.
Mr Zafar, you must be
very surprised to hear my voice.
It's God's miracle that
he returned my memory and speech.
Cut the wire of the microphone.
My brothers, this person who's
trying to collect your sympathies,
is a rascal and a cheat!
He has destroyed many...
You can't stop me
by cutting an electric wire.
I'll make sure that my voice
reaches every soul.
He killed my father!
He kept giving me electric shocks
for 20 long years,
so that I don't recall
my husband and son.
This is injustice!
My brothers, I used to give her
electric shocks,
at the advice of a doctor
and not at my own will,
as she was mentally ill.
You can ask him if you want!
My dear brothers,
what shall I say?
Mr Zafar has spent his life
looking for her husband.
When he found him alive,
he brought him here,
so that he could unite them
in front of everyone!
If you curse him, it'll be
as good as cursing humanity.
Mr. Aslam, proceed.
Your wife is waiting for you.
What are you doing?
I'm doing the right thing.
We could lose a lot
if we don't do this.
If the public gets violent,
we'll be done for.
I don't care about the public,
money and an election.
I've never learnt to accept defeat.
If I don't get Salma,
she can never be with anyone else!
Let's go! I think
something will go wrong here!
Uncle!
- Father!
I'll go on.
I've received the signal.
Iqbal...
He...
- Father!
We have to break the stage!
Move back!
Sunny!
Don't block my way,
or I'll kill everybody!
Leave me!
Let me go!
Come on.
- Leave me!
Zafar!
It's a holy shrine
and you can't enter it.
No one can stop Zafar!
- No!
Let go of me!
Leave my hand!
God.
- Come on!
Oh, Lord! Please perform a miracle!
How long will you survive?
There are three bullets left!
Shoot me!
If you have the weapons to kill
I have God with me!
Let's see if this sheet saves me
or becomes my shroud.
Shoot me!
'Nothing except Allah is worthy
of worship!'
'Peace and blessings be upon, Mohammad,
the messenger of God.'
'Nothing except Allah is worthy
of worship!'
"Allah is great."
Iqbal!
My son!
My, son!
My son.
- Enough, enough mother!
Mom, I'm alive
just to listen to this word.
Please call me your son once more.
I'm embracing you after so long.
Don't leave me.
Don't leave me, my son.
No!
It's God...
who gives life or death.
Oh God.
'OPERATION THEATRE'
Congratulations!
He is safe now.
Thank God!
God!
- Thank you!
Iqbal is here!
'St. PHILOMENA'S HOSPITAL'
Three cheers for Iqbal!
- Praise Iqbal!
Three cheers to you!
I had died.
I'm back
only because of your prayers.
"Hey porter!"
"We lift the weight
of the entire world!"
"We lift it."
"We lift the weight
of the entire world!"
"People arrive and depart,"
"but we remain here."
"We lift the weight
of the entire world!"
"We lift it."
"We lift the weight
of the entire world!"