Hey,even I'm coming...
How far...?
Yes,the path of love is
always like this
The more longer the way is the
more closer the traveler's come
And what's this-
Why do we always keep roaming in the
deserted ruins and broken building
Do you know
Every pillar,each and every
stone of this place
It's like... it's like revealing
a story
What happened?
A thorn...
One minute... one minute...
Sapna,we'll not marry
Hey,but why,Is all your
love over?
It's not like that,if
we get married
Even we'll be left with no identity
of our own like other people
Who don't have any relation
among themselves
Who don't have any turn
in their lives
And,if we don't marry,then?
The love was left incomplete,only
then our story will be built
Hey what,should our story only be
built,why not our history?
Wow!whose Hero will be me and
whose Heroine will be you
Hey madam,don't you have eyes
Is there no humanity in you?
Don't you see,I'm chanting
hymns over here
And you're throwing the
peels of egg
Sinner... Sinner...
a great sinner...
What...?
What...? your head...
What... what's it,whom
are you threatening?
This is the same Maxim,you were
chanting hymns by closing your eyes
They came flying through the air
what can I do in that?
For your sake,should we stop
having eggs?
And start having grass
like you?
Even we don't have grass,only
your wisdom has it
What...?
Oh God,if she's shouting
like that
Why are you also shouting
like this,you come in
Am I shouting,she's only shouting
after throwing the peels of the eggs
Hey Mr. what do you think?
Will I not understand anything
if you abuse me in Tamil?
I'm not going to lose
to you
Even,I'll abuse you one after the
other from the Terrace
What do you think?
Did you see...?
Oh madam,we're not
abusing you
I was just telling,why is this
fight required,you come in...
Yes... oh God! this is the
same Maxim
If they don't want to be
our neighbours
Let them go and settle down
in a forest
Again the same blabberings
the same old non-sense
You keep sticking your butt on
the chair like a pumpkin
By not uttering a word
Didn't you hear the way he
was shouting in Tamil?
Let him shout... He's a
Tamilian...
You say that you don't shout
but you always keep shouting
Yes... If they shout,will I remain
quiet,will I not swallow them up?
I know,if they are a brick
you're a stone
It is better to break my head
with a stone
Than to talk to you
since when I'm talking...
The moment I start speaking,she
stops me by ringing an alarm
My daughter has found out
a good way
What do you want?
Have the notes of professor
Munshi Ram come?
No... If you want,I have
"Love's labour lost"
I don't want that
Sapna,one minute...
Look at this,it's a very interesting
book,just look at it...
What? why... how's the photo?
Is it your Mother's?
Sir,haven't you seen the board
can't you get up?
Even if a woman comes and
stands next to you
Wow! If we say something
they'll start shouting
We'll damage the bus,burn the
bus and so on... get up...
I think,this poor man
doesn't know Hindi
Is it... sir... this seat is not meant
for men but only for ladies
The seat is vacant
come on...
It's on my head,that's
already gone...
Further,it's Dholapur,get down
there itself
This Isn't your Father's bus,that you
can make it stop as & when you feel like
Hey,this bus will not stop here
you'll have to go till Dholapur
Hey,why are you shouting,has
anybody committed a murder?
Don't know,from where he has come
the son of Tarzan?
Son,what's this,you've come
without any intimation?
First,I've come,the letter
is coming behind
Come my son,come...
Mr. Jagannath,what's this
why are you staring?
What?
Have you got lot of jokers?
No... sir,it's been 1 year since
I've had the glimpse of a joker
Look,who has come?
Hey what's this,all
of a sudden?
Who's he?
He's my son
Oh! your son
Hey,have you come on leave?
No...
What about the job?
What's the name of
your son?
My name is Jagannath
I'm the owner of this house
I come for collecting the rent
but I go after paying
In the cards,I don't have
any other work
Very good,I didn't understand
a bit
Good,he has understood
Come on,play your card
How can I play,this Mr. has
quit his job
What an empty-pride?
Father,I don't have an empty-pride
my boss has it,he...
Will you keep quiet
for a while?
He badly scolded me,I told him
to take a long walk,and I quit
Hey,now-a-days,where it's so difficult
getting a job,have you got brains?
Father,I've brains...
Oh God! why all this fight when he's
just entered,you come in,my son...
I'll brush my teeth
- come...
Such a handsome boy
and your son...?
What handsome... my foot
he's a snake gourd...
Did you see,what times
have come
I educated him till B.Com,got him a
decent job in a good company
The boss must've spoken a
little harsh to him
Our man quit the job
and came off
Father is great fief
Isn't it
He's on his father,Isn't it
You've heard that saying
Isn't it
Like father,like son...
If not much,but at least
a little bit
What a strange man
you are?
Even after seeing me,you're
pretending as if you haven't
No talk,no shriek how's
your neighbour?
Whose leg you broke
out of anger
Poor soul,you didn't even think,that
he is the only son for his parents
That person,who's following me
to get rid of him
I'm posing my association
with you
Even you don't take it
in a wrong way
Our Goa boys are really very good
born volunteers...
They consider helping girls
as their prime duty
There are exceptions like him too
he's more like a beast than a human
I feel like hitting a stone
on his head
He ran away,bloody coward...
Probably,he got scared of you
thank you so much
Had you not been there,don't know
what would've happened?
I don't like coming by this way
but what to do,it's a short-cut
That's my college,okay...
But why were you running
like this?
Are you a dumb?
Even the God has strange
plays
You can not speak...?
I don't know Hindi
- Then?
Whatever you may be,but you're
a messenger of God for me
"Messenger of God"
That's why,I say,to teach
a lesson to such Rowdies
It's very important that
girls learn Karate
Just imagine,if there's
a rowdy come for somewhere
You see him and vice-versa
he stops and you too
He takes a step forward
towards you
And you start...
Karate was introduced only
for self-protection
I don't know,whether karate
was born in Japan
Or it was imparted
from India
You have seen that, Bruce Lee's
Enter the Dragon, isn't it
My name is Vasu,what's
your name?
Greetings sir...
Greetings...
Hey,the visiting hours got over
long back
Haven't you people
still gone?
We're going... we don't want to stay
the whole night at your hospital
My dear,I'll leave,tomorrow
morning I'll come with a coffee
Come with a good coffee
Here,no body even knows to make
coffee,I'll leave...
You save this thanks for that
girl who has sent these flowers
I've only brought them
Your name is very good,my name
is Sapna,how's it?
This is my Veedu(House)
What?
That's my house
No... my veedu(House)
Oh! that Non-veg. family
We've come so closer
to each other...
What do you do?
Are you fine?
Meaning?
It means...
Mr. Jagannath,did you see...
our noses have got burnt
Because of the bad smell
of their food
One day,they have eggs,one day
mutton,one day chicken...
Don't they get the taste in their food
unless they commit a murder?
Mr. Jagannath,you yourself
tell-
Should we stay in this house
or vacate it?
I can't tolerate any more
Good,let them vacate,we'll
get rid of them
This is the same Maxim,they
are Tenants and we're the Owners
In my house,I'll do anything
which I feel like
What's an egg,out of anger,I may even
fry my husband and eat
Who's he to ask?
Madam,you eat your husband
however you feel like
But let us live,why can't you
change the direction of your kitchen?
Why can't you chop your head
and keep it in a cupboard?
The kitchen will be
very much there
Should we change our kitchen
for these Tamilians? never...
You always bring South Indians &
North Indians as the bone of contention
I know,all North Indian
are not like you
Even I know that all South Indians
Even if we don't call a Rose
as a Rose
Will Rose become some
other flower?
What's there in a name
it's all in our mind-
It's not a part of our body,like
Head,Hand,Leg,Nose,Ear...
When you address
yourself as"I"
A lot of things are included
in this"I"
Body,Soul,Heart,Brain
name is just a mere label
Like,even if we don't call
Romeo as Romeo
But still,he'll remain only as
Romeo,Juliet's lover
Leave all this,your mother never
addresses me by my name
But this doesn't mean that
I'm no more her husband
What's the meaning of this?
It means,good night
Daddy,I'm feeling sleepy
What's it?
No...
"Love"
What account is this?
This is the account
of the heart
Now, where has the love
disappeared?
It has got merged with the sand
In this?
What's this, is this a rehearsal of
getting burried alive like Anarkali?
No... I'm just seeing,that is
there any other lover like us inside?
Here,you'll not find lovers
but you'll find only crabs
What?
A crab... is crawling on my hand
It's not a crab, it's my hand
it's my finger...
Oh God... DOG...
DOG... DOG
It's only a DOG,Isn't it
what can it do?
What the DOG's generally do,if it
thinks us to be a lamp post,then?
Yuck...
When ever you meet me,you say
"Are you fine"
What's the meaning
of this?
Meaning... Are you fine?
I see... how to say in Tamil
that"I'm fine"?
I'm fine
" NALLA IRUKEN"(I AM FINE)
Not like that
like this...
Oh! like this...
Are you fine? I'm fine...
Why have you come here?
I was seeing how beautiful
you are
Yuck... run from here
Mother... Are you fine?
What?
Learn Tamil in 30 days,do
you have this book?
It's there
What can I do for you?
Learn Tamil in 30 days
do you have this book?
Pregnancy in 10 days,I've
this book-
How can a woman experience motherhood
how fast can she experience?
What is the way if she
doesn't want to experience?-
That book contains
all these
Tamil is the language
confined only to Madras city
But sex is a universal
language
That day,you had told that
this is my Mother's photo
Now,look at it,how's it?
What is this strange bond that
we share between ourselves?
It's neither known to me
nor known to you
One string pulls and the
second comes running
It'll come tied by the pull
of brittle strings
Like a mad lover
Oh! Is it like that?
Oh! as if you've understood
everything
I'll wear bracelets from
your hands
The final destination of my Bridal cart
will be at your courtyard
Let the world do anything...
Hey,you're extremely
beautiful
What's all this?
People speak so many
different languages
But there's only one language of "Love"
in the world
Which the candle stick speaks
to the winged white Ant
Not bad,you sing
pretty well
What?
You...
What you did was
not love
The one which can not rise
above sex and lust
That's not true love,you're
not fit for that
I thought you as my friend
as my companion
But you too turned out to be
an ordinary man like others
And an ordinary man is just
slightly superior to an Animal
This is our last meeting
we'll never meet up again
Now,I regret,why
I met you?
What's all this?
Old news papers and
waste papers
I was told to sell it
to a junk dealer
Who?
Sapna madam
And even that?
Why,have I committed
any mistake?
No... only the place of
your kiss was wrong
So,the separation of these 7 days
has still brought us closer
There are 2 things very
exiting in love
Separation and...
Waiting...
This rock is a memorial for the
await of a girl called Donapoala
History itself is like this
A portuguese girl fell in love
with a Goan boy
Like us...?
Yes,exactly like us
One day,the boy had to go
very far across the Sea
But...
He had to go across
the Sea...
But he never returned
Why,what happened to him
no body knows
But the girl kept constantly
waiting for him...
Then,after standing on
this Rock
She herself became a Rock
And one day,even
If I go
Will you also wait for me
on this Rock?
No need of all this
Rubbish things
First I want to make good
the loss for 7 days
When how and where?
Okay,for 7 days,I'll
sit besides you
Is it okay?
Even 7 days are not required
only 24 hours
Should we go somewhere for a hitch-hiking
I'll show you the entire Goa
What okay... what about
your Mother?
Keep quiet man
Just watch,how I'll manage
with my Mother
We are made for each other
I swear upon him,even if I stay
for a moment away from him
You are stupid,accept it,you are
handsome,understand it
Leaving all other things
recognise the eyes
Eyes have made such promises
to each other
There is no way of
expressing love
That's why poet Ghalib
has told this
We are made for each other
understood?
Madam, why are you crying?
If you cry will you reach
home early?
Then tell me, how will we go
the watch is showing 11 o'clock
The board is showing 16 kms.
The petrol is over and we
are also financially broke
I spoke a lie at home and came
now,it's mid-night
The watch is 5 minutes
fast
Sir,will you give us lift
till PANJIM?
Husband wife and the motorcycle
had gone to Vasco-Da-gama for honeymoon
But there was a pick pocket
the petrol is exhausted
Even I had gone to Vasco-Da-gama
on a marriage
In the mean time,you even
got married to him?
What's your name?
Why do you need name,you can
abuse me just like that
So much of haughtiness?-
Making a young girl speak a
lie at home and bringing her out
And making her roam like a
Vagabond,Is this a joke?
In future,if you look at our house
I'll not only abuse you,but...
Sapna,get into the car
come...
Poor soul,Vasu...
He'll come back running behind
the car, he's a hero, isn't it
Driver,start the car
- Sir...
Are you deaf,start
the car
We are made for each other
understood?
Sorry Vasu,you came walking all
the way in the night
Walking... and me...? Never...
Then,how did you come?
- On the motor bike
And petrol?
Why is petrol required?
I was on the motorbike
the motorbike was on the lorry
And the lorry charges
were on my father
You had to take so much
of trouble for my sake
Trouble...?
I can do anything for you
Anything
Everything,our's is an
Immortal love,Isn't it
Now,tell me,what
should I do?
Do you know swimming?
What is that?
Jump... let me see...?
It's an Immortal love
Isn't it?
Someone please save... somebody
is drowning in the water...
He doesn't know swimming,someone
please save... please save...
I went to catch fish
I caught him
Just see,if he's breathing
or not?
Vasu,regain consciousness
Vasu, I accept that your Love
for me is immortal
Hey,don't shake!
What are you writing?
I saw your back as shining
as a Glass
I thought,let me write
a Love letter
Are you writing some joke,it's
making me laugh
Hey,wait for sometime
It's over...
What have you written?
Read it yourself
Hey,tell me,what have
you written?
I'll not tell
You'll not tell
- No
Alright,I'll tell someone
else to read it
Will you make someone else
read a love letter?
I'll not tell it to a stranger
I'll tell my mother to read it
To Mother...?
Mother...
What do you want?
It's been how many years since
you've come to North India?
It's been 6 years
but why?
It's been 6 years,Isn't it
do you know to read & write Hindi?
Hey,what's this,today you
are speaking in Hindi?
First tell me,can you
read Hindi?
Little bit
Only little bit,Isn't it,okay
then read this little bit
I Love you,"a mad girl"
Oh!God,who's that mad girl?
The adjacent house mad girl
Sapna...
That Girl...?who are they
and who are we?
Is it Practically possible?
How's this possible?
If you think,it's possible,Oh God!
Mother... where are your feet?
Oh!God!...
What...?- Turn back...
- But why?
Mangalam,what are you doing?
I'm oil massaging the child
You're applying oil,let 10 more
years pass off
Mr. Jagannath,come here
- Coming
Look,what's going on
over here?
She's oil massaging a 20 years
old Donkey
If he's given such a Royal treatment
will he ever go out for work?
You get him a job,is he
refusing for it?
Wow!
Stop!
Sapna,I never expected
this from you
I never ever thought that you'll
turn out to be such a girl
Daddy,what type of a Girl?
The way you are
you know my anger
I'm watching the drama going
on between father & daughter
Father,is uttering false words
of displease
And the daughter is pretending
to be innocent
Mother,what do you
want to say?
I don't want to say but I want to
ask you,what's all this?
Now,why have you become
speechless?
Come on say!
The photo is good,give him Rs. 10
and ask him to get out
Had it been in colour,it would've
still been better
Shameless,now tell me,how many
colours are you able to see?
I'm asking her about the photo
she's giving me all stupid answers
Has she become so great?
Only now,I've come to know,what
you do staying outside so late
She's born only to put a blemish
on our forehead
From tomorrow,if you don't
come straight home after college
I'll break your legs
understood?
She-devil,what are you looking at
me for,get away from my sight
I'll come in the evening to
pick you up,understood
Vasu,why did you come here?
What other way is there
to meet you?
Your mother has become
your Body-Guard
She always conceals you
in her saree
Vasu,what can I do?
I can do,come with me
- Now...?
But mother...?
Mother comes only in the evening
Isn't it...
The food was too good
my stomach is dead
What,stomach...?
Is dead!
Not dead,but fully filled
Hindi is a very difficult
language
Are you not having
the ice-cream?- No
My hair has become full
Hair...?
Yes...
You mean to say,stomach
Isn't it
Yes...
Not Hair... but stomach
What's there to laugh
on this?
What you said was hair
Tamil is a very difficult
language
What's this,why have you stopped
the lift in between?
To be with you for a
very long time
I have my Hindi
poetry class
It's Hindi Poetry class,Isn't it
I'll teach you
You?... and Hindi Poem...?
Do you think,I don't
know Hindi Poem?
My life partner,keep loving!
Youth is mad,beautiful
obstinate female neighbour
TRUTH,POWER and BEAUTY
Benhur!... that's an
English Movie...
My life partner,keep loving...
Wow!... wow!
Youth is mad,beautiful
obstinate female neighbour
TRUTH,POWER and Beauty
Bloody lier...
Bloody lier?...
Yuck 420,Vagabond
It's only my heart...
I'm the lover of beauty
Our dreams,infront of
your house
Face to face,after marriage
After marriage,Oh!God!
Our's...
- What...?
Baby,Guddi,Tinku,Mini,Shin
Shinati Babla Boo,out of play...
Shout...
Have you forgotten?
My name is Johnny-I see...
Robbing is my profession...
Ram and Shyam
Yuck... good for nothing
Girl... Meeting...
keep singing a song...
Shameless
The season of love
- Shameless...
Go... Go...
Love... Love... Love...
These paths are of love
by walking my companion
What?
Companion,you're mad in love
mad,care-free,fraud,unknown
Bloody,mad man...
Fraud,unknown,lover,stranger
Loafer,stupid
The one which grows is a Beard
the one which moves is a vehicle
When some one falls in love
my lover...
When we get some one's
remembrance,my lover
Really?
Bond,Bracelets,a Sandal Wood Swing
Sandal,Bracelets,a Bond Swing
A swing of Bond,A Bracelet of Swing
A swing of Sandalwood,swing... swing...
I lend my heart,I took the pain
The sound of tinkling Anklets...
With the sound of the tappings
The stones sang a song,the 7 notes...
TRUTH,POWER and Beauty...
Go... Go...
Wow!what an excellent duet
they sang
What's your father's name?
Sir,I forgot...
Bloody rascal,you're not worthy
of finding a job for yourself
Why do you want love...?
Love?...
We love each other
Did you see,he's wantonly
replying in Hindi
We're not left worthy of
showing our face outside
In broad day light and
that too in a public place
Why do you need to sing a song
Just like in a movie...
We love each other
Didn't you feel ashamed?
For so long,you were inside
the lift with a stranger
First,give me an answer
then,you go in
We both love each other
Let your love get ruined...
this is the same Maxim
Where has that Rascal come from
to put us to shame?
He should die of cholera
he should die a Dog's death
I'm asking you,what's your age... that
you're roaming around with a stranger?
Tell me...?
We both love each other
But,who's this Mr. Haribabu?
Mr. Haribabu is a very good
friend of mine
Yes... he's a very big
Auditor in Hyderabad
So,will Vasu work
in Hyderabad?
Yes... yes
I'll not got to Hyderabad
- Why?
I'll not go,that's it,get me
some job in Goa itself
That's all,I'll not go
Son,you should go...
Why, son...?
He doesn't want a job
he only wants a girl
Why are you talking like this
- You, keep quiet
Jullie,the only difference
between us is that
You have a collar around your
neck and I don't have
If I keep watching at you like this
I think,one day,I'll go mad
And probably,I'll start
barking like you
This dog's face is thousand times
better than that Rascal's
Mother,it's okay,if it's
only the Dog
But,I've to see even your face
for all the 24 hours
You'll go mad by looking
at that Dog
This is the same Maxim
Look,how that loafer is taking
circles around our house
He should die of cholera,only then
we can get rid of him
Do you want to show the entire
city the act of your shamefulness?
Come... come and sit
there properly
Otherwise,I'll cut you into pieces and
throw it down to that Dog,understood...
Sapna,why were you not seen
the entire day?
Have your family members
house arrested you?
Tell me?
Did they beat you?
Sapna,don't cry,no body
can separate us
The entire world...
Let the entire world
turn against us
Even then,we both
will be one
What are you looking at?
Let me see,what these
people can do?
Got ruined... we are
left no where
My daughter's life has
got ruined
The respect of this family
has gone to Dogs
Is there no one,who can
stop him?
Is there no respected person who
can save someone else's respect?
Hey,where are you?
In the world's history of Love
this chapter is not for the first time
This comes everytime
The young love understands
only one language
The language of Love
The old wisdom,burried into
the grave of time
Only know to create the
walls of separation
Some times,the walls of languages
sometimes,the walls of caste
Sometimes,the walls of wealth
sometimes,the walls of hatred
From the time,History
is in practice
From then,this fight between the
young & old is also being practiced
Neither,the old has taken
it's last breath
Nor the young has accepted
it's defeat
We Love each other,we'll get
married,nobody can stop us
After this... now you can say
whatever you feel like
You people are elder to us
in age and also in experience
But still,there is not even one
who can peep into our heart's
And try understand us
They don't understand us,because
we respect them
We treat them as
our elders
Had Vasu stealthily eloped
with me
Then,what you people could
have done?
What ever we have done
We've confined ourselves to the
limitations of respect
Had we crossed those limits
You couldn't have uttered a
word out of shame, isn't it
Scoundrel,shut your mouth
Having born in a orthodox
brahmin family
Do you want to marry a girl who
eat's non-veg?
Aren't you ashamed of it?
I'll stop eating non-veg.
Oh! such a big sacrifice?
Oh God!...
Then,will you be satisfied?
Did you listen,this is all the
tricks of these Tamilians
This is the same Maxim
Why should we get our daughter
married to these Tamilian's Son?
Do we fall short of boys
in our city?
Again the same old fight
of language?
If language is the only
objection for you people
Then give me 1 month's time
I'll learn Hindi and I'll also
be able to teach you
I'll even write poetry in
Hindi and show you
Oh yes... poem...
Son,you'll definitely write,but with
cowdung on our forehead
Your parents have given you birth
only for this Auspicious deed
Listen...
Please be quiet for
some time
Look,they are anyways children
but,we're elders...
What,even if we don't
behave as elders?
We must think as to what
has to be done
What should we do?
First,take your hands off
first take your hands off...
What's the love at this age
It's only Lust
Lust!... my foot...
This word,every father,since
generations in repeating it
Even this mistake,every son since
generations is making it
But every father forgets the fact
that he was also a son
You'll not understand this till
you become a father
That's why,I'm asking you to
get me married
Bloody Rascal,I'll break
your jaw
He's speaking to me
in Hindi?
Why all this is required
our's is true love
Tell us,what are we supposed
to do to prove it?
We are ready to do
Look sir,If you agree,I'll give
you all a suggestion
Separate both of them
for a year
And even after that,If they want
to marry each other
Then,we'll agree,that their love
is only love and not Lust
Why,what do you think?
I see... after that,will we
have to get them married?
Go...
Not only 1 year,even after
100 years
I'll not agree for their marriage
It's impossible
Wo are you to say this,first I'm
telling,that I don't agree for this proposal
It's impossible by me
How is this Jagannath affected by it
he'll blabber,whatever he feels like
He has no one around him,he
has no children... and so on...
Sister,don't refuse so early
give a little more thought
Yes my dear,we should definitely
give a due thought
Even Jagannath's suggestion
looks practical
Why Vasu,Is it okay?
It's not okay,mother,why
all this is required?
Is this any kind of examination?
We outrightly refuse it
Vasu,why don't we agree,are we
scared of their examination?
Let them try their best,our love
for each other will not decrease
Our love will not diminish
this is my firm belief
Is it,then for 1 year they
can-not meet with each other...
They can not talk
to each other
Alright
They can't even exchange letters
between themselves
Alright
They shouldn't even stay in
the same city
I'll send him to Hyderabad
Oh! so finally,you found
an opportunity
You've decided among yourselves
that's all...
We...
Vasu,what's there in it,why are you
so obstinate about it?
Agree...
You don't understand
No Vasu,I only...
You leave about their opinion,first,we'll
have to take a decision,come
Why,can't you take the decision
over here?
No.. here,It'll end up
in smoke
I hate this business of
proving something
Who are others to make us
prove our love?
Vasu,they are not other's,they are our
parent's,who gave us birth
Who brought us up
Their blessings will definitely
be good for us
It'll not be bad
Vasu,listen to me
carefully
There are 3 things very
important for love
Good manners,little patience and
a lot of mental balance
Vasu,agree to their conditions
I have full faith,by the
grace of this God
We'll come out with flying colours
in this examination
But...
Agree for my sake...
But these elder's are too clever
they can even deceive us in the end
That's why,it's has to be written
black & white on a paper
That after 1 year,they'll get
us married
And on that,their...
We should even take their
signatures
You mean to say,an agreement?
Yes,and that too on a
stamp paper
Vasu,now we'll meet up
after 365 days,till then...
Our agreement has started...
Vasu,why have you come back?
No Vaus,no...
Sapna,without seeing you...
Vasu,please go...
Still not even a few hours have elapsed
that our agreement has started
Why should we give people a chance
to point their fingers on us
That their love was so
feble,week
Which couldn't even bear the
separation of few hours
And there are thousand's of
hours in a year
Vasu,we should keep up our promise
we'll have to abide by the agreement
Vasu,go... please go...
What's my fault,what's
my crime?
I stayed away from you only for
a few hours
But I couldn't stay,how am I
going to stay for a year?
And why the hell
should I stay?
In this city,people who know you
people who don't know you
Animals,Birds,Trees,and more over...
the smallest of all the Ant can see you..
Only I can't see you...?
If this is Justice,then it's also
justified to break this agreement
Vasu,why don't you try
to understand?
What should I understand?
Our agreement is not a matter
of court case
This has been given birth to
strengthen our Love and belief
Vasu,do one thing
What?
You arrest me into your eyes
for a year
But,don't come and meet me
Think,that these 365 days
never came in our lives
After that,you'll always
see me
You'll keep seeing me
for life long
Forgive me,if I've hurt
your feelings
But,Vasu,now you go...
You can understand my
condition
Even,I can't stay for a minute
away from you
And today,when you've come
to meet me
I'm asking you to go
How much I would have felt
while saying this?
How sorry and sad
I would have felt?
But,we'll have to bear
this sorrow
Vasu,we'll have to bear
go...
Sapna,forgive me
Sapna,forgive me,I lost my
senses out of enthusiasm
Now,I promise to fulfill that
agreement for your Love
Now,I'm leaving this city
But Sapna,how can I stay
without remembering you?
That's why,I'll daily write
you a letter
But,I'll not post it
And all those remembrances
of your's for these 365 days...
I'll place all that on your feet
after 1 year
Now,I'm going,your Vasu
Okay,you know Hindi,Isn't it
Little bit
Hey,watch Hindi movies
you'll learn more
Okay,where will you stay?
Actually,you can even
stay with me
Because,I'm absolutely
all alone
I'm a chornic Bachelor
since my birth
Neither wife... nor that...
nor a concubine
Come... this is your room
If you look out from this window
you can see Rama Krishna Theatre
Hey,there's a Telegu movie
playing in it
Don't look through that window
The opposite house's bathroom
is seen
Okay,today you take rest,come
to the office from tomorrow
And if you find time,roam around
Hyderabad, look at the city's charm
Look at the beauty
you'll enjoy
And if possible,go on a
blind date...
In the evening,go for a movie
have you seen the film Pakizah?
No...
You haven't seen?Hey,what
are you upto?
Hey,that's a poem
Poem...?
Brother, where are you lost?
Aunty... I've come...
Aunty... where are you?
Hey,Chakravarthy,come...
Where are your Lotus feet,they
are here,one minute...
Let me cleanse this birth of
mine by touching your Lotus feet
And brighten the next birth
of mine
God bless you...
How is everyone in Lucknow,your
mother,your father...?
Hey,leave all those
oldies aside
Where's Sapna baby?
Hey,since morning,she's standing
on one leg and waiting for you
Look, she's here...
Sapna,look,who's come?
Come Chakravarthy,come...
Since morning, I've been waiting
only for you standing on one leg
Don't you have manners
of speaking?
Wow! I think you're a new Piegon
who has entered this hotel
My name is Baby, I stay
downstairs
My name is Vasu
- What?
Your moustache is really
wonderful
Will you come for a movie
with me in the evening?
I don't understand Hindi
very well
Boss,who goes to a movie
to understand it?
I think,I'm too fast
for you
I shouldn't have asked you
so early for a movie
I'll again ask you after
2 days
Chakravarthy,you should show
your Manliness
Aunty,then you yourself suggest
what should I do?
First,you stop sneezing
After you have come,Sapna should
slowly forget Vasu
And not only that,Vasu's name should
get erased from Sapna's heart
How's it?
Very good,my lord,very good
But,what if we change it's
alignment a little,then?
How?
That's all
It means,that's all madam
full stop
Enough of match stick play,please
come to the movie
Really,it'll be very
enjoyable
If it's not palatable
for madam
Then,madam can watch
the movie inside
And your slave will watch
the posters outside...
I'll wait for the lady
No Chakran,I've lots to do
What work do you have?
This one
Sir
- Yes!
I've a small doubt
About what?
About an agreement
There're 1 Lakh agreements
in the office-
Which one are you referring to?
Love agreement,sir
It's most important
Wonderful,I haven't seen such an
agreement in a movie also
I can't meet Sapna,I can't even
write a letter to her
If,I send her an
empty envelope
Then,what can happen?
Your love is very sincere
Love makes the world beautiful
Hey,what's all this?
You had rubbed off
only one name
See how many more have
appeared
What to do now,mother
Darling!
Daddy has seen
Shameless!
My forehead is blank,write
on that too
Dear sir
I drink
You all know & the entire
Town knows
But,I've a unique way
of drinking
Before 9 'o' clock I drink
as much as I can
But exactly at 9 'o' clock
my party gets over
It's neither at 8.59
nor at 8.61
9 'o' clock means exactly
9 'o' clock
I don't compromise on
this matter
This fact,you & the entire
city knows
Hey,Samba.. Oh Samba brother
- What is this?
Till now neither the glasses nor
the heads have broken
Why has the party not
bloomed till now?
He is simple and an
innocent boy
Oh! meet Mr. Ram Singh
he also stays in Goa
I see!
Where do you stay in Goa?
Panaji,near palm beach
light house
So cheers to our simpleton
friend
Have you come for the party?
No,I've escaped from
the party
Have you also escaped from
the party?
Mr. Danny is my elder brother
In Mr. Hari's company,I'm...
I'm the new employee
in his company
My name is Vasu
Please sit down
Why are you telling your name
again and again?
So that you tell me
your name
My name is Sandhya
Your name is very 'ACHHI' (Nice)
Achhi (Nice) not Achhi
but Achha (Nice)
Nice! Nice!
I don't know Hindi properly,that's why
I make grammatical mistakes
Where do you come from?
I'm a Tamilian and Tamil is
my Mother tongue
Okay,tell me...
Why the swimming pool is
like this?"TANNl EllAME"
Some people have similar
lives
Like this pool... empty
I know only two words of Tamil
Greeting and Food
I was in Madras for a week
with my husband
Oh! are you married?
Yes
It was performed & it
has also ended
In air...
My husband died in an
air crash
When a person starts life...
He forgets
That death is not very far
Whenever the lotuses of
happiness bloom
Usually they bloom in the
lake of tears
These are God's divine
plays
God gives smiles and also tears
Your Hindi is very sweet
Hindi is really sweet
Sweet...
Will you teach me Hindi?
Oh! so many names
How many will they be?
May be in thousands! because
Vasu is one among thousands
Madam,Vasu is one among thousands
I agree
But among these thousands you can
accord second place to me!Isn't it
Meaning?
I request you!
Look there! I've written my
name just once
With so much of love Chakram
Please don't erase that or else
all my desires will be erased
After one year,If Vasu doesn't
come,then...
No,no just in case
Then,atleast you can give some
thought to my name
Forgive me Sapna
I lost my balance in my
over enthusiasm
Now I promise
For your love
I'll definitely culminate
that agreement
I'm leaving this city
but Sapna..
Are you real mother or
step mother?
Step mother will not worry
about your welfare
I'm your real mother,I can even
kill you for your welfare
If your madness continues
like this...
Then,I'll kill you with my
own hands,got it
You can kill me but you can't
erase my memories
They are not in your
hands
Where are you going?
Why? Will you also come
with me?
Where ever my heart
& memories will go
Can you go every where
come
Let the ocean & all the
rivers try
Love can't be subdued
Every spark gets extinguished
Vasu,what happened.. please
tell me,what happened?
You naughty,rascal...
Hey,where are you running away?
- Do sit ups
Salutations to the
sweet sixteen
Salutations to the first sight
of love
of love,salutations
The first one in the world who
kindled love in this heart
Salutations to first sweet heart
of the world
Thanks to the paths shown
by love
Salutations to the path which
reaches the heart
The place where this maiden got
calumniated
Salutations to that Town,that Street
& that House
The one who united us &
separated us
Salutations to that Time,to that Moment
& to that Chime
We were meeting here
it is written here
Salutations to this Writings &
it's Punctuations
On the sands of shore,where the
heart quavered like this
Salutations to every Wave which
swelled in the sea
In the depths of the enchanting
lake of the eyes
Salutations to that Whirlpool
which drowned us
Defying the veil,the thing
that slipped away
Salutations to that Green wicked
upper cloth
The enemies of love tried
their best
Salutations to the Look which
wasn't deterred
When 2 of us meet
Both
When both of us will meet
- Yes both
Yes,then
We'll make a new history
M- A-K-E
Create will be better
Isn't it?
Not only better,but
beautiful
C- R-E-A-T-E
And,if we don't meet,then...?
And,if we are not able to
meet,then...?
No... no...
And,if we are not able to meet,then
.. yeah-Yes
If we are not able to meet,then
- Yes,further
Even then,we'll create a
new history
Wonderful! Even then we'll
create a new history
Listen Postman
The letter which you gave that
house,where did it come from?
I don't know
- Is it from Hyderabad?
I told you,I don't know
What kind of a Postman is he?
he does not know anything
Daughter,in the morning,you
were asking the Postman -
Yes,this is Vasu's letter only!
he is alright
Job is also good,and
in Hyderabad...
Enough... Enough...
It's in Hindi,see
- I don't want to see anything
I know that you'll only
talk about Vasu-
And put the blame on me
I've broken the agreement
I beg of you! I don't want to
know about Vasu
Nor about Hyderabad
nor about his job
For God sake,in future
don't meet me
Don't see me & don't
talk to me also
Hello,Mr. Hari,are you fine?
Come.. come the devotee of
Lord Hanuman!
How are you?
Nothing new about me!
Neither wife nor that and
nor concubine
How is my son?
How is Sapna?
Did you see Mr. Hari,he's
asking straight away
How is Sapna?
He didn't even ask
how is mother?
Okay,how is mother?
- Enough!
Now tell me,how is Sapna?
She is like a Pumpkin
Mr. Hari,did you see his
mentality?
I don't want anything
but I wish that-
He should forget Sapna completely
One girl is staying in
this city
She's from our Madras
Caste and Race
matches perfectly
I want that some how Vasu should
get married to her
Mr. Shivaram,caste and Race
are now outdated
This is modern time
First love and later on
marriage
But...
We'll play a game
- What?
In this Love story,we'll
change the girl
How come?...
I'll appoint that girl as a typist
in my office
Then? -Then what?
Their eyes will meet and
they'll fall in love
Then...?- Love marriage
Then?... but how is it possible?
What is the guarantee?
What guarantee? I've seen
many such cases...
It's a small matter
Is it a small matter?- Yes
What's the name of the girl?
Tulasi
What's your age?-
Equal to Actress Hellen?
Zeenataman?.. Teenamuneem?
Who are they?
Oh! My god!don't you
watch Hindi movies?
I watch only Tamil films
Only Tamil movies?
Have you seen a Tamil movie
"Kadhalika Neramilai"
So,you've seen
What's the meaning of
that title?
There is no time to love
Here,you'll get lot of time!
Oh! No.. Aunty,what are
you burning?
Come.. come,your father laid a bet
that this photo can't be burnt
I'm proving that it can
be burnt
But,Mr. Professor,when did you
indulge in the dirty bet
Stop blabbering!
Atlast,I've won the bet
Sir,your Tea
Now,who has won?
Oh! you are here?
Swimming Pool which is filled
with water-
Is pleasant to look at
Isn't it?- Yes
I wanted to ask you
Something
Do you know,how to dance?
Before,I used to dance
but not now
Why?
Everything has got over
with him
But,why did you ask?
I thought you can teach
me dance-Yes?
Why?Am I not fit for it?
Yes! why not?
But,why do you want to
learn this?
I want to tire myself so much
by this practice
So,that the storm inside me
may mitigate
Oh! you want to meditate
- No,I want to forget
Will you teach me?
Why not?but it will be
very experience
Fees for Teacher
- We'll talk about it later
Then,what now?
First,you've to touch
Teacher's feet
Bless me!
When we both come together
we'll create a new History
Even,if we both don't
come together
Even,if we both don't come together
we'll create a new history,even then
How many people had loved
in this world?
Don't know how many,lover's blood
had this world sucked?
Why doesn't the thirsty sword stop?
why doesn't it's thirst gets subside?
We'll subside this world's
thirst!
We'll create a New History!
My heart is agitated
all night!
When the heartless world
tells us...
How many names are there in the books
who had been restricted to meet?
Why should we enter our names
in that list?
We'll create a new History!
Cholera in Hyderabad!
Let him die with cholera
and die a Dog's death
"Are you fine"?
Whenever you meet me,you'll always
ask me,"Are you fine"?
What does it mean?
Means... are you fine?
Her highness!
Why're you sitting alone here?
Sir,will you do a favour
to me?
Order me!
I've written Vasu's name all over
my room's wall,Isn't it?
Yes... Yes!
Can you count them and tell me
how many Vasu's are there?
Immediately!
I'm fine!
72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 78, 79, 80...
81, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86...
Where did I leave it?
Surprise,Seethuram
When ever I want to send you
on an inspection
It'll always be invariably your
mother's death Anniversary
I want to ask you,how many
mother's do you've?
Why have you become a deaf like
Sanjeev Kumar of film'Koshish'?
Come on tell!
Last time it wasn't my mother's,it was
my grandma's Death Anniversary
Grandma's Death Anniversary?
Whose will it be next time?
your's?... Mine?... Whose?
Come on tell
I had arranged everything for
your Mangalore trip
Whom shall I send at
this last minute?
Did you see the film?
Sir,if you permit,shall
I go?
What do you know about
this work?
I'll leave,Sir!
Alright! do you want to
help Seethuram?
No sir,it'll be a great help
for myself
Someone has to go there
you can go!
Who's car is that one
with stickers?
Oh! that Hazel,H belongs
to Chakravarthi
He has come from Goa,he had
enquired about students group
.. And took up a room in
this Hotel only
Have you come here to
spy on me?
You don't get angry my highness
it was Aunty's order to watch over you
She doesn't have any faith
on you,Isn't it?
When she doesn't have faith on me
why didn't she stop me there itself?
Does she consider,am I so shameless
to elope with anyone at midnight?
No.. No..! No.. No!
I've not come alone,I've come with
100 fellow students!
So many girl students,Teachers
have come with me
What'll they think about me,if
they see you spying me?
You don't worry,my highness! neither
I'll chase you nor I'll watch you
It was aunty's order
that I had to...
After all,she's my
mother-in-law
Mother-in-law?
If the agreement breaks down...
If her highness permits me
shall I go for a bath?
What is this strange,bond that
we share between us?
It's neither known to me
nor known to you
One string pulls and the second
comes running!
It'll come tied by the pull
of brittle strings
Like... like a mad lover!
It's neither known to me
nor known to you
Neither I'm getting sleep
nor peace
Even after a Herculian effort
I'm unable to stop it
...You are coming into
my dreams
It's neither known to me
nor known to you
Where did she go away?
Are you a Tourist guide?
Where's Sapna?
She has gone out
Who are you?
Me?... I'm her husband
Husband?
Almost!
I mean would-be husband
I thought,before I get married,I
shall get trained in family life
Sapna has gone with her would-be
husband in car
Both would enjoy their
journey back
Let them enjoy,both are going
to be husband & wife
Let them do anything,how're
we concerned with it?
Who are you?
When did you come back
from Mangalore?
What happened to you?
...Say something
...Let it play on
You're dancing like a
typhoon?
What happened to you?
I don't want to get drowned in
tears,that's why!
I was in such a deep
trance of sleep
...That even,if my eye was pierced
by thorn,I wouldn't have realised it
But now,I've come out of
the trance
And the truth has come infront of me
in it's true disposing form
You always tried to hide
a pain from me
Even when it tried to come out
you always stopped it in throat
Can't you share your pain
with me?
This is not pain..
it's poison
Neither can I swallow it
nor spit it out
In front,till my vision sees
I find only sea of darkness
Sandhya,I feel,I may get
drowned in it
I need a companion
I never saw you in such
a condition
Your eyes are burning like
Embers
Not just eyes,my entire body
is burning
My soul is also burning
I need such a cool shadow... under which
I can forget all my memories
All my memories
Why can't you be that
shadow?
I'm Siramakrishnan speaking
how are you?
Is my son there?
No,it's 6 P.M now,everyone has left
the office,I'm alone in the office
I've some personal work
How's Thulasi,have they started
meeting or not?
You're talking about meeting,she
has stuck,such that
If sensor people see it,they'll
cut them for obscene
Very good.. very good
how are you?
What could be sensational for me?neither
wife nor concubine or any woman
Do you love him?
Do you want to marry him?
Come on tell
If you permit me
by saying Yes to it
How eagerly I was waiting
to hear this Yes from you?
If you settle again in life
with this marriage
There Isn't any happiness which
is bigger than this for me
Sandhya,come whatever may,your
marriage will take place
...Definitely it'll...
You?... In Hyderabad?
I've a book stall in this
Exhibition
Do you want to know
who is she?
She's my future wife
Go and tell in Goa,that
I too can marry
Time?... Yes
I met him in Hyderabad
And he introduced me to his
future wife also
She's from Hyderabad
What a great beauty?!what a
youthfulness? what an eyes?
What great style,what great lips
what great colours?
Oh! Sapna! Is it you?...
come.. come..
How are you,my child?
I've come to ask you about
an important matter?
First time,you've come to our house
just wait for a minute
Child,have this sweet
Is it for Vasu's
Engagement?
What did you say?
Vasu is marrying some one else
Isn't it?
Who said that?
Come on tell
Is it true or not?
This can't be true
Without intimating us,how
can Vasu marry?
Then what I had heard
just now?
It's a lie
That's not a lie! you're lying
...For your son's love
You've gone mad in love
Did you understand my son
only this much?
Vasu will renege his promise
No.. no.. I've known Vasu since his
birth,are you teaching me about him?
Yuck! go away,you mad girl
You seem to be a man of
great conduct
I didn't know that you too have the
habit of keeping false promises
An experienced woman could
manage very well
Are you marrying that widow
with these ideas?
I don't know,what do you men
see in a woman?
That you're ready to die
immediately
Is there any custom & tradition
for it or not?
A big house... large eyes.. If one has
large front & back enough
...Is it enough?
But,Baby! I've not seen anything
big in you
Except,your big dirty mouth
Did Vasu give you an
invitation or not?
Unable to understand... what's that
big in you?
Which Vasu likes in you!
Except that big vermillion
You're Sapna,Isn't it?
- Yes and you
I've something to discuss
with you
It's time for my college
mother is inside,you may meet her
My name is Sandhya!- Is it
- I've come from Hyderabad
I'm Vaus's friend
Come in
What about your college?
Today,it's leave
Come Vasu,do something helpful
for your marriage arrangements?
Write atleast addresses
on these cards?
Isn't Sandhya there?
She has gone out of station
To personally invite her friends
for the marriage
Can't they be invited by post?
It's a normal practice now!
Come in!
Please sit down!
Who wrote all this?
It's me!
It was mother's order not to
utter even Vasu's name
For that order...
...This was my reply!
Mother is the biggest hurdle
in our love
Yes!
Vasu told me everything
Did Vasu tell you everything?
If he hadn't told me
how could I know all this?
Whenever we meet,it's always
about you,we discuss
Are you both so close?
Yes!
So,close... that you both touch
each other also?
Whenever we meet
we shake hands!
How is my Vasu?
This is 30th time,you're
asking this!
Don't count!I'll ask
millions of times
How's Vasu?
Our agreement will not break,Isn't it
If I ask like that?
Poor man!he Isn't a bad man
but he's a simpleton
He has come from Lucknow with a
fond hope that I'll marry him
If the agreement fails
This agreement will never fail
Look at her!
...Hey!...
Is she Vasu's mother?
No!
My mother-in-law!
Sapna,I'm going back by
tonight's flight
So early?
The work for which I'm here
is over
What work?
Do you want me to tell
the truth?
Definitely!
I had come to decide about
my marriage
What did you decide?
Oh! this is Coffee!I had
ordered for Tea
May be my cup of coffee
has come to you
...I didn't defile your
cup of Coffee
When did you come back?
This morning!
You didn't even inform me
before going!
Got the Ticket?have you sent it?
alright
Do you want to go to
office early?
No!
But,why did you call me
so urgently?
Madam,a flight Ticket,that travel agent
brought & gave it
Alright!
Abdullah! what's the date
today?
18 December!
And year?
Madam?- Come on tell
1979!
Isn't it 18th December 1979!?!
Now,you can go,look here
What are they?
They're marriage Invitations
I'm going to post them
Not necessary!- Go!
I'm unable to understand anything
Your silence is making
me go mad
We are made for each other
Understood!
Oh alright! then,you went to
go to Goa,Isn't it?
Alright! did you meet Sapna?
Yes,I did meet her!
Oh! that's why,this new behaviour
this new style
What did Sapna tell you?
Sapna told me everything!
About your love...
About those places...
.. Where you both used to roam around
with hands on each other's shoulders
She told about those
day's matters
.. Which used to come after
a long time of interval
.. But used to get over
very quickly
And about your long
live agreement
...It's big clauses!
Sapna has told me
everything
Is it so?
Didn't she tell about
her marriage?
Before the agreement could end
she's marrying a rich Bastard
If I had the rights,which I
had on you till yesterday
I would've slapped you for
uttering such dirty words
You met same Tom,Dick & Harry
did you believe whatever said by him?
The man you met in Manglore...
He likes Sapana.
But,Sapana doesn't like him.
There is a big difference
like earth & sky!
The difference between
Sapna and you
Sapna Isn't weak minded
like you.
She never forgot you even
for a moment.
She's counting every day,every
minute,waiting for you.
You just tell me only
this much!
When is your agreement
going to elapse?
When are you both going
to meet again?
Come on tell!
19th December 1979.
That means... tomorrow?
Waiting for this day,her eyes
have developed wounds!
How easily you could
forget her?
And were about to marry me?
It seems you had once jumped into the
river on a request from Sapna!
Is it to leave her in the
middle of the stream?
You know that!
When I get angry,I lose
my senses
This is my weakness
But neither such thing ever
occurred in my life!
Nor my anger has ever
let me down
Whatever I heard in Manglore
on that day!
It didn't even have proper means
to clarify it with Sapna
What was the necessity
to clarify?
Couldn't you wait till the
lapsing of the agreement?
Is that all your care?
If your heart get's shaken so
much for trivial matters...
Neither you've any right to
love nor be loved
Now,you only tell me,what
am I do?
You want me to tell you
even that
Take this Ticket to Goa
you leave immediately
After so much has happened
...Thank God
Before that could happen,this
had happened
That's why,I stopped posting of
wedding Invitations also
Me?.. I'll remain myself
My loneliness
...They were with me
earlier also
Now also,they'll be with
me only
Nobody will lose anything
If true love wins
What more can I ask?
But,leaving a Goddess
like you...
Will Sapna forgive me
for this?
Only if Sapna had known
all this?
Didn't you tell anything
to Sapna?
You've become so great,that I can't
look into your eyes & talk
Alright!where's sir?
No need to talk with my
brother regarding me
But,Sandhya,how can I
... No..
My marriage will not take place
with you,I'm saying it myself
Go,Vasu,it's your time
for your flight
Remember it
If you don't go today,you'll never be
able to meet Sapna again
Sapna(dream) will remain a
distant dream for you
Go!
I don't know,why,but,I feel even now
I may not be able to meet Sapna
Just tell me only this much,what
did she say before you came back?
Before I came!
First,she kissed me here
...That was for me
Then,here...
...That was for you
What happened to the Red vermellion
on your head?
Fate cried so much,that it got
washed away in it's tears
Then,whatever I had heard
was true?
He has gone away!and you
didn't even tell me
Even if,I told you,could you've
changed my fate's path?
Brother!
Today,once again,it has been proved that
family life,Isn't written in my fate
Yes... yes,he has cheated and
escaped from here
He's reaching Panjim by
morning flight
I've heard,that he's coming
there to meet some girl
Come whatever may,don't allow
them to meet
Break his hands...
break his legs
If possible,do away with
his life also
Mr. Belli
Every drop of whisky,that's flowing
in my veins
They're always loyal to you
Can I ever forget your favours?
Cheating my sister here,and enjoying
with some other girl there
Understood?
Take it,as your job is done
Today,you got up very early?
I'm waiting for the Sun
Why?
Is it Solar Eclipse today?
It was Eclipsed all the
365 days
And I couldn't forget
even a day
It was a year long of
one dark night
But,today the Eclipse
has got over
Today's Sun will come
with my life
...With my Vasu
Even I too wish,that your
Vasu must return
But,God's record is there
till now
He has always been ruthless
with True lovers
That's why!I'm still with
a hope
No... NO...
...My number will always be
second
First is he...
Look,Sun has come
Your Vasu will also
definitely come
I whole heartedly wish,that you both
should live happily forever
Has the marriage date
been changed?
Who told you?
Senior Boss,was saying...
With whom?
He was talking on phone with
Goa's Ram Singh
He was very angry
... and also over drunk
I came to know this also...
he was ordering to kill Vasu
No Sandhya!I'm not so heartless
to take anyone's life
Last night,in that inebriated mood
don't know,what I told him
Could I tell him to take
Vasu's life?
You're a drunkard
In your drinking binge,you'll not
know what you're doing...
And what you're blabbering?
Don't know,which beast wakes
up in you at that time?
And the man in you sleeps
What's Goa's Ram Sing's
phone number?
He has left home early
morning itself
It seems,he has left home...
Tell me,what are we
supposed to do now?
Look,we've to talk with him
regarding a very important matter
Is there any way that I can get
in touch with him?
Or could you send him
a message?
Do you know anything about
his whereabouts?
All I know is,once he
leaves home...
Even Police can't search
& find him
Can you give your neighbour
Mr. Sivaram's phone number?
How can they've phone
at home?
You may've at least his office
phone number?
I don't know
This really is a bad thing
Vasu has left for home
from here
But... but...
His life is in danger
Oh!God!
Yes!
I've understood
No need to plead so much!
This is my duty,I'll personally
go & inform them
You don't worry
Who's Telephone was it?
Stop... stop... stop...
enough...
Take this.
- Sir, I don't have change.
Keep it with you
Vasu has come
Hey!Mr. Sivaram!your son is coming
where are you going away?
...I know it!
...Why don't you keep quiet
for sometime?
Son,what's this,you've become
so thin in one year?
Greetings!
Wait!I'll get some coffee
for you
Greetings!son... greetings
are you fine?
First,I'll greet you by
folding my both hands
Then,I'll ask,how's your
health keeping now a days?
Please sit,sir!
Wow!Great son!you've started
speaking chaste Hindi
Where's father?
He has gone inside
How did you come to
know about it?
May be,he's feeling embarassed
to show his face to me
Leave it!I'll be back
in a minute
Alright!... alright!
Vasu,where's he?
Are you both father & son
playing hide & seek?
No,I thought of giving him sweets
as soon as he comes in
Greetings mother-in-law
how are you?
Why're you looking at me like
that?I'm Vasu
The barrier of time which you
had built,its over now
I've come to marry your
daughter
But,I don't find any receiptions
for your son-in-law
Isn't there any grand welcome
for me?
I seek your blessings
Mr. Professor
How's your health?
Let my health go to hell
First,tell me,how could you learn
such good Hindi?
Firing like a stengun
It was Mother-in-law's wish, isn't it?
That I must learn Hindi
Come on tell me,which region's
Hindi shall I talk?
Delhi's slang?
Meerut-Moradabadi slang?
Mathura-Brindavan's Brij slang?
Ayodhya's Awadhi?Bihar's Bhojpuri?
or Punjab's Punjabi
Oh!My handsome,my butter sweet
How are you?
Say something!Oh!uncle
open your mouth
Uncle,Isn't it Punjabi?
Mister!why're you staring
at me like this?
Go inside and inform the bride
that Groom has arrived outside...
...To marry her
1000/0 Urdu!
Great 1000/0 Urdu
Get up,Mother-in-law,get up
A heart is beneath your leg!
It'll be a kind consideration
This is Lucknow Urdu
Greetings... greetings!
Hey!fool!what are you
hearing?
Won't you go inside and
call my Bride?
Oh!My God!even we too don't
know such a slang
Which region's language?
Avadh!
Still,you're standing here
come,go away from here
...Bombay's local slang
Mother-in-law!you've become
so thin
Is it yearning for me?
Wood will burn and become
Charcoal
Charcoal will burn and
become ash
I got so much burnt that neither
there was charcoal nor Ash
Professor!Is it enough,or do you
want anymore Hindi?
Enough of Hindi!Truely
enough of Hindi
Firing like a stengun
Professor,tell me only this
why Isn't Sapna seen till now?
Is she getting dressed
up inside?
But,you must agree
one thing,sir
You're the best choice
for Sapna
But,where's Sapna!
Don't you know?
- No
I know!
Ask me!- Where?
Isn't there your Love spot?
... near the Sea shore
There's a mount near
the shore
There's a temple on the
top of the mount
And inside the Temple...
After so many days,I've got
a chance
God promise!I can't leave it
No... No...
No... leave me... leave me...
Leave me!
No!
Police?... Run... Run...
What happened to you,Vasu?
... You're in such a bad shape...
This is price of our Love
and our meeting
I feel,that the entire world
has become our enemy
What happened to you,Sapna?
.. My Love,My body...
My chastity...
Considering all three
as your property...
...How safely I had gaurded
it for you?
But,you've come at such a time
when,I'm about to die...
I'm also holding the last few
breaths only for you
...Just to meet you
Come on tell me,what happened?
Yes... yes!
My entire pain,all my tears
that's inside my eyes
Some how, I wished, it
reaches you
You're disappearing from
my eyes
No!
My eyes are getting closed.
I'm dying!...
No... Vasu... No!
Don't leave me and go away!
Did we both separate from each other to
meet like this in the embrace of death?
Before death engulfs me
somehow take me away with you
Take me away with you
Come Sapna!
Love's Language is different
One who loses in it...
...They say he has won!
And one who wins in it...
they say he has lost
Those who win in this,marry
And those who lose,give their
lives for one another
And become Immortal!