- Bro...
- What's it?
- Bro, can we get a room?
- No rooms available.
Somebody booked all
the rooms for one week.
Bro, we're really tired.
We can't find a room anywhere.
Give us just any room.
Hey! I already told you!
Please, bro! Just for one night.
We'll pay you extra.
Call him.
Reached Madurai?
Yes, bro.
We're near to Mellore.
The newspaper will
arrive by 4 or 4:30.
Take a photo and send it.
Okay?
Hey, vacate by noon.
The person who booked will be here.
Bro, today's newspaper.
- Hello?
- We'll meet at 8 PM tonight.
- I'll tell you the location later. Okay?
- Okay, bro.
I called Maari but
he didn't pick up.
Palani is waiting for
some Kerala gang.
That's why he's late.
You sit here.
Get out.
Hey, you brought this whole crowd
just for a bunch of kids?
Greetings, bro.
Haven't seen you around before.
Are you new to the field?
First time in Madurai, bro.
But we have plenty of clients in
Trichy, Pudukkottai, and Dindigul.
Hmm...
How old?
14 months?
Hmm...
Can I see the item?
Sure, but you need to
show the money first.
What?
Say that again!
The money's my responsibility.
I won't cheat you,
now show me the item first.
Althaf!
The item's safe.
But we'll hand it over
only after you settle the money.
This is Kalidasan's area.
We're with him.
His son, Maari.
Ever since he came back to town,
everything's gone downhill.
His dad died because of him.
That guy is a real psycho.
His father had an enemy...
Ramana.
A hot-tempered guy.
A worthy rival.
He could bring down anyone alone.
He didn't even know what fear was.
The whole town
trembled at his name.
But Maari burned Ramana's
family to ashes.
Now he acts like a
decent man and
tells me not to file a
case or go to court.
Why should we listen to him?
Who does he think we are, his slaves?
Don't we need money?
Of course we do!
Don't we?
That's why we're doing this
snake,
tortoise
and rat business.
Even if one of these go missing,
you can't go and file a case
in court, can you?
Right?
Get out!
Come on!
Hey! Hey!
Why are you beating the kid?
Ask him nicely.
Poor kid.
Go on!
Go and get it.
What are you glaring at?
Please, bro...
Don't hurt us.
Maari's ass!
Hey, get in.
Who's that?
Tell me!
It's a rubber snake.
You thought we came to fool around
in Madurai, huh?
- Move!
- How dare you talk!
- Let him go!
- Feeling like a mass hero, huh?
Go on, say another mass dialogue.
Althaf! Grab everything!
Give it! Hand it over!
- Come on, give it!
- Give it here!
Give it to me!
Get it, man!
Move!
Hey!
Catch him!
Hey, hey!
Why do you need all
this decoration, huh?
Alright, then!
Hey!
Here's the magazine!
- Grab them!
- Manish...
Run!
Come on!
Catch them!
Go!
Bro! Bro!
Bro! Come on, carry him!
Get in, fast!
Quickly start the car! Get in! Get in!
Don't let them go!
Go and catch them!
- Bro...
- Careful, man!
Bro... Bro...
Quick, quick!
Speed up!
Step on it!
Move it!
Fire up the engine!
They're behind us!
Get out and run, Althaf!
Run!
They've escaped!
Run! Faster, faster!
Just shoot him!
I fired all three bullets we had!
What will I shoot with?
Hey!
Did you find those boys?
No, we're still searching, bro.
Chop off the arms and legs of those
three Malayali boys, piece by piece.
When Palani opens his eyes,
it should all be laid out in front of him.
If he dies before that,
throw the pieces to the hunting dogs
before they light his pyre.
Get going!
They're over here! Come on!
"June melts into July"
"If you leave me, I have Julie"
"It hurts, yet brings a
strange sense of joy"
"Once love is gone, it's gone for good"
"No need of assurances"
"It's tough, yes, even a bit cliché"
"Hakuna matata"
"Let's eat, drink, keep on living"
"We're always so high"
"I'm a lonely Dzouza"
"Can't even blink my eyes"
"It's an unknotted knot"
"Can't bow down to others"
"Everybody's so jealous of me"
I'm leaving, Mom.
Do you realise
your dad's getting older?
Well Dad also should realise that.
Even studying, you couldn't manage.
Told you to find a job
and you won't even do that.
How would you?
You're not even scared of your father.
She's yelling at me thanks to you.
Go find a job, man!
"It's nothing but the echo of a big bang"
"Slice it up, fry it down"
"In different sizes"
"It's a great cult, boom boom!"
"Our troubles vanish in a game of football"
"Sorrows glowing brighter, set alight"
"O dear, it's my turn
My days shine in light"
"Though my nights burn in
sorrows and pain"
"I've tasted it all by now"
"My doomed fate
feeds on cheap fish"
"The road of life sparkles with promise"
Yet I can't bear the weight anymore.
Are you really going to marry her?
What kinda question is that?
- Hard to tell with you.
- Huh?
People say you went to Canada,
married some girl
and even have a kid now.
People in this town are nuts.
To be honest,
I only learned what love is
after she came into my life.
"June melts into July"
"If you leave me, I have Julie"
"It hurts, yet brings a
strange sense of joy"
"Once love is gone,
it's gone for good"
"No need of assurances"
"It's tough, yes, even
a bit cliché"
"Hakuna matata"
"Let's eat, drink, keep on living"
"We're always so high"
"I'm a lonely Dzouza"
"Can't even blink my eyes"
"It's an unknotted knot"
"Can't bow down to others"
"Everybody's so jealous of me"
Aparna went to Germany?
Eh?! Did she?
Mm-hmm...
No limits.
A flying bird!
By the way...
weren't you in love with
Balan sir's daughter?
What happened to that?
Don't you know?
They both were in a relationship
from 5th to 12th grade.
Only two people in Unnikulam
didn't know about that relationship.
One was you and the other was her.
How come?
I didn't want her to know.
Oh, please! Not because you don't
have the guts to tell her you love her.
Don't have to make
it such a big deal.
The moment we feel a girl is ours,
courage just starts flowing through us.
And then, it turns into a flood...
one that carries us away with it.
Come here, here...
Mark that player.
Stand closer.
Just fix that cooler for us.
We can have chilled beer from time to time.
- Hey, you!
- Eh?
Get off that phone!
It's about the car, let me speak, man!
Keep that phone away, man!
I'll call you back.
I'll call you right back.
You guys will see!
Is he ever going to buy a car?
Who knows?
Shine, get him!
- Hand, hand!
- No. No, no!
- Didn't you see?
- It didn't touch.
- It touched his hand.
- Thank to you jokers and your foul play
whenever we play,
we lose in the first round itself!
Neither your strategy nor
your game works.
To top it, a stupid captain!
If this is how it is,
my Benz Electronics and I
have pulled out of this sponsorship.
First, learn to respect
the captain's strategy.
That's why we come back
with empty goal buckets every time!
If you can't respect his strategy,
don't play.
You switched teams for banana fritters!
- What's happening here?
- I don't know, man.
What a messy team! Come with me!
Our stock market thing, right?
It was a fraud app, man.
- It's gone...
- 50000 rupees gone, huh?
But good thing we lost it.
- Eh?
- Not like that.
We'll go to Switzerland.
There, it's six months of work
and six months off.
Did you see this in some reel content?
No, man. We go to Switzerland.
It snows there for six months
and at that time, we'll clear
the snow off the highways.
Then it's summer there
for six months.
So, no work.
We get a salary equivalent
to 3–4 lakh rupees.
Then we come back here on
leave and have a blast!
Just think about it.
Putting up posts and stories on Instagram.
I don't have my 10th or 12th certificates.
They're all at the college.
Let us just apply and keep.
Only when we get an appointment,
we'll need the certificates.
Don't think that'll work out.
We've got 4–5 days.
Now go and get it from your college.
Go!
- Hey...
- What's up?
Tell me the truth.
Is my captaincy that pathetic?
Do you think there's a better
player than you here?
Nope.
Do you think there's a better coach
or manager than you?
Tell me, do you think?
You know Pep Guardiola?
You should've been a bigger manager
than Pep Guardiola.
- But you got stuck in Unnikulam.
- That's right!
Go and tell them that.
Okay.
Wonder which one is this Guardiola?
Sir...
It has been so long...
Please forgive...
And forget...
No matter how many years pass,
I'll never forget you.
Come on, sir. He's just a kid.
Just hand it over and let him go.
Who are you?
- Me?!
- Yes, you!
I am the captain cum manager
of Athletico Unnikulam.
I myself came here, skipping practice
because he's our marquee player.
He studied at this college
for only three months.
But the damage he caused
in those three months was massive.
Unless he makes up for that damage,
I won't give back the certificate.
So, why don't the manager
and his star player get going?
Sir...
Please, sir...
Go on!
Shall I just thrash him?
Shush! Stop it!
Wait...
Tell the truth,
did you steal anything from here?
Get lost!
What could I possibly steal from here?
He's asking for 3 lakhs as compensation
for the fight with the seniors.
Three lakh rupees?!
What a pain!
Call Nixon and tell him
we need his car's spare key.
Hm?
Gotta do something.
There is!
Come... come on!
Sir, this car is worth
30 lakh rupees.
You can keep this key
as a token of trust.
Please give me those certificates, sir.
I need to take photocopies.
It's to apply for a job, sir.
Please, sir.
Sir?
His original certificates
are here in the office.
Will check, sir.
He wants photocopies
to apply for a job.
Find it and give it to him.
Admission number?
- Listen...
- Yes?
Where did you say your car was?
Downstairs, sir.
Do one thing.
- Take this key when you go.
- Okay.
And arrange for someone else in
the office to give him the certificates.
- Okay, sir.
- And you sit in that car yourself.
Get out of the car only after he
returns those certificates in the office.
Okay, sir.
Plan flopped. It won't work!
Let's go.
What do we do?
How about we bring your dad?
There's no point.
Either I bring 3 lakh rupees
or I forget about those certificates.
What ill-fated time
did I join this college?
Bro, come with me!
- Where to?
- Come, come!
Don't pull me! I'm coming!
That one won't work out for you.
Come...
Hey.
Come here.
Hi...
Dude, what's her name?
Oh! Nidhi.
Nice...
She's not a Malayali, bro. She's Tamilian.
Tamilian?
Tamilian...?
Don't fall for her, okay?
It's not going to work out.
Anyway, he's good for nothing...
Oh, no... Teacher!
Run!
Bro...
Ah!
I didn't believe
what you said the other day,
but you really are awesome!
What's it? Tell me the matter.
You told me the other day about how
the moment we see a girl and
feel she is ours,
that feeling…
- Mm-hmm...
- I felt it today, bro!
- Really?
- I was just flowing...
That girl is from Tamil Nadu.
Language isn't a problem...
Do you know Tamil?
I do... I know enough...
Really?
Friends who live in my heart,
my dear friends.
Vijay bro is my life!
You still haven't said a word to her,
have you?
Nah.
Describe her to me.
How are her eyes?
Round eyes.
Nose?
Sharp nose.
Pointy chin, right?
Yes.
It's going to be hard.
These kinds of girls are super bold.
But they're also drawn to guys
who are bold.
The moment you see her...
just propose.
- Do you think I'm bold enough to do that?
- Tea?
No, thanks.
Come on, we'll sort it out.
There's a chance
she could be in a relationship.
Or she's already got
tons of guys after her.
When love hits,
don't hold back, just say it.
It's out of respect for them.
And if they don't get it,
we should just tell them to beat it.
Love is not for the faint-hearted!
You said she's a Tamilian, right?
That's where all the romance happens!
Gautham Menon, AR Rahman,
Ilaiyaraaja, Mani Ratnam.
Watch their films, then go for it!
You'll nail it!
Okay.
Can Aryan do it?
Both legs aimed at those eyes!
The heartbeat races just for him.
Only 10 metres left for Aryan Vishwam
to seal the win!
Excuse me.
Sha...
I don't love you but...
Hi Sha... Ahem...
Hi Nidhi.
If you don't mind
I don't love you.
I don't think you're beautiful.
But I'm scared all that might happen.
Think it through and let me know.
Bye, then.
Thank you, sir.
A rainbow from Madurai
lights up the blue skies of Unnikulam!
Aryan, once a coward in love,
now charges forward with courage
to claim victory!
YAY!
Yes!!!
What the hell, man?
Correct.
When she sees you tomorrow,
she'll be stunned all over again.
Since you got a yellow card,
stay away from her class, okay?
Go into defence mode.
Hi Nidhi.
I am Aryan.
Let's look at the next question.
And I don't need a doctor.
I need some oxygen.
Sho... I can't even sit...
Nidhi...
I am in love with you.
Don't take it lightly.
Ever since I met you...
Pounding heartbeat...
Just like when my dad saw my mother.
Same feel...
Something wrong...
Ah!
How do I say this...
Everything in just a second...
I am in love with you, Nidhi.
What's going on?
I love you.
It's not love.
It's obsession.
Why bring me into this?
I mean... I... I... love you...
You think you can come
into someone's life
by talking movie dialogues
and impress them?
It's not right.
Uh-oh!
Only Tamil movie dialogues, huh?
You think she'd fall for it
if it was Malayalam?
I doubt she'd understand.
But now she knows
you're a total goner.
If I'd studied CBSE,
my English would shoot like bullets.
Did you notice something?
She looked at your face
for 40 seconds straight and talked to you
And your "I love you"!
It really packed a punch!
Yeah, man!
Seriously!
She's yours!
Niju! Put petrol in the bike and go home.
I'll catch up.
Here, here! Right here!
Here?
Thank you, bro!
Hi.
What's your intention?
I am in love with you.
I've made it clear.
Please leave from here.
I want to... to...
That... tha... the...
Spit it out in Malayalam itself.
I can understand.
When I see you, it feels like
a band is playing in my heart.
Are you not normal?
Are you nuts?
Don't you ever think?
I do.
I only think about you.
You're standing in front of my house.
This is not love, it is harassment.
Can I ask you one thing?
Are you in any relationship?
Argh!
Just look at my fate.
I'm standing here
talking to an idiot like you.
Please just leave from here.
- Get out!
- Just one more thing, Nidhi.
After chasing you so much
and if you're in another relationship,
I won't be able to bear it.
Get out, you!
Who are you?
I... I am...
Ask Nidhi, she'll tell you.
What?
Mom... just listen to me, Mom...
Who's that boy?
What's he doing here?
I'll call you later.
No matter who stands against us,
it won't affect us.
I just need to talk to your dad
and everything will be settled.
You don't know my family the way I do!
Just stop crying, will you?
Argh!
Come.
Come on!
Got something to tell you.
Where is your house?
- Unnikulam...
- Unnikulam.
- What's your name?
- Aryan.
Aryan...
Idiot!
If I find out you even dare to
go after her again...
this won't be the worst you face.
Got it?
He's on the hunt for love.
Dude, everything was fine...
until you barged into her house like that.
That was very lame.
Isn't that right?
Barged into her house?
Yes.
Bro...
I chased Aparna for seven years.
You all laughed at me
because I never told her how I felt.
Ever since I saw her...
I can't eat... I can't sleep...
Listen... you focus on the game.
And fall in love with football instead.
Tony bro, at least he tried
for a girl at this age
but you even at this age,
have you ever gone after a girl?
You won't understand the pain.
It's when I feel sad
that I go play as a guest.
I always knew it!
Right?
Incoming puke alert!
Use this.
A puke missile!
Where are those red peanuts from?
He's got no manners.
Are you okay?
Okay, okay...
Bro...
- When I saw her face...
- Hm?
Poor fellow...
I felt like whatever I did was wrong.
It wasn't wrong, dear... You were right!
- You were right!
- Dude...
Since you are feeling so bad...
have two more shots
and blackout completely!
Shut up!
- What?
- Get lost!
You can't stand here and smoke.
Fine, I'll sit and smoke!
Get going, man!
- Such guys!
- Sorry, bro!
Dear son, I'll never tell you not to drink.
It's okay to have a drink
or two once in a while.
But don't drink to run away
from your problems.
That will only ruin your life.
No matter what happens,
we have to face our problems head on.
Okay?
Good morning.
Nidhi.
I am sorry.
I don't even know who you are.
You embarrassed me in
front of my class.
Then you came to my
house and did the same.
I'm going for my exam now.
I'm only talking to you so that you
don't come there and cause trouble.
Is it right to say you love a girl without
even respecting her personal space?
Don't behave like this.
Bye.
Nidhi.
Please let me talk.
What's it?
That is...
I studied in a boy's school
from 5th to 12th grade.
And because of that,
I'm not really familiar with love and all.
That's when I met a girl
in my tuition class and fell in love,
but I didn't even have the guts
back then to tell her.
I was afraid this would
turn out like that too.
That's how I ended up doing all this.
Sorry.
It's alright.
Listen...
As an apology for all the trouble I caused,
can I buy you a coffee?
No, no. It's fine.
Listen...
At least to make up for the beatings
I took from your family...
can I buy you a coffee?
Who beat you up?
If someone hit me
and told me not to talk to you,
it must've been your family, right?
Did you see a doctor?
No... So...
my friends and I went to the bar,
had a few drinks and slept it off.
By the way,
how long has it been
since you came to Kerala?
It has been three years.
Oh?
My mother works as a superintendent
in the Railways.
You can speak Malayalam quite well.
I love Tamil
Vijay bro is my life.
I watch every Vijay bro movie
at least five times.
I'm a die-hard fan.
I hope you won't just stay silent
the next time you see me.
Right?
Let me be clear.
Anyone can tell someone
they love them.
That's your right.
And I have the freedom
to respond or not.
The reason I'm sitting here
with you, having coffee,
is simply out of respect.
There's no extra meaning to it.
Even if you come after
me or talk to me,
I won't feel anything for you.
You're just wasting your time.
My parents have had my whole life planned
since the day I was born,
where I'll study, what job I'll do,
who I'll marry
and even when I'll retire.
You're not even
an option for me.
So please, don't come
and talk to me again.
Do you understand?
Or I can explain it in Malayalam.
We're an orthodox family.
Me, my brother, my wife
and our extended family.
We have to discuss with everyone
before making a decision.
Mine's an orthodox family too.
I can have my father talk to you.
It's not going to happen, Nixon.
You know I can't live without you, Nichu.
And I can't live as another man's wife
in this lifetime.
So, Nichu, find another girl
and live happily with her.
Let them suffer
seeing me live like this my whole life.
I was the one
who chased after you for love.
I won't let you suffer because of that.
Bro, think it over one more time
before you decide.
We can sort it out. Tell him, man!
This isn't like going on a trip to Munnar.
Are you sure?
Shouldn't we at least
do something for love?
Bye, then.
Listen, don't give up
just because she said no.
Try harder!
She's your girl!
Also, I haven't told Suhana.
Let it be a surprise for her!
Not just her,
all of Unnikulam will be surprised.
'SUPER FAST TO PONNANI'
This love is something else, right?
- Excuse me.
- Hm?
May I speak with her for
a moment, please?
Thank you.
Babe, I thought a lot.
And I've decided that
not talking to you is…
just so bad, so bad, babe!
Don't call me babe.
Babe... what I mean is...
I mean, babe--
I said don't call me babe!
What's your problem, huh?
Babe, when I first saw you...
it felt like I was transported to
another world!
I have a habit of drinking.
My stupid brain keeps wondering
if you're in another relationship.
I am so madly in love with you, babe.
I already told you, didn't I?
Don't come and talk to me!
Whatever you're thinking
is not going to happen.
You're just wasting your
time and energy.
As it is, whatever I want never happens.
And time and energy…
I have plenty to waste.
But don't you worry about that.
Just forget it, babe.
I just want to know...
if you're in a relationship or not...
Is there a rule that if I'm single,
I have to fall for you?
No, nothing like that.
If you're not single,
I'll just say 'okay, bye' and walk away.
And you're the one
who makes the rules, babe.
Didn't I tell you not
to call me 'babe'?
What else can I call
you other than babe?
You're like a baby
who only listens to her parents
and walks around
like an outdated version of herself?
What's your biggest wish in life?
That would be...
I want to go to Barcelona,
watch the Barcelona vs Real Madrid match
and have a blast.
Do you know what my wish is?
Hm?
I want to go to a hotel, sit by myself,
order and enjoy a meal.
I want to go to the beach at night
and stand in the water.
I want to go on a solo drive
to somewhere far away.
And before that,
I want to learn how to drive.
I want to have pani puri
from a roadside stall.
How can you even call these wishes?
That is the difference
between you and me.
Listen... Babe...
This is why I said
you're an outdated version.
Narayani chechi's shop is 5 km away.
I'll buy you special puttu steamed
in a coconut shell, with duck roast.
Pani puri is nothing next to that!
Pani puri, it seems! What nonsense!
Bhel puri!
Pani puri!
Masala puri!
Those who've eaten, those
who want to eat
and those who've never eaten,
free puri for all!
Pani puri! Dahi puri! Sev puri!
Bhel puri! Masala puri! All puri! Free pu--
You!
- Sir...
- You think this campus is your playground?
It's about your certificates, right?
I've told the office.
You'll get it tomorrow.
Not even your shadow should fall
on this campus after that!
- Sorry, sir.
- Scram with your bhel puri, pani puri!
Sorry.
[Indistinct chatters]
I can't unable to push.
Aryan!
Here she comes!
Why was the principal scolding you?
Oh, he wasn't scolding.
He sweetly said he'd return
my certificates he'd confiscated.
Nothing else.
- What?
- You go, I'll come.
Ah, okay. Bhai, let's go.
I had to go to that Bhai's house
and play with his kid for five hours
to get this stall here.
I thought you'd at least buy a pani puri.
Why go through all this effort?
This is no effort at all.
If I've to go Barcelona,
I'll need to buy a ticket, get a visa,
need money in my bank account...
compared to that your wish is so simple.
We have to try and get it done.
Am I right?
Doesn't matter if it's Barcelona
or this stall.
It's a wish... Right?
A wish is a wish, after all.
Alright, then. I'm off.
Hey!
That day you said...
About puttu and steam?
Where can I get that?
Hey, dear... I am...
You take a bus and go home.
Something came up.
- Bus?!
- Yes.
"A thorn struck me,
Not my eyes, but deep in my soul"
"Splintering, my spirit falls apart"
"Something shattered within"
"Blue waves roll up and kiss our feet"
"We're bound together
By a magician's unseen thread"
"Is my heart swimming in delight,"
"Or fluttering like a pigeon in a cage?"
"Did a dragonfly drop a rock
On my chest?"
"Don't set my heart ablaze with desire"
"Don't slay me with
Sharp, piercing glances"
"Don't shine too fiercely,
I might burn to ash"
"Don't wilt, you're a delicate feather"
"A gentle blossom,
Shaped from my very rib"
"Blue waves roll up
and kiss our feet"
"We're bound together
By a magician's unseen thread"
"Is my heart swimming in delight,
Or fluttering like a pigeon in a cage?"
"Did a dragonfly drop a rock
On my chest?"
"A thorn struck me,
Not my eyes, but deep in my soul"
"Splintering, my spirit falls apart"
"Something shattered within"
Today was really nice.
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
Can you give me your number?
9994924-
- Shall I dial for you?
- Yes.
Yes, of course.
Lock.
- Hello?
- Is this Nidhi Sathyaprakash's guardian?
- Yes.
- I'm calling from RMV College.
Ma'am, this coming Friday there's
a compulsory parent-teacher meeting.
There was a student strike against
the management in the college today.
And none of the students
have attended their classes.
No, no, she must be in the class only.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
- Please ensure you attend the meeting.
- Okay.
Yes, we will attend.
Nidhi.
Didn't you go to college today?
Why? What happened?
I got a call from your college.
Apparently, you didn't attend class?
You said you were late today
because of the extra class, right?
No... I did attend, Mom.
Hm... why this confusion?
Friday there is a meeting in
the college, it seems.
Management said parents
must attend.
I'll call your dad right away
for the meeting.
Okay.
Oh!
Ha...
Hel...
Hi Nidhi.
I told a lie.
Huh?
And now I'm in trouble.
What's the problem, Nidhi?
They called from college
because I didn't attend class.
There's a parent-teacher
meeting on Friday.
My mom will come.
My dad will come too.
I'm going to be dead!
Don't worry! Just calm down.
We'll talk it out and sort it, okay?
Our--
Argh!
Hey!
Give me that phone.
Just give it!
We'll sort it out right away.
- Hello.
- Hello Usha?
- Yes?
- It's me, Tony.
Tony, dear!
Why don't you call me
like you used to?
Dude...
If her parents come to college,
she'll probably just get a punishment.
If you make him handle
this kind of responsibility,
dismissal is guaranteed.
By the way, could you
do me a favour?
Of course!
- Hello?
- Hello.
Is this Nidhi Sathyaprakash's mother?
Yes.
Nidhi.
Sorry, Nidhi.
It was nothing.
Looks like the college staff
called by mistake.
Sorry, dear.
Nidhi!
Hello, Aryan.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Mom spoke very sweetly to me.
I feel like there's someone
who'll help me if I
ever have a problem.
Aryan, I've a doubt...
Put her on speaker.
Hope she won't find out
it was a fake call?
Will Mom get a call again?
No, no.
No, no, she won't get any call.
I've also got such calls
from college many times.
Don't take it too seriously.
There won't be any more calls.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Good night.
Bye.
Bro! Thank you!
You're so damn powerful!
That number you called before,
just delete it.
Aha!
Hey! Get in.
How's it?
World class!
- Really?
- Of course!
- Shine! Come on, man!
- Get lost!
We need to go on a long drive with this car
and have a blast.
We shall!
Just amazing!
Hey! Close it gently.
Why are you so sad?
He didn't let me take the car for a spin.
But the car is right here, no?
I don't think he'll get out of it
for at least a year.
The family group is flooded with pictures
of Chachan's car.
Goodnight, Tina.
Okay.
Also, Shine... there's something...
I'll tell you tomorrow.
Look at this.
I don't wanna see it!
- Dude!
- Dude...
He gave you the car?
Yes, I made it happen.
Where're you off to with the helmet?
I am off to collect my certificates
from college.
College?
She called me last night and was all...
I miss you... I love you...
She said now there's someone
who looks after her.
I've got a feeling
this is gonna work out, dude.
Leave the bike and get in the car.
No, it's okay. I'll take the bike.
I haven't had a chance
to take this one for a spin.
Let's go through MC Road
and fly this beast.
Let her know that you've
rich friends too.
Park it and come.
- Come on, quick!
- Alright, I will.
There's a mirror, you can comb your hair.
Nidhi.
Where were you yesterday?
- You know Aryan, right?
- Yes.
I went out with him
and ate a lot of spicy food.
Great!
I had gone to the staff room
to submit the draft.
They were discussing about you.
The management is already really angry
about calling the strike yesterday.
And on top of that,
the teachers were saying the students
called the strike just to roam around
and take rooms.
Why did you make a fake call?
That fake call was the biggest problem.
The teachers have called your mom
to inform her about it.
Stop, stop here!
Isn't that Mary's sister?
She's grown up so fast!
Who cares?
What do you mean?
Huh!
Nidhi!
- What's happening?
- Can you start the car? Please.
Please, please.
Start the car.
It's okay, we'll see.
We'll go now.
Go where?
This is my friend.
Shine.
Nidhi... what's it...
What happened?
Can you please stop that music?
Chachan is calling me,
I need to go soon.
- Look, he's calling.
- Just calm down!
Ugh!
Chachan and Mom are
calling me non-stop.
I stepped out saying
I'll go bless the car and be right back.
Tell me where to go, I'll drop you.
I'm going for a smoke,
be right back.
Do you have cigarettes?
Nidhi.
What happened?
I'll only know if you tell me.
My family found out about the fake call.
They called the college
and informed Mom.
Oh, no...
My mom is in college
for the parent-teacher meeting.
I don't know how to face Mom.
I feel so ashamed.
Oh, no... I don't know what to do...
Nidhi...
The blessing is over, Mom.
I'll light two candles and come.
Joy has been ready since morning.
Just make him understand, Mom.
Two have shown up early
in the morning to flirt.
I'm getting worried seeing you worried.
Please calm down.
We will figure something out.
- What are you doing in the car?
- Get out!
- What's it?
Wait a minute.
What is the problem?
- What were you doing?
- Brother...
Hang on! Wait a minute.
Just a minute... Let me speak.
You stop acting smart!
Stop pushing me! Just talk it out.
What's wrong?
Go get a room!
Don't create nuisance for people!
Who are you--
Give your father's number.
Give your parents' number.
- Why Dad's--
- Say it!
Hello.
We found your son and a girl
in a compromising situation in a car.
If you don't raise them properly,
the townsfolk will tear them apart.
Townsfolk will tear them apart?!
- Which bloody townsfolk, huh, you moron?
- Eh?
We live in a democratic country
where we vote.
If something happens to my kids…
bloody moral policing scumbags.
Hang up, you moron!
Get lost!
Well, it is his dad after all.
Clearly, the apple doesn't fall
far from the tree.
Give me your father's number.
We already gave you the number.
Why are you simply creating an issue?
Move aside, you!
Who are you people?
Move aside!
- Bro...
- 626
Hello.
Oh, Tamil, huh?
We found your daughter
and a guy in a compromising situation.
This is the last warning.
You'd better advise your daughter.
We better not see them
around here again.
Hey, hey!
You dare wear those Kunnamkulam crocs
and step on a 15-lakh car?
Move your damn feet!
- Shine, don't... don't...
- Who the hell are you, huh?
Who are you, huh?
Who the hell are you guys?
Move! Shine...
His bloody...
Oh, no!
Get the hell out of here
with your damn car!
I said get going!
Get inside the car.
Was this car part of your
dad's dowry, you pig?
- It hasn't even been blessed yet!
- Move away!
- Who are these jerks?
- Get inside the car!
I know how to get into my car, man!
Get going!
We're going, man!
Don't dare come here again!
Dude, where are you?
Is Nidhi with you?
What's the problem?
It's a huge issue in college now.
Nidhi's parents are here.
Apparently, she ran away with someone.
They're heading to the police station.
And they're saying it's you.
Tell me the truth.
Is she with you?
I'll call you back, okay? I'll call.
Haven't they had enough?
Didn't you get enough?
Use her to the maximum!
We're leaving, bro! We are!
- Shine!
- Go quickly!
Get going!
Shine...
What are you doing?
Sir, this guy had intruded
into our house once.
I let him off with a warning.
I suspect he's under the influence of
weed or drugs.
Reduce the speed, Shine!
- Be quiet!
- Calm down, dude.
- Hello?
- Yes, hello.
- Is this Chandran?
- Yes.
I'm calling from
Chooravattom police station.
- What's this regarding, sir?
- Isn't Aryan your son?
- -Yes.
- We've got a complaint against his name.
What complaint?
He has kidnapped a girl called Nidhi.
We tried calling their number
but it is switched off.
You will need to come to the station.
- I'll come.
- Don't be late.
- Okay, sir.
- Okay.
Joy!
Dude, just switch it off.
He keeps calling.
- Who?
- Chachan!
- Joy!
- Yes.
His phone is switched off now.
Idiot took my car and went!
Why are you staring at the road
so early in the morning, Mary?
What happened?
Shine left early in the morning
with the car to bless it.
His phone was ringing just a while ago.
Now it says it's switched off.
So sad, Joy bought a car
and can't even use it himself.
What about his course?
He's saying he doesn't want to
do that course.
He's saying he'll do some other course.
I feel some peace
thinking about Aryan now.
He's saying he wants to work,
go abroad and all.
He went to college to meet the principal
and get his certificates.
It's such a relief.
Hey!
How come you're here?
- Go and get the car keys.
- Why?
Need to go to the police station.
Apparently, Aryan has kidnapped a girl.
A girl?!
- I'll be there soon.
- Oh, dear goodness!
I always told you
not to spoil these kids too much!
What happened?
- Aryan ran away with some girl.
- I knew this would happen!
Shine took the car early morning.
He's not back yet
and his phone is switched off too.
- Joy!
- Yes.
I'll go get ready and come.
We need to go to the police station.
- Listen...
- Hm?
The petrol tank is almost empty.
Brand new car
and the petrol's already over?
Chachan said the
Unnikulam pump has dirty fuel,
so he wanted to go to town to fill up.
What a pain!
How much cash do you have with you?
Less than 100.
Pull over to the side somewhere.
I won't need to pull over.
It stopped.
Get out and push,
I'll steer it to the side.
- What a task!
- Get out and push!
I'm at the station now.
I've filed a written complaint.
We are investigating in our own way.
I had given him a good thrashing before.
He's such a total loser.
Where did you find this crazy girl?
Dude...
What terrible timing on my part
to take you into the car!
I told you I'll take my bike!
You're the one who
dragged me into the car.
You're the one who said highway
and dappankutthu dance.
As if she's my aunt's only child
for me to take her on
a family trip in my car!
Hmph!
Just tell her to leave right away!
She's the girl I love, dude.
If you love her,
take her to your house, man!
Dude, please calm down.
I don't want to hear anything.
Ask her to leave immediately.
Go and have a lime juice.
His bloody lime juice!
- Cool down, man.
- Get lost!
Nidhi, we can explain it
to your dad and mom.
We can tell them what happened.
No, no.
I can't face them.
You don't have to go through
all this trouble for me.
I can take care of it.
Nidhi... Nidhi...
Please, sit.
Stay seated, please...
Nidhi.
You must understand our situation.
We can somehow convince your parents.
Please...
I said I'll go, right?
You can't even cross the road
on your own, so where will you go?
Nidhi, his uncle bought this car
after wanting it forever.
He got it yesterday and now
we're stranded without petrol.
We don't even have money for that.
Please try to understand.
What is the problem, sir?
If the kids have gone out,
they'll be back by evening, right?
Would you be okay if it was your daughter?
What else do I say, sir?
This isn't a place where kids
aren't allowed to roam, right?
Do you have any number
where we can reach Aryan?
No, sir. There is no other number.
Who's that?
Sir, this is Joy, our neighbour.
Are you a member?
A lot of people have invited
but I haven't joined.
I'm not interested in politics, sir.
Sir, Joy's nephew, Shine.
He's also been missing since this morning.
Joy bought a new car.
We think they all left in that car.
Car.
Friend.
Hello.
I am SI Shaji from
Chooravattom Police Station.
SI?!
Shine, I'll give you two hours.
For what?
You, Aryan and that girl
should come here and surrender.
Or we'll catch you and lock you up.
Or else I'll charge you with
every possible offence
and throw you in jail.
It's more complicated than you think.
That girl's family
is very strong politically.
So, you, him, and that
girl should come to this station
within 2 hours and present yourselves.
We'll be there, sir.
Promise, sir. I swear on my mother.
Dude...
- Full problem.
- What happened?
The police just called me.
They're saying her dad
is some big influencer.
We can't go back now.
They're going to beat us up
and throw us in jail.
Stop shivering like this,
we can figure something out.
Figure what out?
We've got no money
and the car's running on empty.
Hey!
This must be our fate.
Shouldn't we help her
get out of this misery?
The highway isn't safe.
Let's take the coastal route.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
What was wrong with me! Damn!
Bro, is there any finance place?
To pawn a gold chain.
There's one over there.
And on that side too.
"O introvert enchantress,
You cast a silent spell of magic"
"You are the soft mist
That drifts beneath moonlight"
"Your lilting melody calms
The deepest storms inside me"
"Petite as a deer,
You are my tender beloved"
Hey! Switch off your phone!
You look straight and drive.
Get lost!
Haven't you done enough?
"I've fallen in love"
His bloody photography.
"What sorcery has changed me?"
"I wander as a Romeo"
"I've fallen in love"
"Lost in the universe of you"
"What sorcery has changed me?"
"I wander as a Romeo"
"Is it fate's quiet conspiracy"
"Ripples of our love circling the world?"
"You shine like a star
Glinting beyond reach"
"This love is a fever without remedy"
"A gentle blossom
That scorches with longing"
Come on, let's go.
"Leaving only ache behind"
"A distant frenzy"
"Come, sit beside me
As the journey begins"
"All doors knocked, all dreams pursued"
"Nothing gained but a lost soul"
"Weary and adrift,
I wandered without compass"
Call him and...
"No complaints left, no one to hear them"
Or I should...
Brother...
Eh? Brother?!
Why did that boy's parents
speak so rudely?
Which boy?
Friend...
That's because at midnight... Ugh!
How am I going to explain it in English?
Sister...
If a girl travels with two guys at night,
people in Kerala don't like it.
You may sleep.
What's so wrong about that?
There's nothing wrong... You please rest.
Wrong, it seems!
Also, would you just get into
any car like that?
What is this behaviour?
How shameful!
Yuck!
Why did I even bring these
two into my car?
This is like losing the car you want
and wrecking the one you have.
Hello.
Dude, where are you?
We are in...
Ottapalam.
Dude, there's nothing to worry.
Just come home.
All the problems here are sorted.
They're saying they'll get them married.
Married?!
Yes, marriage.
Her family is embarrassed
because she ran away.
Everyone here is upset about it.
I'm more worried than they are, dude!
One guy kicked
and broke Chachan's car tail lamp.
If he sees that, he'll definitely kill me.
Chachan loves you more
than his car.
Eh?
He's been waiting here
without even eating,
just to see you.
Everyone is upset, you guys come back.
Come soon.
- Did Chachan really say that?
- Yes.
Also, don't switch off your phone, okay?
I won't!
Sister!
You're getting married!
Aryan!
My dear Aryan!
Why didn't you go along too?
Just missed it.
Hey!
Advance happy married life, dude!
They've fixed your wedding with her.
- Fixed our wedding?!
- Yep!
They're under pressure and embarrassed.
So, they're getting you two married.
- Who told you?
- Niju called and said.
Niju?!
- Get lost, man!
- I swear on my mother!
Why will he lie?
For real!
Dude, I can't keep living like this.
I need to find a job
and take good care of her.
You've finally become a man!
- Of course, you should!
- Let's go?
Come.
Let's go back home straight.
Then we will tell her.
Nidhi... Frooti!
- I don't want.
- Biscuit?
No.
Let's go.
Nidhi, I know the husband
of your dreams
is well-settled, well-educated,
well-standard and all.
But I'm going to try to be like that now.
Wow!
Bravo!
You know, I never thought
I'd get married before my brother.
But Nidhi...
Everything happens for a reason.
Yes.
Don't worry, don't worry!
Dude, it's the police!
I'll deal with them.
Why are the police here?
Sir, we're a family, sir. Family...
- Whose family?
- Sister... sister...
- Sister...
- Whose sister?
But sir...
- Get out...
- Family... We're going home, sir.
Shine, you said the marriage was fixed?
Sir, it wasn't just me.
They were on it too!
He's the groom, not me.
Aryan!
Isn't it morning for you yet?
What world are you living in?
You'll be walking in and out of courts
for a while now.
I'll make sure of it.
Please sir, please, please...
You don't worry.
We've asked your parents
to come to the station.
Stay strong.
This isn't such a big deal.
Her parents will definitely
get you both married.
You two can live happily ever after
once you're married.
Aryan...
Can you pass me that Frooti?
Dude, give me some.
- Give me...
- Drink water or something else.
Just give me some, dude...
Give...
Hey, get in!
They kept the bar
open past 11 till 12.
- Sit over there.
- Sit down.
And purposely targeting
people with money.
What kind of ethics is this!
What a pain!
Aren't you tired of sitting
so close to him?
Move over!
Do you want something to drink?
- No...
- Don't want anything?
- Anything to drink?
- Can I get a tea?
One tea for me too.
Be quiet!
Do you want something to drink? No?
I want a double large on the rocks.
- Hey!
- Yes, sir.
Lock him up.
We'll serve him his drink over there.
- Get up.
- I'm okay!
Get up, man! What okay?
- I'm an NRI!
- You come to the cell, you bloody NRI!
- Walk, man!
- Let me go, sir!
Sir, we got hold of those kids.
We've informed them.
It'll take at least 5 to 6 hours
to get here from Kottayam.
Alright, sir.
Okay, sir.
Hey, hey! Get up!
Aryan...
- Get up! Wake up!
- Open your eyes.
Hey...
Aryan!
Don't worry too much.
We can work out a compromise.
Did you have something?
Aryan...
Dad!
Dad! What happened to you?
Oh, no... I don't know what to do...
Eh? Is this for testing in the lab?
Aryan...
Can you pass me that Frooti?
Hey...
Chettan, she's had the same thing too.
- What's happening?
- Look, Dad...
- It's nothing. You're okay.
- What's happening to you?
- What happened?
- Sir, come fast.
What did you all do to them?
Stop staring and go get some water!
Prakash! Nidhi!
Nidhi, what happened to you?
- Sir, come fast.
- Water, water.
Drink some water, dear.
- Aryan, drink some water, son.
- Nidhi, open your eyes.
- Nidhi, look at me.
- What happened?
- Looks like they took poison.
- Poison?!
Is it poison?
- Speak up!
- Aryan...
Bro!
Joy...
Ask that jeep to come back.
- Take him to the car.
- Slowly, carry her.
- Carry her.
- Sir, ask them to start the jeep.
- Start the car!
- Come on.
Quick, let's go.
Start the car, soon!
- Put her in.
- Careful...
Quickly, put her in.
Let's go fast.
- Come on, let's go quickly!
- Get in! Get in!
Nidhi...
Do you love me so much that
you don't want me to have poison?
- Get going!
- Hang on!
How's Aryan?
He's okay now.
He was in critical condition
when they brought him in.
Nothing to worry, she's fine.
You take rest.
"My heart disappearing at intervals"
"With memories chasing after"
"Wandering all around"
How's he now?
He's alright now.
He's tired because he was in the hospital
for so many days.
Got some work at home. Alright, then.
Alright.
Wish I could see him.
This is what you call true love.
Aryan...
Why did you do that?
Why are you so obsessed with me?
I drank poison because I didn't know
how else to handle that situation.
But...
Why would you die for me?
I feel so much respect for him now.
Why? For taking poison?
Don't do stupid things like this again.
I've already told you...
My choices or decisions
have no value.
I also had someone.
She changed her WhatsApp picture
without asking me.
I dumped her right then and there.
You need to be more serious.
Don't waste your life like this.
His is what you call true love.
Look at what happened to Nixon.
That guy threw away assets
worth millions for a girl.
- As-salamu alaykum, Uppa.
- Wa ‘alaykum as-salam wa rahmatullah.
Suhana?
Suhana...
Dear, she has been
missing since yesterday.
We received a phone call
at 8.30 this morning.
Apparently, she ran away with someone
and got married.
She betrayed both you and us,
then just left, dear.
You know I can't live without you, Nichu.
And I can't live as another man's wife
in this lifetime.
So, Nichu, find another girl
and live happily with her.
Let them suffer
seeing me live like this my whole life.
This love is something else, right?
Keep an eye on him.
When I keep checking on him,
he will feel bad.
Okay.
Son, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Okay.
'The little time I spent with you'
'are the happiest moments of my life.'
Hey...
Are you okay?
Why does everyone keep asking if I'm okay,
over and over?
Why would I not be okay?!
Listen...
Your life isn't meant to be ruined
for someone else.
Come to the ground.
Everything will be fine.
Hey... I'm sorry...
At the station, they said they'd let me go
only if I said all that.
- Sorry...
- I can understand... no worries...
Don't be sad.
We're there for you.
Don't waste water, man.
There's something powdery in the water.
Hello.
Why weren't you answering?
'I was sleeping.'
I can hear the sound of water
in the background.
What's wrong with you? Are you sick?
'I cannot sleep, dude.'
When I close my eyes,
all I think about is her.
'Her face won't leave my mind.'
And on top of that, all these people here.
Dude...
They're driving me crazy
with all this self-care
and counselling stuff.
Dude, I'm not in a position
to help you out.
Just think about poor Nixon.
They won't even let him back
into his own house.
Compared to him, you're so lucky!
Do you know how many poor people
are dying in Somalia
every single day
without even a drop of water?
Who am I talking to?
And here, rivers of alcohol are flowing.
Our youth is getting ruined.
You're wearing a football jersey.
But what's the use?
Our youth don't even get to play.
There's no ground here. We must protest!
Random people are leading us.
Let the youth take the lead!
It's when the youth lead that
new changes happen in the world.
That's when real developments take place.
Don't we need development?
Please somehow get a bottle, dude.
- Want to get him drunk and knock him out.
- Your silence is the curse of this nation!
'She stopped coming to classes.'
'I think they took her back to Madurai.'
'She is not in contact with anyone.'
Son, did you eat?
Yeah.
Kochumon...
Everyone was making fun of us
at the function.
Running away...
that's not the problem.
You should've just brought her home.
What was the issue?
But... you taking poison...
that really broke me.
It's alright.
Don't do such things, okay?
[in unison] Happy Birthday to you, Tony!
Thank you.
Play music.
Hey, didn't you invite Aryan?
Go and call him!
I'll go get him.
Please don't finish the drinks.
Hello.
You said you'd come
for Tony's birthday today.
No... I'm not coming today.
It has been a while
since we all got together. Come soon.
Super!
From today onwards
our team isn't Unnikulam.
- It is Funnykulam.
- Hey, bro!
Dude!
Have a drink, dude.
No need, bro.
No mood.
Not as bad as the poison you downed.
Come on, drink.
Enough, enough.
Happy Birthday, Tony.
- Forgot to wish you.
- Thank you, dear.
Dear...
Let go of all this love nonsense.
Come back as the old Aryan.
Girls will come and go.
Look at him! Look how cool he is.
- Chug it!
- Look at him dance...
Look at him sing...
Lost his tip and his chick, Suhana.
Still... look at him celebrating.
"Today's the little one's birthday
What a fine and happy day"
"Wonder who poured it out"
Next time, we cut the cake first.
And only then, the alcohol.
Now there's no one here
when I'm cutting the cake.
I can't believe I was praising this whiner
just a while ago.
You drank like a fish!
Nixon...
Hey...
- You don't know, man...
- I don't...
You don't know how my dad looked after me.
After my mother died,
he took such great care of us.
Bad upbringing.
I left him and...
Don't ruin your birthday.
I've everything, man...
Get up you sigma male.
And despite all that... all for her...
- It's okay...
- Just think about it...
What all I did for her...
I went and told her the day after you left
that you'd given up your house,
car and all assets for her.
Did you?
You think she thought
you gave up everything
and would come back as a beggar?
Get up now.
Dear...
I'm telling you again...
Love is nothing but politics.
It's got caste, religion,
money and all that nonsense.
No girl will stand by you...
Correct.
You better watch out!
And look who's giving advice!
Are you drinking poison again?
Are you itching to go to the ICU again?
It's okay, dude...
Let it go.
When will I see her again?
Even my dad gave me
the sad look and cried.
We'll start a relationship
only after signing an agreement!
I want to see her.
I need to see her.
Let it all out! It'll be fine.
Why are you wailing, dude?
Guys even go to Nagaland
for the woman they love.
Really?
Don't you know?
If you catch a bus
from Kottayam in the morning,
you'll be in Madurai by evening.
I'll come with you.
Sibi...
You're the one who
motivates him for no reason
and gets him into trouble.
You go to Nagaland alone!
Why'd you wanna take him?
His stupid Nagaland.
Huh?
Your motivation boost is peaking right now.
I haven't been able to sleep since.
Motivation...?
You were right.
I've to go to Madurai and see her.
That was the booze talking, dude.
Why would you listen to that
and get all set to go?
Go and pack your bags. Let's go.
I'll pack... For now, you just wait here.
Go and come back in the morning.
If you sleep it off now,
your problem will be gone.
I promise you...
- You should come...
- Just go, dude...
- You're the one who motivated me.
- It was an honest mistake. Just go!
- You said you'll come.
- Let me sleep. You're mad!
- Sibi...
- Good night.
No chance.
You won't get an address from college.
'Looks like they've blocked everything,'
thinking you might go looking for her.
Hey, I'll break your bones
if you do anything stupid.
There's no place in Madurai
I don't know, no one I don't know.
Where will you hide, huh?
You better be here!
Greetings, bro.
Bro, my name is Aryan.
Do you have an address?
No address.
How will we find her without an address?
It's going to be very difficult.
Her name is Nidhi Sathyaprakash.
Her mother works in Railways.
- Where are you from?
- Unnikulam.
Unnikulam?!
This isn't like Unnikulam,
it's a huge city.
A 10- day celebration is happening here,
the Meenakshi Temple festival.
The whole city will gather here
to pray to the Goddess.
- Ah, okay.
- Got it?
There's a chance your girl will also come.
You can look for her.
If you find her, call it destiny
and take her with you.
"I search for your glances"
"Wandering lost and alone"
"This too shall pass"
"The endless chatter will return"
"Please come back,
Grant me that moment once more"
"I search for your glances"
"Wandering lost and alone"
"In the midst of my pain"
"My vision and voice tremble
Along the way"
"I search for your glances"
"Wandering lost and alone"
"In the midst of my pain"
"My vision and voice tremble
Along the way"
"Don't fade away"
"Don't vanish into
The earth's deep shadows"
"Don't wither"
"Don't disappear like a bird
Caught in flight"
"I am the burning sun"
"You, the soothing raincloud"
"As the world's sorrows shake us"
"We fall together as rain, in rhythm"
"Don't fade away"
"Don't vanish into
The earth's deep shadows"
"Don't wither"
"Don't disappear like a bird
Caught in flight"
"Here in this corner, I wait alone,
Still searching for you,"
"While clouds drift by
On our path, indifferent"
"Like seagulls casting
Fleeting shadows on the sea"
"Will we bloom as a flower
Opening in the night?"
'It's been almost
four days since you left.'
Your mom is quite worried here.
'Come back once you've sorted things out.'
I'm guessing you don't have much
cash on you.
I'll put some cash.
No, Dad. No need.
'I've got money.'
Try to come back soon, okay?
No, Dad. I'll only come back
once I see her.
Alright, you take care, okay?
What the hell, man!
What a crappy place this is!
Couldn't you stay in a better place?
- What's this, man?
- Ugh!
We came here because your dad
told us to.
People say you ended up like this
because of me.
That's ruined my reputation now.
Let's catch the bus back tomorrow morning.
I'm not coming.
Huh?
I'll only come after I see her.
So, you haven't seen her yet?
What have you been doing all this time?
I was searching for her address.
Pick up that phone and call her.
I don't have her number.
Man...
You don't have her number,
or her address
and she hasn't called you even once.
She must have long forgotten you
and moved on by now.
Look at you wandering around aimlessly!
You will end up looking like a clown.
So I've become a joker to you, huh?
A joker before my family and friends.
A joker who eloped
in the name of love.
A joker who drank poison.
A joker who's doing something and all!
A clown...
Mmm...
But I won't be at peace until I see her.
That's all there is to it.
I'll come home only after I see her.
Nixon bro!
I can't find him here.
You shouldn't have told him
all that yesterday.
After all, you do have a part to play
in his current situation.
He keeps cutting the call.
Hello bro!
Over here, bro!
How are you, bro?
I'm good. How are you?
How's your dad?
He's good.
Are you here for purchasing?
No, now we courier everything.
Oh, is it! Good, good.
- Bro, I wanted a help.
- Tell me.
A friend of mine from my hometown
has a lover.
So, we wanted to find her...
We've been roaming around
for a few days now.
Do you've an address?
No, bro.
Any other details?
No other details, bro.
- Do you've a photo at least?
- Nope.
Nothing?
What the...
There's a guy called Lara here.
He knows every girl,
from the little ones to the big ones.
He's like an encyclopaedia
when it comes to girls.
- But the timing is bad.
- Why?
There's a major conflict brewing
between two gangs right now.
Oh...
One gang is Maari's.
The other belongs to Ramana.
This Lara caused Maari some trouble.
And now Lara is in hiding.
So, there's this guy who's Lara's friend.
Let me call him.
He'll definitely help you for my sake.
- Tell me.
'- I need a small help.'
What's it?
A few guys I know have come here.
Okay. Anything bothering them?
Yes, it is quite urgent.
They're very close to me.
Alright, we'll see.
Send me the details.
- I've told him.
- Okay.
I've told him everything.
He'll take care
of whatever problem there is.
Come, let us take a selfie together.
Selfie?!
- Fine... I guess...?
- Come closer?
Come on, smile.
Give a good smile!
Alright, then.
Thank you. See you.
Greetings!
He will definitely help us out.
We'll see.
Whatever happens we will leave Tamil Nadu
only after finding his girl!
Hey!
Yes, you. Come here.
Take this.
Are you from Kerala?
Yes, sir.
Are those your friends?
Yes, yes.
Come, come.
Come on.
Is this Ranga bro with a beard?
Sit down.
You also sit.
Dear, don't smoke cigarettes.
Your lifespan will be cut short
by 25 years.
You won't live as long as you should.
Drink this.
Is it a love issue?
Yeah, it's my friend's love issue.
Grandpa... my... our friend...
He came here to search for his lover.
And we came searching for him.
But he doesn't have her
address or anything.
Around 35 years back,
if I had friends like you...
I wouldn't have lost my love.
My girlfriend's family killed her...
right before my eyes...
Get me a piece of paper.
Go and drop this off at that place.
Go right away!
Don't wait for anyone.
Sir.
Greetings.
Sit down.
Give it.
Sir... someone gave this.
What is this?
Muthu bro!
Bring the bundle from B shelf.
Will get it now.
This...
I've seen him somewhere...
Sir, who is on that flex?
You don't know him
but you took the paper he gave you?
He's our party leader.
He was a former MLA.
Party leader?!
He doesn't even know who the leader is
and he brought his letter!
Here you go, bro!
This is Madurai's latest voters list.
Take a look at this.
If not,
I'll ask him to get the next bundle.
Whoa...
Bro, where's KK Road...
Do you know KK Nagar?
Tell him the address.
- Bro...
- This girl was studying in Kerala.
Do you know this address?
This one...
If you go straight and turn left,
- ...there will be a large pavilion.
- Okay.
Today is their child's function.
Function?
Yes, it's the child's function.
That's why they have installed a pavilion.
What function?
Ceremony.
Don't you know what a function means?
Where do we go search now?
- There's a small problem.
- What?
It's her wedding.
- Wedding?
- Yes.
- Who said?
- That guy.
- Got the house?
- Yes.
Let's go and look.
- Who are you?
- We're college friends.
Eh?
We're Nidhi's friends.
Oh...
We're from Kerala, friends of the bride.
Sister, please come to the side.
We're her friends.
So, we wanted to wish her.
Facebook friends?
No, college friends.
I don't know
which girl you're talking about.
What happened?
What's it? Who are you guys?
Bro, we studied with the girl
who lives here.
We wanted to give her certificates
as well as wish her.
How are you, Tamil sir? All okay?
Enough... enough...
Oh, no!
Which college is giving what certificate
to a 13-year-old, huh?
You guys are thieves, aren't you?
Come out!
Why aren't you saying anything?
Come on, come outside!
We're very hungry, bro.
We thought it's a wedding ceremony.
We're sorry, bro.
Right, guys?
Sorry... sorry...
Say something, you dogs!
They've printed a photo of that girl,
like a bride.
Whatever! Let us just eat and go.
Walk fast, uncle!
How do you come up with
lies like this, man?
I don't know, bro.
I'm full of lies,
right down to my fingertips.
Even her address was fake.
They're totally prepared.
They have shifted her from here.
Find a way to get him out of here.
You think he'll come!
We'll drag him out of here if we have to!
What's the situation?
You look for our return tickets.
We'll find a way to convince him to leave.
But he just cannot understand.
Nidhi!
Look!
- Is that Nidhi?
- Yes.
And you dragged us to that house!
That guy said so! What can I do?
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Save us, O Jesus!
You sure this is her house?
Didn't you just see her go back in?
Shall I call him?
No, first let's plan.
We talked it all through
and took an advance.
How can you say this now?
Who's that?
Looks like some Gounder,
a community leader.
You're right, he does.
I'm hanging up.
He looks like Mafia Shashi.
Oh, he's coming this side.
Who are you lot?
We were looking for a house.
Real estate.
Bro, ask them to come in.
Come in.
Come...
Hello, brothers.
Be seated.
Why have you guys come here?
As if the trouble there wasn't enough,
you had to come here too?
Open your mouth and say something.
Hey!
Oh, no...
Everyone, please step out.
Why have you come to see Nidhi?
Aryan committed suicide five days ago.
- Huh?
- What?
Yes, sir.
He came to Madurai searching for Nidhi.
He tried hard to find her.
But he couldn't...
Overwhelmed by sadness,
he went home and
committed suicide five days ago.
Aryan really loved Nidhi.
Come on, get up.
We just wanted to let you know, uncle.
We shall take your leave, uncle.
Please let everyone know.
He was very innocent.
Please...
don't curse him...
Walk, you dog!
Alright, then.
Why'd you say he died?
Let me go! I'll tell you!
Tell what?
Calm down!
Why did you say such unnecessary things?
If I hadn't said that, you'd be done for.
He signalled with his eyes for the machete.
You don't know her well enough.
I suffered a lot in the car that day.
She's a complete lunatic.
I'm sure she has already taken poison.
Now everything will be on our head.
Let us do one thing.
We'll go to the lodge and see him.
Come.
Hey!
Why didn't you answer your phone?
I've almost figured out the area
she lives in.
I'll meet her tomorrow.
Yeah, right!
We're coming back from her house.
Eh... And...
Did you meet her?
We met her and her dad.
Did she ask anything about me?
Yes, and he told her you died.
If I hadn't said that,
they'd have chopped us up.
Her family is a terror.
Nixon bro... Shine...
I want to see her.
Go walk right in.
Her dad will chop you into pieces.
That was meant for you.
Now we're not going back
without seeing her.
Come on.
Auto, auto!
Those boys beat us up and escaped.
They're over here! Come on!
Hey!
Good thing you didn't find her house.
They'd have cut you up and boxed you.
Hey, where does that bus go?
It goes to Mellore GT bus stand.
- Is that so?
- Mellore GT last bus.
Kani's there now.
Ask him to find out.
Okay.
- 9, 10, 11...
- Hey!
Weren't there three Kerala guys
at Mellore sugarcane farm?
No.
He says no.
From Mellore,
a boy from Kerala had got in.
He kept talking in Malayalam
but I couldn't understand.
Tell me their description.
'One of them is short and fair.'
Was there a short, fair guy?
No.
And another one is short and dark.
Was there a short dark guy?
No.
Hey, I don't think they got on this bus.
There was a fair handsome guy.
'His t- shirt had a teddy bear on its back.'
Below it...
A bear chasing someone...
I think there was a teddy bear.
Dad... I don't know...
Mom is in the Railways.
Bro, did we reach GT stand?
Wait! It's the last stop.
We've found him!
What if you got slashed on the head?
What would we tell your parents?
Hey, found him.
Ask them to finish him off right there!
We found one of them!
Come on!
The others must be there itself!
Look out for the one wearing
a black t- shirt with a teddy bear.
He's the one who slashed Palani bro.
Finish him!
It wasn't just one guy.
What are you saying?
There were four of them.
Four people?!
They beat us both up and escaped.
'- What's it?'
- A few guys I know have come here.
Okay. Anything bothering them?
'Yes, it quite urgent.'
Get out.
Kani, did you get them?
It's not three, there were four people.
- Four people?
- 'I didn't see.'
By then they beat our guys and got away.
We need to find that satchel!
Lara.
Something important has come up.
Where are you?
It's her dad's goons.
Bro, we found those boys.
'Careful.'
'They got a gun.'
Gun?!
Run!
What the hell is happening!
You understood her dad's range, right?
This is beyond our control.
When I saw her trembling
with fear back then,
I knew her dad was a gangster!
Whatever happens,
I'm definitely going to see her!
Shut up, you idiot!
Run!
Hey, Niju!
Nixon bro!
Come on!
Run! Come!
The meeting with Kalaidas was at 5.
The last thing he said on the phone
was that he had returned safely.
Palani has attended another meeting
after meeting Kalaidas.
He was dealing a red sand boa
with three Malayali boys.
But during the deal, it turned
out they weren't there for business.
Maari, they've planned something big.
Maari.
Maari, listen to me.
Hey...
Where's it? Where's the item?
Where's it, huh? Where?!
Those Kerala boys took it.
What they hell were you all doing, huh?
It's going to be a big problem
if we don't find it.
I need it!
- I need that satchel!
- We'll find it, Maari, you go now!
Come on, start the car!
What's happening?
Did you find those boys?
No, they're hiding somewhere near GT stand.
Our men are looking for them.
We'll find them!
Search every nook and corner.
No one should leave our area and get away!
We'll nab them.
We'll definitely catch hold of them.
Hey, stop!
Reverse, reverse!
Look if anyone's there.
Hey! Wha...
Who are you!
Get in!
Run!
Hey, come on!
- Go quickly!
- Hey, come this way!
Where to...
Call everyone we know in Madurai
and ask them to come out and search!
Tell them to check every single place.
Kill if they have to!
I need that satchel!
Why did that guy
make such a stupid decision?
Does he have no responsibility
towards his family or what?
What makes you think
you can talk about responsibility?
You're talking about his parents' feelings.
Do you not value my feelings?
Mom, why didn't you try for
another child after having me?
Tell me!
Tell me why, Mom!
Tell me, Dad!
Tell!
I was a burden for you.
It's not what you think!
Don't lie!
Nidhi...
I've been listening to everything
you said since I was 13.
Go there, go here! Sit here, sit there!
So that everyone in the family says,
"Wow, what a disciplined child!"
You don't care about anything else!
Even my studies...
I'm doing what you like!
You only think about yourselves.
You don't care about anyone else.
Hey!
I know you guys are here.
If you come out yourselves, I'll talk.
If not...
I'll come catch you myself...
and cut off your tongues first!
And then only I'll talk!
Hey...
Do you know Palani?
Hey, you!
There's a big gang after him.
How did you barge in so easily
and attack him?
I'm a very valuable person here!
Do you know, huh?
Where's the satchel that you stole?
Where's the satchel, huh?
Don't stay silent, spit it out!
They're going to kill him.
Speak up! Stay silent and you die!
Where's the satchel?
That boy, Aryan...
The love you two never gave me...
In that short time...
I got so much love from him.
Actually, I've no feelings for him at all.
I didn't get into his car to go
roaming around town.
I didn't have the courage...
to face my parents...
That's why...
I went along with him, my head blank...
Where's the satchel?
Bro...
it was three of my friends who went...
I didn't even go.
Where are your friends?
Where are you lot hiding, huh?
I last saw him in the ICU.
And I could see it in his eyes...
The love he has for me...
Bro... I know...
Her dad sent you all, right?
I wanted to see her until now...
Now I don't wanna see her anymore!
Nothing! Please, bro...
I'll go back.
He gave up his life for me...
What have you guys given me?
No, dear... not like that...
- Tell me, Mom...
- It's not like that, dear...
Tell me...
Tell...
- Tell!!!
- No, Nidhi.
- Please hear us out, Nidhi...
- Please, dear...
Hello.
Sorry for the disturbance.
Yo!
Are you such bad parents?
If not you, who else will take care of her?
Look how she is crying.
Aunty, even you're a woman.
Lara, we've found a way
to save you from Maari.
The four Malayali guys who killed Palani
came here searching for a girl.
You nab that girl.
That way, we can hand those boys
over to Maari.
This is a great chance.
You and Maari can leave everything behind
and be at peace.
Let's go?
Hey!
The girl those boys were searching for,
she's with me.
Tell Maari.
Call those boys
and tell them to come to your house.
Keep an eye on them.
We found that girl.
'I'll come to your house with her.'
Okay
Lara, for now just take that girl
around the city.
When I say so,
bring her to the address I send.
Come to the tractor mill near GT stand.
We've found them.
Do you have any idea where you are
or who you just laid hands on?
Where's the satchel?
Bro, please let go... please...
Give me that knife!
Please don't....
No...
Where's the satchel??
You!
Open your mouth and speak!
Nixon bro,
I think he's asking about the guy
you beat up and threw in the gutter.
Hey, you!
Tell me where!
Bro, he came to slash me for no reason.
That's why I beat him up.
- Sorry, bro...
- No, no!
The satchel! The satchel!
The bag! The bag!
Isn't that Balu's vehicle?
- Yes.
- Go upstairs and check.
Watch him die right in front of you!
Bro...
After hitting him...
we took an auto
and left that place immediately.
I don't know anything else.
- Tell me.
- Ravi has caught those boys.
They're at GT mills right now.
- Found them?
- Yes!
- Coming!
- Come quick.
Come on.
Hey... Upstairs...
- Up...
- What's upstairs?
Hey...
Maari's gang, all mighty and strong!
Yet four guys attacked their very core.
And they're just kids in diapers!
You needed Ravi to nab them!
Got it now?
- Who are these people?
- What do you mean who?
Hey, hey!
The Madurai gang who killed Palani
and ran away with his satchel.
Boys!
The boys!
Now do you realise...
that this Ravi...
is so damn valuable!
Stupid moron!
This is why everyone calls you Moron Ravi!
These guys weren't the ones who were there.
What?
Giri, come to Vasantham Lodge quickly.
- Why?
- Those guys have been hanged.
What are you saying?
Something feels very off.
Hey!
Shucks!
Go and look for it!
I don't care how, I need that satchel.
- Ask everyone to be present there!
- Search everywhere!
Everybody, come to Vasantham Lodge.
That satchel should be there itself.
This doesn't feel normal at all.
This seems like a big sketch.
Be alert!
Come quickly.
Looks like we got the wrong guys.
Get going!
Everyone, back in the cars.
Look everywhere!
Check the other room.
Bro...
Hm?
Niju...
We came here looking for a friend.
Why'd you beat us up so mercilessly?
Go and look!
Search every single room!
Sorry... Go on now.
You treated us like dirt, huh!
I can't breathe!
You!
Ravi anna!
Looks like it is poisonous gas!
Get out! Go, go!
You went after her because I told you to!
And I'm telling you again!
Even if we don't get to see her...
We'll only step back in Unnikulam
after we've beaten those who beat us.
Come and beat the hell out of them!
Beat them!
Chop off their heads!
Throw it!
Tell me.
'Looks like those boys planned something.'
'Don't go inside.'
'Whatever happens, don't go inside.'
I'm already inside the lodge.
You lot look like school boys!
Where's the satchel
you stole from Palani's car?
We didn't want to steal the satchel
from the car,
it was a bait to get you here.
You!
I hit those four boys
without knowing who they were.
But now...
They're hitting me even though
they know who I am!
Don't let them go!
Grab all of them!
Come on!
Where the hell is my satchel?
Hello.
I'm at the end of the street.
I'll check and tell you.
Here...
Take that knife.
Take it!
Take it, man!
Does it hurt?
Tell me where's the satchel?
Damn it, just say it!
Where have you kept that satchel?
Tell me!
Hold him!
Tell me.
Ramana has been here for the past 14 days.
He has booked the whole of
Vasantham Lodge for some work.
He has come here with a team.
Ramana?
How's that possible?
He died and turned to ashes.
Hey...
Whoa...
It was you...
So, this was your sketch.
Your life is my mercy.
That mercy is gonna go waste now.
That day, in that incident...
I died...
What remains now is just a shell.
You tortured my 12- year old daughter...
I can still hear the sound
every single day.
You destroyed my whole family...
You!
You shouldn't die so easily!
I'll cut your head off
and hang it for my whole village to see!
Only then will the souls
of my wife and kids find peace.
Come on, fast!
Close the door.
Where's all this confidence from?
You think you can get out of here alive
after taking down all my men?
You!
To kill your Palani, steal that satchel
and wipe out all your men,
I just need four guys!
What are you looking at, huh?
That there are only three of them?
It's not just three of them.
There's one more guy.
Who's that?
His name is Danny.
He's quite a troublesome guy.
These boys are from Angamaly.
Their first attempt...
was a perfect attempt!
Be it them or anyone else
who comes for you,
no one can escape my area!
Not this area, not any area…
And after all this,
you still don't believe?
No...
I need his head.
Drag him down!
Come on! Hit them!
Run!
Don't let them escape.
- Kill all of them.
- Run
Open the door.
What the hell do you want, huh?
Oh, no! Which way?!
Run till you reach the bus stand!
Hey!
Why won't he answer his phone!
Ugh!
Hey dude.
You think I'm kidnapping you?
Nope!
I liked you the moment I saw you.
Aren't you sleepy?
Wait.
Jump!
"Listen..."
Hey, what happened to your Maari?
Three small boys are carrying him upstairs.
Should I attack?
Don't.
Those boys aren't what you think they are.
'They're very dangerous.'
I'm also looking for a way to escape.
We unnecessarily got into this mess!
Hey!
I think I'm in love with this girl.
- That's why...
- You!
You feel the same with everyone you see.
Stupid guy!
'Don't jump into trouble!'
Those boys are very dangerous.
Try to escape or you'll be done for!
Shucks!
What unlucky moment did my dad conceive me!
No girl ever falls for me!
Pah!
You won't leave this place alive...
- Shut up!
- You'll die.
Hey...
You ended up falling in love
with these guys of all people!
I thought this is a love story
but it's full of violence!
Get going! Go, go!
I'll take it off.
Uncle, can you drop me home?
Uncle?!
You think I brought you here for a tour?
Get lost!
Hey, go that way!
Get out and close the door.
All the feelings
I had for her face have vanished.
Let's go!
Get in! Get in!
Go!
"I've fallen in love"
"Lost in the universe of you"
"What sorcery has changed me?"
"I wander as a Romeo"
"My lovely angel"
"After I saw you"
"Longing my heart"
"To go close to you"
"The swift of breeze"
"Is entering into my heart"
"And encircling me"
"You are my lovely angel"
Hey, drive carefully!
This marriage such a nerve- wracking thing.
That's why I don't even think about it.
Here you go.
- Yes, bro... tell me.
- Need to hit the gym and work on my body.
- Yes, man...
- The girl in green salwar was eyeing me.
- Nice...
- Bro, got the house keys?
It's next to the shoes.
It's time for the ceremony.
Where are you going?
You idiot...
I loved you to live with you,
not to die with you...
You look amazing in this dress.
How are you? Good?
I'm great.
I was on an all- India trip
for the last 40 days.
Since none of us knew each other,
it felt like we'd known
each other for years.
Seeing this place on the list,
you came to mind first.
But I never thought I'd get to meet you.
How are you?
Hey...
Why are you so quiet?
Did the stalker Aryan I knew
lose all his energy in that accident?
Huh?
You've changed a lot.
You've also changed, Nidhi.
What did you say?
Repeat it.
You've become someone else.
Oh, that...
I always kept my dreams
and happiness to myself.
Now I'm living for my
dreams and happiness.
Maybe, that's the reason.
Was I ever a part of your dreams
and happiness?
Wait, wait... Speak slowly.
Did you ever love me?
Nope.
I used to wonder
if you'd ever come looking for me.
But thank God you didn't.
You hold a big space in my life, Aryan.
But I don't know if it's love.
I did think about it.
But I realised my life
is more important than you.
The last sound I ever heard was of yours.
You were the one who told me to live.
I'm living.
I lost my hearing in the accident.
Even with all this noise around,
I can only feel the vibration.
Still I'm very happy.
It's like I...
I found a new world!
If you hadn't come into my life...
I'd still be that old Nidhi.
Even though I lost my hearing...
I like this Nidhi better.
Thank you, Aryan.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you for all this happiness.
I'm so happy I got to see you.
I hope you are happy too.
The best feeling is seeing
the people we love happy...
isn't that the greatest happiness?
If you don't die here...
remember one thing...
Don't bottle up your dreams...
because you're afraid of your parents.
Live for yourself...
Okay?
Nidhi...
I promise I won't come after you again...
But I will wait...
'Nidhi...'
'I was searching for you
to tell you all this...'
'But this is how we ended up meeting...'
Like everyone else,
I dreamed of living my life
with the girl I loved.
But even though
that dream never came true...
I am genuinely happy.
Love isn't just about making her mine.
I just want her to be happy.
If you ask me whether my love story
had a happy ending or a sad one...
For me… it was a happy ending.
What is this? A protest over
your wedding not happening?
Brothers and sisters.
The Word of God says,
"Love your father and mother."
Without their blessings,
our lives can never truly prosper.
Likewise, those who fall
into the trap of marijuana...
- Hallelujah!
- ...are not only destroying their own lives
but also the lives of their families.
- Hallelujah!
Everyone else has moved forward in life.
Mom has even started talking about
my sister's marriage.
How long can I keep
living off my brother?
Now he has a family too.
Shouldn't we at least try to
make it in life?
Hope is the only thing
stronger than fear.
You know, right?
I only buy dresses that are unique pieces.
Yeah, right.
Ever since they took that satchel from us…
everyone's lost their trust, fear
and respect for us.
Before finishing off Ramana,
I should've taken them out first.
But they got caught in a case
and landed in jail.
Did you think everything was over?
Where's that sa-
Are you here for revenge?
This ends here!
This has no prequel and no sequel!
"Delhi, Bombay, Kalpetta"
"On the road to Madurai we wander"
"As I travel these miles"
"I feel so distant, almost like I'm dead"
"Delhi, Bombay, Kalpetta"
"On the road to Madurai we wander"
"As I travel these miles"
"I feel so distant, almost like I'm dead"
"Will you come closer, oh Bella"
"Graceful as a deer, sweet Stella"
"Like a blooming rose"
"Come near me, my dear Laila"
"You're the endless Nile"
"I watch you, forever flowing"
"Life is low, low, low"
"Something slow, slow, slow"
"Do you know, know, know"
"Melting snow, snow"
"Life is low, low, low"
"Something slow, slow, slow"
"Do you know, know, know"
"Melting snow, snow"
"Delhi, Bombay, Kalpetta"
"On the road to Madurai we wander"
"As I travel these miles"
"I feel so distant, almost like I'm dead"
"Delhi, Bombay, Kalpetta"
"On the road to Madurai we wander"
"As I travel these miles"
"I feel so distant, almost like I'm dead"
"You conquered my heart and held me tight"
"You stood by me like my heartbeat"
"Like a roaring beam of thunder"
"You crashed into my soul"
"You stood by me like my heartbeat"
"Like a roaring beam of thunder"
"You crashed into my soul"
"Hey, intoxicating girl"
"Smiling so bright, like milk"
"Shining from afar"
"Oh girl, oh girl"
"With mascara's whisper,
You stole my glance"
"Took me soaring beyond this world,"
"To a far- off, foreign land"
"Oh girl, oh girl"
"Life is low, low, low"
"Something slow, slow, slow"
"Do you know, know, know"
"Melting snow, snow"
"Life is low, low, low"
"Something slow, slow, slow"
"Do you know, know, know"
"Melting snow, snow"
"Delhi, Bombay, Kalpetta"
"On the road to Madurai we wander"
"As I travel these miles"
"I feel so distant, almost like I'm dead"
"Delhi, Bombay, Kalpetta"
"On the road to Madurai we wander"
"As I travel these miles"
"I feel so distant, almost
like I'm dead"