Please sit.
Gentlemen,
you are responsible officers
of all the defence services,
the police and intelligence
department.
The problem we're going to discuss
in this meeting is very serious.
Very dangerous. All that we speak
about it is insufficient.
According to this
report of the CBI,
the powers spreading violence
and vandalism are on the rise.
Business groups who indulge
in black marketing.
And smugglers today smuggle
drugs as well as weapons.
They don't work separately.
It's a huge organization.
And there's a power outside
our country funding it.
Hail Mogambo!
- Hail Mogambo!
Mr. Mogambo, after burning down
the government warehouses,
wherever there was shortage
of grains in the country,
adulterated goods has been
dispatched at black rates.
Mr. Mogambo,
about 100,000 gambling dens
and pubs have been opened!
We are making millions in profits
from the adulteration business.
Mogambo is pleased!
Daga! Teja!
Use this money to destroy and ruin
other things in the country.
These riots, killings, stabbings,
lootings and all this confusion!
If it continues
in this vein in India.
The day is not far,
when Mogambo's dream
will be realised!
Captain Zoro.
We want such a place on the
seacoast of Mumbai
from where we can send weapons
whenever and wherever we want.
Will it... be arranged?
Yes definitely
- Yes Sir.
Mogambo is pleased.
Senseless and illiterate Indians!
Till date they have learnt
nothing from their history!
Whenever they fought
amongst themselves,
an outsider
was able to enslave them.
And still they fight amongst
themselves. So let them!
Let them fight in the name
of religion, caste and creed!
Mogambo will provide them
weapons to kill each other.
And when these Indians,
destroy the very
foundations of their country,
then I'll take my next step.
That day the whole country
will be at my feet!
And every Indian my slave!
All will say,
Hail Mogambo, the king of India!
Hail Mogambo!
- Hail Mogambo!
Mogambo is pleased!
You.
Hail Mogambo!
Jump.
- Hail Mogambo.
Mogambo... is pleased.
That's it!
The day I get the formula.
What formula?
- With the help of it,
a person becomes invisible!
Think! These soldiers
who obey my orders loyally,
who can confront them
if they can't be seen?
A formula which
renders a person invisible?
Doctor Fumancho!
20 years ago an Indian scientist
had invented this formula.
He died but never gave
that formula to anyone.
A formula which renders
a person invisible?
How is it possible?
And why not? Science has
progressed in leaps and bounds.
It's wrong to say what's impossible
today will always be impossible.
I am not going too far in history,
about 100-150 years.
Those days if someone claimed
that steel planes would fly...
Going 1000 miles in a few hours
people would call him crazy.
But planes were made,
and no one questions
their existence.
If King Akbar would have been told
about telephones, radios,
motor cars...
he would not believe it.
The fact is, we are unwilling to
believe which we haven't seen.
If somebody said,
that it was possible to take
pictures of your insides,
then people laughed as you do now.
But X-rays are quite normal today.
Sir.
- Yes Raman.
Just as X-rays help you to look
at the insides of a person.
Can science invent something which
will turn a person invisible?
What...
What a stupid question?
You can't make such a thing!
But sir you said science...
- Please sit down!
This is no time for jokes.
Sit down!
Doctor Jagdish Varma we want,
you to give us the formula.
- No way!
Don't be stupid!
If you remain adamant,
your assistant Professor Sinha
will give it to us at any cost.
That's why don't be so foolish!
Give us the formula
and we'll pay you in millions.
You can't buy me out!
I'll call the police right now!
No!
- Mr. Sinha?
Catch him! Don't let him escape!
Sir!
Raman? What's the matter?
I upset you in class today,
so I...
No, it's not a big deal.
Actually I made a mistake.
Your question was right.
But only he has
the right to answer it.
Who is he?
He was a great scientist.
You might recall I had
introduced you to his son, Arun.
He is Arun's father.
Do you remember?
Sir the one with many kids.
- Yes that's him.
He spent his
childhood without parents.
He feels their pain.
When he sees an orphan,
he takes them home with him.
His house is but a mini hostel.
Calendar, oh! Calendar
Oh no the egg... Calendar!
Hey Calendar.
What's the matter Arun brother...
What is it Arun brother, like a
madman are you yelling for me?
I don't understand why did your
parents named you Calendar.
They wanted to keep a name
in English.
If your name would have been Queen
Elizabeth instead of Calendar...
then too you would
have been a cook.
Where did you vanish?
Well I vanished in my room.
Vanish wherever you want.
But inspite of you being here, why
do I have to cook all the time.
Why Calendar?
Come on... tell me...
Answer me.
Your luck is such Arun brother.
I don't there is anybody's mistake.
The mistake is - you do not know
difference between sleep and death.
People who sleep, wake up
You refuse to wake up.
Look Calendar, If you get up late
tomorrow morning...
Then something or the other would
surely get cut from your salary.
Sure... Please cut it.
Atleast I will get a salary
because of this.
By god, its been five years,
years,
that I haven't got my salary.
How does it look like?
Its purple like a brinjal.
Really?
Big brother let me tell you the
morning news before you leave.
The groceries are on the verge of
being extinct ib the house.
We will bring some
from the grocers.
Second news,
landlord came for rent.
We will give it too,
We aer not running away anywhere.
The kids have showered?
Yes, did so yesterday, right now
they must be sleeping in their beds
sweet dreams.
Good morning children!
Good morning! Good morning!
Children get up quick! Come down!
Good morning!
- Breakfast is ready!
Go to the bathroom,
one by one. Get ready.
Brush your teeth, c'mon,
C'mon Jugal. Hurry up!
Brother Arun, wouldn't it be
better if there were,
no rains every morning?
It's even better if you wake on
your own to get ready for school.
Why do we have school
so early in the morning?
Because everything starts
early in the morning.
Life sleeps all night
and awakes in the morning.
If we have to keep pace with life,
we have to get up early!
Brother Arun, why Monday
always follows Sunday?
Just as sorrow
follows joy and vice versa,
the day follows the night,
that's why Sunday
is followed by Monday.
And Saturday is followed by?
- Sunday!
Sunday!
"Life's like that."
"You win only after you've lost."
"Some tears and a few smiles."
"If there's sorrow today,
tomorrow will be bright."
"Life's like that."
"You win only after you've lost."
"Some tears and a few smiles."
"If there's sorrow today,
tomorrow will be bright."
"Life's like that."
"You win only after you've lost."
"Life is night also
Life is day also."
"Life is a journey,
Life is also a abode."
"One moment there is pain
from a wound."
"The next moment there is a
shade of happiness."
"In every new moment there
is a new song."
"This is the way of life."
"When sorrows bother you."
"You should keep on smiling."
"There should always
be hope in your eyes."
"For today's loss
will be tomorrow's gain."
"Fortune changes in no time."
"Time is your friend."
"Life's like that."
"Life's like that.
You win only after you've lost."
"Some tears and a few smiles."
"If there's sorrow today,
tomorrow will be bright."
"Life's like that.
You win only after you've lost."
Budhwa, you lazy bones,
carry all those sacks in quickly!
Why are you working so slowly?
Good day Mr. Roopchand!
- I'm doomed!
You're back! Again?
You'll shutdown my shop
by taking things on credit!
I'll be ruined if this goes on.
May your rivals get ruined!
I always pray that you prosper.
I'm doomed!
Hi Roop.
Oh hi.
I thought I'd make
all your payments together.
What do you think?
Full payment?
You?
He's laughing! He started laughing
when you speak of money.
Don't stand there. Take the rice,
wheat and everything you want.
It's Roopchand's shop.
Accountant, add it to my account.
Every month I think I should
stop giving you things on credit.
But my heart is so soft..
- You've a big heart!
Else who gives food-grains as
cheap as pebbles and stones?
1 kg of rice contains
half a kg of stones.
The price for rice, wheat and
pebbles is the same in your shop.
Isn't that wonderful?
- I'm doomed!
You find pebbles in my rice
and wheat? Go to another shop!
Mr. Roopchand, how can we go?
We are used to it.
Until we gnash a couple of pebbles,
we don't relish the meal.
Brother Arun, we must go home.
I have to cook.
Before cooking I've to pick
the rice out of the pebbles.
Ok Mr. Roopchand,
full payment in a couple of days.
Shall I leave?
I've to go for music tuitions.
Bye Roop, thanks.
I'm doomed!
This is the house.
I see! This is it.
Mr. Teja, we must
have this house at any cost.
Why? Why this house?
Mr. Mogambo had said,
he wants a place where he can send
any amount of weapons to India.
C'mon.
- Don't worry Mr. Daga.
I'll get it vacated in no time.
How?
- Wait and watch.
I've a pawn in this locality.
Mr. Teja consider it done.
Curse me if I can't do it.
Tolaram!
Have you got black pebbles to mix
in the black lentils? - Yes.
Black pebbles for black lentils,
white pebbles for rice
and brown for the wheat.
We've got 100 sacks of each.
The Boss'business is doubling
everyday By the grace of God.
Why? Aren't you benefiting too?
With your grace, yes l am.
Sir shall I take your leave?
- Yes leave.
Yes.
- But I want the house vacated.
The owner, Maniklal works for us.
We'll get him round. You want
the house and you'll get it.
Vacate the house?
Mankilal, what are you saying?
You've heard me right.
Just think it over.
We've been living here since years.
Why should I? Why shouln't I think
about the rent you haven't paid?
I'll pay the rent but..
- You've to pay it!
Look at this notice.
Pay up all that you owe me
or vacate the house.
You're doomed now!
You can't pay that much money.
You'll have to leave the house!
Let's go Mr. Maniklal.
Take this.
Get it?
If we don't pay our dues,
we'll really lose this house.
And these kids?
Where do I take them?
Brother Arun I've an idea.
What if we rent out the room on the
top floor? I mean paying guest!
Sounds good.
- Of course!
I'll give an
advertisement right away.
**Typewriter clicking... office
chatter**
How can l tolerate this?
Still you don't know,
how to use the grammar.
You have been in this office since
10 years but...
You don't know anything...
you don't have any sense at all.
Hello.
- Ruby Talkies?
What? No need to print
this news take it with you.
No need to print.
- Look mam I am not talking to you.
Listen, can you book tickets for
my matinee show.
I cannot book the tickets
for your matinee show.
Its Ruby Talkies right?
Look this is not Ruby talkies, this
is Crime's of India paper office.
Why don't you try to understand?
Its a wrong number Lady...
Now go... go... uhhh...
go give this to the reader now.
Hello,.
- Hello, yes speaking.
What?!... your buffalo
stopping giving milk.
So what can I do now?
I mean... hey what can I do?
This is not a veterinary hospital
please try to understand man.
Now please for god's sake,
Please for god's sake.
Hari Om
- Yes Sir.
Did she come?
- Who Sir?
That girl... what's her name?
Its that girl
- Which girl Sir?
That same girl you fool...
whats her name?
Crime times of India.
Type this and send it to the
editor's table today itself.
Sorry...
Sorry is like an escape for some.
Ruin everything and say sorry.
Mr. Gupta... why is this news item
still lying on my table.
Why didn't you give it to me
along with the other papers.
I am sorry
Again Sorry!
Just wait and watch, one day people
will loot and sorry for that.
Sorry... sorrry... sorry
Ecxcuse me.
Good morning Sir.
- Come in Seema please come.
I have brought the article which
you gave me to write.
You brought it... good.
Oh but, why did you keep it on the
chair.
You are sitting on the table.
So I thought of keeping the papers
on the table.
I am sorry.
My Pajamas are not washed properly.
Okay so if your Pajamas are not
washed properly, what shall I do?
This is not any Bharat Laundry...
Its a wrong Number.
But... you this
This article can't be
printed this Sunday.
You've delayed it.
- Obviously, it is delayed.
The landlord of the house
where I live, has kids.
And I can't work around kids.
I'm looking for a new house.
Please have a sit.
Sir, Why do kids even exist?
Hoe could it would have been.
If everybody were born as an adult,
I agree with you.
Now do you have some work for me?
Yes, there's a job for you.
Very interesting job.
A criminal has just
been released from jail.
He's 25 but has been
to jail 50 times!
What's his name?
- His name is Manglu.
I've sent Khanna
to get him to the office.
Take his interview, readers will
read it with great interest!
Hello, Crimes of India.
- Sir!
Yes!
Madam!
I've a house with a spare room.
I want to give an advertisement.
- Go to that room.
Give me 4 copies of this.
So, It's you?
Yes it's me.
Please sit down.
Please!
Pencil!
Speak your mind.
Don't be scared.
Why should I be?
It's a matter of joy.
Good!
Well.
Sorry.
Ok tell me one thing, since
when have you been like this?
I've been like this
since childhood.
Since childhood?
I see.
Why do you do what you do?
For money! Simple!
Actually I'm not happy.
But sometimes one has to go
against his wishes to earn money.
Helplessness you know.
You think all those
who are helpless become thieves?
No, many are honest.
You get all types of people.
That's life.
Ok. What was your age
when you first went to prison?
I must've been...
What are you saying? Me? Prison?
Haven't you been
imprisoned 50 times?
50? Who told you?
So how many times have you been
there
I did not go to the jai
even once.
But why do you want me to send me
to the jail.
Is this a newspaper office or a
police station? - Don't shout.
What do you mean?
Look Manglu.
- Manglu?
What Manglu? Who Manglu?
Whose Manglu?
My name is Arun Varma!
- Arun?
If you're not Manglu then
what are you doing in this room?
You too are here and I don't
think you're Manglu either.
I'm the crime reporter.
Who are you? Why are you here?
What do you want? - To print an
advertisement about a room on rent.
But now I want to leave! Goodbye!
One...
- Careful.
What are you doing? - Does
the lady in red-white work here?
Come here.
- She's back again.
Are you married?
I didn't come here
to advertise in the matrimonies.
I know that, sorry.
I just want to know
if you have kids.
I'll have kids when I marry.
Of course.
- Sir, make her understand.
Listen! Just listen to me.
Give me the room
you want to rent out.
Yes.
Then say so.
Madam, what a room!
Lovely room.
A balcony in front of it.
A garden in front of the balcony
and then the sea.
Cool breeze all day long.
Madam, that too absolutely free!
I've taken it.
- Without taking a look at it?
The moment you said no kids,
I decided. Here's Rs. 500.
But the kids?
- You don't have any, do you?
That's why I'm taking it.
Fine, the room is yours.
God will take care of the rest.
Here we are!
Madam have a look!
I was talking about this.
"Build a beautiful bungalow."
Calendar!
- Calendar?
Calendar the cook.
Did you notice it? It's so
beautiful and peaceful around here!
Calendar, have all
the arrangements been made?
Yes the kids...
Kids?
- Not the kids.
I meant all the bags.
I've arranged all the small
and big suitcases.
Enter madam. Enter!
Thank god!
Brother Arun the coast is clear!
What?
He is speaking about
the cleanliness in your room.
What a beautiful? what a lovely?
What a peace.
What a peaceful house?
And its so quiet here
What do you think?
- Yes
If there is peace where I live,
it would help my work a lot.
You have come at the right place,
here you will crave to hear humans.
Shall we go upstairs?
I'll show you your room.
What happened?
- Shall we go upstairs?
Yes.
Can you see this?
These stairs go up.
Then they also come down.
It's amazing! Very nice.
Everything is looked after.
C'mon madam.
Calendar!
- Yes brother Arun.
Have you kept all the bags
in the right place? - Yes.
But what about
the little bags downstairs?
Something will be done.
- Yes.
Take care. It's in your hands now.
Madam!
How is the room?
Nice.
I can write ghost stories here!
What's wrong?
What happened?
- Cockroach!
Cockroach!
Where is the cockroach?
It's looking at me!
You're scared of a cockroach?
I'm not scared of lions.
But yes, I fear cockroaches!
I'm not scared.
Why get scared of a cockroach?
Call somebody who will kill it!
I will but they're all kids!
Call them! At least
we'll get rid of this pest!
The cockroach will die!
But the kids will remain.
Whatever it is, just think.
- Quickly call somebody!
Children! Help!
Cockroach!
- Children! Help!
Help!
Children! Help!
Cockroach!
My god!
Madam take care.
- What's going on?
What are kids doing here?
- Killing the cockroach.
O god you fraud!
You said, you don't have kids!
- I was right.
They're not mine.
- You rogue!
I'll report you to the police!
Take you to Supreme Court!
Sure!
Look, how much trouble these
little kids are taking for you.
They will not spare the pest!
They've caught!
You took 500 bucks then
and a deposit later.
I want all my money back.
Right now!
But we spent that money.
Cockroach!
Deepu, Tina! Kids run!
Get lost!
Madam!
You cheat! - Stay here until
you get your money's worth.
If you want you can stay longer!
The room is not so bad.
Room with a balcony.
A garden beyond the balcony
and then the sea.
Mr. Sinha, you always used to say
that dad was a great scientist.
And he had made something which is
one of it's kind in the world.
What was it?
I don't tell people because
I know they won't believe me.
But since you're his son,
I'll tell you.
He had created a gadget.
Wear it on the wrist, switch it on
and the person becomes invisible.
Person becomes invisible?
How is that possible?
Why don't you see someone in the
dark? - If there's no light then..
Why can he be seen
only when there's light?
I'll tell you.
When light reflects from a body
and enters our eyes,
we are able to see the person.
If something can create
a reaction in our body,
whereby instead of reflecting,
light goes through the body
then a person can't be seen.
Didn't understand?
For example a glass.
Light goes through the glass
so you can't see it.
I think you don't believe me.
No, Mr. Sinha! If you are saying..
But where's the gadget that sends
light through our bodies?
Your dad knew
that it could be misused.
So he burnt the formula.
But where is the gadget?
You have it?
Forget it.
You were looking
for a paying guest.
Found anyone?
We've found a girl.
And what a girl! Wonderful.
Stop it... Stop it
- (Children screaming and playing)
If you don't stop making noise now,
I will file a complaint against you
You would land up in jail,
wearing handcuffs.
What do you mean by jail?
Welcome, You have come at the right
look whats happening over here.
Arun brother,
we will be wearing a handcuff.
What happened Madam?
- You are asking me, what happened?
When you told me there is a room,
a balcony and a garden outside it.
You didn't tell me that there
would be kids playing football too
I am sorry Madam, they won't make
any noise.
Thank you very much... Thank you!
I told you right?... that don't
make noise over here.
But brother we also stay here,
shouldn't we play here?
What does she think of herself?,
that she is warning us like this.
What does she think of us...
Its not done.
She is always yelling at us.
I don't mean to say that,
but don't play here,
go to the beach.
Infact I will also come
with you guys to play on the beach.
Yay!!... hey catch it... lets go
- (Cheers)
Madam... I am sorry Madam.
Its my fault.
Madam...
atleast listen to me once Madam.
Madam, this time its not the kids.
But it was me... who... i did...
- Yes... Yes I know very well.
All of this is a plot against me,
a scheme, a plan
this plan
would not be successful even
if kids around the world unite
Mr. Arun Verma...
I will sue you for this.
Now this football will be presented
in the court
But why in the court, football
isn't played in the court.
I will see...
I will see you in the court
Madam...
madam atleast listen to me.
I won't... I won't spare you now.
Won't spare you at all.
How dare you?
I will drag him in the court.
"We don't want gold or silver,
we don't want a apology."
"Look we hold our ears
to say you sorry."
"We don't want gold or silver,
we don't want a apology."
"Look we hold our ears
to say you sorry."
"Our ball that you are holding,
is very dear to us."
"Come on now give it, give it to
us, that football oh dear sister."
"Give that football, back to us."
"All of you keep irritating me,
all day and night."
"Even if you try to request
touching my feet today."
"I won't give you the football."
"All of you keep irritating me,
all day and night."
"Sorry, sister now we will never
make any nose."
Not nose dear...
its noise... noise.
"Sorry, sister now we will never
make any noise."
"But if kids don't play, they will
get bored."
"Sorry, sister now we will never
make any noise."
"But if kids don't play, they will
get bored."
"Oh stop it now stop it,
I know this is a drama of yours."
"This is all a fake story."
"Girl you too are not that
innocent..."
"You are the head of
their regiment."
"I know this is a drama of yours."
"Between you and my kids."
"What kind of a fight is this..."
"What kind of a fight is."
"What's this affair about, please
do let me know too."
"What's this affair about,
please do let me know too."
"Between you and my kids,
What kind of a fight is this..."
"Oh our cap wearing brother,
help us get the ball."
"Don't know why this sister is
annoyed at us."
"Get us our ball."
"Oh our cap wearing brother,
Oh our cap wearing brother."
"Oh our cap wearing brother."
"My name is calendar,
I will go now into the kitchen."
I got the ball.
Yay!... Lets go.
Welcome Mr. Maniklal.
I've come.
But remember one thing that today
the period of grace expires.
Either pay me the rent
or vacate the house right now.
Either pay the rent?
Or vacate?
- Yes.
In that case if I've to choose,
I'll pay the rent.
What?
- Ok.
Entire amount!
- Anything to drink?
Goodbye.
You mean you couldn't
vacate the house?
Roopchand, why shouldn't
I empty your shop?
Now I'm doomed!
Teja darling,
your blood pressure will rise.
Mr. Teja,
you're needlessly getting worried!
Karga runs a gambling
den for us in that area.
He'll take some men
and what's his name?
He'll beat him
and his kids and throw them out.
What is the problem?
- Sir, wait for a few days.
Why? What will you do?
I'll strangle him
so bad that he'll leave!
If they starve,
they'll surely vacate the house!
Calendar! Give us food!
Quiet children!
Why are you raising hell?
Calendar, we'll scream
until we get food.
Am I right brothers?
- Yes!
Calendar! Give us food!
Jugal!
- Shut up!
Change yourself!
I swear, I'm right.
If you instigate people like this,
someday you'll become a leader!
Thank you Calendar.
- Shut up!
We are hungry.
- But I just have two hands.
It takes time to cook.
Calendar give us food!
Calendar! Give us food!
Kummi, help me out in the kitchen.
Can't you all keep quiet?
- Calendar give us food!
Look at this!
There's neither flour nor rice
or lentil.
How do I explain to you kids?
Isn't there anything?
- Can't you see these empty tins?
I swear, I can't tolerate
to see the kids like this!
Now something can be done
only when Arun returns.
Can't we stay hungry for a day?
If there's nothing here why don't
you get it from Roopchand's shop?
I had gone there this morning...
but only brother Arun
can convince him.
You won't die
if you don't eat for a day.
And if I die?
Tina, we'll eat goodies
when brother Arun returns.
Ok.
Brother Arun!
Brother Arun I won't die.
If I don't eat for a day,
I won't die.
You didn't have your meal?
- Calendar didn't serve us.
Calendar!
You're too much!
The kids haven't eaten
and you didn't serve them!
I couldn't help it.
Thought I'd bring groceries
from Roopchand.
But he said..
- He might have asked for money!
No problem kids. I've the money.
I've got the tuition fees.
Just wait for 15 minutes.
I'll go and get lots to eats. Ok?
What do you mean?
What sin have I committed?
I'm running a
business not charity!
Want something?
Pay up and take the groceries.
I've the money, here!
I'm doomed.
I've always paid
you sooner or later.
But the children were hungry
because I wasn't home.
The entire sum.
- Yes it is.
That clears our account to date.
Thank you very much.
What are you waiting for?
Get lost!
Give me the groceries!
Got money for it?
I cleared all your dues.
So that you could
take credit again?
I want cash or else
I won't give you anything!
Don't do this.
The kids are hungry at home.
What can I do? Let them die today
instead of tomorrow! Swines!
Roopchand!
- Help!
I'm doomed!
Raghu! Bansi! Help me!
Let me go!
If you abuse my kids I'll...
Throw that rascal out!
Strides into my shop
as if it were his own!
I gave him groceries on credit
and now he attacks me!
Have I ever denied you,
but the fact,
I don't have money today.
That's the issue in giving a job,
to people like you.
Take all your stuff out of here,
we don't want your tuitions.
Leave your car in the garage,
If it sells then we will pay you.
I just can't you an advance,
for a crap like this.
Arun Brother hasn't come yet.
My dear, let's wait for some time.
He must be on his way.
Come on.
The fairy wielded her magic
wand and the door opened.
You know what happened later?
The fairy took the prince.
I don't want to hear this story!
I'm hungry.
Tina not again!
- Brother Arun..
Brother Arun I'm hungry.
Tina then the fairy
flew with the prince.
Went to the stars.
She hid behind the moon.
Then it started raining.
It rained heavily.
Then there was a loud noise.
And she got scared.
So scared that...
Brother Arun we are not hungry.
We are just feeling sleepy.
- Really, we aren't hungry.
Even I'm not hungry.
I promise you brother Arun,
we're not hungry.
I have failed today.
I spent my entire childhood,
without my parents.
Helpless, alone.
I brought you all...
one by one in this house...
so that you won't experience...
the pain that I went through.
So that I could give you the joy,
Which I didnt get.
But...
I couldn't do much.
I have failed.
I have failed today.
I failed.
Calendar!
Yes madam?
- Why is everyone quiet today?
What happened?
Why are the kids so quiet?
They haven't eaten since 2 days.
What noise will they make?
Good morning.
You've a holiday on Sunday.
I too have a holiday.
Why not give our war a break?
I thought we'd have a picnic here.
Let me tell you, you don't look
good when you're quiet.
You look nice when you make noise.
Make noise later. First let's eat.
I'm very hungry.
What will you eat?
Chips? Snacks?
Pastries?
Chocolates?
Tina, what will you have?
First of all.
Snacks?
Here eat it.
Eat it.
Let's make friends.
Tina will you be my friend?
Yes.
Calendar,
serve everybody and me too.
I'm really terribly hungry!
Really?
Madam!
I gave you 3 months'advance.
But I love this place.
The balcony and the garden.
And the sea beyond.
So if you want,
you can take 6 months'advance.
And if again the football hits
my face...
then you will never get it back,
Understand?
Daga and teja...
The future Knights
of my future empire.
Are such fools
and good-for-nothing,
that you cannot even find a place
on the seacoast of Mumbai
from where I can smuggle
all my weapons into India
But Mr.
Mogambo, the thing is that...
Mogambo doens't want to hear
any clarifications...
but just wants to see his victory,
his rule and his monarchy.
Mogambo's intentions are even
higher than the sky.
And you.
The place that you wanted on the
seacost of Mumbai, will be arranged.
Mogambo... is pleased.
Hey... hey... ohh... you crushed my
head.
Wait you little girl,
now i won't spare you.
Who are you? What do you want?
Calendar!
Leave the kids alone!
Leave me I said,
What do you want man?
You scoundrel, let me go.
Let me go! Who are you?
Brother!
- Calendar!
Let me go!
Leave my children alone!
Please don't beat brother Arun!
Brother!
Leave my children alone!
Now you're really doomed!
My children!
Greetings Mr. Daga and Mr. Teja.
Welcome.
- Come in.
Is he the man?
Whatever your name be, listen.
Vacate this house within 2 days.
Sir, it's best
he leaves this place.
Tells the world our
grains contains pebbles.
Really?
All these businesses
and men are ours.
Wherever you go,
if you utter a word against them,
I'll be very severe on you.
Understood?
Let's go Mr. Teja.
Two days.
Get up brother Arun please.
Uncle, they are very
dangerous people.
Yes I do felt that Arun
is worried since some days.
But I didn't know such type
of scoundrels would be after him.
You did a good thing informing me.
Just ask Arun to meet me,
May be I can be of help to him.
Now son you go home,
I have to go somewhere.
Go safely son... go.
Sinha! Driver stop!
That's professor Sinha!
Reverse the car!
Take it back! C'mon!
Sinha!
He's Sinha! Catch him!
He shouldn't escape.
Get him! Get out!
C'mon get him!
Catch him!
Sir, can I make a call?
Yes but where?
- In the Press.
Oh I mean to say from
where will you do it.
Where is the phone?
This... Its here.
This is not a phone,
This is a radio Seema.
Either wrong numbers ring up,
or when you dial up, then other
ongoing calls can be heard.
A unique program keeps airing on it
all the time. - What program?
Sometimes two women gossip about
their mother in laws.
Or sometimes two traders have
a discussion on various spices.
Or sometimes out of love two crazy
one's talk about their crazy love.
Mr. Malhotra don't talk.
Hello!
- Yes Mr. Daga.
What do you want? Gold?
Silver?
Guns? Rifles?
Bombs? Hand grenades?
Thank you Mr. Walcott.
Come over this evening.
We'll discuss this
and entertain you.
How? - You must know the famous
dancer, Hawahawai, from Havana?
She'll entertain you this evening.
Ms. Hawahawai! I've heard of her.
So have I.
So come over. We'll see her too.
But where do I come?
- Powai lake, cottage no 24.
Cottage no 24, right.
Ms. Hawahawai!
Brother Arun, good I met you here.
There's a letter for you.
Letter from Mr. Sinha?
'Arun, I'm going faraway.'
'But before I leave I want to tell
you the secret I never did.'
Looks like there's no electricity.
'Whoever wears this gadget
and switches it on,'
'he will become invisible.'
'In this case, a person can only be
seen in red light or red goggles.'
'This gadget has no effect
on red colour.'
'Otherwise in any coloured clothes'
'or any other coloured light, the
moment you switch the gadget on,'
'the person will be
completely invisible'
'and no eye will
be able to see him.'
Jugal, what do you say?
What do we do with this?
Sinha's words turned true.
Should I wear it?
Yes.
Shall I switch it on?
- Yes.
Brother Arun the light.
Brother Arun!
Where are you?
I'm here Jugal.
I can't see you.
Can't I be seen?
- No.
Not at all?
I can't believe
that I'm really invisible!
Jugal! I can't be seen
even in a mirror!
Come look!
Even I know that.
But how will you come back?
Shall I press the button again?
Brother Arun you've come back!
I've come back!
Then I couldn't see you.
Now I can!
This is amazing!
- Amazing, isn't it?
Yes.
- Shall I vanish again?
Yes. No!
Brother Arun please come back!
I'm scared.
You are my sweet brother, please.
I can be seen!
Look, I can be seen!
Should I vanish again?
- Yes!
Come back my nice brother!
Yes!
- Jugal! What's happening?
I'll go crazy!
Come back.
Once more.
Come.
Isn't that amazing.
Brother Arun,
don't do this! I'll fall!
Please!
Put me down! I'll fall!
I won't talk to
you if you do this!
Then I'll vanish forever!
Jugal look behind you.
- Yes.
There are some red glass pieces
lying there. Get some here.
Look at me through it.
I can see you through
the red glass!
And now?
- Now I can't see you.
Can you see me?
- Yes.
Beware of the red colour.
I'll stay away from red.
But wherever Daga and Teja are,
they can't escape from me!
Good
- Very good.
Ah Ms. Hawa hawaiii,
Please come in.
Hello... You
You Mr. Dhaaga?
Not Dhaaga, Daaga.
Dhaaga... Ouiuiuiui.
This is Mr. Teja.
Pager... Funny name.
Teja... Pager?
Teja... Pager right?
Ms. Hawahawai one of our esteemed
guests Mr. Wolcott is here. - Yes.
Wallclock?
- You have to entertain him.
Oh really... I don't mind.
But for changing costume,
i need one loo.
Ya room... room?
- Room
Ya... ouiuiuiui.
Gyan Singh. Just take madam to her
dressing room.
Thank you Mr. Pager.
Pager.
- Have a banana... Pager right!
Daaga Sir.
Why did she call me Pager?
Madam this is your room.
Wow.
- Thank you!
Thank you!
Don't worry Mr. Daga,
I'll give you as much gold
as you want. - Good.
And I can also
give you guns and drugs.
Fine Mr. Wolcott, we'll take the
gold, drugs, as well as the guns.
But first I want one thing.
- What?
A golden Hanuman.
Let me see.
- Recognise it?
This statue?
It's in the big temple in the city.
It has a high value in our country.
Mr. Wolcott we will get it for you.
First, let us start the business.
Where is Mr. Daga. Mr. Daga!
"Hawahawaiiii ouiuiuiuui."
"Hawahawaiii ouiuiuiuiui."
"I'm the princess of dreams,
I've charmed every heart."
"My tresses, the clouds.
My squirms, lightning."
"I'm here to cast my spell."
"They call me Hawahawai."
"Hawahawai!
- Hawahawai!"
"Hawahawai!"
"I'm here to cast my spell."
"They call me Hawahawai.
- Hawahawai!"
"Hawahawai!
"Hawahawai!"
Where is she going? What's wrong?
"I bring colourful stories."
"You too hear, madman."
"Let me make your heart restless.
Let me drive you crazy."
"In my eyes, magic.
In my breath, fragrance."
"When I sway my body,
everybody is floored."
"Everybody is floored."
"My face, unparalleled."
"They call me Hawahawai."
- "Hawahawai!"
"Hawahawai!"
"I'm here to cast a spell."
"I'm here to cast my spell."
"They call me Hawahawai."
"Hawahawai!"
"Hawahawai.
- Hawahawai!"
"Hawahawai!"
Who are you?
She can be anyone.
Police informer, CID agent.
Or a spy of our enemy!
Whoever she is, she'll tell us.
Jhonny... go to my room.
You will find
a soft leather hunter kept there.
Get it.
Did you hear the sound?
Now this whip
will hear your screams!
What did you come
here to find out?
Whatever you came here for,
I'll tell you myself!
We're involved in smuggling,
black marketing, adulteration,
gambling, drugs, liquor or
anything you can think of.
Before you die, you will tell us
who sent you here?
I got it. Now this whip
will loosen your tongue.
I fainted!
Move!
Doesn't matter.
I'll deal with Miss Hawahawai!
Mr. Daga what's going on?
Mr. Daga grab it stealthily.
What?
- Grab it stealthily!
Mr. Teja did you see that?
His is my whip! My own!
Who slapped me?
Who is slapping me?
So Mr. Teja.
What did the girl reveal?
Who is she?
What is the matter?
Mr. Daga what are you doing?
What happened?
Who is slapping me?
What nonsense?
You've had a drink too many.
No.
- Who will slap you?
There is nobody here.
- Somebody.
Mr. Teja it's all
because of liquor.
Because of liquor.
Girl!
Cheers!
Beware!
- What happened to you?
I will kill you.
The situation is under control!
Everything is under control!
I'm here!
Mr. Daga!
- I'm here.
Somebody slapped me!
- You too?
Mr. Daga...
Why don't I shoot both of you?
Who are you? What are you?
- Where are you?
I'm no ghost or shadow or spirit.
I'm a victim of the atrocities
of men like you.
An ordinary Indian.
My name is Mr. India.
Mr. India!
Oh my god!
This is front page news!
Mr. India, why are you invisible
if you are an ordinary Indian?
Because your eyes
are filled with greed!
Until today you never
saw an ordinary Indian.
How can you see him today?
What do you want, Mr. India?
- To explain to you.
If you try to throw
those children out of their house.
I'll remove you from this world!
- Excuse me!
Excuse me, Mr. India.
I want to ask some questions.
Pen!
One minute!
Excuse me, thank you.
Mr. India you...
- I'm here.
Were you invisible
since childhood?
Since when are you in this
not to be seen profession?
You know what I mean?
Do you want to give a message
for our readers?
Ms. Hawahawai,
you forget where you are. - Where?
Oh my god you are right!
Mr. India these men...
- Don't be afraid.
I'll drop you home.
- Thanks a lot.
Daga and Teja! This is my first
and last warning to you!
I'll never venture
near that house!
It's not just a matter of the house
but of the whole nation.
You were heating the market
of dishonesty and atrocities.
But now your atrocities and sins
have gone over the top!
You'll pay for every crime!
This is not a threat
but my promise!
Let's go madam.
This is enough for today.
Ok.
Mr. India?
Why are you worried?
This is great news!
Because if there is a Mr. India.
It means the formula
which I was looking for,
will sooner or later
be in Mogambo's hands!
Mr. India.
- Mr. India?
Is he a body builder?
Sir you don't understand.
He is an amazing man.
He can't be seen.
Can't be seen?
- Yes.
Where does he vanish?
Even Malhotra is not to be seen.
Doesn't he want his job?
Hello. Yes! Fire brigade? No sir.
Sir, this Mr. India is invisible.
He'll be in front of you
but you won't be able to see him.
But you'll hear his voice.
He picks up a thing, you'll see it
being picked but you won't see him.
I've seen him with my own eyes.
I mean I haven't seen him.
But I've seen him.
Sir, I hope you understand.
Invisible!
Seema, you haven't gone
on leave since a while.
You need the rest very badly.
No problem, go and take rest.
- You think I'm wrong?
There'll be chaos,
when his interview
is printed on the front page!
What?
In my newspaper?
- Yes.
Front page?
- Mr. India.
An interview with Mr. India
who can't be seen?
You weren't here
so I gave it to the press.
Oh god!
You'll close down my business with
your trash! - What do you mean?
My writing is trash?
- Of course it is!
You are fired.
Sir...
- You are fired!
You're not going to believe me!
Just like he can't be seen, you
become Miss India and just vanish.
Out! Go away!
All right I'm leaving!
Sorry madam.
Malhotra...
- Yes Sir.
Follow this lady and whatever
she said,
just stop that from getting printed
in the paper... Go. - Ok Sir.
Hello... What... Yes.
Yes... you dialled
the right number.
Yes is hospital?
Now pls send all the crazy ones in
your family.
I will make all of them a Crime
Reporter for sure.
My editor says I'm crazy!
But those who don't
believe me are crazy!
I'm telling all of you
there is a Mr. India!
There is a Mr. India!
Yes he exists!
- But why have you brought us here?
Because Mr. India is going
to come here very shortly.
He'll come here?
- Yes right here!
Nobody is ready to believe me.
I even told Arun!
To come here.
But he didn't want to come.
There is a Mr. India!
He won't understand
what Mr. India is.
You tell me what he is.
He is a friend of the weak.
Enemy of the evil.
He says in this world...
But why are you asking?
You don't believe that
Mr. India exists.
You didn't want to come here.
Why did you come?
I thought Mr. India won't be
coming here, so I might as well.
I wasn't even talking to you.
You interfered and now you...
This is strange!
If we don't want to talk about
Mr. India, you feel bad.
And if we do, you feel bad!
Jugal, what does any one do?
Do whatever you want
but leave me alone.
That's enough! My god!
Brother Arun she's leaving!
She is furious! You wait here.
Madam! Wait! Listen!
Please!
You're unnecessarily getting angry.
I'm your well wisher.
Take my advice
and forget Mr. India.
How can you trust
a man who can't be seen?
I completely trust him.
In just a couple of days, Mr. India
has became so important to you?
He has brain washed you!
If I meet him,
I'll teach him a lesson!
So this is it.
- What?
Now I know why you hate him.
Why will I hate him?
- You envy him!
Why should I?
- Because you..
You know why.
- I know?
What do I know?
"I'm in love with Mr. India."
"I wish to meet him
a hundred times."
"I'm in love with Mr. India."
"I wish to meet
him a hundred times."
"Will you meet someone
who can't be seen?"
"The poor thing can only be heard."
"What's the big deal
about such a Mr. India?"
"I'm in love with Mr. India."
"I wish to meet
him a hundred times."
"I'm in love with Mr. India."
"I wish to meet
him a hundred times."
"He's the prince of my dreams."
"Silly! It's time you
came to your senses."
"He's so brave!
- Someday he'll bite the dust."
"He's beyond compare!
- Don't put him on a pedestal."
"He's no ordinary man,
someday I'll show you."
"Someday you'll find
out his greatness."
"No use meeting Mr. India."
"Stop meeting Mr. India."
"I'm in love with Mr. India."
"I'll meet him a hundred times."
Someone is drowning!
Could it be Mr. India?
- Shut up! He can't be seen!
Somebody help him!
- C'mon hurry up!
Arun brother!
- Tina!
Put him here. Poor guy is alive.
This is Mr. Baburam.
I know suicide is cowardice.
But I had no other option.
My daughter's marriage
had been fixed.
The groom's family
was to come in just 4 days.
I scratched and scrimped
to save money.
No sir let me go!
This money is
for my daughter's wedding.
Wants to get his daughter married,
scoundrel!
Let go!
- My money!
For my daughter's marriage!
Your daughter,
Sarla is like our sister.
I'll arrange for something
by evening. Trust me.
You've said it but
what will you do by evening?
I'll have to think.
- Think! You keep thinking.
But I'm going to that rascals den!
If I don't get Baburam's money
back then shame on me!
Aunt, I'll take you to his den.
Ok, let's go.
Good morning. Good afternoon.
Good evening!
Who are you?
- Who am I?
Charlie!
- Charlie, who?
You don't know about
Charlie Chaplin? How funny!
Your name?
- Dabarcha.
Dabarcha.
Who are you?
- My name is Karga.
Ghurka (security guard)?
- Karga!
Good name!
Come gentlemen, try your luck.
Put your money and take it all!
Hurry up, try your luck.
This is roulette!
No fights please.
Brother please. Come one by one.
Sister Seema, he has an eye on us.
Gentlemen try your luck.
Now we'll have to play
to save our skin.
This.
- There, not here.
50 bucks on number 7.
Number 7, turn around.
- C'mon!
The number is coming.
Number 3. Number 7!
Number 7.
- 7!
My lucky number. Money please!
On number 5!
Number 5! Excuse me.
Number 5!
- Number 5!
We told you number 5!
Number 5! C'mon!
The number is coming.
The number... Number...
Number 5!
Excuse me!
I think 200 has become 2000.
Thank you.
Sorry brother, you hit the wrong
number...
Okay so now who is next?
Anybody?
- Excuse me, these are two thousand
How much?
- On the Number 4.
Two thousand?
- Yes on the number 4.
On Number 4?
Hey come on move,
- Get out of here.
Hey, what number did she bid on?
- Number 4.
Shut up.
Hey you bid on number 4,
you lost your money!
Twenty thousand out of two
thousand.
Money... Money... money please.
- Money Money.
Money... Money... Please.
- Money.
Hey, Don't give her.
You have cheated.
- What are you saying?
What... Charlie and cheating.
What's going on dear?
Okay... Okay Mr. Gurkha...
I will hit this target again.
You just wait here... Okay.
Such a freak.
Take it... Come on hit it.
Number 4?
- Yes.
Hit it... Hit it Boss.
Hey.
- What?
Not on number 4, you must hit on
Number 7 now.
Yes on the number 7... its my lucky
number 7. - Yes.
My Twenty Thousand.
Nab these rascals!
Don't let them escape!
My god! Run!
My money!
Catch the ***!
Thrash both of them.
Guys... Don't let her go.
She ruined everything.
Catch her.
Yahoo Mr. India!
Now put me down.
You...
Hurry up!
- This way.
Not that way.
This way, the bus has arrived!
Greetings.
- Greetings.
Take this Mr. Baburam.
All this money is yours.
Get your daughter married grandly.
How can I thank you?
- Thank Mr. India.
It's his doing.
It's your generosity.
She risked her life and gambled.
And gives the credit
to some Mr. India!
Is it necessary to say this?
- Not really, yet..
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye!
Well done Seema!
Mr. India! - What you did
for Baburam's family,
I liked it very much.
Thank you Mr. India!
But if you had not come
to Karga's den,
I'd be in serious problem.
You won't face any problems
while I'm around.
So sweet of you.
I've heard your editor
has fired you?
Editor? Don't mention him!
What does he think of himself?
Seema don't worry.
- Why not?
He thinks I'm crazy!
He's not willing to believe
that you actually exist.
Tell him I'll meet him
tomorrow in his office at 5.00.
Promise?
- Promise.
Hello... Hello... No... No...
Sorry, wrong number.
No... this is not a hospital.
- Okay boss.
So you mean to say that the door
open at exact 5:30 pm.
But there would be nobody... right?
But somebody... I mean
Mr. India will come in. - Right.
And the chair will move by itself,
he will sit.
And will call me, Hello
Mr. Gaitonde, how are you?
And I will say Hello Mr. India,
please have a cigar.
And all by itself the cigar will
go up in the air.
And he will smoke.
It could be.
Yes it could be...
definitely it could be.
That you suddenly open your eyes
and you realise you were dreaming.
Hello Seema.
Hello Mr. India!
Hello Mr. Gaitonde. How are you?
I'm fine. I'm actually fine sir.
Thank you.
Why do you seem so shocked?
- Nothing at all.
Actually, it's nothing.
The strange thing is,
I can't see him.
And he asks me why I'm shocked!
Cigar Mr. India.
- Thank you Seema.
Do you have a match or a lighter?
Yes I've a lighter.
Sorry! Very sorry sir.
Thank you.
Editor!
I've heard that
you've fired Seema Soni.
No! Who told you?
It's not possible.
Please tell him. Our staff,
it's like a small family.
No injustice done here.
We live in harmony and love!
Why will I fire her?
It's her own newspaper.
Why should you ask me?
You may interview him and print it.
Strange!
Actually I had not seen you.
Now that I've seen you.
Haven't seen you.
Then I knew you can't be seen.
Call for you.
Ok Mr. Gaitonde, I must leave.
Ok bye Seema.
- Bye Mr. India.
I will meet you tomorrow at 7 pm
at the same place. - Okay.
The phone is in your handsSir.
What.
- Phone Sir... in your hands.
Oh Yes.
Hello... Hello... Hello...
What's happening Seema,
this isn't working.
He is not visible.
No!
She is crying a lot.
- Don't take my baby away!
She hasn't eaten anything
since morning. - Enough!
How much will you cry?
- No!
Laxmi enough!
What harm had my baby done?
The poor woman has gone mad
because of her son's death.
I saw him this morning,
playing in the lane.
What happened suddenly?
- He came home ate lunch
and died within 15 minutes.
This is a common scene.
Countless people are dying everyday
because of adulterated food.
Let me go! Let go!
It's in the newspapers.
It's happening everywhere.
What kind of people
indulge in adulteration?
Whoever they are. Let me tell you.
They will pay for their crimes!
Move!
- Sir my kids are starving!
They haven't eaten since days!
Sir please!
Anything else sir?
- Ask madam.
Neelam darling, anything else?
- You know that I'm on a diet.
You know how little I eat.
Isn't it?
People tell me,
there's shortage of food in India.
Tell them to come
and look at this table.
Where's the shortage?
Fantastic food!
Mr. Teja it's wonderful!
Have some soup please!
I'll drink poison
if you want me to.
How sweet!
What are you doing?
I'm so sorry Mr. Teja!
It's all right.
I don't know, my hand...
This spoon! In your ear?
Darling I don't eat with my ear.
Never!
I'm sorry.
But now I must feed my Teju.
Take this.
What's going on? I'll go mad!
Can I help you sir?
No, we were just talking.
You may go.
Neelam!
- Yes.
Are you all right?
Believe me, on both occasions
I felt someone holding my hand.
Oh god!
Got it! C'mon let's leave!
Sit down Mr. Teja.
You'll leave only
after you finish your dinner.
No.
- Where are you going madam?
You'll feed Teja
with your pretty hands.
I've brought special your dinner.
White pebbles,
which you mix in rice.
Black ones for the lentils.
And the brown ones for the wheat.
You've to eat this today.
She'll feed you
with a silver spoon.
Start feeding madam! C'mon.
Pick up the spoon!
- Yes.
Mr. Teja. Please.
- Open your mouth Teja!
Please, I'm sorry.
Now feed him the lentils.
Very good.
Mr. Teja open your mouth.
You'll be glad to hear that.
I've got the addresses of all
your warehouses and offices.
Keep chewing!
The police is raiding
all your warehouses at this minute.
You are ruined!
Who are you?
- An Indian.
Who knows what hunger feels like.
Mr. India...
- Long Live.
There are protests everywhere apart
from bombay, kolkata and bangalore.
Today a government speaker gave us
an information
that Mr. India has helped raid
illegal godowns and factories
and helped the government a lot.
But, Who is Mr. India?
Nobody can tell this with
conviction even today.
In the Parliament session today,
the opposition party.
Demanded the ruling party to give
all the information about Mr. India.
Arun bro, I know who is Mr. India.
- Hey, shut up.
Hey Shut up.
- Tell me who is it?
My classmates were discussing
that Mr. India is in the Army.
In the Army?
- Yes.
And that's why he is fighting with
our nation's enemies. - Just shut up.
Ohhh. - Arun bro,
I know who is Mr. India?
My teacher says, he is a Doctor.
- A Doctor?
- Yes, and that's why he help raid
the illegal food godowns.
That's enough Arun bro, Switch off
the TV and let's get out of here.
Or else Sister Seema will come and
catch us red handed.
But how will she come...
Today evening...
Oh... I didn't even realise that.
Mr. India,
you've so much love for people.
Just for people? Not you?
How would I know?
You never said anything.
Does it have to be told?
No.
Some matters are best
said through the eyes.
But even that can't be done.
What you couldn't hear
till today nor see.
I'll come close to you and say it.
Very close!
Touching you!
Taking you in my arms!
I'll say it in such a way,
you can feel it with your lips.
"I love you."
"These days and nights
are tough to spend."
"Wanting to pour
my heart out to you."
"These days and nights
are tough to spend."
"Wanting to pour
my heart out to you."
"Let me say it to you tonight."
"I love you."
"In solitude
with only you beside me."
"I wished to let
a secret out to you."
"In solitude with
only you beside me."
"I wished to let
a secret out to you."
"I shall say it tonight."
"I love you."
"Full of fragrance.
- Is your body!"
"Totally ecstatic.
- Is my heart!"
"Full of fragrance.
- Is your body!"
"Totally ecstatic.
- Is my heart!"
"Oozing with desire.
- Is your beauty!"
"Slowly but surely.
- I'm being intoxicated."
"Oozing with desire.
- Is your beauty!"
"Slowly but surely.
- I'm being intoxicated."
I'm being intoxicated."
"Now that I'm so close to you."
"I must tell you my secret."
"I shall say it tonight."
"I love you."
"These days and nights
are tough to spend."
"Wanting to pour
my heart out to you."
"In solitude
with only you beside me."
"I wished to let
a secret out to you."
"I shall say it tonight."
"I love you.
- I love you."
"I love you."
- love you.
- I love you.
"I love you."
I love you.
- love you.
Tongue.
Teeth!
Broke.
Next!
Nails!
Teeth!
Next! Come Tina.
Tongue! Teeth!
Nails! At the back
of the palm not in front.
Didn't cut your nails?
I did.
But they grow back.
- Really? Kummi cut her nails.
Nails!
- Arun!
Did you hear? Lord Hanuman's idol
has been stolen from the temple!
Who could've done this?
I know. Daga the big businessman
of the city has stolen it.
Where can I find Mr. India now?
Fantastic!
You've got
what you wanted Mr. Walcott.
In return what we want..
- You'll get it!
Johnny!
Good! Very Good!
Vinod!
Store everything in the basement.
Tomorrow I'll take the golden idol
out of India in my private jet.
Sure why not?
Soon Indians won't need a temple,
or a place to worship or
a god or goddess to pray to.
Because the day
is nearing Mr. Walcott,
when the 80 crore
population will bow,
only to Mogambo! And before us!
That day is not too far,
when the life and death of Indians
will be in our hands!
And then the population of India
will only worship us. Only us!
We'll be the new gods
of this nation Mr. Walcott!
Indian god hits too!
***! Shameless!
On one hand you sell these pure
idols to these foreigners.
On the other hand,
you ruin the lives of poor Indians
for your own selfish needs!
If you had your way, you'd sell
our lives, souls and our country!
I won't allow this to happen!
It also laughs!
Wait! You're my Hanuman!
You want to be the new god
of this country? - Yes!
Yes?
- No!
Daga you're the devil not god!
No!
- The devil!
- Traitor!
No!
Good god!
- Now you take my name!
Hail lord Hanuman!
You Englishman!
Where are you fleeing?
I didn't know you
were holy for the Indians.
I'm a donkey!
I'm a fool! You are god!
I know it.
- Will you steal idols?
No lord Hanuman!
What happened O lord?
What crime have I done?
Will you sell guns to
these traitors? - No lord Hanuman!
Hail lord Hanuman!
Sorry lord Hanuman!
No lord Hanuman!
O lord Hanuman!
Say Mr. Walcott!
Hail lord Hanuman!
What did you say?
- Hail lord Hanuman!
Hail lord Hanuman!?
Say it again!
- Hail lord Hanuman!
Louder!
From your heart!
- Hail lord Hanuman!
Hail Mother Goddess...
Sir there's the lord Hanuman
idol which was stolen.
Yes!
Drugs?
Oh my god bombs!
This is just the tip
of an iceberg officer.
If you search this house,
you'll find out about a gang,
who wants to destroy India.
Mr. India?
- Yes I had called you.
Thank you very much Mr. India.
No officer,
I've done nothing as yet.
My work is incomplete.
It'll finish on the day,
when the enemy of India,
Mogambo meets his end.
By defeating Daga and Teja,
does Mr. India think
he's the protector of India?
Does he think he
can clash with me?
With me? With Mogambo?
And these *** Indians!
Let's see how he helps them!
Captain Zorro!
Bombs must explode in various
cities, roads, markets of India!
In transistors, books, toys!
Spread such fear that every person
will think before leaving his home
that this might be his last step!
Run...
Round and round!
Hold it! Don't let it go!
Cheeku hold tight!
Don't fall off!
Round and round!
C'mon children!
Brother Arun put me down.
I want to go there.
Ok go, take care.
Kummi!
- Tina.
Tina.
What is that?
Kunnu.
Kummi what is that?
Tina!
Sister! Hurry! Move aside!
Move please.
Tina... Tina... Nothing will happen
to you Tina.
I am here... we all are there with
you.
Please Move.
Doctor our Tina is badly hurt!
Prepare for operation!
- Ok doctor.
Give this to me... and go quickly
bring the glucose.
Tina!
He may try hard but Mr. India
can't change Indian's fate!
Hail Mogambo! - Indian people
are fated to be Mogambo's slaves!
But first they'll
face destruction!
Hail Mogambo!
Dr. Watson are the missiles
ready to attack India?
Yes Mr. Mogambo.
We're only waiting for your orders.
I want to look at my missiles.
These buttons will get the missiles
out of the underground bunkers.
Mogambo is pleased!
Dr. Watson next.
This button starts the countdown.
Missiles would be ready
for take off Sir.
Press the button!
- But sir!
Press the button... Dr Watson.
60 seconds after the countdown
begins, there will be a blast.
And the missiles will take off.
They can be stopped
while there are 20 seconds left.
After that if you try to stop them
there will be an earthquake here.
Missiles will explode
and the island will be destroyed!
And if they aren't stopped.
- These missiles will take off.
Travelling hundreds of miles,
they'll explode
in various cities of India.
Indian cities will be destroyed!
But Mr. Mogambo
Mr. India will also die,
with him that formula
will also be destroyed.
Dr. Fumancho you are a fool!
Why haven't I launched these
missiles on India until now?
Captain Zorro,
according to our computers,
Mr. India loves the entire country.
Specially those orphan children.
Who live with
that good-for-nothing violinist.
You know what you've to do.
Put them all in the vehicle!
C'mon!
Hurry up!
- Brother Arun!
Hail Mogambo!
Hail Mogambo.
So these are the lowly children,
Mr. India loves so much?
If you value your lives,
tell me who he is
and where can I find him.
If you don't answer me,
I'll throw all of you
into this acid!
You'll crumble to the bones!
Captain Zorro!
One by one, take the kids.
- No!
No!
Not the kids! No!
Mogambo!
Listen to me!
- Help me!
Help me! rother Arun!
Spare him Mogambo.
- No.
Mogambo spare him Mogambo.
Brother Arun
- Mogambo.
I'm Mr. India.
Mogambo I'm Mr. India.
No, he's lying!
Just to save the kids
and Mr. India.
He was easily beaten up by my men.
I slapped him in his house
and he did nothing.
He can't be Mr. India!
Silence!
So you are Mr. India?
Let's see you disappear!
Untie my hands and I'll show you.
You can't fool Mogambo.
Take them away and lock them up!
Listen to me!
Seema... untie my hands just once.
You think lying like this you can
win... you can save all of us.
Please untie my hands.
I'm not lying. I'm Mr. India.
Look!
Where is it?
So you are him?
- Yes.
Arun!
I wish Mr. India would really come.
There's no Mr.
India other than me!
Jugal, how do I explain to them?
I'm telling the truth children.
Don't be under false hopes that
Mr. India will come to save you.
Because I'm Mr. India!
But I don't have any proof
to make you believe me.
I believe you! You are Mr. India.
I believe it too.
- So do I.
Me too.
- In you, I believe.
Me too, we know you never lie.
Madam don't expect anyone.
Ronnie, what's round your neck?
- Magnet!
Remove your belts.
The time is not far off
when Mogambo will be crowned.
Captain Zorro get my crown.
Where did the bracelet fall?
Now I recall.
When I barged into the trolley,
it would've fallen into it.
Take this Crown along to
show Mr. Mogambo.
Oh no.
Let us try one more time... Yes.
Yes!
Hurry up!
Not this way that way, c'mon.
Let's go madam hurry up.
C'mon on hide.
Hail Mogambo!
- Hail Mogambo!
C'mon hurry up.
- Come on.
Calendar, you, the kids
and madam go this way. - But you.
I'll get the bracelet.
Where will you hunt for it?
Where could the trolley be?
No matter what, the bracelet
shouldn't fall in their hands.
They will misuse it.
Go on, I'll follow.
- Ok.
C'mon hurry up.
- Come with me.
Go madam.
You've supported me so many times.
Do you think
I'll leave you alone now?
No Mr. India. I can't do this.
"I love you."
Who are you?
Hail Mogambo!
Hello?
Come take some rest.
Come on.
Arun bro... its you.
- Why are you running this way?
We ended up running where we
started from.
By god, these ways are
very confusing
Run... quickly...
Come on get in...
You all wait here...
Calendar I will come in a while.
Oh my gosh...
- What's this Calendar?
Calendar What is this?
What is this Calendar?
- Stop all of this.
- Its my head.
Here our live are in danger...
and you are asking what is this
and what is that?
What is this?
My name is Calendar.
- What your name is please?
My loyal men who bow before me!
My missiles are ready.
My army is ready.
Many of India's enemy
nations are ready to support me.
Captain Zorro.
Bring Mr. India's fans here.
Everything is happening
the way Mogambo wanted.
Only the invisibility formula
which makes man invisible,
will soon be at my feet.
What are you doing here?
- Waiting for Seema.
Strange! She went away
and made me wait...
Calendar they have caught Arun.
We can't keep quiet.
We'll have to do something.
*** Indian!
Do you think you can succeed
in escaping my confinement?
Where will you escape? Now your
whole country will be mine!
The time of your death has arrived.
It's the royal tradition that
a death man's wishes are granted.
Tell me if you've a last wish.
Tell me.
- Mr. Mogambo my last wish is,
that I acknowledge before death
that I was mistaken.
I want to do this by touching
the feet of the great Mogambo.
Mogambo is pleased!
Just once I want to fall
at your feet and say.
Hail Mogambo!
I want to say
Mogambo has the right,
to rule over the whole world!
Mogambo is very pleased!
I want to say that death
at the feet of,
the great and noble Mogambo
is better than life!
Mogambo,
is very pleased!
God like Mogambo.
I offer myself and my life,
at your feet.
At your feet.
How easily
these Indians accept defeat?
Today just this Indian.
Tomorrow all of India
will bow at my feet!
You'll get to see it!
Tomorrow the whole
of India will bow at my feet.
Just as this...
Where is he?
Mr. India?...
- Mr. India.
Guards
- Mr. India is here.
Fire!
Stop! Stop!
Fire
Stop Stop Stop Stop!
Oh god!
- Very good!
Mr. India your game is up!
Show up! Else the girl..
Captain Zorro!
Stop!
Mr. India!
The formula?
Ms. HawaHawaiii...
Block all the gates!
Let nobody in!
Let me see
how Mr. India saves India!
Switch on all the red lights.
Keep the guns ready.
I've found out Mr. India
can be seen in red light.
Mr. India!
Wherever you are, hear this.
You've lost this war with Mogambo.
My finger is on the button
which will send the missiles off.
And destroy every corner of India!
It would be better
if you surrender to us.
Mr. India!
If you don't hand yourself over
to my men within one minute.
This button will be pressed.
Mr India. now nobody can save your
India from me.
Who is it?
Mr. India?
No Mogambo.
I am not Mr. India but a common
and simple Indian.
Who resides in every city of India.
Is in every home, walks every city.
Mogambo, I'll take you
on not as Mr. India.
But as an ordinary Indian.
Because an ordinary Indian
is enough for you.
Then I'll crush this ordinary
Indian like a pest!
Don't think you've won Mr. India.
I've pressed the button.
In a few seconds,
my missiles will take off
to destroy India!
No! You can't do anything now!
The missiles have been charged!
Now if you stop them,
the missiles will explode here.
Save yourself now!
Or your India!
The missile is going to blast...
This island will burn into ashes...
- Run...
Seema!
C'mon hurry up!
Calendar, are the children ok?
Brother Arun!
C'mon hurry up.
The island is going to blow up.
Come Chikoo.
Hail Mogambo.
Seema
- Give me too...
Oh Seema.
Now atleast tell me that
who is Mr. India.
Where can I find him?
I have a lot of work with him.
Sir... please meet him,
maybe he can
Listen I will meet
him later... please.
Atleast... okay... if you insist
I will meet him.
Tell me Sir, How do you do?
Are you fine?
It was nice to meet you...
Okay!
Okay so atleast tell me
who is Mr. India.
What is so important that you want
to meet Mr. India.
Hey look, Please try to
understand my problem.
He has fixed a lot of world's
major problems.
Can't he fix my telephone?
This thing is difficult even
for Mr. India.
"I'm in love with Mr. India."