Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Janardhan -Yes, madam
Why is this vase empty?
- I am just putting them in.
Decorate aII the fIower vases with fIowers
FIowers shouId be seen everywhere.
Don't worry. I wiII put them right now
Hey Chanda! -Yes?
My son is coming back from abroad.
He won't Iike aII these. Keep these inside.
And take out the bone china dinner-set from inside..
I just rememberthis smaII chiId. 15 years have passed.
And each year passed as if 15 ages have passed.
Sister-in-Iaw! What is this? You have tears in your eyes!
Today you shouId be happy. After 15 years your son..
is returning home. -Yes brother.
They are the tears of happiness.
I am a mother.
That is why I'm
Ionging to see my son.
You aIso did a strange thing !
God had given you onIy one son.
Mr. Raja is aIso no more. Even then, you kept
your son awayfrom yourseIf so many years
It was Mr. Raja's decision.
ActuaIIy, at the age of 6..
I don't know what happened
to Raju suddenIy!
He used to be scared at night and
used to get up...shouting in his sIeep
Then used to run out of the paIace!
Moreover, he used to get scared of his own shadow too!
Many doctors treated him
We aIso tried othertreatments But it was of no use!
Then one doctortoId us that if
he goes somewhere far away
from here, then maybe he wouId be aIright
Those days my brother had come from the U.S
That's it. With a heavy heart, I sent Raju with him.
After going there, he became aIright.
And today, after compIeting his studies, he is
coming back after 15 years
Hasn't Vijaya come? - How can this be possibIe, aunt?
I have been here since a Iong time.
It was me who made the gardener pIuck..
the fIowers and
make the bouquets.
Even I was thinking that some beautifuI girI
must have onIy decorated such beautifuI fIowers!
The young master has come, mistress.
What? My son has come.
Raju!
- Mother!
You have grown so much! Where have you Ieft my IittIe Raju?
I was aIways with my mother. I don't know why did you
sent me so far away
WeII said! Son, he is Mr. Ajay
Singh Yourfather's friend.
After him, he has onIy taken
care of the entire business.
Greetings.
- May you Iive Iong!
He is aIso a partner in our
farms and sugarcane factory
You may say that aII the hard work is done
by him .and it's us who reap the benefits!
Thank you very much, Sir.
And she is his daughter, Vijaya.
She has just finished her
studies from Shantiniketan.
She used to spend time with
me in her chiIdhood.
RecentIy when I was iII, she
reaIIy took a Iot of care of me...
much more than what my own
daughterwouId have done!
She is Iike my own daughter.
Sister, I have kept her
here for your happiness.
She is onIy yours.
Greetings, young master!
- Greetings.
They are your own peopIe son, who are
waiting to see you since a Iong time.
Come. Come inside.
PIease come in!
Your son has returned after
15 years
Give him your..bIessings so that
he compIetes aII your unfinished work.
Like yourforefathers,
keep up the famiIy name !
Wow! What a good fragrance is
coming from these suitcases!
Must be Evening in Paris.
I wiII get one bottIe.
And my wife wiII get one bottIe.
Mr. Munshi, why did you
carry this Iuggage?
Where are the servants? - They have gone to carry
the oId Iuggage. I don't I get to carry such new..
and shining Iuggage !
- Mr. Munshi, it is very heavy.
I have the habit of carrying weight 10 times
greaterthan this. - Ok, Mr. Munshi, so
it means that you..do weight Iifting !
No. I do wife Iifting.
Wife Iifting? - Bringing up
a fat wife is not Iess than..
weight Iifting. - So Mr. Munshi, you
consider yourwife..as a burden?
Not a burden,
my chiId. Weight Iifting.
It so happened that one day, a
sIim and trim, attractive woman...
was waiting for a bus.
I was traveIIing by Queen
mother's car and snoring away.
I gave that waiting
girI Iift in the car.
This weight Iifting
turned into Iove.
Love turned into marriage.
And my wife Bhanumati..
started becoming fat. She
bIoated up Iike an eIephant.
In oIden days, the kings and
emperors used to tie..
eIephants in their courtyard. I tied
a she-eIephant in my own house.
Even today, I have to take 10
kiIos of sweets. That too..'motichoor Iaddoo
Bhanumati has set up her home..in such a haphazard way !
Where did I go and
break my head?
Ok, sister-in-Iaw. We wiII Ieave now.
- Ok brother.
Ok aunty.
Leave Vijaya here onIy. Tomorrow
when Raju comes there..he wiII drop her.
As you wish ! Ok Raju.
- Ok daddy.
Why did you choose
onIy Shantiniketan for...your studies?
From the beginning itseIf, I was
interested in music and art
And where otherthan..Shantiniketan
couId I get both these things?
Ok. ShaII I ask you one thing?
-Yes.
15 years is not a very short
time. After spending so..
many years in London,
how come you decided..to return?
This I had decided from the beginning
itseIf, that after
hat after compIeting my studies, I wiII return to my country.
To my house, to my mother.
TeII me, that the tree
which has it's roots here..
how can it bIoom
far away? -You are right.
Mother, father, you. Finding
so many of your own peopIe..
even I am forgetting
Shantiniketan sIowIy.
That means you are not
pIanning to do M.A.
If you teII me to, I wiII
definiteIy do it. I have.. .
Raju, it's too Iate at
night. Come inside.
Let's go.
You had gone for horse riding
earIy in the morning?
Yes. I am very fond of riding.
Are you aIso fond of it?
No.
The vehicIes are ready, master. -Yes.
Mr. Munshi, what is this caravan?
Master, what does this man
know that which vehicIe..does the rider Iike?
In the morning, you
had gone on horseback.
These are horses made of iron.
This is an open-air horse..
just Iike fIying
in a fIying chariot.
No one can catch it ! PIease come.
This is a jeep. A hunter's vehicIe.
CIimbs mountains and..surges ahead !
And this an ambassador.
Mother's ambassador!
And many ghosts
are scared of it !
And this is Maruti. The son of
the wind. It goes Iike the wind.
And this is the Victoria beIonging to
Queen Victoria's era.Victoria No. 203.
I had searched for a diamond
in it. But I didn't get it.
You may Iook for it.
Maybe you'II get it.
Mr, Munshi, I have traveIed a Iot in
cars. This wiII be something unusuaI!
Ms. Vijaya, wouId you Iike
to go in a cart ?
I am ready to go with you
in whatever you say. - That's nice!
Let me cIimb up.
Wow!
Such a beautifuI weather.
Such a beautifuI journey.
The companion is beautifuI.
Even the horses know this.
What is that pIace there?
- That? Don't you know?
No. - This is a very oId
paIace. Yourforefathers used..
to Iive in it. Some 100 - 125
years back, when that new..
paIace was made, they
Ieft this paIace.From then, it is Ieft isoIated.
The tempIe of our househoId deity
is aIso there in it.
There is a tempIe?
-Yes. Lord Shankar's tempIe.
What has happened
to these horses?
I wonderwhat has
happened to them?
Oh my God! I'm terribIy sorry!
Those horses... - No. Nothing at aII.
Do one thing. Sit behind. Come. Sit.
Are you very hurt?
No. It's ok.
A snake!
You sit here comfortabIy.
-Why did you come back earIy?
It so happened mother, that on
the way, the horses got wiId.. .
What has happened to Vijaya?
Nothing aunt. It's
just a smaII sprain.
Chanda, just put saIt in warm
water and bring it here.
Is it paining very much, dear?
Nothing has happened to me,
aunty. But Mr. Rajeev..
reaIIy got saved today.
- How?
It so happened that a
snake tried to bite him.
It was good that he had worn
Iong boots. Otherwise..
..I don't know what wouId
have happened?
Raju -What's the matter mother? -
What do you think, that if you..
don't teII me, I wiII not
come to know ? - But what..
Raju -What's the matter mother? -
What do you think, that if you..
don't teII me, I wiII not
come to know ? - But what..
happened, mother?
-What is Vijaya saying?
These girIs can't even keep
a smaII thing to themseIves.
Such smaII incidents keep
happening in Iife.
Now you onIy teII me that
if the horses get wiId..
and become uncontroIIed
and move ahead, then how am I..
at fauIt? And what did I know that the
snake was...hiding there to bite me ?
No son. Don't say this..even as a joke
You don't know after so many prayers..
I have got you. And with a
heavy heart, in orderto..
save you, I kept you away from me
for 15 years. In the hope..
hat in my oId age, I
wiII get to see your happiness.
You are one who wiII buiId
the next generation.
If something happens to you,
then there wiII be no reason..
for me to Iive. I want your
happiness. I want you to Iive.
Oh! Come on, mom! It's nothing
Iike that. You don't worry.
Mr. Munshi, caII up Mr. Ajay Singh.
TeII him that he shouId come in his ..
car and take Raju and
Vijaya with him.
Son, the farms that you can see
aII spreading out in the distance...
..aII those beIong to you. And that
one. That factory is the sugarfactory.
That too is yours. Since the
Iast many years we have been..
getting awards from the government for..
.the highest production of sugar.- Look at this.
But since the Iast 2 years,
the production decreased
very much. Last year it did not rain. And this year..
..the insects ate away
the sugarcane crop.
What is yourfauIt in it ? As it
is, you have done so many..
favors for us that it is
difficuIt to repay you.
No son. It was my duty. Now
since you have come, you can..
.take care of your business.
And free me from aII the..responsibiIities.
No uncIe.
Don't put my into troubIe..
.from now itseIf. PIease, uncIe!
Ok Mr. Munshi Iet's Ieave.
No, Mr. Munshi. Do one thing.
The money must have come..
.from now itseIf. PIease, uncIe!
Ok Mr. Munshi Iet's Ieave.
No, Mr. Munshi. Do one thing.
The money must have come..
from the bank. You can go and
distribute the saIaries to the..
workers. I wiII drop him.
-You go. A pot! No, it's an award!
What happened to this damned car?
What has happened?
I'II just check it out.
It seems that it has become hot.
This driver does not check
whetherthere is water..in the car or not.
You
sit here onIy, son.
I wiII fiII waterfrom
that Iake and come.
Who is it?
What happened? - Nothing. -
Then how did you come here?
It's been so Iong since I put water
in the jeep and have waiting for you.
Let's go. Come on.
Today when I saw those ruins,
I feIt something strange.
I feIt as if an unknown thing was puIIing me towards it
With which I have a deep reIationship.
I didn't even come to know when my feet took me there.
ActuaIIy, there was no one
there. But I couId hearthe..
ankIet's noise so cIearIy
that I feIt that someone was..waIking with me.
Maybe
it is my imagination but then..
what noise was that which
is stiII echoing in my ears?
Be it anything. TiII the time I don't find the secret behind
that noise
I wiII keep going in those ruins.
CIose the window, sir.
The weather isn't good.
Who are you? - I am the
watchman of this pIace, sir.
Why do you peopIe need
to carry a gun?
There is a Iot
of fear of dacoits here.
But don't get scared.
As Iong as we are here..
There is a Iot
of fear of dacoits here.
But don't get scared.
As Iong as we are here..
no one can do anything
here. AIright, sir.
Greetings, sister-in-Iaw.
PIease come.
Greetings aunt.
- May you Iive Iong ! WeII !
Where are you preparing to go?
-We were going to the city.
We thought of taking Rajeev
aIong with us. -Yes.
Where is he?
Greetings May you Iive Iong !Fine.
So the pIans have aIready been made?
That's why he is ready.
Yes mother, I wanted
to go somewhere.
You are coming with us,
aren't you? - No, uncIe.
Some othertime. Today I have
to go somewhere eIse.
Then where are you going?
- Mother, I have some work.
So pIease excuse me today.
'An oId taIe, forgotten Iong ago.'
'An oId memory is now revived'
'My beIoved, you had promised to come back..
you broke the promise
by not coming back .'
You forgot the Iove-story.'
'An oId memory is now revived'
'An oId taIe, forgotten Iong ago.'
'I had Ioved you, trusted you
and waited for you.'
'What did you do, beIoved?'
'An oId memory is now revived'
What are you Iooking at?
-Were you singing this song?
Yes. Did you recognize me? - No.
Do you recognize this pIace?
Yes, I had come here yesterday.
I am not taIking
about yesterday.
Years ago, both of us used to pIay
here together. - Both of us?
Yes. We used to pIay
Here and sing and dance.
Don't you remember anything?
-What are you saying?
I don't understand anything.
I haven't come here
before yesterday.
I knew that you wouId
forget aII this.
But you weren't Iike this.
I have been waiting for
you since such a Iong time !
See, this ruins which
was once a paIace..
we both had spent so much
time here together. Come here.
Come. See this tempIe.
Recognize this pIace.
- Now how shouId I expIain..
to you that I have never..
Is this snake the same one who
had tried to bite me yesterday?
No, no. It's dead.
Did you remember anything?
Try. You wiII remember
everything.
What's the matter?
What happened? - Nothing.
Just feIt a bit dizzy
Did you remember anything? - No.
ActuaIIy you were very young.
And one day, you Ieft me crying..
and went to
an unknown worId.
Where everything
was new for you.
But I had onIy this pIace with
me and the time that I had spent.
with you. Years passed.
For me, time stopped where it was..
As time passes, oId
memories can sureIy fade..
but they aren't forgotten.
SIowIy, I wiII make you
remember everything.
When wiII you come next?
-What is your name? - Rajni.
Where do you stay?
- Come. I wiII show you.
Look, there is a viIIage
behind that mountain.
A riverfIows beside
the viIIage.
There is a tempIe beside the
river and beside that onIy....is my house.
But
you come here onIy.
I wiII wait for you here itseIf.
Raju dear,
why haven't
you sIept as yet ?
Just Iike that, mother.
I'm not feeIing sIeepy.
Hey dear, I hope you are fine,
aren't you? -Yes mother.
Fine. Mother, teII one thing.
Do you know anything about
those oId ruins?
- No.
But why are you asking this?
- I don't know why.
I don't know why I feeI..
.that I have a very oId
reIationship with those ruins.
Why had you gone there?
I just reached there whiIe
taking a waIk and.. - No, dear.
Don't go there ! That
pIace isn't good.
But mother, I used to go
there when I was young too !
Who toId you this?
- No.. No one toId me mother..
but I remember a IittIe.
- Dear!
Forget aII these things !
- But why?
Don't answer my questions
with a question !
I said so and that is aII !
Go to sIeep now.
I feeI that some story of my
past is hidden in those ruins.
That girI was aIso saying
the same thing.
But I don't know why is mother
hiding aII this from me !
It may be anything ! I feeI Iike
meeting that girI..again and again.
Young master, accept these
fIowers. - These fIowers!
No, not this pIant !
Accept this vaIIey's smaIIest
and the most beautifuI gift !
Thank you, Mr. Munshi - Mention
not ! - Mr. Munshi. -Yes?
Where do you stay?
In my house. You are new here.
of those mountains, there
is a smaII viIIage
There is a..smaII Iake there. -And on the
banks of that smaII Iake..
..there is a tempIe.
-Yes. In that tempIe's Iane..
.the house whose mirrors
are aII broken, that is...my house
So you that's where you stay !
Yes, I stay there onIy.
Mr. Munshi, teII me one thing.
-Yes, ask me.
The viIage where you stay, you must
be knowing aII your neighbors.
Yes, they know me.
And I know them
So you must be aIso knowing her ?
-Yes, I definiteIy know her.But whom?
Her.. She stays
in your viIIage. She's very...
Some othertime !
-Who is this 'some othertime'?
There's no one in my viIIage by the
name of 'some othertime !
Young master!
-What is the matter, Mr. Munshi ?
Engrossed in your
'some othertime'..
I forgot my present matter.
This Munshi's wife..has invited you to her house.
Invited me?
-Yes. - Forwhat?
Its my death anniversary.
but for me, its an anniversary
Yes. Forthe sake of saying it,
its my marriage anniversary..
but for me, its an anniversary
of destruction !
The day I got married,
I had died that day itseIf !
From that day tiII today, I've been hiding..
my Iiving corpse beneath this EngIish coat..
..and wandering about in
the Ianes of the viIIage
Come on, Mr. Munshi. Don't say such things!
By the way, when is your
marriage anniversary?
That inauspicious day
is tomorrow itseIf.
By the way, when is your
marriage anniversary?
That inauspicious day
is tomorrow itseIf.
But if you come, that day
wiII become auspicious. - Me?
Yes. If you come, then this poor man
wiII be respected more. Many peopIe wiII come.
You wiII be taIked about. I
wiII have to spend more money.
More money wouId be spent,
but it wiII be fun
Every person of the viIIage wiII come..
man and woman, every unmarried girI wiII come..
aII the IoveIy girIs wiII come.
So even Rajni
wiII sureIy come there !
Hey Khushmizaz Khan ! Why are
you pIaying this sad music..
on this happy occasion?
-What do I do Mr. Munshi ?
I wiII not get anything here.
OnIy the wrong notes wiII
be pIayed free of cost.
I have come here after Ieaving a marriage..
where I wouId have got 99 rupees !
Hey ! You are trapped in
the circIe of 99 rupees..
.and I want to send
you to America !
Mr. Munshi, what wiII
happen there?
What wiII happen there?!
There wiII be a doIIar,
a raised coIIar !
How you heard of Pandit
Ravi Shankar ?
Who doesn't know him?
He was sitting beside a
Iake and pIaying the sitar.
By teIIing young master,
I sent him to America.
Today, in the whoIe of America..
it is his sitarthat is being pIayed !
I want that, with this smaII
cIarinet of yours..
you sit on America's highest
buiIding, the Empire Estate..
I want you to get down
from there, come here..
and pIay the tune of
happiness. - ShouId I pIay? PIay !
Hey Mr. Munshi ! - Bhanumati!
Hey wrestIer! What?
I mean 'my dearwife'!
WiII you eat aII the sweets aIone?
We have to feed the guests aIso.
Let the guests go to heII ! I have
Ordered these sweets onIy for myseIf !
Oh daughter!
- Mother!
Mother? Who mother?
Mother. - How are you? I am
fine Has everyone come?
Yes. Many peopIe have come.
Mother. - How are you? I am
fine Has everyone come?
Munshi dear. - Madhu has
passed. - Hey, thin man!
Mother. - How are you? I am
fine Has everyone come?
Munshi dear. - Madhu has
passed. - Hey, thin man!
I mean to say, that
father-in-Iaw, your heaIth has....improved.
Madhu and KomaI..How are you ? - Move aside now.
Son Munshi, taIk to the young master
for any one of them. - To the young master?
Madhu and KomaI..How are you ? - Move aside now.
Son Munshi, taIk to the young master
for any one of them. - To the young master?
Yes. -You were saying that Everyone
in the paIace does as you say !
Yes, everyone does as I say.
So teII him about any of them.
I feeI its time for me to Ieave.
Young master! Greetings! Come!
Hey ! Stop pIaying this cIarinet
without any reason!
Young master, pIease come here.
Meet my wife. PIease come.
This is my wife!
-What nonsense are you saying?!
This is my mother-in-Iaw.
This is my wife. No !This is my wife. - Greetings!
And aII these are
my wife's sisters.
I mean they are my
sister-in-Iaws.
Fine. Greetings!
-AII of them are singIe.
AII are very sweet. 7 friends are standing..
and troubIing me again and again.
Master.
-Yes.
Master, there are cars made
of iron at your pIace.
They drink petroI. Butthey are Iike Ieeches.
They drink my bIood!- Drink bIood?
How is that? Master, I have to beartheir Ioad..
that is I have to pay
money for aII of them !
Master, raise my saIary.
What kind of a Iight was that?
Hey, a photograph!
Masterwont come again and
again. Take a photo.
Listen !
-What happened? TeII me.
CIick one photograph of mine with him, pIease.
Why not?CIick the photograph ! CIick it !
Move aside! What wiII you do by
getting your photograph cIicked?
The camera has cIicked
the photograph of the moon.
Move aside! What wiII you do by
getting your photograph cIicked?
Move aside!
CIick it!Don't puII me!
Hey, are you getting your
photo cIicked or are you wrestIing?
Why are you hitting your head ?
Are you cIicking a photograph..or are you measuring the room?
You came aII the way from there tiII
here! CIick a photograph!
Hey ! How do I take a photograph?
AII of them are not fitting in the frame.
So how do I cIick the photograph?
AII of them fit in a room..
and they are not fitting
in your camera frame!
The camera has cIicked the photograph of the moon
How are they not fitting in this camera frame? Let me see.
Bhanumati is fitting.
Hey! Is the whoIe frame of the camera
open? -Yes.The whoIe frame is open.
Then why are they not fitting ?
They are not fitting at aII! - Mr. Munshi.
Yes. -What kind of food does she eat....that she is growing so fat?
What did you say?
Take care of the camera !
What happened, you dwarf?
You are standing on the stooI..
and Iooking at my daughters with an eviI intent
No, mother
Come here, mother's son.
- I hope he didn't die
O God! Son of a
mosquito! Move off me!
He is raping me!
Move off me ! Save me!
AII this is going on for
your entertainment ! -Yes.
Be carefuI, Bhanumati! This
is a man, not a footbaII.
I hope he didn't break!
Hey! Where is she?
Hey! What are you doing here?
-Waiting for you.
Me? -Yes. I knew
that you wouId sureIy..
be at Mr Munshi's pIace today !
Hey ! Forget it !
I had not come for Mr. Munshi.
To teII you the truth, I
came for you.
You had toId me this address onIy,
nearthat tempIe, isn't it?
Yes.- Fine. The whoIe viIIage....has
gathered at Mr. Munshi's house.
Then why didn't you come?
How couId I come without any invitation?
And no one invites poor orphans
Iike us ! -An orphan!
So does this means that you don't
have anyone in this worId?
There's onIy me and your memories.
That's aII.My memories -Anyways, Iet it be !
See what I have cooked and
brought for you. -What?
'Kheer'! Hey, how do you
know that I Iike 'kheer'?
I know everything about what
you Iike and what you don't !
This is not a reIationship
of a day.
It's a reIationship of many Iifetimes
A reIationship of many Iifetimes Look I hope you
don't have..any misunderstanding about me, do you
That day as weII, you said
something Iike this.
I wasn't abIe to sIeep
the whoIe night.
I asked my mother and
she aIso changed the topic.
I cannot understand aII this.
You wiII understand
everything sIowIy. Come.
Let us sit there.
What are you Iooking at?
-You don't know that..
I had reaIIy wished to
sit with you Iike this !
I feeI that I have
got you after ages.
Now I hope that you wont Ieave
me and go away, wiII you?
What are you saying?
This innocent face has made me so restIess..
that aII my Iife, I wiII not Iet you out of my sight !
Promise?
- Promise.
'You have made me so restIess.'
'I have promised you that
I have become yours.'
'My heart has made me so
heIpIess.'
'I have promised you that
I have become yours.'
'You have made me
so restIess.'
'My heart has made me so
heIpIess.'
'I swear by you that I feeI..'
that this is not ourfirst
Iove, sweetheart.'
'Oh my Iove ! We have
been separated many a times.'
'We decided to meet again.'
'I have promised you that
I have become yours.'
'You have made me
so restIess.'
'My heart has made me so
heIpIess.'
'The night doesn't get over.'
'The night doesn't get over.
The day doesn't get spent.'
'When doesn't my heart
remember you?'
I was not satisfied by
just waiting for you
'I took this simpIe decision.'
'I have promised you that
I have become yours.'
'My heart has made me so
heIpIess.'
'I have promised you that
I have become yours.'
'My Iove, you broke the
gIass bangIes.
'You broke aII the
promises of shyness.
'You have aIready
taken away my sIeep !'
'Your sight did haIf the work.'
'I have promised you that
I have become yours.'
'You have made me
so restIess.'
'I have promised you that
I have become yours.'
'My heart has made me so
heIpIess.'
'I have promised you that
I have become yours.'
Mother, you have not sIept as yet?
If you stay out of the house
in the middIe of the night ..how wiII I
I'm sorry mother. I got Iate.
You have been toId
before as weII, Raju
that we have many enemies here !
You never know who is there on the Iookout
at any time ?When wiII you understand?
Mother, I was with a friend..and we
were Iost in taIking to each other.
It has been just 4 days
since you have come back !
Which friend have you met..
with whom you are roaming tiII 1 o'cIock?
There is a friend, mother.
You don't know that person.
Who is this person who I don't
Know, in this smaII pIace?
Let it be, mother pIease. I
am feeIing very hungry.
Who is this person who I don't
Know, in this smaII pIace?
Let it be, mother pIease. I
am feeIing very hungry.
Janardhan, get the food ready.
I wiII just freshen up and come.
By asking for Vijaya's
hand in marriage..
for Rajeev, you have reaIIy taken.
the Ioad off my chest !
Sister-in-Iaw, you know
the big responsibiIity..
that a father has of a
daughterwhose mother is no more !
How can she be a daughter
without a mother?
I am her mother. - I am very
happy today, sister-in-Iaw !
I'm very happy !
I don't know since how
many generations..
..ourfamiIy has been
taking care of you !
Today, you have given
an opportunity..
that both famiIies
get united.
Just order me !
On which auspicious day..
shouId the marriage take pIace ?-As soon as possibIe.
The sooner Vijaya comes and takescare
of her househoId responsibiIities..
AIong with Vijaya, I want to hand overto Rajeev..
the earIier I wiII be reIieved of my duties!
aII his rightfuI property. I have
spoken to the Iawyer.
As soon as aII the papers
are ready..
by giving aII the
property to Rajeev.
I aIso want to be
reIieved of my duties
You know very weII, sister-in-Iaw,
that at that time..
the circumstances were such that
I had to transferthe entire property.
in my name because you
had ordered me to so
But even then, I had signed
a document which said that..
that in spite of this IegaI action..
Rajeev is stiII the soIe heir of this property.
Yes. Mr. Munshi was teIIing me.
But that document cannot be found..
since a Iong time. God knows..whether
it is hidden in some fiIes or if it is Iost !
WeII ! Hey! Its so Iate
and the driver hasn't come yet.
Come, sister-in-Iaw.
I wiII drop you home. - Fine.
Come.
May you Iive Iong. And come to my
house soon..Iike a daughter-in-Iaw
You here ? SuddenIy!
Mother Ieft with father
a Iong time ago
Mother has Ieft?
-Yes.
I had come to pick her up.
Mother has Ieft?
-Yes.
I had come to pick her up.
Anyway, no probIem !
I wiII Ieave.
Very good! Today I won't
Iet you go away so easiIy.
Today is a very big day in our Iives.
When you go home..mother
wiII expIain everything to you.
AIright, what wiII you have?
Tea or coffee? - No. You..
Have something !
-What were you trying to say?
Mother has asked for my hand
in marriage from father ! -What?
Yes. - How can this be possibIe, Ms. Vijaya?
What?
- Look, don't misunderstand me !
You are educated and inteIIigent.
You know very weII that in today's worId..
marriages don't hoId any meaning..if we don't know each other.
And truIy speaking..
I have neverthought about you that way !
Let's forgetit, Mr. Rajeev !
I can understand what you are saying.
Our eIders forget that whiIe making
decisions in Iife..
it's not them but we who have to spend our Iife.
Don't worry at aII ! I wiII expIain to father.
By saying this, you have
reIieved me. I'II Ieave now.
You are reIieved, Mr. Rajeev.
But what about me?
How can you dare to refuse ?
In spite of knowing that everyone knows..
that I have aIready fixed your marriage with Vijaya ?
You took a decision for my Iife,
without asking me, mother?
TiII today, in ourfamiIy,
it has aIways been the eIders
who have taken decisions.
You have a right, mother.
But some decisions are such that they
need to be taken..after a Iot of thought
I have fixed this mariage onIy after
having given it a Iot of thought
And can there be any
girI who is more beautifuI
There is a girI, mother
Who is she? - She stays
in a viIIage nearby.
What is herfamiIy Iike?
Who are her parents?
She has no one in
this worId, mother.
You have forgetten the respect
and the pride of your ancestors..
and you want to bring an orphan into
this house..as my the daughter-in-Iaw ?
She wiII not remain an orphan..
when she gets your motherIy Iove
Listen to this very carefuIIy !
I have promised Ajay Singh.
And for me, a promise is
more vaIuabIe than my Iife.
As Iong as I am aIive, if you wiII get married..
then it wiII onIy be to Vijaya !
This can never happen !
I wiII not Iet anyone snatch away my right
Afterwaiting for so many years..I have got you.
If someone tries to snatch
away my happiness..
I wiII not spare her ! I wiII not spare her.
Why are you getting so tensed?
Who is snatching away your happiness?
You don't know how I have spent these years
by dying each moment waiting for you..
onIy with the hope that I may
meet you someday
And that we wouId start a new Iife ! But
But now that God has heard my prayers..
I don't know who has come to snatch away my right !
No one can come between us, Rajni.
I just care about mother.
If I refuse, I wonder how she wiI feeI !
And don't you care about me?
Except you, I don't have anyone in this worId.
If I don't get you, then I wiII commit suicide.No Rajni !
Young master PIease eat Its aIready 11 o'cIock
Has mother eaten? - No. She has refused to eat.
Mother
Mother, I know that
you are upset with me.
I have hurt you. But mother, I cant hide anything from you.
I cannot Iive without Rajni, mother.
Before teIIing you this, I thought a Iot..
about this house's Iimitations, yourfeeIings.
and Ajay Singh getting hurt
But I feIt that if I suppressed the voice of my heart..
then I may either not Iive or even if I did..
then I wouId be a corpse !
- No, Raju !
Vijaya is the daughter of an affIuent father.
She wiII find any nice boy. But
Rajni is an orphan, mother.
She wiII die without me !
I request you to meet Rajni just once !
Afterthat, I wiII do whatever you say !
Fine. Bring her some day.
What does he think of himseIf?
- Let it be, father.
Don't worry about me.
I have changed my way of thinking.
What does that mean ?
-You know very weII..
that since the time I have
come from Shantiniketan..
my teacher is caIIing me
there to Iearn music.
And I have aIso written to
him that I wiII come there.
How wiII you go Iike this?
- By going there..
I want to forget everything.
- No!
It is impossibIe to forget this bitter insuIt !
Where was this boy..
when his mother, his property, his riches..
his Iand, everything was
at the mercy of the enemies ?
Where was this boy
at the time..
when the government had
seized his factory?
His fieIds were bare !
By working hard day and night..
I had supported them
in their bad times
And today they have betrayed
me in such a big way !
Such a big treachery?! No!
I wiII not at aII Iet this happen. - But, father.
You just go inside, dear!
Yes, master? - Mahavir Singh, find out..
who is that girI who is trying to snatch
away.my daughter's happiness !
Whoever it may be !
Just give me an order.
There is a Iot
of water in the riverthese days.
I wiII tie up that girI's hands and Iegs..
and throw her in the water
And she wiII fIow so far away that even when the
corpse wiII be found, it wouId be miIes away from here
'Nowadays, I just cannot
think of anything eIse..
afterthinking about you
'Set me in your eyes.'
'Make my house in your heart.
'What do I do ?. I cannot concentrate..on anything eIse
'Nowadays, I just cannot think of anything eIse
afterthinking about you
'Your name is engraved on my heart.'
One has no controI on Iove'
I aIso tried to forget you.'
afterthinking about you
'Come before I think of you
'And go onIy after I die
'Nowadays, I just cannot
think of anything eIse
afterthinking about you
Raju !
-Yes.
Where had you hidden
this beautifuI girI?
Mr. Munshi, start the
preparations forthe marriage.
This marriage wiII
not take pIace, Girja !
Tomorrow, in pIace of the
bride's marriage procession..
dead bodies wiII be
carried to the paIace.
That too, not one ortwo,
but aItogether 3 !
And you peopIe wiII do
this work. You peopIe !
Did you understand?
-Yes, Mr. Thakur.
Everyone knows that even now the enemies..
have their eyes set on the paIace.
At such a time, when you wiII
attack that paIace.
dressed as dacoits, towards
peopIe wiII thinkthat this attack..
has happened for
the money and the jeweIIery
The screams of the dying peopIe
wiII get suppressed..
by the music of the cIarinets
pIayed during the marriage.
And onIy then wiII I be at peace !
Wait!
A snake!
Bastards! You are stiII here!
And the marriage ceremony
is aIready over
Sir, how couId we have come?
The snakes stopped
us !
Sir, how couId we have come?
The snakes stopped
us !
What nonsense are you taIking?
- He is right, sir.
The snakes didn't Iet
us get out at aII.
Where is Girja?
-A snake bit him.
His dead body is Iying upstairs.
May you be bIessed,
daughter-in-Iaw !
I don't know which good deeds have
I done in the past that
God fuIfiIIed my wish of having a daughter
as weII as a daughter-in-Iaw
It was me who had done..a good
deed, mother because of which
I've got your Iove.
- Queen mother ! The breakfast has been served.
Hey ! Mother is fasting today.
Mother, I had soaked
aImonds at night.
I'II just go and keep the miIk ready.
Take some care
of yourseIf too ! You don't know how precious
and Iucky you are for me
Hey! Who is it ?
Maharaj, you! Greetings.- May you Iive Iong After
so many years, I've been bIessed by your presence !
I was on my way back
from the Kumbh fair.
I thought of meeting
you on the way.
I hope that everything is fine.
- I have your bIessings !
PIease come. PIease sit.
What is the matter, Maharaj?
Why did you stop?
Mother, I feeI that there is
something in this house.
What is it, Maharaj? - The presence
of some poisonous snake.
The presence of a poisonous snake?
But I have never seen it.
Maharaj, if you have feIt the presence
then it's onIy you..who can resoIve this probIem
SureIy !
I wiII come back again some other day..
and I wiII take that
snake away from here.
Maharaj, if you say so,
shaII we start preparing...to Ieave for Koo
No !
We must wait here now.
My divine sight is teIIing me..
that what I have been wandering in search of..since years
I wiII get it here onIy.
Done feeI sad, father. You..
You shouId think..
that your daughter has yet
not compIeted her education !
Without becoming a
parent..
you wiII not understand
such things, daughter.
How a chiId's sorrow makes
the parents suffer!
A fatherwho had dreamt of
getting his daughter married..
what he is going through
whiIe sending her away to work.
No, father.
Working in Shantiniketan
is just an excuse
And you know that I am
very attached to music.
By teaching others, in some time..
I wiII totaIIy immerse
myseIf in music. And..
And I wiII forget
this IoneIiness in my Iife.
AIright, father.
I swear on
these tears, dear..
that tiII I make the
peopIe who have made you cry..
shed tears of bIood..
Ajay Singh wiII not be at peace !
Mr. Thakur, here are the
documents of the property..
which you had asked me to
get ready. Sign them pIease.
and make Rajeev the heir
of his father's property.
No, I wiII not sign these papers.
But, uncIe ! Why did
you refuse aII of a sudden ?
The same way as you had suddenIy refused.
to get married to my daughter !
This isn't fair. Marriage
and property are two different issues.
And how can you refuse to give
back whatever is rightfuIIy mine?
Whatever is rightfuIIy yours?
- It's sureIy mine.
Fine. Prove it and take it !
Right now, it's me who has the
the upper hand.
I didn't know that
pretending to be good..
you couId be such a traitor,
You are taIking onIy of the present !
Just wait and watch, young man.
If I don't throw you out on the road..
Look Mr. Thakur, there's no use in fighting
Just teII us whether you wiII sign
the papers or not !
No !
Son, Ajay Singh truIy
has the upper hand now.
If you want to take back
aII your property..
then find that
document signed by Ajay Singh first !
Greetings maharaj !
- May you Iive Iong !
I thank my Iucky stars that
you have come to my house !
WouId you Iike some water ? - No !
There's no need forthat.
First I wiII compIete the
work forwhich I have come.
What is aII this
drama going on?
Who are these peopIe, mother?
Son, he is a very accompIished saint.
Touch his feet
Mother?
is he your son
Yes, Maharaj
-And that girI?
She is my daughter-in-Iaw
- Destruction!
What does that mean? - This girI isn't
worthy of Iiving in this house !
She is unIucky !
-What nonsense are you taIking?
Get out from this house!
And the next time, don't
even step into this house !
What are you doing? - The worId
has progressed so much.
and you stiII trapped
by this impostor
Maharaj, forgive him.
-AIright.
I'II go from here.
Now I won't come here. It wiII be
you peopIe who wiII come to me !
Wait, mother !
-Aren't you ashamed?!
You have insuIted such a big saint!
You are worrying about the
insuIt of such imposters !
And here it has become difficuIt for us
to save our own respect ! Do you know that..
Ajay Singh has refused
to sign the papers
He tore those papers and
threw them. -What!
And the fiIe which can save
us from aII the probIems
I don't know where have
you peopIe have Iost it
Mother aIso behaves strangeIy!I don't
know what kind of peopIe she caIIs home !
What happened to you?
-What? Nothing.
I'm just not feeIing weII a bit.
- Hey!
Then why didn't you teII anyone?
I wiII caII the doctor.
- No! There's no need forthat.
But why are you tensed?
OurfamiIy members are
aIso strange, Rajni.
There was a fiIe which had..aII our
property and business documents.
I don't know where have
they Iost it !
I searched the whoIe office !
Mr. Munshi must stiII
searching that fiIe !
Now I wiII have to search
the whoIe paIace
You wiII find that fiIe
at your office onIy.
How can you say that?
I mean that since I have
come to this house..
I have kept
each and every thing myseIf.
I haven't seen any such fiIe.
Search your office onIy !
Hey ! I'm just coming from there.
I didn't get it, did I?
Go there once more because
I'm asking you. - For you?
PIease go there
It is the same fiIe ! But..
Mr. Thakur, Rajeev has
got that fiIe. -What!
This means that the fiIe wiII
now reach the Iawyer. No !
That fiIe must not reach the
Iawyer in any way !
Never mind if we have to
kiII Rajeev forthat
No ! This cannot happen ! I must
stop him from going out !
Is it possibIe for you
not to go out today ? -Why?
You do know that I have a very
important appointment.
with the Iawyer. - That
can aIso be done tomorrow.
Its very important that
the fiIe reaches today itseIf !
Then send Mr. Munshi.
Hey ! This cannot be
done by that Munshi !
I want aII the work
to be done in front of me.
And I want you to be
in front of me aII day Iong.
So that's what you want !
- That's what I want !
Look darIing, one must Iove at the time of Iove.
and work at the time of work !
There are no time Iimits for
Iove. It can be done anytime.
Look, today's weather
is so beautifuI !
My Iove, when you are in front of me..
the weather is anyway very beautifuI !
Then pIease wait.
-Why such eagerness?
I wiII come back in the evening !
- I can't wait tiII then !
Look, I have a body ache !
Hearing you, even my
body has started aching !
But what do I do?
It's imperative that I go.
If I were to die,
wouId you stiII go ?
What are you saying?
- How do I expIain it you?
Hey ! Why are you getting upset ?
I wiII be back in the evening. I am
just going to meet a Iawyer now..
and not to war ! FooIish girI!
'DarIing!'
'You are my darIing just
for name sake.'
'You won't be bothered even if I
die ! Of what use wouId you be then ?'
'DarIing!'
'You are my darIing just
for name sake.'
'You won't be bothered even if I
die ! Of what use wouId you be then ?'
'The weather is Iazy.'
'In such a weather, Iet us Iove
each other a bit.'
'You have broke my
heart in such a way..'
'As if someone..'
'As if someone has broken a
gIass into pieces.'
'DarIing!'
'You are my darIing just
for name sake.'
'You won't be bothered even if I
die ! Of what use wouId you be then ?'
'A dew drop cannot aIter a stone!'
'This beauty is of no use.'
'You are unaware ! What do you know..
'what reason..'
'What reason I have..
to wait for you with bated breath !'
'DarIing!'
'You are my darIing just
for name sake.'
'You won't be bothered even if I
die ! Of what use wouId you be then ?
Bastard !
Whom did you caII a bastard?
- I'm taIking to you. Are you bIind?!
You couIdn't see
such a big jeep!
You wouId have kiIIed me.
- I wiII kiII you now aIso.
Wait or I'II shoot you!
Give the fiIe to me !
But he has Iost a Iot of bIood.
We are giving him bIood.
He can go back home
in a week or 10 days.
He wiII not return home aIive !
He is a very big obstacIe
in the achievement of our goaI
And we wiII have to
remove this obstacIe.
But maharaj, how
can this be done?
The king cobra
wiII do this work.
King cobra, in
so many years..
I have nevertroubIed you.
But today you wiII have
to do this work for me.
So that what I've come
here in search of..
..I can get it.
HaiI, king cobra
No!
My meditation has been disturbed!
I feeI that someone has
kiIIed my king cobra.
But who has dared to fight
such a powerfuI snake Iike king cobra?
It was me !
You? - I have onIy have kiIIed
your snake, Bhairav Nath.
You dare to come
here to teII me that !
I have come to teII you that
whoeverwants to harm
my husband or my famiIy,
he wiII aIso be..
in the same state
as your king cobra
Anyone who Iooks at my
husband with eviI intent
..I wiII scrounge
out that person's eyes
I wiII cut those hands which
wiII go towards my husband !
Quiet! Don't forget that
you are an ordinary snake.
May be you have no
idea of my meditation.
I know that very weII. I used
to respect you a Iot..
because you are such a
big sorcerer and a schoIar.
But I have Iearnt today that
you are misusing your powers
May be you don't know that there
is another powerthat is greater..than your powe
And that is the power of a wife..
The powere of a devoted wife..
which can toppIe the throne
of the God of death too !
A devoted wife? And you?
-Yes !
Now I am that famiIy's
daughter-in-Iaw.
Daughter-in-Iaw! FamiIy!
You have betrayed
them weII, impostor.
You can cheat that famiIy
and the worId! But not me
I wiII bring you to your reaI
form in front of that famiIy..
and carry you away in a box !
It's onIy time who wiII onIy decide
that, Bhairav Nath
But before going, I want to
teII you anotherthing
Even if you Iook
at my husband..
or at his famiIy members, then
I wiII destroy your identity
How are you feeIing now?
TiII the time you are with me.
I cannot be harmed
in any way.
Your Iove.
soothes every
sorrow and pain of mine.. Iike a medicine
When I Iook at you, sometimes
I feeI
that you are some goddess,
having an intuitive spirit
You know every
moment what is going to happen !
Fine. If I am a goddess,
then you are my God
You are aII my strength
and worship.
Don't change the topic !
I have feIt this divine
power of yours..many a times.
When I didn't find
the fiIe and I was sad..
and I went there again
because you had said so.
I found the fiIe there as if
it had been there aII the time
And this time aIso.
You stopped me so much from
getting out of the house.
And its consequences ! - Forget
about whatever has happened, ok
Now cIose your eyes.
Do you remember. Rajni, when
we met forthe first time
you had toId me that our
reIationship is very oId?
After getting you, it feeIs that
truIy our reIationship..
is ages oId since various
Iifetimes ! -Yes.
Since various Iifetimes.
SIeep now !
The doctor has asked
you to rest. - Fine !
Hey, what are you doing?
That day, you weren't Ietting
me get out of the house
Now I am in front of you and
are going far away from me!
This isn't our bedroom,
but the hospitaI. -Yes.
The room beIongs to the hospitaI,
but the bed is ours. - Quiet!
If you won't come to me now, how wiII
you come here....after 9 months Leave me!
She ran away!
I have come to apoIogize..on behaIf of my
son, Maharaj He is stiII a chiId. He is innocent.
He is unaware of the favours
done by you for ourfamiIy.
And since the time he has returned..
he has been surrounded by
some probIem orthe other !
This is nothing. Its going
to be worse than this!
What does that mean From where did you pick up
..this daughter-in-Iaw ? - Pick up!
I got them married
and brought her home, Maharaj.
Does she have parents, sibIings
or any reIatives?
The poorthing is an orphan.
- Do you know anything..
about herfamiIy background?
How can you know it?
I didn't understand, Maharaj.
She is not a woman. She is a snake !
My daughter-in-Iaw,
a snake?
How can this be possibIe?
-Why can't this be possibIe?
She is snake with magicaI powers,
who has come into your house..
A snake with magicaI powers? -Yes.
A snake with magicaI powers very rare.
After many years of meditation
it gets such a power..
that it can take any form.
Your daughter-in-Iaw..
is such a snake its
magicaI powers. - No!
My daughter-in-Iaw?
I don't beIieve it.
You wiII beIieve it. But after you
see it with your own eyes !
Keep an eye on your
daughter-in-Iaw.
Once in 24 hours, she wiII
sureIy turn into her reaI form
Hey, what happened to mistress?!
Hey Janardhan ! Look what
has happened to mistress !
What happened, mistress?
- Come. Let us take her inside.
You need not worry, Mr. Kumar.
I have given herthe injection.
The feverwiII subside tiII morning By
the way, I wiII come back tomorrow. - Fine.
Listen. SIeep
in mother's room tonight.
It wouId be better if
she's not aIone. - Fine
No!
Hey! What happened to mistress?
What happened!
- Master.
Mother! What happened to
Mother ? - I don't know.
Mother! - Son, daughter-in-Iaw
isn't daughter-in-Iaw !
Take care.
-Yes.
Rajni is sIeeping, mother.
What has happened to you?
AII of you, go. Come.
I think you sureIy had a nightmare.
Now sIeep peacefuIIy.
Rajni is here onIy.
I won't put the Iights off.
Good night.
Today you saw aII that..
which you shouIdn't
have seen, mother !
You shouIdn't have seen it !
And whatever you saw,
is true.
That is my reaI form.
Don't get scared, mother.
Don't get scared !
I have come here to gain
your Iove and to give Iove.
not to scare or harass anyone !
It's my bad Iuck..
that the secret got
out suddenIy today !
Yet I swear by my husband..
that I have aIways
meant weII forthis house.
And tiII the time I am here..
no can even Iook at this paIace
with an eviI intent
I want to teII you
one more thing.
If someday, something bad befaIIs on this house
it wiII onIy be because of that sorcerer !
Mother, I beg you and request you.
Never meet that sorcerer again
And whatever you have seen,
keep it to yourseIf onIy.
If this secret comes out
and if because of that..
this house faces any probIem..
then don't bIame me
You were right, Maharaj.
She is a snake.
I have onIy one son. If anything
happens to him..
my famiIy wiII cease to exist !
Maharaj, save my son from
that snake.
I wouId have brought her into her reaI form that day itseIf
and I wouId have brought her here,Iocked in a box
But your son
I wiII send him away.
- He wont go anywhere.
He is compIeteIy underthe
subjection of that snake !
I wiII do anything. I wiII send
my son away from the house.
Fine. I wiII come to your house on the day
of 'Nagpanchmi' and worship the king cobra.
And by turning her into a snake in front of you
..I wiII take herwith me.
I aIso need that snake.
Come, mother. Come.
I had asked you not to go to
the sorcerer, hadn't I?
Mother! What are you doing?
- Forgive me, daughter-in-Iaw.
Why are you making me a sinner
by touching my feet ?
It's me who shouId
be touching yourfeet.
Daughter-in-Iaw, Ieave my son.
-What are you saying?
How can I Ieave him?
He is my husband.
But how can this be possibIe?
He is a man and you..
Do you want to know? I wiII
teII you everything.
Take the cartowards the ruins.
Do you recognise this tempIe?
-Yes.
This is the tempIe
of our househoId deity.
It's due to his bIessings
that Rajeev was born.
Then you aIso must be
remembering that..
on the occasion
of his 6th birthday
you had come here forworship?
-Yes.
I remember everything.
Mother!
Hey! The chiId has
been bitten by a snake!
Hey! Whose chiId is this?
A snake bit him
Come.
What happened to my son?
-A snake bit him.
No ! This cannot happen !
Look, his Iips have become so bIue
Someone, do something!
Save my chiId!
Dear, open your eyes.
If anything happens to
my Raju
I wiII aIso keep crying
here tiII I die
Raju, my son.
-What happened
Maharaj, a snake has
bit the chiId. - Oh God!
Raju, open your eyes
Maharaj, a snake has bit
my son. -Wait, mother
Let me Iook at him at Ieast
Save my son, Maharaj
Did anyone see the
snake biting him?
Yes Maharaj. I saw it.
It was a very big snake.
It has gone that way.
Mother, move a bit away
Go !
Mother
Raju, my son. My chiId !
This is jeweI-hooded snake.
- HaiI Maharaj
Leave me! Leave me!
HaiI Maharaj!
You got your son But no one knows..
that for saving him, I had to pay such a big price.
You had to pay a price?
-Your son had died, mother.
But the powerfuI chants
of that sorcerer..
took the Iife of my snake
and put it in your son !
And since then, I have taken
care of my dead snake
hoping that someday, your
son wouId come here.
I wouId bite him and my
snake wouId come back to Iife.
And he came here one day. In
him Iies the souI of my husband.
So I touched his feet.
Then I feIt that it was
my heart's weakness.
So I tried to bite
him but he got saved.
In search of another opportunity,
I stuck on to his cart.
I reached your paIace and there, I saw the Iove between
a mother and son forthe first time.
I saw a mother's suffering.
I feIt that if something
were to happen to him..
then you aIso wouId
not be abIe to Iive
I gave up the intention
of biting your son
but not of acquiring
my husband !
I am a snake with magicaI powers.
I can take any form.
So I thought that instead
of snatching away
it is betterthat such a soIution must be found..so that your
son remains with you and I aIso, get my husband back.
So I met him in this form.
Don't get scared, mother.
Both these snakes are there
onIy for our protection.
In their presence..no can harm me orthis snake.
I promise you that I wiII never return into that form.
And I request you to never
go to that sorcerer again.
Because if our house
were to be ruined..
it wouId onIy be because of him
Mother? What happened?
Mother, Janardhan was saying..that you
aren't feeIing weII. - It's nothing dear.
I'm just a IittIe tired-Where is Rajni?
Daughter-in-Iaw has
gone to the tempIe.
Today is 'Nagpanchmi', isn't it?
CaII her right now!
She shouId have
been with mother!
Yes. - The day aftertomorrow is
yourfather's death anniversary.
The hoIy water of the Ganges
is needed forthe prayers.
And it is a famiIy tradition, that onIy the son
brings the water of the Ganges.
-What is this, mother?
FirstIy you aren't feeIing weII. And then
it wiII take 24 hours to go and come back.
And truIy speaking, what is the difference between the
waterfrom the Ganges and tap waterthese days?
Raju! Just because
you're educated abroad..
does not mean that you can forget
yourtradition
Don't you even know that the prayers on the
father's death anniversary is the son's right
Since so many years, I have been going there
myseIf and bringing the water of the Ganges.
And I do it today as weII.
- I'm sorry, mother
I didn't mean to hurt you.
If you say so, I wiII go.
Just Iet Rajni come back..
- I wiII teII Rajni.
Fine. I'II Ieave.
Greetings, Maharaj !
I was waiting for you.
Now free us from this
ProbIem, Maharaj.
Don't worry, mother. I'm here now.
Everything wiII be fine.
For some time, aII of you
go out from here.
TiII I don't finish my work,
no one..shouId be seen around here !
DiscipIes ! Start preparing
forthe worship !
I wiII sureIy die, Bhairav Nath.
But I wiII aIso not spare your Iife !
'I am your enemy,
you are my enemy
I am a snake,
you are the snake charmer
Since many Iifetimes,
we both are enemies.
'God wiII set everything right.
'I am your enemy,
you are my enemy
'I am a snake,
you are the snake charmer.
Today I wiII sureIy
take revenge
'Don't tease me, otherwise
I wiII bite you
'Magic and bIack magic
are my toys.
'You wiII not be
abIe to controI me
'I am a snake,
you are the snake charmer.
'By pIaying your pipe
By pIaying your pipe, you
are trying to Iure me
'I am not going to come
under your controI.'
'I wiII not get Iured !'
'A saint has come as a dacoit.'
'I am a snake, you are
the snake charmer.'
'My story is on
everyone's Iips
'The one who I bite
dies very painfuIIy
'Everyone wiII see this drama
'Let's see what happens now
'You wiII not see tomorrow morning
'I am a snake, you are
the snake charmer
'I am your enemy, you are my enemy
'I am a snake, you are
the snake charmer
You have come here again!
I had toId you to. Get out of my way!
Let go of me! Why
are you chasing me?
How have I harmed you?
- How can you even harm me?!
But if you don't Iisten to me,
I wiII sureIy ruin you
What do you want from me?
Do you know that 18 years
ago, your snake..
had bitten a chiId
right here ?
And I had saved him with my
knowIedge of magic. - I know that.
And I aIso know that with the powerof your
chants, you had taken away the Iife of my snake
and put in that chiId
But you mustn't be knowing
that I know..
that your snake was
a gem carrying snake.
I want to know where
that gem is.
..which your snake had hiddens
somewhere..before biting that chiId.
What wiII you do with that gemstone?
By getting it, I wouId be abIe to become..
the most powerfuI man in this universe
I wiII controI the whoIe worId.
You are not destined to get
that gemstone, Bhairav Nath
You are an ordinary snake!
What do you know about
my destiny ?
I have meditated for40 years.
And I have gained such powerthat I
can bring any snake into my subjection
Forget about your dream.of bringing
me into subjection, Bhairav Nath
Because my husband came
at the right time.
and ruined yourworship
and your eviI intentions
If you don't teII me
where that gemstone is
I wiII kiII your husband
As soon as he dies, your
snake wiII come back to Iife
And then I wiII force him
to take me to that gemstone.
You! You aren't a saint
but a sinner..
a mean person and an imposter!
You are duping the worId
disguised as a saint !
Listen to one thing very
carefuIIy, Bhairav Nath !
If you harm my husband..
If you want to save
your husband's Iife.
teII me where that gemstone is.
I wiII go away from here quietIy
And I wiII keep this secret to myseIf forever
that you aren't a woman but a snake !
Even if you teII it to the
whoIe worId, I'm not worried
After getting the gemstone, you
wiII kiII thousands of peopIe
To save their Iives, even if I
have to sacrifice my own Iife..
it doesn't matter
But I wiII neverteII you the
Iocation of the gemstone. Never
You wiII have to teII me!
RascaI! Cheater! You're supposed to
be a saint and you hit a woman!
Its good that you came
here to die on your own
You have made my work easier.
I had promised queen mother
that I wiII never Iet her
famiIy get harmed in any way.
It's time for me to prove myseIf.
There is onIy one way to save
the heir of this famiIy.
And that is to perform
his death ceremony.
Maharaj, what are you doing?
Mother!
No!
Mother! Open your eyes
What have you done
This was my Iast hope of getting
to that gemstone ! And you
You must fear God, Bhairav Nath !
It's not good for a
saint to do such deeds
Before the power of a devoted
wife turns you into ashes..
go away from here
I wiII go away but onIy
after I kiII you.
No !
Take this, Bhairav Nath. It wiII
heIp to remove the poison.
Eat it quickIy, Bhairav Nath.
You'II get saved.
You know that I was trying..
to kiII your husband and you
And you stiII want to save my Iife !
It was not you Bhairav Nath,
who wanted to kiII us
It was the demon of greed
.and pride that was within you,
which made you do this
It was the demon of greed
.and pride that was within you,
which made you do this
But I want to save that man..
who is a very accompIished
I want you to Iive.
And I want you take away the grief of
the peoIe with your saintIy powers.
Eat this
It's too Iate now !
You were right.
I have misused my powers.
I must pay for it now.
Oh God ! If you want to grant me a boon..
for my 40 year oId meditation..
I wouId onIy ask you..
to free Rajni from
this birth of a snake !
So that she can Iive with
her husband happiIy ever after
That is aII I pray for
And for your bIessings
HaiI, Lord BhoIe Nath.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org