What is this! Not again!
You see, Savitri..
How long will you go on risking
your life for your employer?
Look Savitri, we are
deeply indebted to him.
Even if I were to die for him,
I wouldn't be able to repay him.
Why risk your life like this?
Why not inform the police?
Not now. I suspect his step brother
Girdhar. But I don't know for sure..
You look for some other job.
Remember when Arjun was sick?
The doctors here had given up.
And he flew in doctors from America.
He spent hundreds of thousands!
Can we ever forget
what he did for us?
What a thing to say!
lf my son is alive today,
it's all because of Savitri.
No money is enough to
pay for a mother's milk.
Were it not for you and Savitri,
I would've been without an heir.
Why did you take the
trouble of coming here?
You could've called me over.
- The matter deserved a visit.
I have appointed Savitri
as the trustee of my will.
I?
Yes, my sister.
We live in the shadow of death.
Should anything happen to us..
..there should be
someone to look after my son.
In any case, my Raju has
taken to you like his own mother.
Mr. Mehta. - Yes. - Handover the
trust's papers to sister Savitri.
Till things change for the better..
..send Raju to live with
my friend Mathur, in London.
You've placed a grave
responsibility on our shoulders.
People might misconstrue it
and say that for your money..
I don't care what they say.
I thought it over before I did it.
Besides, who do I have but you?
- Fire..
Sir!
Savitri.. you have
to fulfill my duty.
You will have to take care
of sir's son, Rajkumar.
And you will have to bring him up..
..as your own. Even if you have to..
..sacrifice the
interests of your own son, Arjun.
I promise!
I will care for him
more than my own son!
Mr. Mehta, take Raja away from here!
But in this condition?
Just do as I say! Go away!
And that money! You
must never touch it!
Never!
Send Arjun away to his grandfather
Dashrathh Singh in Lakhanpur.
Lakhanpur?
You must complete
my responsibility!
No.
Let go of me.
I am opening it.
Dashrath Singh?
- Yes.
Your grandson. Arjun.
His father has been murdered.
Bhim Singh?
Killed?
Who killed him? Tell me!
Now I have
delivered your heir to you!
Where is his mother?
She..
- Tell me!
You shameless woman!
You are a slur on womanhood!
A woman prays to God
for her husband's life!
And you! You killed your
husband for the sake of money!
No! That isn't true!
Just get out of here!
Get out of here before
I start cursing you!
Go away! Get out, I say!
lf this be my fate,
I have to go away.
But for once! Please!
Let me embrace my son!
I won't let you go anywhere
near him! He isn't your son!
He's my heir! My blood!
You killed my son!
And I gave him to you!
Now you want my heir!
And who will give my
son back to me? Tell me!
As of today, I
cannot prove my innocence.
Let it be as you wish.
But some day, you will
know for sure. I am innocent.
But if this is what you wish..
..then I will make a sacrifice
my love for your happiness.
For your sake I will
forget that I ever bore a son!
What greater test
for a mother than this?
Then promise me that you'll never
tell him that you are his mother.
All right.
I swear on Arjun. I will never
tell him that I am his mother.
lf he ever asks for his mother..
..tell him that his mother is dead.
What brings you so early,
Mr. Mehta?
Have you seen the newspaper?
- Newspaper?
No. What is it?
- Bad news. But for us, it's good.
Plane crash? - Yes. Girdhar
died in the Pune plane crash.
Now there's no
threat to Raju's life.
lf you so wish, we can
call Raju back from London.
No. I want to give him
the best of education.
Let him take his education.
Let him stay there till..
..he is mature enough to
assume his father's mantle.
You'll fall asleep in a minute now.
Sleep.
Sleep, come into the eyes.
Sleep, come slowly.
Wake up, the sacred one.
Arjun! Arjun!
The sun is up! Get up. Hey Arjun.
No! I won't let you go!
You are my whole life!
I'm not letting you go!
- Hey Arjun! - I'm not letting..
Grandpa you?
So it was a dream!
Who were you dreaming about?
Go on. Tell Grandpa.
Don't feel shy!
Who did you see in your dream?
You.
Me.
- Yes.
In the dream, I saw
Grandpa is leaving me.
And I'm screaming,
grandpa don't leave me!
You are my whole life!
I'll die without you!
Oh no!
I thought you were
going ahead in life!
But you're just the same.
You're a young man.
And you dream of me!
There's lot more to dream about!
Lot more to dream about.. about?
You're everything to me!
I listen to you! Look up to you!
And you are all I have!
Who else can I dream about?
All of 25 years, and still a baby!
At your age, they dream of mermaids!
They sing songs, and their
eyes are bright with desire!
What about you?
I do too.
What? I like mermaids.
I love songs. And I'm
bright with desire too.
Desire? What?
Oh I want to take care of you!
And I want a big house.
And a large farm.
And I am going to feed you!
lf that's what you
dream in your youth..
..then something is
seriously wrong! - What's so wrong?
Nothing! Just get out bed.
- Remember when I was a kid?
You used to pick me out
of bed. Go on. Pick me up.
Good God! Don't
people get older with age?
I know. It must be that song.
Now on, I'll play another song.
Which one?
- Wake up to a beautiful morning!
What a shame! At your age!
What the hell do you mean?!
Never mind. Now get out of bed.
Now take you. You were a
Private when you joined the army.
And when you retired,
you were a an officer.
You've seen many lands.
You've fought so many wars.
And you've seen the world.
But your Arjun hasn't seen
anything in the village!
That's what I want to consult
you about. What do I do with him?
Send him to the city
to live with my son.
The city!
No! I've already
Lost a son in the city!
It's going to break my heart!
Sometimes you have to accept
sorrows for the sake of happiness.
You will have to bear with it.
Besides, my son
Bhairav is also in the city.
I'll write to him.
He'll find a job for Arjun.
You send him to the city.
All right.
I heard everything!
You want me to go to the city!
And Bhairav is
going to give me a job!
I'm not going anywhere!
You cared for me all my life.
And now that I'm grown up..
..you want to kick me out!
No way! I'm not going.
I can never leave you!
You want to be a
liability to me all your life?
Sure! I've been a
liability all my life!
Why do you want to
throw me out of the house?
Do you want me to get
Lost in the big bad city?
Six-foot four! And
he talks like a sissy!
How long are you going to
rot here? Go to the city.
Stand on your own feet!
- But I'm standing on my own feet!
Look at my legs!
Have you no brains?
A man is born twice.
First he is born of his mother.
Second, he goes out to the world.
And he makes a name for himself.
You must make a name for yourself.
Make me proud of my grandson!
Go on. Do something
while I'm still alive!
I haven't much time left.
My time is nearly up.
No! Don't say that!
lf your time to die comes,
I will go instead of you!
I'll tell him that I am grandpa!
You want me to go to the city?
All right. I'm going.
I'll make a name for myself.
And I'll stand on my own feet!
Happy?
God bless you, son!
- But don't talk of dying!
God bless you, dear.
Its time I told you a
well-preserved secret of my life.
You must always keep this in mind.
Son, 20 years ago, you
were in boarding school.
I was coming back to
Bombay after seeing you.
At Pune airport, I saw a man.
He was pleading desperately with
an officer for a ticket to Bombay.
A dying relative in
Bombay or something like that.
But the flight was full.
I took pity on him and
I gave him my ticket.
He thanked me profusely and he
boarded the flight to Bombay.
The flight took off on
what was it's last flight.
A few minutes later..
..the flight crashed against
the mountains of Panvel.
Everyone on board died.
And there I was. Alive.
Maybe because of that one
good deed I ever did in my life.
That ticket, you know.
I gave it to a man in need.
But my name was on the
list of the casualties.
And I took full
advantage of the slip.
To the world, I was dead.
Understood? That was the
first part of the story.
Come.
Here's the second
part of the story, son.
Daddy, this is my boss!
Not your boss! She is your servant.
No more than a servant.
This is the Sanyal hotel in
Bombay where you work as a manager.
Singapore, Hong Kong,
London, America.
You own half of all this property.
Half! What are you saying,
daddy? I own half of all this?!
No daddy. Don't joke with me!
I'm going to go insane!
Don't. And listen to me carefully.
The person who owned all this..
..was my brother.
Sanyal. He was my elder.
This is his photo.
My uncle?
He was my stepbrother.
I tried to kill him. I
also tried to kill his son.
Sanyal died. And that Bhim Singh..
..died trying to save his boss.
Bhim Singh was very loyal.
Savitri was Bhim Singh's wife.
She's the woman you call boss!
She sent my nephew into hiding.
To a place safe enough.
So that when he grows up he
can assume his father's mantle.
But she doesn't know
that I have a son too.
Daddy, I get it!
I won't spoil the opportunity
you've waited for all you life.
Till today, I've been
managing their hotel in Bombay.
But now, I'm going to
start eating at its roots.
Not as easy as you think.
Rajkumar is expected to return.
Find him before he can come back.
Find him before he
assumes his father's mantle.
Find him. And kill him.
Stand in a row.
Take this.
Aunt, why the sweets?
It's my son's birthday today.
- Where's your son?
Excuse me.
Greetings, can you tell
me where this place is?
I've just come to town.
This is my friend's address.
First right off the main road.
It's the first house.
Thanks.
- Listen.. - Yes?
Have this.
- What's this?
A sweet. For my son's birthday.
- Great! It's my birthday too!
Really?
- Yes!
But my mother is dead.
Well, never mind that.
You're just like my mother.
Thank you, mother.
Cab!
So one more adds to
the millions unemployed.
But you told me to come here
as I am educated and a grown up!
And here I am.
Very nice. But why didn't
you write to me before coming?
I hadn't a chance!
Grandpa was after my life.
He wanted me to come to
the city to stand on my feet!
So here I am. To stand on my feet.
Very good. - You'll find me a job,
won't you? - Now that you're here..
I guess something has to
be done.
I have a friend, he's a manager in
a big hotel. It's a five star hotel.
Look, I don't care.
I just want a job.
Well all right. But what
kind of a dress is this?
You forgot! I had worn this on
Rao sir's daughter's marriage too!
What could be better than this?
I guess I'm paying for your clothes!
No matter. Now go and take a wash.
I'll talk to him about you.
Here comes Arjun Singh!
Who the hell?
The moustache-man!
So you were taking snaps when
I was with that fatso's wife?
Not my neck! I don't mean ill!
Let go of my neck!
Give me the negatives.
- What negatives?
The snaps you took.
Where are the negatives?
- Inside the camera.
Where's the camera?
- On the table!
Where's the table?
- In that corner!
Which corner?
- That corner!
I'll see.
Oh my God. What are you doing?
My roll! No! Don't expose it!
What have you done!
- If you ever try..
..to shoot me while
I'm with a woman..
..I'll bury you alive!
Fool. Get it?
Just joking. Like old friends!
Greetings, sir. - Oh God,
I am done for. Greetings, sir.
Did you get the snaps?
- Yes.
Give them to me.
I'll fix my wife now.
And I'll fix that moustache-man!
That fellow has an eye
for other men's wives.
What a profound thought!
Stop staring and give me the snaps.
I got them. But something went wrong.
The snaps didn't come through.
What do you mean? I've sued my
wife on the basis of those snaps!
I've paid the lawyers!
And I paid you in advance!
And now you tell me
something went wrong!
Not my fault. The
camera malfunctioned.
Where's the lousy camera?
- On the table!
Where's the table?
- In that corner!
Which corner?
- That corner!
So is this the camera?
- Yes.
I'll make sure the camera
doesn't give you the slip!
Smashed my camera!
- Shut up! You idiot!
lf I ever see you here,
I'm going to break your legs!
Just joking. Like old friends!
Now don't get angry!
And don't go back. Please!
Or I'll be exposed.
Grandpa will get angry with me.
I'll get you a good job.
Look, there is a party today.
Now get dressed.
We're partying tonight.
Hello Tom.. Tom..
Fabulous!
Fantastic!
What is it?
- Talk in whispers here!
This is a big hotel!
Bhairav, I hope no one
is going to bash you up?
Not here! No one dares
lift a finger against me!
lf you get bashed up once again,
I'm getting into the act.
And I'll make sure I write home.
- Please! Don't do anything here!
People respect me here.
- Respect you?
Is that clear?
- Yes.
Come with me.
Being educated,
you've ruined everything.
Why? What happened?
- You were supposed to take a glass.
Not the whole tray. - I didn't
know that! What do I do now?
Give it back.
Believe me, darling! I
could never betray you!
Hello, my friend. Hello.
Friend.
My friend.
Mr. Kamdhenu! People are
waiting for you your song.
People are waiting for your song.
Please, come on. Hurry up,
come on. Come on, sing.
I can't sing. My friend will sing.
- What's the matter?
Get up.
- Let me be here.
Where were you?
- My friend.
My friend.
I can't sing today.
Sing.. - What's he saying?
- He wants.. - Actually..
I have a sore throat. I can't sing.
I touched your hand. You
are a very strong man.
I want to hear you!
I want to hear your voice!
Ladies and gentlemen,
my best friend..
..is going to sing for you today.
His name is..
What's the name?
- Arjun.
Arjun. Give him a
big hand. A big hand!
You're singing!
No, no. I am not singing.
No, I am not singing.
What are you doing?
- Sing. Sing anything you can.
Wait!
Hey, listen to me.
Hey, why are you
taking me amidst girls?
No. - What are you doing?
You sing well. So, sing.
Hey, sing anything you want to.
There are big people here.
You might land a job!
Am I going to get the job?
- As good as done.
Ladies and gentlemen, my friend
is going to sing now.
I am here. Start singing.
Yes, orchestra! Ready?
Old people told us
to stand on our feet.
Then you will
rule over this world.
Go hand in hand with
the upcoming generation.
Then you will be able
to anything you want to.
Then, look here. I am
standing on my feet.
And I've begun to get
in sync with the world.
The whole world will be amazed.
The world will be
astonished to see us.
Wonderful. Wonderful.
Thank you. Anklets in the feet.
Meera danced with
anklets in her feet.
I danced without anklets.
Meera danced with
anklets in her feet.
The arrow is of no use,
which misses its target.
With anklets in her feet.
Meera danced with
anklets in her feet.
You seem a double faced man to me.
You look like a thief to me.
You've spent your life in robbery..
..and have kept all your
happiness in locker of sins.
I feel your dream is.. praise
the lord and fill your pockets.
lf you live in this country,
be honest to it.
Be an example of
honesty for everyone.
Don't look at other's
money or other's wife.
It is a bad habit, so change it.
Because, this habit
ruins your house one day.
With anklets in her feet.
Meera danced with
anklets in her feet.
You are my little love.
Little, little love.
I am the desire
mesmerized in love.
I feel we are made for each other.
I feel, I am not thinking wrong.
I feel, you are my
own and not a stranger.
You are carved marble statue.
You are very
charming and beautiful.
You are very auspicious.
People crave for you.
I'll tear open my chest to
show your beautiful face.
Don't you think we've met before?
Your beauty, your youth,
your name are wonderful.
Why should I
bother about all that.
Listen to me.
When we meet our Romeo and
Juliet stories will begin.
Meera danced with
anklets in her feet.
I danced without anklets.
Meera danced with
anklets in her feet.
Hey Arjun, come here.
- Is my job done?
I've recommended you.
You're going to be interviewed.
I've set everything.
Now don't be nervous.
And make sure you give smart
replies to all his questions.
Don't worry at all.
Greetings, sir.
Are you out of your mind?
Who is this?
This is too much. Sir, it is me..
I'm Arjun Singh. Son of Bhim Singh.
Grandson of Dashrath Singh.
Of Lakhanpur. Intermediate passed!
I topped the exams from the village.
Back home, my grandfather
and I are the most educated.
The rest are uneducated louts.
Before I came to the city,
Grandpa taught me three lessons.
Do not covet another man's money
Do not covet another man's wife.
Be loyal to your employer.
And don't bow before injustice.
Isn't grandpa right?
- Absolutely right.
But now you're in the city.
How about a spattering of English?
In English, I can
leave the English behind!
Look, sir. I can talk English, I can
walk English, I can laugh English..
..because English is a
very funny language.
Bhairav becomes Barren and
Barren becomes Bhairav..
..because their
minds are very narrow.
In the year 1979, sir..
..when India was playing against
Australia in Melbourne city..
..Vijay Merchant and Vijay Hazare..
..at the crease and Vijay Merchant
told Vijay Hazare look Vijay Hazare..
..this is a very
prestigious match..
..and you should consider
this match very carefully.
So, considering the consideration..
..that Vijay Hazare
gave Vijay Merchant.
Vijay Merchant told Vijay Hazare
that ultimately we must take a run.
When they were striking
the ball on the left side, sir.
The consideration became..
..into an ultimatum. And ultimately
Vijay Hazare went to Vijay Merchant..
Shut up!
Listen to me, sir.
In the year 1979..
..when India was
playing against Pakistan..
..in Wankhede stadium in Bombay..
..Wasim Raja and Wasim Bari
they were on the crease.
Wasim Bari gave the same
consideration to Wasim Raja.
Wasim Raja told Wasim Bari..
..look sir.. this ultimately has
to be added as an consideration..
..which I cannot consider.
Therefore, the consideration
that you are giving me..
..must be considered
very ultimately.
Therefore, the run they were
taking, Wasim Raja told Wasim Bari..
Wasim Bari you take a run and
ultimately both of them ran and..
..considerately, they got out.
Your kind comments
on my commentary, sir?
What? - He means he'd
like your comments if any?
Not at all. Your English is fine.
And your general knowledge is okay.
Arjun Singh. Son of Bhim Singh.
Grandson of Dashrath Singh.
Okay. - May I have the job?
Sure. Now please stand outside.
Let me talk to Bhairav.
Hail the motherland.
- Hail the motherland.
Yes, sir. Someone new? A trainee?
Okay, sir. I'll show him around.
Okay, thank you.
Ms. Poonam. This is Mr. Arjun.
Mr. Ranjit has sent him to you.
I feel we are made for each other.
I feel, I am not thinking wrong.
Listen..
Ms Poonam, Mr. Ranjit has
sent him for job.. - I know.
You want a job here?
But you sing so well..
Not with standing, I need to
take care of my stomach.
Therefore the need for a job.
Come. I'll show you around.
Found himself a job and a girl too!
This is the store
room for this floor.
You do the
housekeeping every morning.
Every morning?
- Yes.
People who stay here must be dirty!
What?
- Why change every day?
What do they need fresh
sheets and towels every day?
Shall we?
This is your table.
So where do I stand?
- Stand?
I mean; my post..
- Post.
You answer any calls that come here.
And you go to the guests
who buzz you on this board.
And you ask him very politely,
What can I do for you, sir?
A buzz. - Here's a buzz. From room 666.
Come. I'll show you
how to go about it.
I think the man in this room is
like his room number. Come on.
What a surprise! I
wanted to meet you!
So I'm here.
And what can I do for you, sir?
So much!
But as of now, keep
standing and let me admire you!
Mister, I told you already.
For me, you're just a number.
666.
And I work in this hotel.
I don't work for you. Got it!
No. Don't go away. I
have a gift for you.
Look at this. Such
a pretty nose ring.
Go on. Put it on.
I'm sure you have many sisters.
Just like me.
Give it to one of them.
They will thank you.
lf you don't have sisters,
give it to your mother.
She will keep blessing you! Till
the day she dies! Understood Mr. 666!
Let's go, Ms. Poonam.
You must take good
care of this room.
Is it for someone special?
- Someone very special.
In fact, the most
special man in this city.
And who is he?
Mr. Raja. He owns the hotel.
The owner himself!
Am I glad to be of service to him!
I'm going to make this room
the best one in this hotel!
Where does he live?
- Abroad. - Okay.
That's him in the photograph.
Greetings Boss!
- Good morning, dear Raja.
Good morning, Mr. Mathur.
You're going to win the race
this time too. I'm confident.
And I'm sure. No one can beat me.
The medal goes to mummy of course.
Oh, I am sure.
Yes, Mr. Ranjit.
You know Rajkumar?
- Very well. He is here.
Finish him!
- Done.
But, price?
- 500,OOO. - 500,OOO?
Accepted?
- Okay.
Okay.
- Did you get it? - Good.
You tracked the quarry in no time.
You're a hunter, I say.
Thank you, daddy. Thank you.
I want to down two birds at a go.
Rajkumar and Ms. Savitri.
Good, good. Very good.
That's like my son.
The race is ready to go.
3, 2, 1, go!
Why do you want to kill me?
Speak!
Who are you? Who sent you? Speak up!
The letter..
- Letter?
Who were they Raja
who wanted to kill you?
Uncle Mathur, the answers
to all your questions are here..
..in this letter.
Savitri!
Mr. Mathur, why are you silent?
Tell me one thing, can a mother
ever want to kill her own son?
You'll be sorry to hear this.
Savitri isn't your mother.
What?
Yes Raja. Savitri has fostered you.
Fostered me? Only that?
Now I understand it all.
Why are you laughing, Raja?
Uncle Mathur, I want to see the woman
who wants to kill her foster-son.
Please send a telegram soon.
I'm going over.
My son is coming back after years.
I need leave. For 2 days.
Give the application to me.
It is accepted.
- Thank you.
What are you doing? Hurry up!?
- Okay, ma'am.
Nothing must be left wanting.
Everything will be in order.
I'm looking into every detail.
Hey, there on the table.
Ranjit, check the room once again
before you leave. - Okay, ma'am.
Mother, I don't get this.
You have a palatial house.
And your son wants
to live in a hotel?
My son is a bit moody.
He's a bit odd.
He'll even go hunting
tigers without a gun!
He loves to eat ice
cream when it's snowing!
Is he kind of eccentric?
Not at all. He's slightly moody.
And I thought what if..
..he wants to come to the
hotel in the middle of the night?
My word!
Raja. - Homes are for the homely
types. I'm the footloose type.
Where else but a hotel for me?
Raja! My son!
Not too hard, mother.
You could kill me.
What a thing to say!
Can a mother's embrace kill?
Everything is adulterated nowadays.
Friendship and even
love is adulterated.
What do you mean, Raja?
- Leave it mummy.
You just said I'm moody.
Never mind. I don't
care what people say.
Who are these girls?
These? They are my friends.
Friends.
Yes mummy. Friends.
What's life without friends?
I want to live it up.
Who knows when time's up?
A man needs a few friends.
To give him a decent funeral.
What are you saying?
What's gotten into you?
You see your mother after years!
And this is what you have to say!
Have you changed so much? Tell me!
I have come home after years!
And you greet me with tears!
Never mind all that.
Let's change the subject.
It's my birthday tomorrow. Tomorrow.
The 13th. What an ugly date to be born.
No fault of mine, is it?
Anyway, we must celebrate.
Well mummy, what's my birthday gift?
Whatever you want. And
whatever there is, is yours.
As long as I am alive. Afterwards,
it's yours.
Raja..
- Hey..
Yes boss?
- Who are you?
I'm just an ordinary man.
And what do you do?
I'm your loyal servant, sir!
Loyal?
- Yes, sir!
What's all this loyalty about?
No loyalties here.
This is a selfish world.
Given a chance, people will kill.
Right, mummy?
Well Mr. Loyalty, you
can do something for me.
Sure sir!
4 bottles of champagne. Chill them.
Chill? - Chill! - Chill? - Chill.
- Chilled. - Understood?
Put them in ice.
- Okay, sir.
Well mummy, see you tomorrow.
But you were supposed
to be here tomorrow!
Are you in trouble seeing me here
today? Has the atmosphere changed?
Yes sir, no sir, I mean sorry sir.
And who are you?
- I'm Ranjit. Your manager.
My manager?
- I mean I manage your hotel, sir.
Very smart.
- Thank you, sir.
Manager, do one thing, give the
best suites for my guests here.
And the best hospitality.
- Understood sir!
Please come.
- Very smart. - Please. - Idiot.
May I say something, madam?
I didn't quite understand
the mother-son exchange.
Do you have a mother?
- No.
Then you needn't bother.
And mind your own business.
My son mustn't have any complaints.
Yes ma'am.
Sir, many, many happy
returns of the day. - Thank you.
Please cut the cake.
I'm in no hurry. 2 minutes 45
seconds to go before I was born.
It was up in no time. Come on now.
Come.
- You leave, I'll be there.
Owner of the dog!
- What did you say?!
I mean, is the dog yours?
- Yes.
This isn't your
dog's birthday party!
He's eating the cake!
He has ruined the party!
Sorry for the inconvenience.
- Sorry doesn't get the cake back!
Why didn't you train
your dog not to eat cake?
Lousy dog!
Manager, whose birthday
is it? Mine? Or the dog's?
It's your birthday sir, but..
But sir it has turned
out to be his death day!
What happened to it?
It ate your birthday cake and..
You've killed my dog!
The cake is poisoned!
No more partying with dogs!
Thank God the dog ate
your cake, otherwise..
Anyway I'll make the
baker close his shop!
I'll ruin his business!
I'll destroy his family!
I'll hang him for this!
I'll give him to the police!
Manager, the dog is dead now.
Stop barking. - Sorry sir.
Who ordered the cake?
Your mother told me..
I mean I ordered it.
You say you manage this hotel?
- Yes, sir.
Brilliant management!
- Thank you, sir.
Shut up.
- Sorry, sir. - Nonsense.
Get hold of another cake. And
send it to my room. - Yes, sir.
Make sure this one
doesn't go to the dogs.
You will eat it. Before I do.
- No, sir. Yes, sir.
Saw that mummy? I told
you 13th is ominous!
That cake wasn't meant for the dog.
I'm the one who was
supposed to die. Like a dog.
Anyway, I'm ready
for any eventuality.
Come on, mother. Cheer up.
It's nothing. Cheers everyone!
Let's have fun. The
party continues in my room.
Come on, everyone
into my room. Come on.
Don't weep, mother.
That was a perfect plot. To
kill him. And implicate you.
God willing, I will
never let that happen to you.
What do you mean?
- Ma'am it is very clear.
Give everything to me
that you've stolen inside.
You mean I'm a thief!
- Worse. You're a pickpocket!
Just give it to me.
Else, I'll thrash you!
Arjun Singh, why are you screaming?
- Sir, this..
Look Mr. Raja, your man
was trying to molest you!
What?
- Idiot! How dare you?!
Boss!
I'm working for you. And I am loyal.
That's why my hands are tied.
Else I could've given
you a fitting reply.
Now how about a sample
of her lady-like virtues?
See her wonders too. Come here.
There you see?
These dare-bare dresses conceal..
..more than meets the eye!
Are you leaving, Arjun Singh?
- Yes.
What if I won't let you leave?
- No. I won't do this job.
Even grandpa hasn't ever slapped me.
And you slapped me!
For that disgraced woman!
It was my humanity that
I didn't give a fitting reply..
..otherwise I could
have hit you back too.
You cannot appreciate loyalty.
Besides, I wouldn't like to
serve a man who has scant respect..
..for his mother. - She's not my
mother. She is just my foster-mother.
Fostered you? The woman
who has fostered you..
..has given you more
than the woman who bore you.
The one who has kept you alive
is the mother who fostered you.
Lord Krishna was born of Devki.
But Yashoda reared him.
That's why so much is spoken
of Lord Krishna's foster mother.
We are just humans.
She wants to kill me for my money.
Will a mother who has given
you this priceless gift of love..
..ever yearn for your riches?
No one else gains from my death.
Who else might want to kill me?
Several attempts have been
made on my life already.
Do you remember? That
cake laced with poison.
You don't understand anything.
- Boss!
Boss, I think I'm
beginning to understand.
Where are you going?
- I'm not going anywhere..
..until I have found out
who wants to kill you.
Arjun Singh, now onwards,
consider yourself my friend..
..and not an employee.
Hello!
C'mon Ms. Poonam,
I'll drop you home.
I don't think I've
forgotten my way home.
Or maybe you want to know?
Nothing like that.
- Then please don't waste my time.
Someone is waiting for me. Get it?
It's about to rain.
Come. Let me drop you home.
Not necessary, thank you.
What's unnecessary for you,
might be necessary for me.
Think about me from
your heart sometimes!
Mind your language.
I can control my language but
how do I control my desires?
Come.
- Hey, let go of her.
Hey, come on.
- Help.
You aren't hurt, are you?
Did he hit you?
You should use the stick on him.
- Please! Help Poonam!
Rajesh.
- Poonam, Poonam!
Are you all right, Poonam?
I'm fine. Are you all right?
Got you at last!
A ladies' man, are you?
You broke the lamp post.
Now municipality people
will apprehend you.
On your feet, you fatso.
Hey, where are you taking that
cart? Want to go there, okay. Go.
You've ruined all the oranges.
What's this?
I see!
Mr. Nathulal! This is
that same nose ring, right!
Want me to put it on your nose?
Passed out!
Come in.
- Please come in.
This is our home.
This is the first time
this gentleman has come home.
How about tea and snacks?
- All right, brother.
Come.
Brother?
I should be leaving.
Please stay for tea.
I'm quite full. Excuse me.
Please be seated.
Please tell Poonam I'll
be here some other time.
Why did he leave all of a sudden?
I don't know.
But he's a fine gentleman.
Hey, no!
lf I am bowled over today,
don't wake me up.
lf I slip today, don't pick me up.
lf you do so.
lf you do so, then
you'll be bowled over.
Even you'll slip.
lf I am bowled over today,
don't wake me up.
This rain is unique.
It has rained like
this for the first time.
This rain is unique.
It has rained like
this for the first time.
The breeze is
lighting fire in water.
My body is craving.
Your wet body makes
me yearn for you.
I am getting intoxicated.
I don't know where I am.
Don't get me into
senses if I get intoxicated.
Even if you do so..
Even if you do so, then
you'll get intoxicated too.
lf I am bowled over today,
don't wake me up.
The lightening struck
many times in the sky..
..but this is the first time,
it struck to my heart.
The lightening struck
many times in the sky..
..but this is the first time,
it struck to my heart.
Scared girl, she has come
close to me and has embraced me.
You are enjoying it.
I am very restless.
Beloved, where are
you going stealthily?
Don't explain if I am confused.
lf you do so..
lf you do so, then
even you'll be confused.
lf I am bowled over today,
don't wake me up.
The clouds are raining liquor.
The breeze is raining youth.
The drops are chiming.
The rain is singing a song.
It is making me yearn.
Our hearts united. The
environment became colourful.
You hearts met each other.
Whatever had to happen has
happened, why do you fear?
Don't save me if I drown.
lf you do so..
lf you do so, then
even you'll drown.
lf I am bowled over today,
don't wake me up.
lf I slip today,
don't pick me up.
Are you blind? Can't you see?!
Boss!
Bravo Arjun Singh, great!
Get on with it!
After the formalities.
Let me drop you.
No! This trailer is
good enough for us.
Let's go, Poonam.
What a time to go on an inspection!
We are leaving, sir.
Arjun Singh! Arjun Singh!
Arjun Singh!
Who is this Arjun Singh?
He's becoming an obstacle!
He has bashed up Devaa!
He stopped Rajkumar just when
he was about to eat the cake!
He reminds me of Bhim
Singh and his loyalty.
Forever trying to
protect Sanyal like a shield!
It's as if Bhim Singh has
been born all over again!
Daddy, please relax.
You need not worry.
I've come up with such a plan..
..that not even Arjun's father
can save Rajkumar!
Keep your plans to yourself!
And pay attention!
Just look how
easily I kill Rajkumar!
lf not by the sword,
he will die for love.
I don't understand, daddy.
- There's a beauty.
She specializes in seduction.
A honey-trap to death.
What? Another prey?
Not another prey. Another kill.
What?
- This one is to be killed.
You mean, finish him.
Yes.
- But mummy, we've never done that.
Let's do it now.
Don't know why mother..
..every night is a horror for me.
Not to be afraid.
There's always a tomorrow.
Time to get into the act.
Sir, this lady is a
famous cabaret artiste.
Every hotel she has worked in
has turned out to be a winner.
She's coming to us. We're lucky!
Here comes a dancing girl who
promises to seduce her audience.
And you say this is lucky for us?
- Yes, sir.
The hell with it!
Do we depend on
dancing girls for luck?
Let her come. Let her dance.
And let her move on.
That was a cheap thing to say.
Go away.
I told you to leave!
Excuse me, sir. But she is here.
- Who is here?
Miss Nisha.
- Is that why you're so effusive?
Please meet her. For once.
You don't seem to understand
what I'm trying to tell you.
A matter of mere formalities, sir.
Well all right. I'll deal with your
mere formalities. - Thank you, sir.
Give her the flowers.
Not you. You've gone
overboard already.
You.. what's your name?
- Arjun Singh, sir!
Yes Arjun Singh. Deliver the
flowers to that dancer. - Okay, sir.
And why are you still here?
Get me the London call, quick.
- Right. - Hurry up. - Right, sir.
Who are you?
- What?
I'm Arjun Singh. Son of Bhim Singh.
Grandson of Dashrath Singh.
You don't know what you should
do before entering someone's room?
No I don't know what is
to be done before..
..or after entering
someone's rule.
You should knock the door.
Those doors that are
already ajar cannot be knocked.
Besides how could I when
my hands are occupied.
What is this?
Bouquet.
- For whom?
For you.
From whom?
- The boss.
Doesn't he have any etiquette?
He sends a servant with flowers!
Are flowers any less fragrant
because they are sent by a servant?
Take it!
It's the whole bunch of them.
People get away with less.
A whole bunch of flowers for you.
Wait.
- Yes.
You wait here.
For your boss. From me.
Sure.
Listen..
- Yes. - Give this to him too.
Okay.
I see!
- And a letter.
A letter too?
- Letter.
After searching for so many years,
I've found this from garden of life..
..if you want I'll present..
..a few thorns for you.
With best regards.
You sent me what you had.
I'm sending you what I had.
I must say I like this!
Arjun Singh. - Yes boss? -
You just met her, didn't you?
What does she look like? - Sir,
as far as looks are concerned..
..she's just what I thought.
- Just what you thought?
Then she must be pretty.
I'll make sure I see her.
What time is her show?
- At nine.
At nine?
Hello. I want to kill you.
I will kill you.
Young beloved and
beautiful girlfriend.
When they unite, they
fall for each other.
Young beloved and
beautiful girlfriend.
When they unite, they
fall for each other.
The hunter is here but
prey is already dead.
What an injustice is this?
How and when did it happen?
Neither I know nor him.
Young beloved and
beautiful girlfriend.
When they unite, they
fall for each other.
Your beloved has come from..
..a long distance.
Your beloved has..
..been depressed.
Their eyes met.
The effect was intoxicating.
There eyes met and
everything changed.
I've been hit by my own arrow.
How and when did it happen?
Neither I know nor him.
Young beloved and
beautiful girlfriend.
When they unite, they
fall for each other.
The hunter is here but
the prey is already dead.
What an injustice is this?
How and when did it happen?
Neither I know nor him.
Look, what state you..
..come to in love.
Look, what state
you come to in love.
Found a beloved.
What an injustice.
Enemy became my beloved.
I love the one I used to hate.
How and when did it happen?
Neither I know nor him.
Young beloved and
beautiful girlfriend.
When they unite, they
fall for each other.
The hunter is here and
the pre is already dead.
What an injustice is this?
How and when did it happen?
Neither I know nor him.
Fabulous!
You sing very well.
I don't want to prolong
this conversation unnecessarily..
..by thanking you.
But the fact is that
I do sing very well.
May I see you to your room?
- No thank you.
That pretext may be used
to get inside my room.
I'm used to living alone.
I feel suffocated when
someone else enters my room.
Very well. What are you
doing tomorrow evening?
Do you want to interview me
for a magazine or a newspaper?
I was just asking..
It is better if you do not ask.
I'm here to perform.
Not to tell you how I
occupy myself in the evenings.
Before we part.. how about
a good night or something?
I would've wished you if there
was anything good about the night.
Who knows what the night holds?
Boss! Maybe you need this?
- You.. - Take this, sir.
Arjun..
- Come, sir. Come.
One minute. One minute. Move back.
Open sesame!
Come. Careful. One minute.
Close sesame!
Let's go, sir.
Arjun Singh, did you see that?
I saw it all. And what I saw
is more than what meets the eye!
Such grace!
- That is what I'm saying!
Such poise!
Brilliant danseuse!
- That is what I'm saying!
What?
- Hey.. - Yes.
lf you're the one who says all that,
I'll have very little else to say!
That is what I'm saying, sir!
- What?!
I'm saying what you said and
you are saying what I said!
Yes?
- Yes!
Yes!
Beautiful. Good decoration. Good..
Good food,
marvelous, beautiful hotel.
Good evening sir. - I want a
room that's as beautiful as you are.
Excuse me sir, do you
have a reservation, sir?
Grandpa!
Hey, my grandpa.
Hey, who are you?
- How did you come here, grandpa?
My grandpa is here!
Hey move, move! What are you doing?
Grabbing my feet
and grabbing my neck!
Sweety, is this the way you greet
your guests who come to your hotel?
Only he embraces and not some girl?
Sorry sir,.
Arjun, what are you doing?
Grandpa! It's me! It's me! It's me!
That I can see.
It is you! It is you! You!
But the question is
who the hell are you?
I am your grandson, grandpa.
Grandson! What's this now?
Never mind. What
happened to your big moustache?
Next you'll ask me
what happens to my tail!
Stop joking. Now where are you
coming from? From the village?
Village. Oh! You mean village.
Oh idiot, where are your spectacles?
Do I look like I'm
coming from a village?
Does my luggage look
like it is from village?
I am coming to India all the way
from France, Japan, and Italy.
Now get lost.
Sweety, I called you from
Delhi asking for a reservation.
Enough is enough, grandpa.
It's too much now. Stop joking.
Let go of me! Are you drunk?
Crazy guy, making a scene here.
Stop it, Arjun! Now
don't create a scene.
He's the one who
is creating a scene!
He dyes his hair and he wears a suit
and he pretends to be someone else!
But he's really my grandfather!
- I'm nobody's grandfather!
What grandfather? Whose grandfather?
Neither am I your
grandfather nor anyone else's.
Is that clear?
Excuse me sir! Your name please!
Dashrath Singh. Son
of Sankata Prasad.
I'm no Prasad. I have not come here
from a temple. Take my name down.
San Francisco Albert
Contino D'costa Rodrigo.
Here you are, sir. Room number 616.
Arjun, he's your guest.
Take his luggage.
It means, he will be on
the same floor where I am.
Oh mister, this is the last warning.
Don't you ever call me
grandpa again. Get it?
I get it, sir. I get it.
Oh Sweety!
Bye, bye. Bye.
- Bye.
Welcome, sir.
- Thank you.
This is your room. Your
bedroom is over there.
I'll get your luggage.
Thank you. Very good.
Radio.
Good, good.
Keep it there.
Sir. Sir, what are you doing?
You might get a slip disc.
Who me? But the
girls just love my style!
But your music is third class.
Not worth a jive.
Please check your
Luggage and let me leave.
I haven't ever counted my millions.
And you want me to check my luggage?
As you please, sir.
- Listen.
What is it grandpa?
Sorry.
What's on the menu? - Punjabi
rolls. Kashmiri flavoured rice.
South Indian dishes.
- What a shame!
And Shammi Kebabs a from Lucknow.
- I don't want that junk.
I want inter-continental dishes.
So that..
Please use your phone.
Dial 3. For room service.
Please ask for anything you want.
Listen.
- Yes?
What about something to drink?
- Tea, coffee and yogurt-shake.
Yogurt-shakes are meant
for doddering old men!
I want something for
the younger generation!
Whiskey, rum, gin!
Call the police station
for doorstep deliveries.
Police station?
- I mean the bar. - Listen.
Yes.
What about the other thing?
What?
The other thing!
- Which thing? Who?
This!
You mean snuff? It's available
at the tobacconists' downstairs.
I'll have it sent up.
- Listen!
I don't need old age stuff.
What I need is a young girl.
Girl?
- Yes.
You want a girl?
Feel ashamed. Look at you!
You want a girl!
I'm about as old as your grandson!
And you're old enough..
..to be my grandfather!
- Not again!
How many times have I told you
not to mention your grandfather!
And I won't! I won't bring
my grandfather to shame!
My grandfather is a million
times better than you are!
Shut up!
- You shut up!
I care two hoots for the likes
of you! Get it you old fool?
Old fool?
- Yes! A drunken old fool!
You're just a
dirty old man! Old man!
You could never be my
grandfather you lousy old fool!
Wait.
Knocking at 3 a.m. Is
this a hotel or hermitage?
Wait.
It's 3 a.m. Is this any time
to come knocking? What is it?
You can't be my grandfather.
Yes, it is me.
No. Please don't take any action.
I'll be up directly.
Sir, I am really sorry.
I apologize on Arjun's behalf
if he has given you any trouble.
No! Call the manager! The manager!
lf you complain against him,
he will be fired.
He deserves to be fired!
- Please! Arjun is a very nice man.
lf you stay here for a few days,
you too will begin to like him.
You too!
What do you mean by 'too?'
I mean you will have a
soft corner for him.
So you have a soft
corner for him 'too?'
Yes, I mean no.
But he's very sympathetic.
No one can dislike him.
Who can dislike someone who
is upright and loyal? Right?
So who do you have at home?
My brother and I. He's blind.
And you take care of your brother?
Who else is there? And women
are born to care for others.
My work is done. Wonderful.
I'll tell my grandson I want him
to find a girl who's just like you!
lf he marries anyone else,
I'll beat him very badly!
Thank you, dear. You can go.
I won't complain
against that tall man.
Thank you so much, sir.
Listen.
- Yes.
God bless you!
Thank you, sir.
Good morning, sir.
Where's that tallish captain?
You mean Arjun Singh?
- Yes.
It's his birthday today.
Birthday?
But how can it be his birthday?
- It is. He's celebrating.
Where?
- In the staff quarters.
I see. You may leave.
Where does Arjun Singh live?
- You want a drink?
I am asking you, where does
Arjun Singh live? - The girls?
They are in there. With Arjun.
Are you invited too?
Shut up!
Julie! I've warned you!
To love me and enjoy..
..but don't become pregnant!
Why the hell are you pregnant?
What's going to happen to me?
You'll marry me, won't you?
Marry! Marry! Marry!
Get this clear! As long as
that grandpa of mine is alive..
..I can never marry one of you!
Just wait for him to die.
I'll inherit his property.
And then I'll sell the land.
And build a four-storied house
with the money. For you girls!
The first floor is for Julie.
The second floor is for Rano.
The third floor is Sheela's.
The fourth is for Jawano!
And the ground floor
is going to be mine!
Everything in the house
is going to be automatic!
And we'll have fun!
Just wait for that old fool to die!
What's the guarantee that he'll die?
Full guarantee!
What if he still doesn't die?
- He will! For sure he will!
He will surely die.
I have faith in God! Trust in me.
Grandpa has never
denied me anything.
And you girls choose this
day to pick a fight with me!
Have you forgotten
that today is my birthday!
You mean, birthday?
- Yes, it is my birthday.
Happy birthday.
- It is my birthday.
Thank you.
You aren't going to drink tonight.
- Why not?
I'm going to get drunk
and make others drink too.
Julie! Get the bottle!
Sheela! The soda!
Rano! Fetch water.
And Jamalo! The ice!
Quick!
Bobby!
- Yes, ma'am.
Whisky!
- Soda!
Water!
- Ice!
On the double!
- Coming up!
Listen.
- Yes.
On a man's birthday, you
have to feed him fruit..
..butter and buttermilk.
Why whisky?
Oh I forgot!
I'll get it right now.
I am just drunk a bit.
Haven't done any crime.
O Julie, O Sheila, O Rano, Jamalo.
Somebody stop me and support me.
See that I don't fall.
I am just drunk a bit.
Haven't done any crime.
O Julie, O Sheila, O Rano, Jamalo.
Somebody stop me and support me.
See that I don't fall.
I am just drunk a bit.
Haven't done any crime.
I too know that drinking is bad.
Why shouldn't I,
this night is exotic?
I too know that drinking is bad.
Why shouldn't I,
this night is exotic?
When surrounded
by beautiful girls.
O Julie, O Sheila, O Rano, Jamalo.
Somebody stop me and support me.
See that I don't fall.
I am just drunk a bit.
Haven't done any crime.
My ways are different
from that of the world.
I have nothing to
do with this world.
My ways are different
from that of the world.
I have nothing to
do with this world.
Don't know why
people are angry with me.
O Julie, O Sheila, O Rano, Jamalo.
Somebody stop me and support me.
See that I don't fall.
I am just drunk a bit.
Haven't done any crime.
I am done for.
Little intoxicated by your youth.
Besides intoxication of your love.
This intoxication
has taken me high.
Don't stare at me
and make me restless.
See that I don't fall.
I am just drunk a bit.
Haven't done any crime.
Beloved, listen to me,
don't get angry. Come embrace.
See that I don't fall.
I've fallen.
Listen.
Julie.
- Hi Arjun! Happy birthday.
I came uninvited.
It was your birthday and you
didn't invite me, did you?
Not really my birthday.
As of now, was celebrating my
birthday and now it's my funeral.
Everything kind of misfired.
It's love, it's a bit
painful in the beginning.
And afterwards?
It's worse.
Why are you weeping?
Arjun just put up that act.
Just an act?
He was singing and dancing with
them! And you say it's an act?
That's just what it was. For me.
To irritate me.
To draw me out in the open.
In the open?
I've been putting up an act.
As Alberto D'costa Rodriguez.
I'm no Alberto etc. I'm his grandpa.
Grandpa?
I'm his grandfather.
For him, I am a mother.
And a father.
I mean everything to him. And he's
my sole support. The apple of my eye.
I love him so!
Then why did you do all this?
He is very innocent. He
doesn't know the ways of the world.
I wanted him to see
what the world is like.
I wanted him to stand on his feet.
As between us, we can't
live without each other.
But life teaches otherwise.
In the end, we always part.
How long can I possibly live?
But now I know that my boy has
learnt the ways of the world.
He is able enough.
All I want to do is take
him back to the village.
I'll give you a grand marriage!
The house feels so empty.
With you and Arjun around,
things will be livelier.
God bless you!
Ms. Poonam..
- Yes.
That tallish man who
works in your hotel..
Yes. What is it?
- He has been run over by a bus.
My boy!
Tears in your eyes, sir?
Look son, play any joke. Not this.
Not this joke with an old man!
But you aren't old! You're young,
Mr. Albert D'costa Rodriguez!
And what are you doing in here?
Just sauntered in, have you?
You know what my grandpa says?
Two men can't share one woman.
It's either Mr.
D'costa or I. Choose.
Aren't you ashamed to talk like
this in front of your grandfather?!
What grandfather? Whose grandfather?
What's this about your grandfather?
All right. You win. I lose.
San Francisco Albert Coutinho
D'costa Rodriguez? Or aren't you?
He's dead! Run over by your bus.
I'm your grandpa!
What about whisky?
I've never sipped
a drink in my life!
I was drinking sacred
water by mixing color in it.
Dear, this old man has
been suffering within.
Come to me, son. Let me embrace you.
For once! Let me embrace you!
Grandpa!
Did you ever think of
the quandary I was in?
You walk into that hotel
and you start asking..
..for whisky, you ask me for girls!
And all night I didn't sleep!
I was so disturbed!
Back home, every time I had a cold,
you'd call all the doctors!
Everyone in the
village used to be worked up!
My dear!
And you come here, and you
don't even ask about my welfare!
That's when I swore it.
lf you're the grandpa, then
I'm the grandson! No less!
I took it as a challenge to
bring you out in the open.
You've made me feel
so miserable, grandpa!
You've made me cry.
So that you won't be
miserable ever again!
Let's go back home now.
I came here empty-handed.
I'm going back with
my grandson's bride!
Not now.
Why not?
You told me that I must be loyal.
My boss is in danger.
I can't go back till
I have repaid him.
lf that be the case,
then I'm with you!
Mummy!
- Take her mother away.
You see, the matter
is out of your hand.
There's no going back now.
Do what I want you to do.
I'll let her go.
Else she dies.
Raja dies too.
And you're going to be framed.
So what do you think?
Good.
Greetings, miss Nisha!
Mr. Raja sends you this bouquet.
Didn't he come along?
No, Mr. Raja is
running a temperature..
..401 degrees. So, he couldn't come.
- 401 ?!
I meant 104. 104!
What is the matter? You look sad?
Does Mr. Raja's
absence spoil your party?
I mean, look at this.
Such a grand party!
It's all a waste, is it?
- Not at all. The party goes on.
What does Mr. Raja
think of himself?!
So what if he's rich? He's
is flying in the fifth heaven!
Ms. Nisha, it is actually the
seventh heaven. - Shut up, please.
Now don't lose your temper.
He's just joking.
How could I not come?
You invited me!
For you, I'd walk out of my grave!
Have you had your say?
Anything else?
The hangman would talk like that.
Asking for a last wish.
Lots more. There's more to life!
Then there is death.
I have a lot to say!
And a lot to hear!
But now..
Well what?
The night is still alive..
..and so is our conversation.
Let anything happen.
The night is still alive
and so is our conversation.
Let anything happen.
Don't think, just see.
Beloved, just
look at me with love.
Don't think, just see.
Beloved, just look at me with love.
The night is still alive..
..and so is our conversation.
Let anything happen.
Heart, full of desires
struggles to contain its emotions.
The destination
of love is nearing.
Heart, full of desires
struggles to contain its emotions.
The destination
of love is nearing.
Come, see..
..the fun of..
..losing your heart in love.
The night is still alive..
..and so is our conversation.
Let anything happen.
Don't think, just see.
Beloved, just
Look at me with love.
No!
I won't let Raja die!
Whom? What happened to you?
You're sweating.
Whose death is it?
Mine? My life and my
death are in your hands.
People in love
aren't afraid of death.
The beginning is so beautiful,
why fear the result.
Lovers don't fear death.
The beginning is so beautiful,
why fear the result.
Lovers don't fear death.
Come, beloved..
..embrace your lover.
The night is still alive..
.. and so is our conversation.
Let anything happen.
Don't think, just see.
Beloved, just
Look at me with love.
Don't think, just see.
Beloved, just
Look at me with love.
The night is still alive..
..and so is our conversation.
Let anything happen.
Raja sir, please to step aside.
What is it?
The night is alive and
so is the conversation.
There's more to this
than meets the eye.
Stay here. Let me find out more.
lf I don't come back alive,
don't tell grandpa I'm dead.
Arjun Singh!
Manager, what's going on?
Come with me!
Miss Nisha!
lf anything happens to Arjun Singh,
I'm going to kill you!
Boss!
Boss, nothing happened to me!
Something could've happened.
But I didn't let it happen!
Here you are.
- Who is he?
A crocodile! Son of a crocodile!
He was waiting for you.
With a knife.
And there I transpire.
And he takes me for you.
My leg was in his hand and
his neck was in my hand.
He grabs my foot! I grab his neck.
Sometimes I over him and..
..sometimes he's over me.
Sir, in this chaos..
..I ripped his mask off!
And then I ask him, who are you?
Where have you come from? Are
you amphibious, or terrestrial?
But he's dumbstruck.
And when I was bringing him to you..
..he took out a pill from somewhere.
And this is the result!
Who might it be?
Sir, this..
No. How do I tell you? His
soul has already departed.
That leaves your friend. Your
well-wisher. The light of your eyes!
Miss Nisha! She is the
only one who can tell us.
It was her party after all.
And..
So this is what you really are!
But you aren't going to kill me.
I fell in love with you. And
in you, I looked for life!
But you were for sale!
Going to the highest bidder!
And you're fascinated
with death, aren't you?
Take this and shoot yourself.
Set the good soul free
from these evil trappings.
lf you can't help yourself,
I will have to.
Mr. Raja.
All I want to hear from you is
the passing of your last breath.
I am not sorry to die. What makes
me sad is that I found the man..
..I looked for all my life. In you.
And all of a sudden, I lose you!
I know you don't believe me.
But this is for your sake.
Let me live a while longer.
I will protect you.
I guess I'm destined to kill you.
I will not let you commit the sin.
Arjun Singh! What is this?!
Bullets. I emptied her gun.
Otherwise, she wouldn't
have spilled the beans.
By now, she'd be gone.
And with her the names of
those who intend to kill you.
You know Miss Nisha, Grandpa says..
..don't kill a sinner.
Slay the Satan within.
And you know the
names of these Satans.
The ones who want to kill Raja.
Please give us the names.
Your demons will be exorcised.
Believe me! I know nothing!
I haven't met them.
All I've heard is a voice.
A woman's voice.
A woman's voice?
Yes. - Hear that?! A woman's voice!
It's Savitri mother!
Who else can it be?!
Boss!
Boss, I don't know why
this happens to me..
..every time you mention my mother!
The effect is electric!
Do me a favor. Don't accuse
her until you have the evidence!
You want evidence?! Okay.
Here's proof. I found it on a
man who was about to kill me.
It explains itself.
Read it! Have you
anything else to say?
Mother!
What? But how could it be?!
No, no Mr. Mehta! I
couldn't be! He's still alive!
Find out, why is he alive till now.
Okay.
- Yes.
You?
I'm here at an inappropriate
moment? You thought I'm dead.
Mission accomplished, did you think?
But I'm alive. Sorry to
have ruined your plans.
Who were you shouting at?
Who is this assassin?
Every time you wag a finger,
he's after my life!
Tell him if he's man enough,
he will face me!
Call him!
What are you saying, Raja?
You expect me to kill you?
Can a mother kill her son?
Whose mother?
I know everything! Stop acting.
My mother is dead.
And you are the one
who killed my father!
You must've seduced him and..
Raja, what did you say today!
You've insulted me!
You insult my loyalty!
You've humiliated me today.
I sacrificed so much
to live to this day!
My husband gave his life!
My family was destroyed!
My son taken away from me!
For the money!
I know everything about you!
What did you and
your husband sacrificed?
Your husband, that Bhim
Singh deserted his father!
He left his home in Lakhanpur.
And why did he marry you?
Because you and your
husband wanted to loot my father!
My husband was loyal.
When he was dying..
..he extracted a promise from me.
That I must protect you..
..be it even at the
cost of my own son!
Give him his rights.
Because of you, my
father-in-law hates me.
He took my son away from me.
He threw me out!
And he made me promise
that I must never reveal..
..the secret to my son! I
cannot tell my son who he is!
And all my life, I
have lived for you!
And today, you call me greedy!
Go, my son.
Lord, preserve you!
I was born poor.
I've worked for a living.
Wealth means little to me.
Everything here, all
this wealth belongs to you!
May the fires of Hell
consume the wealth..
..that threatens my own life!
I don't want anything!
I'll sell everything!
Each and every thing!
I'll sell it all!
Madam..
Arjun! Raja wants to
sell everything off!
He has a death wish!
Stop him, Arjun!
He won't listen to me! He hates me!
Don't let him sell anything!
It'll be the end of everything!
I won't be able to keep my promise!
I beg of you!
- Hey Mother..
What are you doing?
No mother, these
hands are not to beg.
Your hands are to be
raised in blessing!
Mother. I remember telling
you that my mother is no more.
I was mistaken mother!
My mother is standing
right in front of me!
You had promised your husband.
Today, your son is promising you.
I will not let him
sell anything, mother.
I won't let him
I won't let the boss sell anything!
I swear it by my father! I
won't let him sell anything!
I will not let him sell anything!
I won't let him
sell anything, mother.
Yes, I lied to you till
now that your mother is dead.
You want to know the truth?
- Then listen.
She took my son away
from me! Your father.
No, Grandpa. My mother
could never do that.
The woman who has sacrificed
everything for the sake of others..
..could never have done this.
It's nothing more than hearsay.
Why, Grandpa? Why did you
take me away from my mother?
You have denied me my
mother's love! Tell me.
Have I not given you love?
- Yes. You gave me all your love.
But today.. I heard
someone speak ill of my mother.
And she wept! And I
couldn't even console my mother!
And all this because of what
you taught me. About loyalty.
All I could do was watch silently.
But let me tell you something.
After what I've seen and heard..
..in my place you would
begin to respect her too.
Let Rajkumar sell his hotels..
..why are you so worried?
- We might lose the hotels.
And who do you think is
going to buy the hotels? Our men.
Nice to know you gentlemen.
You are here to bid
for this hotel? - Yes.
You see, my boss is a bit eccentric.
Before you, there have
been men of wealth and worth..
..who wanted to buy this hotel.
But the boss shooed them out.
But this hotel is unique, for sure.
So I guess you will have to put
up with Mr. Rajkumar's tantrums.
And what are we expected to do?
Just do as he does.
Stand up if he stands up.
When he pulls this chair back,
you pull your chairs back too.
When he sits down, you sit down too.
lf he sneezes, you sneeze too.
When he scratches his nose, be
sure to scratch your nose too!
And when he clears his throat..
- We do too!
Mr. Arjun, sir is here.
Sir is here, so
everyone be ready now.
Hello!
- Hello!
How are you?
- How are you?
Fine, thank you.
- Fine, thank you.
Strange!
- Strange!
Arjun Singh! What's going on?
Please go ahead, sir.
Yes.
- Yes.
Let's cut the
drama and start eating.
Please go ahead.
I'll take care of them.
A fly?
- A fly!
Arjun Singh! You know I hate flies!
Not to worry, sir.
I'll take care of the fly.
Got her, Boss!
I caught it. Where is it?
Shameless, idiot.
- What nonsense!
Sir, not you, but was
telling it to that fly.
This man doesn't tolerate
the hair on his own head!
And you dare sit
right on top of his head!
Don't you move, sir! Don't move.
This fly is an insult!
I'll break her head!
Oh no! There she is! The bitch!
You know what you're sitting on?
That's Mr. Talwar's nose!
Mr. Talwar!
You know what will happen
to you if you annoy him?
Sir, don't move. Not even a bit.
I'll take her!
Now where is she?
You're going to find
me wherever you go!
Look at her now!
Mr. Kirorimal's whiskers
are worth a million each!
Does she think it's a
place to go picnicking?
Don't you move, sir!
Don't move.
I caught it.
A tooth!
Sir.. take it, your property..
But where's the fly?
There you are!
Beware! Don't you move, sir!
No matter what, but today
I'll surely kill that fly.
That's how they run scoundrel!
They want your hotel, do they?
Sir. If this hotel goes on the
block, I'll be ashamed of myself!
Arjun singh!
- Sir! Don't you move!
I won't move, sir.
Sir, don't sell the hotel!
Poonam, tell me fast! Do you
recognize the handwriting?
I think I know.
It looks just like the manager's.
It's Mr. Ranjit's handwriting.
Give it to me.
That's half the job done!
Arjun Singh!
Tell me, Mr. Zalim(cruel) Singh.
- Zalim Singh?
Are you out of your mind?
I'm Ranjit Singh!
- Never mind your name.
I'd rather call you Mr. Villain.
- Just a little thing.
What nonsense!
No nonsense, Mr. Villain. I
appreciate your handwriting.
It's beautiful! Excellent!
Whether it's a note in
a file, or a letter..
..the handwriting remains the same!
But.. wonderful!
The letter is signed by the lady.
But it's the villain's handiwork!
Now what, Arjun Singh?
- Here..
You can have another.
Burn as many as you want.
And I'll produce more.
But take care, you
might burn your fingers..
..your hopes of making it rich
quick might be dashed! - Yes.
What do you want?
All I want you to understand is..
..I want to become
rich too. Just like you.
So I came here looking for a deal.
What deal?
Rajkumar's death.
You have been trying to kill him.
And I have always saved him.
Pardon me for saying this,
you couldn't even touch him.
lf I was in your shoes, I would
see that even you would be benefited.
Yes. So it's best
for us to join hands.
Partnership. Fifty-fifty.
Arjun Singh, if I accept
your proposal, what do I gain?
At last you speak your mind!
Yes.. right said.
The thing is.. excuse me.
Sir, listen to my plan too.
I started planning the very
day I set my foot in here!
Why do you think I risked
my life to save Mr. Raja?
So that when I kill him,
no one would suspect me.
And after he is dead, we
divide his millions. Fifty-fifty.
I started planning the very day,
I set my foot in here!
Why do you think I risked
my life to save Mr. Raja?
So that when I killed him,
no one would suspect me.
And after he is dead,
we divide his millions.
Fifty-fifty.
You are a different kind of man.
Like a mug without the bottom.
You make a deal with me.
And then you sell me out!
Then this is true!
Sir. The evidence is here.
How can I lie?
Scoundrel! Traitor!
Listen, sir. Use your mouth.
Not your hands.
Sir.. I am warning you.
Enough of bossing over me!
You have raised your hand. This
is the end of the relationship.
lf you raise your hand,
I'll send you to heaven.
You think you can kill me?
What are you doing, sir?!
You want to kill a mere
servant and go to jail.
He can't take any risks.
To do that, you need guts.
Arjun Singh! Go away! Or else..
- What can you do?
lf you are born out of wedlock
you'll see me outside the hotel!
Arjun Singh!
- Sir, what are you doing?
Hey you! Let go of me!
- Sir, calm down!
Let go of me!
- No, sir.
Mr. Raja, what you saw was loyalty.
Now wait till you
see what treachery is!
lf I don't ruin you,
I'm not Arjun Singh!
Whom do you want to ruin?
My son? My Raja?
How dare you?!
You scoundrel!
Father! You!
All my life, you have
put me to test, Lord!
I have gone beyond the call of duty!
And You have a duty too.
Your duty towards me!
What more do you
want to extract from me?
Dear, I didn't come to
extract anything from you.
I am here to apologize.
I have erred. I cannot
give those years back to you.
But by apologizing,
I can lessen my sins.
What can I give you? A human
does what is written in his destiny.
Were it not destined,
I'd never have promised.
And I'd never have kept my promise.
I wouldn't have abandoned my son.
Then put an end to this.
Embrace your son.
Arjun!
My son!
My son.
Mother!
Son! - Mother!
- My son..
My son! I slapped you!
No!
Enough, mother.
That is all I ever wished!
How I wished for a mother..
..who would scold me,
who would slap me!
A mother who would embrace me!
Don't say that, my son!
Don't say that.
Let me say it, mummy! Let me!
I have never spoken to my mother!
How unfortunate are these people
who are denied a mother's love!
How lucky I am! I
have found my mother!
She hit me. I got her love.
No son, I slapped you!
For your sake, I would even die!
What? What are you saying?
Yes. Savitri is
Arjun Singh's mother.
Mother?
Yes.
But she admonished him in public.
Yes, this all was a melodrama.
She played it front of everyone.
People will do anything for money.
All she did was to slap him.
She has her eyes on your money.
So! - I bet I know who is
behind these attempts on your life.
It's Savitri. But everyone
seems to think so highly of her.
You don't believe me,
do you? Then ok.
Bhairon!
This is Bhairon.
He's from Arjun's village.
He's Arjun's childhood friend.
Bhairon, tell him how Ms.
Savitri and Arjun are related.
They..
- Tell it!
They are mother and son.
Did you hear that? You may leave.
Where is Arjun Singh?
Not to worry, sir.
Wherever he is, I will find him.
Sir, let go of him.
Brother.
For the last time,
where is Arjun Singh?
For the first time, here I am.
Leave it!
Arjun!
Thank you!
Yes. Mr. Zalim Singh..
..you always miss your target.
Missed your aim on the
owner as well as his servant.
And that's because you're
basically a rotten fellow.
Look here. See? The ace villain that
you are, I took a few tips from you.
So first you pay up for my dress.
And then you take a lashing.
Because, the bullets that
you shot here and there..
..if by mistake you
would've hit here.
Like the one that I
am going to shoot now.
Then you would stand to gain.
You understand at last, don't you?
Yes. Now tell me, who
is pulling the strings?
A moron like you can never
hatch such a sinister plot.
This must be the handiwork
of some big-time villain!
Speak up, my boy. Who is it?
Who?
My dad?
Yes. Ultimately, the
cat's out of the bag!
So, you even have a father.
How many fathers do you have?
I mean.. where is your father?
Come with me, I'll show it to you.
- Let's go.
Come, son.
Where's your daddy?
Where is he?
You have a lot of daddies!
- Not at all. Not at all.
Dear, everyone has only one father.
Not only his, but
even you have a father.
But I must give you credit.
To reach me, you've
used my son as a pretext.
When your father couldn't do
anything to me, who are you?
Look. Over there.
Don't be surprised, dear.
Let me introduce you, son.
Dear, this is your mother
and this is your grandpa.
This is your childhood friend.
Nisha's mother.
She is your master's.. Ms. Nisha.
So you've seen it all.
Now you decide.
Give the revolver to my son.
And let's strike a deal.
Else, your family is dead.
Arjun Singh, I'm running out of time!
Give the revolver back or.. - Wait!
Here.
- Smart kid. Give me.
Good. Smart kid.
Not stubborn like daddy.
Your daddy was a fool.
You can have the
deal your daddy missed.
I want Rajkumar to
sign these papers.
And then, I'd like to see him dead.
You can take your family home
as soon as you've done the job.
No.. I can't do this.
I can't kill Mr. Raja!
At least you can get him to sign.
My son will do the rest of it.
You will hang for it.
Tell me. Do you agree?
Think it over.
Raja sir. Yes.
Mr. Raja, it's been two days,
and there's no news of your mother.
I think.. - What can I do?
Why have you come here?
Call the police if
you want to find her.
Fine. If I don't find them,
I'll go to the police station.
As of now, take this testament.
And please relieve me
of this responsibility.
Testament? Whose?
Your mother wrote
this will 15 years ago.
She told me that in the
eventuality of her death..
..I am to hand it
over to her son.. Raja.
Mother has willed me everything!
And I have been cursing her!
Mother..
- Sir..
Please step outside, sir! I want
to talk to you! It's urgent! Ok.
So what have you decided?
For the last time, will you do it?
Or should I?
No. I'll do it.
I'll do whatever you say!
- No, dear.
You must never do it!
lf you do it, the sacrifices
your father and I have made..
..will have been for nothing!
Don't do it, son! Don't do it!
And what have you gained?
You left your family!
You abandoned your son!
And what has Raja given
you for what you did for him?
He insulted you!
There's no question of being
loyal to a man who is selfish.
I say, you should always
cheat people like these.
Don't talk like that!
We are indebted to them!
You mustn't betray him.
Keep your lessons to yourself. See
what your principles have led to?
And this is what happens
to you and to my mother.
Stop, son!
I bind you with my oath.
You owe your life to the
father of the man you want to kill!
No! Don't stop me!
After so many years, I
have found my mother.
I don't want to lose my mother.
I'll sacrifice Mr. Raja
for your love and affection.
Don't stop me.
- Stop!
My son goes with you. Go on, son.
And listen! If you
try to get smart..
..there will be no one
left to give them a funeral.
Yes sir, Raja speaking.
Yes.
My mother has been
missing for two days!
Please, do something and
find her out. Thank you.
The mother whom you were
cursing till yesterday..
..today you are very
concerned about her.
Her life is in danger!
- I know.
And until you have
signed these papers..
..she continues to be in danger.
Arjun, what..
Don't waste time. Just
do as I say. Come on.
Use the pen.
Go on.
Wait.
Don't shoot him before
he signs the papers.
Come on.
Yes.
Here.
Give me..
- No..
Mr. Raja, we don't need you anymore.
Don't shoot him!
No!
Now you are left out..
Thanks. Mister.. give it to me.
Give it to me.
What is the meaning of this?
Mr. Giridhar.
You wanted to kill my family.
I wanted to kill yours.
This son of yours is a two-timer.
He killed Raja.
No!
And after that, he tried to kill me.
That means, my son..
- Yes.
Your son shot Mr. Raja.
He killed my Raja.
- Yes, mother.
The condition was Mr. Raja's death..
..will be the cause
for their release.
I'm holding the price.
You must let them go.
Yes, but the papers.
- You'll get it.
Give and take.
Untie them.
Fine.
Mother.
Don't you call me mother!
I'll explain later.
Bhairon, you take all of
them and leave. - Wait!
What is it now?
The signatures have disappeared.
This is too much.
God must have decided
not to answer your prayers!
I went through all this!
And to no avail!
You must be a sinner!
- Shut up!
Son! Look. What do we do now?
But he signed it.
Right in front of me!
Now which one of you goes to
heaven to get Raja's signature?
You're the one who goes, son!
- No!
Who shot the bullet?
We didn't.
It was me.
Rajkumar?
About turn! Hands up.
So you are the evil uncle!
Son! He's alive! But
you said you killed him!
When you are alive even
after you are dead for all..
..I never died.
You don't get it?
Arjun Singh!
- Yes boss?
Please explain.
- Yes boss!
So, Mr. Giridhar. The thing is..
..your son shot him..
The pistol was real, but..
..the bullets inside the pistol..
..Were.. Were..
You get it?
Or don't you?
Look! Now how about me
shooting your son? No!
See? The scoundrel that
he is, he's still alive.
And you think Raja could die?
And because, this was the same
revolver used by Mr. Vijay Merchant..
..and Mr. Vijay Hazare.
Didn't get it.
Hey!
Yes, Mr. Rajkumar.
Every dog has its day.
Now there aren't any fakes.
No dud bullets. No dud pens.
Time to sign up. Come on.
Come on.
In any case, I stand to inherit
the property after you're gone.
Go on. Sit here, and sign it.
Let's finish off with
this legal things first.
So that there are no
hazels after you die.
Sir!
I have an old score
to settle. For my son!
Sir! Where are you going?
Not here, go there.
Poonam!
Will you tell it to me or not?
Yes, where were we?
Isn't that Mr. Talwar?
Dear, your name doesn't
suit your personality.
There won't be any
cause and no effect.
Get lost!
Poonam, I was telling you that..
..you did a very good
thing by saving Mr. Raja..
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, don't pull me so hard.
Hey, hold me.
You missed your target again.
Take this.
Yes, nice position.
Poonam, so where were we?
Yes! So you wanted this signed?
Why are you standing there? Come.
Don't be shy. Come here.
He's an old friend!
Yes, you want this to be signed?
Take this. I'll tear this will.
Here are your signatures.
Come on, on your feet.
Get up.
Here you are, you useless guy.
Take this.
Get up! Take this!
Take this!
Finally, take this.
The Boss!
Arjun Singh!
Boss.
Arjun Singh, what is this.
Breastplate, boss!
Arjun Singh, stop fooling!
- I'm sorry, boss!
Wait, brother.
Mr. Kirorimal!
Where is your big moustache?
What is the matter?
Mr. Kirorimal, now it
is not going to work.
I want all your teeth. Come here.
Please stand in front
of me. Right in front!
Oh God!
Forgive me. I'm not a pervert.
But you could dress properly,
you know. What?
Wait!
There is a glass here.
That's what is
called through-the glass
I don't spare traitors!
Don't do what I told you.
This road leads nowhere.
Mr. Raja needs you.
Don't leave him. Ever.
Stop right there, Arjun Singh!
lf you hit my daddy,
I'll behead her!
Your turn Mr. Raja. Come here.
You are all I need.
You have to sign the papers.
Come on!
No, sir. You mustn't!
No Arjun Singh,
Poonam is in danger!
That's good.
Come.
Come on..
Come, Mr. Raja.
Don't try to get smart.
Hands up. That's good.
Now get up in there.
Latch the other
cuff on the handlebar.
Throw me the keys.
Over here.
Yes.
Don't you move!
So Mr. Villain,
please take the cuffs off.
Else, you know what
happens to your daddy.
Let him go! Son! Let him go!
- Yes.
The keys are under the seat.
Come.
Come, come.
Thank you, boss!
Boss?
- Yes.
How about trading places?
From now, you're the boss.
Order me, boss.
So boss.. I mean Raja..
..first of all, you tie
the villain to his father.
Alright.
So that both the donkeys
are together when they die.
What next, boss?
The next is..
Deflate all the tires on
this truck. - Sure, boss.
Now you rascals, you'll tell me how
far the nearest police station is?
Two miles.
- Two miles.
And what do we have around here?
It is a jungle.
- Jungle.
And what do you find
in the jungles? Tigers.
What do we do now?
- What do we do now?
You don't need to do a thing.
Leave it to the tigers. - Yes.
I hope the tigers find
you before the cops.
Greeting.
Son, I have kept my promise.
And I have done my duty.
But I have a lot more to do in life.
I want your leave. For
a few days at least.
No, mother. You aren't
going anywhere alone.
We are all coming with you.
Oh! Thank God!
I came to town to see my grandson.
I had one. You've given me two.
And two brides to boot!
Let's hope I live to see the day
when you become grandfathers. Yes.
Tell me something,
grandpa. How did you get here?
Yes. Ask him.
- What's it, Bhairon?
Why should I tell you
that I sent him a letter!
Just a minute, please.
Let's have a family photo.
Come on. Arjun, you go behind.
Yes. Ready, smile.
Arjun, it is dawn, wake up.
Arjun! Get out of bed!
No! I won't let you go!
I will
You are my whole life!
- Daughter-in-law!
Daughter-in-law!
Come here quickly.
You wake him up from now on.
I will not do that.
lf I knew this would happen..
- You're old! At last!
It is you, your father, your..