Can't see Raja anywhere.
Where can he be?
Was I keeping a watch on him
all night at sea? He'll come.
There he comes, sir.
Hey, Raja...
I was just asking about you.
Where were you?
Everybody came home, except you.
- Look over there, sir.
Nobody must've got such a haul!
Nobody's as good as you either.
Come and unload this stuff.
- Coming, sir.
Hey! Take your money.
You total it. I'll take it later.
Cheena, what are you doing here?
Have you eaten anything, or not?
Here, take this. Eat something.
Hi Johnny!
- Raja!
Your wedding, eh?
- Must come.
I'll just have a wash and come.
- Your house is this way.
I'll have a cup of tea first.
Hey! Come fast. We'll have fun!
What's this here?
You rascal!
Raja!
- Yes!
Come on... Come on now...
- I've come...
He ran away, damn it!
Did you have to come now?
You only called me.
I called the mouse, not you! Well?
Nothing. Just a cup of tea.
- No way!
Why not?
I've to get ready for
Maria's wedding as yet.
Even I've to go to it.
- Hey...
What?
I just cleaned up the place.
And look what you're doing.
Sorry.
I've been sitting up all night
in a little boat at sea...
And you... you refuse me
a cup of tea?
Okay. I'll just...
Alright. I'll give it to you.
Now sit properly first. Come on.
I won't spare you today.
I'll just get the poison.
Down! Get down! The other side!
You always bug me! Here!
Clean it up!
Mona...
- Don't ask for anything else.
Okay.
Papa!
What are you doing here, Raja?
Miss Joseph's looking for you.
I know.
We've to go to the wedding.
Oh no!
- Sorry.
What's that?
- Poison!
Poison?
- For the rats!
Mona, this...
- What is it?
The tea's fine, but without sugar.
Look you...
- No sugar in it...
What's the matter with me?
All this work together!
Johnny in the kitch. You're to get
wed. The mice want sugar. Mad!
Johnny in the kitch? I'm getting
married and mice want sugar?
Great! She's mixed all the 3
like milk, tea and sugar!
Sugar!
- Don't need it now.
This...
How did this get empty?
- It had sugar. I put it in tea.
This...
Why are you so worried?
I just put it in my tea.
And you... you drank it all up?
Then? Should I wash my face
and hands with it? Honestly!
But they adulterate even
the sugar nowadays!
Raja!
For God's sake! Go get ready.
I'll also go and get dressed.
This wasn't sugar, it was poison!
Poison?
No!
Mona.
- Yes.
You're not telling the truth
by any chance, are you?
That's what I was trying to say.
You drank poison!
Papa.
- Mona.
Raja!
I can't see properly...
But, I'm alright. Don't
you worry. I'm fine.
Raja.
- Mona.
Where are you?
- I'm here.
Raja!
Help! Mona, I'm feeling giddy.
- Help!
Help!
Sit.
Raja!
- This isn't the time to sit. I'm going...
I'm going...
- But where are you going?
Good bye, Mona!
- Good bye!
Hello God!
Raja!
Papa!
What's the matter, dear?
- What's happened, Raja?
Get up. Say something. The tea
had rat poison in it.
But what was it doing in the tea?
Mice don't drink tea!
Listen. I was in a hurry.
He asked for tea. So I...
I see.
You were in a hurry. He asked for
the tea, so you poisoned him!
What the hell have you done?
- I didn't poison him!
Who'll believe you?
The court needs proof.
It wants witnesses. And where
will we find a witness?
There's nobody here!
- I'll be a witness.
Will do.
He seems to be fine.
Raja... you're alright?
You're safe?
- Yes, because...
the poison is in my hankie, not tea!
I'll not spare you today.
Mona, It was just a prank.
- Just you wait!
I'll teach you a lesson!
I'll not spare you today.
I'll break your legs.
No!
"O Maria, O Maria..."
"when Johny proposed
marriage to you..."
"did he go down on his knees?
Tell me..."
"O Maria, O Maria..."
"when Johny proposed
marriage to you..."
"did he go down on his knees?
Tell me..."
"O Maria, O Maria..."
"A spark must certainly been
ignited in your body?"
"Johny's word must surely have made
your heart skip a beat?"
"Were you quiet,
when he spoke...?"
"I'll ask Mummy"
Is that what you said?
"O Maria, O Maria..."
"when Johny proposed
marriage to you..."
"did he go down on his knees?
Tell me..."
"O Maria, O Maria..."
"When Johny proposed to you..."
"were they days of summer?
Or nights of winter?"
"Did he say something weird?"
"Like being locked up
in a room together?"
"O Maria, O Maria..."
"when Johny proposed
marriage to you..."
"did he go down on his knees?
Tell me..."
"O Maria, O Maria..."
"Were you lost in thoughts,
as to how the wedding would go?"
"Or did Johny take
your hand in his?"
"When you said yes,
did he get closer..."
"and give you a tight hug,
with "Oh my darling...?"
"O Maria, O Maria..."
"when Johny proposed
marriage to you..."
"did he go down on his knees?
Tell me..."
"O Maria..."
Thank you.
Maria's married too!
One by one all the girls
are getting married!
You'll get married too some day.
Tomorrow, when Raja goes
fishing I'll tell him.
What?
To net a groom for me!
What's wrong with Raja himself?
Raja!
My glasses... what's this?
That...
Not that, this!
- This!
That's a hankie. With which one
wipes sweat, cleans nose.
I've reared you since
you were this small.
You try to be smart, with me?
I know everything!
You know everything? What?
Why don't you marry her?
Marry? Whom?
- Mona of course. Who else?
Honestly, Miss Joseph you
misunderstand things.
Okay. I thought you would
open your heart to me.
But if you want to hide it,
who am I to probe?
No, Mrs. Joseph. Don't say
who are you to question.
If you won't ask me, who will?
Is there anybody else?
Then tell me, when you have
so much fun with her...
...why don't you pop the question?
Because this is not a joke.
I know, that when I ask her,
she won't refuse.
But let me become capable
of doing so first!
After all, what do I own?
The boat belongs to a contractor.
So do the nets I use. Even
the fish I catch, is his!
I do make some money, but how will
I keep her happy on this small sum?
You mean all your life, you'll...
- No, Mrs. Joseph.
I'll see good days too.
Then I'll go to Mona.
When I own a boat.
When I work for myself.
When I earn for you, and Mona.
Mrs. Joseph... you'll see.
One day, your Raja,
in these very waters...
...will ply his very own boat.
These small boats really
look fantastic.
I mean they look really good.
How do you feel about it?
If you think they're nice, you
better feast your eyes on them.
They won't be seen after a few days.
- That's fantastic, sir.
They'll not be seen at all.
My eyesight is getting weaker.
Even now, though out of focus,
I can see the boats hazily.
You're a born ass! I wasn't
talking about your eyes.
I meant the policy of
Kamladevi's company.
We don't want these small fishermen
casting their nets here.
They sell their stuff in the same
market as our company does.
And this affects our
prices very severely.
I feel they'll not listen to you
by you not letting them fish.
They'll have to give in, the way
we're giving to convince them!
Get me?
- Of course. It's like, big fish...
...devouring small fish!
Isn't that what you mean?
That's the first time I'm hearing
you talk some sense!
Thank you, sir.
Captain! Let's turn back.
- Yes, sir.
Madam has called me at 10 sharp.
- 10 o'clock? Then we have to turn back.
Because her clock strikes ten,
exactly at ten!
But I do feel one thing, sir.
I'm your humble servant, no doubt.
So I'll address her as `Madam'.
But you, sir...
You're her late brother's son.
So she's your Aunty.
Why don't you call her that?
- Because, my dear man...
...I want to remain her G.M.!
Kamladevi is `Madam' to one and all.
Including me!
Why isn't the work finished yet?
- That land is at a low-level.
And now it's flooded due to rains.
That's why I had to halt everything.
Don't worry though. I'll try to
finish the work by 26th instant.
You don't get paid
just to try your best.
If that work is not done by 26th,
you better send your resignation!
Good morning, madam.
The estimate for the three
Japanese trawlers, is ready.
Vikram.
- Yes.
I haven't called you now
to discuss those trawlers.
Ravi's coming!
And as you know...
...this property, this
widespread business...
...he has to manage some day.
Of course! Why not?
If he stays with you, he'll
learn the ropes by and by.
After all, he's your grandson.
He has your blood in his veins!
True.
But his veins...
...also carry blood of an ordinary
girl from an ordinary family!
With whom my son was...
Anyway...
Why recall all these memories
after so many years?
I wish, when Ravi comes,
by and by...
put some responsibilities
on his shoulders.
Right.
Greeting, sir!
Come.
Is Gran at home?
No. She's busy in the office now.
Thank you.
- Sir.
How do you like the bungalow?
It's lovely.
And your room?
That's lovely too.
It can be developed a lot.
We've started fisheries, and
now I've other plans too.
Just take interest in work,
and you'll soon know everything.
What did you do after college?
Just roamed here and there.
You stay here now. I've spoken to
Vikram, to teach you the ropes.
Okay.
And you must get married too.
Your father spoilt his life!
But I won't let you do the same.
My father hadn't spoilt his own life.
He led it according to his wish.
According to his own wish,
or that woman's wish?
Before you go any further, Gran.
Remember it's my mother you speak of!
If I'm really doing so,...
...then I shouldn't be.
Because I don't want to talk
about her at all!
You haven't finished
your soup as yet.
Excuse me.
Do you live in this lighthouse?
- Yes.
I've not seen you around before.
Are you a stranger here?
Correct.
Must be taking your morning walk.
Yes.
The sea looks so beautiful
so early in the morning.
Why just morning? The sea has a
lovely look each moment of the day.
Blue, or aqua or silver.
Sometimes it's bright red too.
And then it roars...
...as though an army's marching in.
And sometimes it's so quiet...
...as if a friend's chatting,
his hand on the shoulder.
There are countless forms of the sea.
If you look carefully, son...
What's your name?
- Ravi.
What's your name, Pop?
They all call me `Pop' only.
Pop?
Okay then, I'll go now. See you.
- Most certainly.
Aren't you going to work today?
- Yes, I'm going.
You see her photos before
you go to work.
And go straight to see her after
you return. What all this?
I don't know. But it's something.
May I go now? I'm late.
Hey look! The company's boats.
They aren't company's boats, son.
That's a kick from the rich, which
will hit our stomachs one day!
We're ready, sir. Shall we go back?
- Okay.
Why do you always take
such a long detour?
I think because the fishermen have their
nets spread over there one has to do it.
Is the sea their private property.
...for them to spread their nets
wherever they please?
Captain Sharma!
- Yes, sir.
Today, take this boat straight!
But sir, that boat, the net...
Do as I say! Take the boat ahead...
Yes, sir.
Hey! He's coming straight at us!
Don't come this way...
There's a net spread here.
Can't you hear me?
Go the other way.
- Don't come this way.
Sir, I feel...
Have you gone deaf?
There's a net here. Don't come
this way. Go from there.
I say stop! We've cast a net here.
Don't come this way.
We poor have suffered huge loss.
Let us go in.
Get lost! I told you before.
If we can't come in, we won't
let you come out either!
What is it? Why this noise?
- I'll tell you why!
Sir, they want to barge in!
What do you want?
- Hey, come here.
Your boat destroyed his net.
We want money for it.
- Yes! Money!
What money?
Had we told him
to spread his net there?
And listen. We'll ply our boat
whichever way we wish.
The sea is not your property.
Okay, we agree we don't own it.
Neither does it have your company
stamp on it to do as you please!
You have caused him loss.
You'll have to pay him.
Look, if you want to start a fight...
- One minute, uncle.
What's going on here?
Nothing. They are local fishermen.
Their net came in front of our boat.
And now they demanding money.
Our net didn't come in your way.
You deliberately went over it!
If you've done it, why lie?
Tell him.
You mean your net is useless now?
- It's wrecked. It belonged to him.
He had borrowed money on interest.
Now what will he earn and eat?
Ravi, why do you listen to such lot?
They're just...
They may be anything, but
whatever happened, wasn't nice.
This man must be compensated today.
Just now!
But if Madam.
- Don't worry about her.
I'll talk to her. You just pay him.
Okay.
Take this man to the office,
and pay his dues.
Yes, sir.
Have this chilled beer.
It's a fantastic thing.
You will feel cool.
I heard that Ravi behaved
like a damn fool today.
I don't know about your feelings,
but I felt very bad, sir.
After all I'm your sycophant, sir.
So naturally I'll feel bad.
But what can we do?
He's Madam's grandson.
He's her heir!
- Heir, my foot!
Even his father,
Arun was her heir.
Madam's only son.
But what happened?
He lived like a beggar all his life!
So what if he's her heir?
Exactly! What a fantastic
thing you said.
But sir, one thing really hurts me.
When Madam had asked her
own son to get out...
...how did this grandson come in?
He was 7 years old.
When he lost his parents
in a road accident.
Then Madam brought him here.
Lived all his life in a hostel.
Now she has called him here to stay.
What the son couldn't be...
...she wants her grandson to be!
Damn fool.
But take my word...
...all this estate, this business,
will one day belong to me!
The son didn't get a penny.
Neither will the grandson!
Let's sit in the Giant wheel.
- No! No.
What's the matter?
- I get very scared.
Please come on. Let's go.
- No, please.
No! I get so dizzy.
Come on, sir. Get down.
Come along you folks.
- My name is Ravi.
What's yours?
- Come on. I'm famished!
Hey! Where are you?
"A face as radiant
as the moonlight..."
"your tresses remind me
of dusk..."
"your eyes are as deep
as the oceans..."
"but could you tell me
what is your name?"
"A face as radiant
as the moonlight..."
"your tresses remind me
of dusk..."
"your eyes are as deep
as the oceans..."
"but could you tell me
what is your name?"
"How would you know
how my heart pines for you"
"How would you know what
dreams I see for you"
"Now that you are with me,
I wish this moment would freeze"
"As the oceans flow,
I wish they would freeze too"
"You've driven me crazy..."
"how is my poor heart to blame?"
"Your eyes are as deep
as the oceans..."
"but could you tell me
what is your name?"
"Even if I'm away from you
and we're complete strangers..."
"if I don't have you,
I shall be heart-broken"
"I wish there was no noise..."
"and we rejoiced the solitude"
"I wish there were no one else
in the world..."
"there were only you and I"
"I dream of you..."
"I have nothing else to do"
"Your eyes are as deep
as the oceans..."
"but could you tell me
what is your name?"
"A face as radiant
as the moonlight..."
"your tresses remind me
of dusk..."
"your eyes are as deep
as the oceans..."
"but could you tell me
what is your name?"
Mona!
Caught you!
What had you come to steal?
See? Honesty has no value here.
I was going to my contractor.
Thought I'd ask...
- Spray it.
...if you wanted anything.
- No, nothing.
Nothing.
- Oh Yes! Raja...
I had bought this dress material.
I want some buttons for it.
Sure.
- Blue. Big ones.
Thank you.
Anything else?
So sweet.
It was a wise move to be
friends with you.
It came in handy today.
- Bringing buttons is work?
I'm willing even to take life...
I mean stake my life for you.
Really? Is that so?
Then come here.
Now jump off the balcony.
- Jump? Off this balcony?
Okay.
Raja!
Come on, Ramsingh. Start.
Don't worry. I'll get your
big, blue buttons!
So what you're saying is...
...we reduce our prices
in the market, by and by.
Yes.
And what about the loss?
We can afford the loss
But the local fishermen...
...it'll break their backbone.
That's because...
...every man has borrowed money
on interest for his boat and nets.
Or, got them from a contractor,
either on commission, or on hire.
If the prices are reduced
like this, then...
...the men will never repay their
debts and lose their daily wages.
Then we'll have a monopoly
over the market.
Start reducing the prices.
Quiet! Quiet! Shut up!
- But these company people...
I know why they've reduced the rates.
Just to devastate us!
But how will shouting help us?
- Then do we keep quiet?
No. I'm not suggesting that.
Look... we've to unite and think cool.
What's there to think now?
If you listen to him, you'll
just sit and think.
Oh yes? Then what do you suggest?
I suggest there's only one way.
Burn the company boats
and burn their godowns!
And then you all go to jail...
...and your kids starve and die!
So? They'll starve as it is.
I think what he says is right.
- Yes, he's correct.
Correct, my foot...
- Raja, forget it.
Okay, if that's how you feel.
Do as he says.
Get lost! You're all `yes' men!
Go and listen to them all.
May I've one feni?
- Sorry, but the bar is closed.
Closed? But they're all drinking.
True.
- Then?
It's closed just now.
Wait, sir.
Uncle. Let him have a drink.
Make another one like this.
How much?
- Rs. 5/-.
Thank you.
For you.
Hold on, Sir!
Uncle, two more.
Look sir... you're a big shot.
We're simple folk... fishermen.
Have a drink with
our hard-earned money too!
Now 2 more, on me.
Uncle! Two more please.
What's your name, Sir?
I'm no `Sir', and my name is...
"Ravi", Raja.
"Ra-ja".
He's a Company man,
not a friendly soul.
Ravi is my guest.
Get one more bottle.
Raja, you don't know it, but
The Company is your foe!
They had enough.
Please give it to me.
Uncle.
No more after this.
Why?
- You both have taken enough.
Who has taken too much?
Enough.
Well uncle, you think that...
Careful.
No!
Okay.
Well, Uncle, you really think
we're drunk?
Get up.
- Go away.
We've finished just 1-2 bottles.
And why not, boys?
We're just...
What is it?
Making merry...
We're just `high'... Okay?
"Let's keep singing..."
"and smiling"
"Come, let's sing and dance
and make merry... c'mon"
"Let's keep singing..."
"and smiling"
"Come, let's sing and dance
and make merry... c'mon"
"Let's drink all night"
"Let's let our hair down"
"For my sake, my friend..."
"forever be my friend"
"So let's sway and sing now...
c'mon"
"Let's keep singing..."
"and smiling"
"Come, let's sing and dance
and make merry... c'mon"
"Love makes the world
so beautiful"
"There's no bigger kick than love"
"I'll go wherever my love takes me"
"Here it is that you will
find your love, my friend"
"So let's freak out here in
these lanes and sing... c'mon"
"Let's keep singing..."
"and smiling"
"Come, let's sing and dance
and make merry... c'mon"
Sir! Sir! Sir!
You seem to be very happy.
- I've got a fantastic news.
You always think I'm...
...an absolute fool, Sir.
But this time I proved you wrong.
- Really?
What news have you brought?
Last night, Ravi was seen dancing
and singing with the fishermen, Sir.
Singing and dancing.
And also, ... drinking, Sir.
Very good.
This ...
- My mother.
Shall we go?
How old were you,
when your mother...
12 years old.
Lucky.
You've enjoyed your mother
5 more years than me.
I was just 7 when...
both my parents passed away.
My Dad... who was the only
son of a millionairess.
They fell in love and married.
My grandma was so furious...
...that she never saw
her son ever again!
Ravi, just remember this.
That how good your parents were.
How much they loved each other.
And forget the bitter things.
I remembered it all because
the history's going to repeat!
You didn't say anything, Mona.
What shall I say?
What your heart wishes.
One doesn't always get
what one's heart wishes.
Life has its stark realities too.
Like this reality that we both
come from two different worlds.
But our worlds are not so apart
that we cannot bridge the gap.
But... You hardly know me! And...
Yes. I don't know much about you.
But I want to know.
I want to know everything!
Your every idiosyncrasy...
every bit about you.
I wish that we sit together.
And you talk about yourself.
While I listen and look at you.
And if possible,
let the life thus go by.
No, Ravi. I'm a poor girl.
Don't show me such dreams.
It's me who's poor, Mona.
I don't have a dime
of anyone's love.
If you can, give me some,
from your treasure of love.
If you refuse, I'll go away.
Exist somehow, somewhere.
But I swear, I'll miss you
every moment in my life.
"Here, on the seashore..."
"my heart calls out to you..."
"I have no one, except you"
"Here, on the seashore..."
"my heart calls out to you..."
"I have no one, except you"
"Here, on the seashore..."
"The sights have come alive..."
"there's mischief
in the air"
"The sights have come alive..."
"there's mischief
in the air"
"When love awakened...
it awakened everything"
"Not for a moment has my heart
let me go to sleep"
"Here, on the seashore..."
"my heart calls out to you..."
"I have no one,
except you"
"Here, on the seashore..."
"On the waves sing
fairies of light..."
"I'm as lost as the river
that flows into the sea"
"You're not the only one
who feels lost"
"Here, on the seashore..."
"my heart calls out to you..."
"I have no one, except you"
"Here, on the seashore..."
What are you watching so intently?
That boat.
You didn't come here yesterday.
Where were you?
Yesterday?
I feel nice when I come here.
The vast open sea. The open sky.
Large-hearted people.
The more I breathe fresh air here...
The more I feel suffocated
in my grandmother's mansion!
Look! See how that boat
is swaying on the waves.
As though the waves are heartbeats
and the boat, a desire.
Wow! How beautifully you put it.
Being educated, you can express.
With me...
I can talk nineteen to a dozen,
but I can't express inner feeling.
Why? Are you keeping something
hidden in your heart?
Buddy...
...what kind of a heart is that,
which harbours no feelings?
Really?
But how to express one's feelings.
Teach me that.
Okay, I will. And you teach me
how to row that.
This thing?
No great shakes.
I'll teach you right now!
Like this...
- Like this, eh?
Yes.
You're getting the hang of it.
Yes, I'll learn it soon.
- Sure you will.
But I think I won't learn
how to open my heart.
So what?
Tell me what to say, to whom...
and I'll tell it for you.
Really? You'll tell?
- Of course I will.
But whom do I tell it to.
Tell me that first.
Shall I tell you?
- Yes.
Well then...
Shall I really?
What nonsense is this? Tell me...
That's why I told you to sit.
But you...
You said it was easy.
Raja!
Hurry! Drink it up.
Did you get hiccups on the way?
- Why?
Because we were talking about you.
He's Ravi. My friend.
God bless you.
Thought I'd show him our house.
- What's that?
It's just a glass...
Did you offer him something to eat or
drink? Or were you just badmouthing me?
No I didn't, but I was going to.
- "Was going to" indeed! Heathen!
Sit down, son. I'll get some tea.
- No, Aunty. Don't bother yourself.
I was just leaving. Sit please.
- I know, I know.
When you both were alone,
you had a lot to talk about.
Now that an old woman is here,
he's wanting to run!
No, Aunty.
It's not like that.
The things he told me about you.
The way you showered love on him.
If I could...
... I'd have exchanged
places with Raja anytime.
No! I'll not give you
my precious Miss Joseph.
Let go!
God bless you.
- Thank you.
Okay then. I'll go now.
- Keep sitting. - It's okay.
I didn't know that the rich
were also good human beings.
Why? Weren't they also made
by God?
He's a very nice boy.
He has to be nice!
Whose friend after all.
Here's your mutton-patties
and this too.
Don't shout!
I'll just get it for you.
Here's you keema-pav and omelette.
Mona, why's it taking ages
for the soda?
Tony, give him a soda.
No tea for the past 1/2 hour.
- Please wait.
Listen.
- Yes, what do you want?
May I have one plate of Time?
Just a plate of Time.
I've run out of it!
Mona...
- Yes, Papa.
You'll only get it tomorrow now.
- Hey, listen...
One tea, Mona.
- One cup of friendly look...
And 2 tea-spoons
of sweet nothings.
Sorry. Out of stock.
See how habits are formed.
You didn't come yesterday...
...and one day seemed incomplete.
Yes, I couldn't make it.
We had gone to that village fair.
Mona and I.
This life is also a fun fair, son.
Where people meet...
...and where a hand, held
in the crowds, just slips away.
This hand will never slip away.
I'll won't let it!
Have you spoken to your Grandma?
Not as yet. But I will.
I'm not worried about her.
But I must speak to Mona's father.
I don't know how I'll...
I think I'll get cold feet.
Then have someone else tell him.
But who?
Anyone who knows you and Mr. D'Silva.
I just know Raja...
That's it! Raja!
Thank you very much. I'll go right now...
- Where?
Don't leave anything for tomorrow.
Do it now! I'll go right now...
...and tell Raja
to speak to Mr. D'Silva.
Raja!
What's all this you've bought?
- Not all, son.
Didn't you say the house needs
to be painted? Hold this.
Here you are.
I'll get some more if you need it.
This is fine.
But, what's this? Red?
If I use red colour, people will
think I used blood to paint it!
Blood. You know...
Mona!
Raja!
I've come, Mona.
Papa!
What happened?
- Don't know. It's very cold.
They were four, and
I was all alone.
What?
But I risked my life for you.
For me?
Yes, Mona... for you.
There were 4 hooligans
behind your house.
4 hooligans? What do you mean?
They were planning to kidnap you!
I heard them talk. And they saw me!
Then what happened?
- Fighting began...
They boxed. I kicked.
They used Judo. I, Karate.
Then those 4 drew knives!
Oh my God! Four knives!
Yes. One knife per head...
Raja, you're not up to
one of your pranks, are you?
Raja!
- Miss Joseph!
I'm dead now!
- No! Don't die.
What shall we do about him?
What's happened to him?
Look dear, he left this tin
of red colour open in the sun.
Red colour?
This tin of red colour... that...
- What the hell are you up to?
Why have you put this red colour
on your clothes?
I'll tell you.
But first, I'll show him!
She'll kill me.
Ravi! Help! Save me!
I'm being murdered! Help me!
Rascal!
Raja, what happened to you?
Where are you running off to? Ravi!
Then I just dropped dead,
with this knife in my back.
Tell me. How do you think
of such pranks?
When Ms Joseph brought the tin,
I just casually remarked...
"Blood"! You should've seen Mona!
Scared to death she was!
Naturally! With that knife...
You are the limit, I tell you!
That I am! I've been
telling lies since morning.
Then finish your week's quota today.
Say whatever you want to.
Okay.
Shall I say whatever I want to?
Yes. Because I've something
important to say too.
Then listen.
I love a girl very very much.
And I'm telling you the truth.
But who's that girl.
- She's a very very nice girl.
And the day's not far
when we'll get married.
Okay, but...
But who is she? What's her name?
Name? Her name is...
Mona!
Why alone? I'm here to help.
- What will I do without you?
I don't know. But if you come to
the club tonight, we'll have fun.
There's a party there at 10/- each.
Haven't danced for ages.
Let's dance tonight.
- I'm dancing since morning, you...
Hurry up, Mona! I've to go to work.
- Even I had to go some place.
But I couldn't. Can't you see I'm
alone. You're lucky to get this!
Hurry up.
Tony.
- Coming.
No 5 and 7 table.
- Here's the money from No.3.
What happened to our drink?
- Hold on. I'll send it across.
Mona. Mona...
What is it?
- Come with me.
How can I? I don't have time
to scratch my head!
I'll scratch it for you.
We've to go in the evening.
Take this.
- I thought...
...I'd call Ravi too.
Hey, Mona... Please come.
Okay. After 7 O'clock.
Papa will return by then too.
That's more like it.
Tonight, at 7 p.m. then.
Listen! Ravi...
- I'll call him.
Ravi... What are you doing here?
There were so many girls there.
Why didn't you dance?
Just like that...
- I'm tired.
This Raja...
He's got wings on his feet! Right?
Yes.
He is so good.
But let me tell you one thing.
No other girl can dance with him.
We were dancing so well.
And you didn't even see.
I saw as much as I could.
Others come in between.
Never mind. Where's Raja?
- He went off to drink beer!
Mad!
Mona, why doesn't he get married?
Because...
Never mind.
You don't even have a drink?
Later. But you didn't answer me.
Whether he tells me anything
or not, I can sense it.
He thinks, what does he have
at this moment?
Why should he share his poverty
with anyone?
He'll think of marriage...
...when he achieves something.
And you also think he shouldn't
marry before that happens.
I don't think so.
But who'll convince him?
That if he wants he can easily
have a girl of his choice.
But he's waiting
for such a day...
...which I doubt will ever come.
- That shouldn't happen.
Yes. That shouldn't happen at all.
But what can I do?
It's happening.
When it shouldn't be happening.
- What shouldn't be happening?
That there's a party going on inside
and you both are standing here.
Now that you came, she left me.
- What else could I do? You...
It's all in the past now.
Come, let's dance.
Come on.
Where are you dragging me?
My shoes!
Want some beer?
Ravi, say something.
Ravi, please come.
Raja is a very hard working
and an honest man.
When he starts working, I'm sure
he'll return your money too.
If not, I'm responsible.
No. I'm not worried about that.
I owe a lot to your father.
One thing, whenever you meet Raja.
He mustn't know I've put in a word...
In fact, he mustn't even know
that you know me.
Resham Singh.
- Yes, sir.
Give this letter to Mr. D'Silva's
daughters in the village.
Okay, sir.
Where were you, son?
She comes and waits for you every day.
I'm going away from here.
- Where to?
Very far away.
That's all I know for the moment.
But suddenly, like this?
Have you thought about Mona?
Whom will I think of except her?
The more I thought, I realised,...
There's more in her life than me.
And you?
I'll manage to live on her memory.
Thought I'd meet you
before I leave.
Okay then. I...
"...that I'll have to forget you.
I can't forget you of course..."
"But yes. I can go away from you.
So. I'm going."
"But wherever I go, I'll always
have your memories with me"
"Your flower-life face will
always bloom in my eyes"
"The scent of your hair will always
be found lingering on my shoulder"
"If you can, take my helplessness
as infidelity."
"It may ease things".
"On the seashore..."
"all day and night..."
"there is a mellow light..."
"and a shade of darkness"
"So why this distance between us?
What holds you back?"
"How do I convince my heart?"
"My love for you is still very deep,
I'm very lonely without you..."
"How do I tell anyone?"
"You are not with me..."
"so what do I ever possess?"
"Just one dream..."
"just one hope"
"Your memories..."
"the things you said..."
"I can't spend my days,
I can hardly wait through the nights"
"I'm so crazy about you,
I haven't slept in days"
"Here, on the seashore..."
"my heart calls out to you..."
"I have no one except you"
No, Mona. This isn't proper.
What has happened to you?
If you've decided to leave me,
then I can't stop you.
But surely I can ask
what wrong I've done.
You're not in the
wrong, Mona. I am.
I didn't know I was snatching you
from somebody else!
Whom are you talking about?
I'm talking about Raja.
Raja!
I didn't know that Raja loved
you and you too loved him.
Raja loves me?
And I reciprocate?
How did you come
to that conclusion?
Mona, what I've told you is what
Raja told me himself.
What!
- Yes.
If Raja thinks it's like this,
then he shouldn't!
I'll tell him.
But why punish me for it?
Ravi! I love you. Only you.
Then forget me. Dump me and go.
Even if you don't ever meet me,
I'll still be yours.
I can't belong to anyone else!
Please don't go away... I'll die!
What the hell...
Put me down. Else I'll fall.
I'm feeling dizzy...
- It's me who's feeling dizzy today.
I've scored a jackpot!
- Let go of me!
What's the matter? Tell me.
- Then listen.
Sorry.
Today, what I wanted,
has happened!
I was mending my old nets
and what do I see?
A big car stopped before me
and a man in a suit got down.
Who was that man?
- Obviously a rich man.
R.C. Shukla. R.C...
- Shukla.
He must've heard somewhere,
that I'm the best fisherman here.
I didn't say it, somebody else
must have. And I am the best.
Listen. He wants to invest money.
He's willing to put in such a large
sum that I can buy 4-5 boats!
Buy nets. Do my own work,
start my own company...
Joking again?
No. It's the truth.
Is it really? I can't believe it.
Even I didn't believe it for
some time, that my dream...
...would come true one day.
But it has come true!
He has called me after
4 days in his office.
Do you remember?
- What?
What I had said?
That one day you'll see Raja
in his own boat in these waters!
I remember everything. You had said
something else too. Remember?
Yes. I remember it all.
But for now,...
I'll go to Mona and say...
What will I say?
That... The day I was waiting for...
...is here at last, Mona.
I can give you a good life.
And I'll also tell her...
Okay. When I say all this...
...what will Mona say?
How do I know, silly!
Why not go and ask her?
- Yes, why not? Stupid!
I'll go and meet her now,
and tell her everything.
Hey! Wish me luck at least.
God bless you.
- Yes. Thank you.
Wipe the powder properly...
What are you doing?
Cheena!
Mona! Mona!
Raja, get up! It's very late.
Raja!
I want to say something to you.
Yes?
Raja...
I don't know,
what I want to say...
...but keeping quiet will also
not be proper.
Raja...
It's not that I don't like you.
You're very nice.
My bum-chum.
And I always looked upon you
as a very good friend.
Who always laughed,
made others laugh.
I couldn't think of you
as anything else.
When you told Ravi...
...whatever you told him.
After that he stopped meeting me.
And when he did meet me,...
He told me all this,
after I questioned him.
He doesn't wish to be a
hinderance in your way.
And he said, had he known before...
...he'd have never become
so close to me.
Raja, I don't want to hurt you at all.
I want you to be happy in every way.
But you only tell me.
What should I do?
Shall I lie to you?
Because...the truth is...
...I love Ravi.
Raja!
If you can... please forgive me.
What happened? Why are
you laughing like this?
"If you can... please forgive me."
But, what is it?
I wasn't going to tell you.
But now that you became emotional,
I'll tell you.
The thing is you are an idiot.
A stupid fool.
Silly girl. Is there anything
up here, or not? No?
What do you mean?
What I mean is...
...you think if you don't tell me
about Ravi and yourself...
I won't know anything!
Am I blind?
I knew everything.
I said, "Okay, since both
are keeping me in the dark..."
"...I'll make them tell me.
I'll spin such a yarn..."
Listen. First I cornered Ravi.
And the idiot believed it immediately.
But I was scared that when
he tells you, you'd guess.
But you turned out to be
even a bigger fool than him.
See how I took you both for a ride?
You mean this was all a joke?
Then what else? You only said...
...I was your bum-chum, who
laughs; makes others laugh.
It was just a small prank,
and you started weeping...
Does anyone play such a prank?
Then how does one play it?
I won't leave you today!
- Not this... not this...
I won't spare you.
I won't spare you today.
You coward! Just you wait...
- I explained and you throw shoes...
Shoes? I'll break your head!
- No...
I won't let you get away.
What should I do?
Help! This girl is crazy...
You fraud, rascal...
Let go of me! Let go!
Either get angry, or laugh.
Silly girl!
You're very bad!
That I am. But can't help it.
But there's one thing.
Here, hold my hand.
Just because I told you everything
don't go and tell it to Ravi.
We'll needle him a bit more.
He's bugged as it is!
Only for 5 minutes.
No...
Two minutes? Okay?
Yes.
But, don't stretch it too far, okay?
I don't understand, Raja.
Mona, you said...
- I'll explain.
It's better you forget Mona.
She'll never be happy with you.
It's different with me.
We're from the same place.
Our way of life is
also similar, and...
You better explain it to him.
What Raja says is true.
I've also come to this
decision, that I...
Mona... - Oh Lord! Can't you
control yourself a bit?
Bungled it, didn't you?
- I couldn't stop myself...
See his face? That's what
you also looked like!
Why are you laughing?
- This was all his idea.
It was this prankster's joke.
But it wasn't a joke that day.
He wasn't joking. Ask him!
He is also laughing.
Listen to me, Mona.
- You don't know him.
See how seriously he
was talking just now?
Had I not burst out
laughing, this man...
No... I was going to
tell him today.
Look Ravi, this is all a joke!
Silly...
Remember? We had come to this
very place that day.
Yes.
- And what had I said?
I'm going to lie all day.
And you said...
"Finish your quota for the week.
Do what you like". Am I right?
Yes.
And I said all this after that.
And you didn't get it?
Yes... yes you did.
- Now he's saying "Yes"...
You're dangerous! You nearly...
- Put you through an acid test?
Yes.
If you hide something from a pal,
you'll be punished!
I wanted to tell you that day.
- Why didn't you?
With you...
We laughed so much today! Right?
Yes, and while laughing,
tears filled our eyes.
Forget it. May I say something?
I bless you with all my heart.
Be happy, always.
I know it for sure.
She loves you very much.
Promise, you'll never ever
leave her.
Raja... I promise.
I promise Mona, and you too.
See this ring.
It's my mother's.
And you're a witness. I want to
put it on her in your presence.
This ring is an assurance
of my love...
...and a lifelong promise too.
We'll always remember today. Right?
- It'll be remembered alright.
Let's have a celebration then.
Tell him. He made our life hell.
His punishment is, that
he'll throw a party for us.
That's no punishment.
Right
you sit, and I'll go now.
Where to?
There's a party.
Must make arrangements.
Tonight, at my place, okay?
Ravi...
His one prank may have
made us very unhappy...
But he's such a wonderful friend.
Isn't he?
"It's true, my love,
true love is something..."
"that is requitted
by the woman you love"
"Everything else is meaningless,
my dear friend"
"It's true, my love,
true love is something..."
"that is requitted
by the woman you love"
"Everything else is meaningless,
my dear friend"
"When you see someone
holding her hand..."
"you know that's the lucky guy"
"What distances,
what goals...?"
"they mean nothing when
your companion is with you"
"When she makes Lady Luck
smile upon you..."
"she's the woman for you,
my dear friend"
"I was always told
that life..."
"was about joys and sorrows"
"What I have seen, however..."
"that life is a game..."
"in which one wins and the
other loses all he has"
"As for me, I stand to lose,
my dear friend..."
"It's true, my love,
true love is something..."
"that is requitted
by the woman you love"
"Everything else is meaningless,
my dear friend"
We had fun at Raja's
house last night.
I hear he and Miss Joseph
have left for Goa.
Miss Joseph's sister lives there.
- Yes.
This chap Ravi... don't know much
about him, but he seems nice.
Papa. Why don't you ask
what you want to know?
Me? I don't want to ask anything.
Okay, don't ask anything,
but I'll answer you anyway.
Yes!
Ravi and I love each other.
We want to get married.
And he wants to talk to you
about this personally.
My dear!
You're being so childish.
Have you ever thought, who
he is and what we are?
They're very different from us.
We are poor people.
The lower class.
No, Papa.
Being rich and poor doesn't decide
whether a man is high class or not.
Neither Ravi believes in it,
and nor do I.
Tell me the truth.
Don't you approve of Ravi?
Nothing like that, my dear.
I just...
Your choice, is my choice.
Papa!
My dear... I just want...
...you to be happy.
Does his Grandmother know you?
Ravi's taking me to meet her today.
And listen...
You're looking beautiful.
Listen to me, Ravi.
Greetings, sir.
- Resham Singh.
Where's my Grandma?
- She has gone to Palnagar.
When?
- Just now at 4 o'clock.
Said she'll return tomorrow morning.
- Okay.
Okay.
If it's okay, then...
shall we go back?
Okay. What's your hurry anyway?
We'll go back.
Listen Resham Singh...
It's a day off for you servants.
It was Resham Singh calling.
You didn't believe me did you?
Well, go and see for yourself.
You're here, 50 miles away,
in Palnagar.
And there, Ravi has sent the
servants home.
And right now...
Ravi and that girl are all
alone in the bungalow!
My car! I'll go home, now!
- Yes, Ma'am.
Mona!
Listen to me.
I am not doing anything.
- Ravi, leave me.
Ravi, what are you doing?
Ravi!
"Let me go, please"
"Come closer, please"
"Don't touch me..."
"don't touch me, please"
"Let me come closer"
"Let me go, please"
"Come to me, come to me..."
"come to me, please"
"Let me go, please"
"Let me come closer, please"
"The story of my thirsty lips..."
"I've got to get closer
to tell you"
"They're things beyond
my comprehension..."
"don't get closer,
I may fall"
"Come to me, come to me..."
"come to me, please"
"Let me go, please"
"Come closer, please"
"I toss and turn all night..."
"my body's on fire"
"Desires that are awakened
in your heart..."
"mustn't be allowed to
burn out"
"Don't touch me, don't touch me..."
"don't touch me, please"
"Come to me, please"
"Let me go, please"
"Come to me, come to me..."
"come to me, please"
"Let me go, please"
"Come to me, please"
Grandma... she's Mona.
I had brought her to meet you,
but you weren't here. So...
Where do you live?
- I...
Here... in the village.
It's late. Go and leave her home.
It's late no doubt, but I...
Okay. Some other day I'll...
Some other day.
- Shall we go?
May I bring Mona to meet you
whenever you say so?
No need. I've seen her.
Heard about her from you, so,
it's not necessary to meet her.
But, just once...
- Tell her father...
...to come and meet me.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Okay. Send him to me.
Tomorrow morning.
Right.
At 10:30 sharp!
Do you think I should go there?
Something tells me
they are not like us.
Papa!
There you go again!
Why should we care about them?
Ravi's like us, isn't he?
That's fine. Now get up.
You've to reach there at 10:30.
Okay. Okay.
Good morning.
I'm...
- You! You're that girl's father.
What do you think?
Will they be talking now?
What does that mean? They are
either discussing or not discussing.
They must be discussing.
Throw him out of the house!
Let me go! And you...
Show the money-power to others!
My daughter will spit on your
money! You talk about her?
So what if we're poor? We're
much better than you at least.
Okay then. May I go now?
Wait, Ravi. Papa may have returned.
Make way... make way.
Get a cot, somebody.
Papa!
What happened to him?
Open your eyes, Papa.
Why doesn't he speak?
What's wrong with Papa?
Papa!
What happened to D'Silva?
- Kamladevi's men beat him up!
Really?
Grandma! Who the hell
do you think you are?
Who are you anyway? Don't
you have any decency?
You had called him over yourself.
I never thought you were calling
that gentleman over, to insult him!
Don't be stupid.
Only they feel insulted...
...who have any respect!
In your eyes, only you have it!
Because you have money!
But you better understand one thing.
He hadn't come begging to you.
You had no right to treat him so...
"Insultingly" is a very mild world.
- And this mild word...
...is so appropriate for
a lowly man like D'Silva!
He doesn't know how to tack!
I just said something to him...
...and he lost his control.
You must've insulted him cheaply.
One has to talk in that manner,
when one speaks the truth about them.
Such people have no control over
their tongue. He began to shout.
So my servants came and...
- How dare the servants manhandle...
My servants are loyal to me!
And they can't bear any one
speaking in a raised voice to me!
You'll have to apologise
to Mr. D'Silva and Mona.
You're not on your senses
at this moment.
Because only a mad person
would talk to me like this.
I've not heard such a thing
from anyone else before.
Then I'll say something which you
have heard before from your son.
I'm leaving your house!
I advise you to drop this idea.
Because when your father
had left this house...
...I had totally forgotten him.
But maybe I made a mistake.
Had I tried later on,
I may have saved him.
If you go, I'll keep you in mind.
I know that girl's not worthy of you.
Live wherever you want to. I won't
let that girl mar your life.
Grandma, this world has seen
many people like you before too.
Who tried to become God!
But neither they, nor you are God!
You are God in your company,
and in the 4 walls of this house.
And today I'm going out
of these 4 walls.
Where do you think you're going?
I'm going in to see D'Silva.
Aren't you satisfied even now?
We know who beat him and why.
Try to understand me. I came here...
- Get going!
If I see you anywhere near here
I'll kill you!
Why you do you think the girls from
our village have no self-respect?
You call people home and hit them?
- I've nothing to do with that.
Ravi!
Where are you going?
You shameless girl?
Mona!
Ravi!
Stop? Let go of me!
Stop! Look don't hit him. Please.
He's not at fault at all.
- Get up!
Your father's lying unconscious,
and you're out to humiliate us?
Get inside!
- Why don't you understand?
Ravi!
Mona!
Get inside!
- Leave me.
Mona!
- Ravi!
Mona
No!
No! No! No!
Take the rascal away!
Let me meet Mona. Please.
Upstairs, girl.
- Maria!
Tell them to let Ravi go.
Look, listen to me.
Mona!
Why don't you all listen?
- We'll see to her. Let her go.
Maria, please.
Mona!
Ravi!
- Let go of me! Let go, I say.
Mona!
I've left that house for good.
Why don't you all understand?
I've nothing to do with all this.
I had come to apologise to D'Silva.
No!
Throw him outside the town.
- No, please don't be so cruel.
I beg you!
Leave him alone. Let him go.
Ravi!
This work must be done
within 2 days!
All the loan papers
of all the village fishermen...
...whatever is with the village
moneylenders and contractors, buy it.
But, those people may not
be willing to sell, Madam.
We'll give them 4 times the amount.
Who can refuse such an offer?
How many more to go?
Give them the Court Order...
And finish this matter.
Mancha Ram! Who's he?
What's all this, Bosco?
Why is the police here?
It's all over. There's not a single
man here, who has a boat now.
We've all got Court Orders.
- Court orders, my foot!
I won't give them my boat!
- Your name's been called too.
What! Sir! Won't part with my boat.
Sir, if we give our boats,
how will we earn our living?
Why don't you also tell him?
- Just give me the papers.
What's your name.
- Surkiya.
Is this your signature?
- Yes.
You owe money to a money-lender.
You haven't paid him interest either.
And it clearly says here...
...that he can confiscate
your boat any time he likes.
But that's between him and me.
Who are you people?
That man has sold these papers,
that is your boat, which you claim...
...your own, to Kamladevi.
- How can he do that?
Let's see how anyone
takes away my boat!
Do things within the law.
Else you'll be jailed!
Make him understand. Next!
I told you.
I can't do anything.
But if you take away a boat
from a fisherman, he'll be ruined.
Look, only Madam can help you
in this matter.
Then shall we meet Madam?
- No!
But yes...
If D'Silva's daughter meets Madam,
Then Madam may agree.
What's happened?
All of you here. Like this.
Mona!
No! I didn't call you.
The villagers have sent you!
But why would you do that?
What do you have against them?
You live in this village!
- I ...
Look, Madam, I love Ravi.
And if this is a crime,
then let me be punished.
Why should others suffer?
They are not at fault.
I see!
So you do sympathise with them.
If you wish, that
I let them live...
...then you'll have to promise me,
that from this very moment...
...you won't meet Ravi again!
- What are you saying?
Don't say that. Listen to me...
- You're wasting my time now.
And you're ruining my life!
Don't you care about that?
And are you bothered, that because
of you, a village will be ruined?
Then... then what shall I do?
I'll give you 7 days.
Marry somebody else by then.
- What!
So that Ravi will believe...
...that you're out of his life...
Forever!
No! This cannot be.
If it can't be...
...then every man in the village
will be homeless and out of job!
And you'll be responsible for this.
Not me, but only you!
Don't say that. Don't be so cruel.
I'll do as you say. I promise.
I'll never utter Ravi's name.
I won't talk with him, but,
marrying somebody else...
I beg you!
I won't be able to do it.
I can't do it...
And another thing...
Don't come here again.
I'll know if you're married or not.
And so will the villagers.
"If you refuse, I'll go away."
"I'll live somehow, but I swear,
I'll miss you every moment of it"
"Life will go on without you,
but it won't be worth living!"
No!
This cannot be.
I just don't believe it.
But the sad part of
it is that it's true.
Mona will be married
in a few days now.
But with whom?
I couldn't find that out, but
the villagers say...
...that this is all due
to your grandma's pressure.
Hats off, Grandma...
You'll dictate my life.
And what you don't want,
shall never happen.
If you don't wish it,
I can't meet Mona.
My life is firmly in your hands,
and it shall always be so.
If you come back, I'll
give you back your life.
No, no... No Grandma.
I've not come to return to you.
I've came just to tell you...
...that my life may be in your hands...
...but my death is in my own hands.
I agree that Mona will get married.
But that day...
That day will be the last day
of my life.
If my life is in your hands...
...then, the day Mona marries,
your hands will become empty.
You've won, Grandma.
But I won't lose either.
How are you, Cheena?
All well?
D'Silva wants to see you.
Raja, who else will I think
of except you, Raja?
You know each other since
you both were kids.
And I always wished,
that you two would...
But now, the ball's in your court.
What do you say?
Okay, I'm ready for the marriage.
Yes, son Raja has come back.
He can help you. Shall
I go and talk to him?
No, don't.
I'll go myself. I'll...
But now, how can he help me?
- He'll do something.
He's your friend.
Raja!
Papa said you wanted to see me.
Oh yes. Come on in.
Here, take this. Sit down.
- No thanks.
I wanted to hear you say, that
you're willing for this marriage.
Is it true?
Raja. - Had you regarded me, a friend,
you wouldn't hide your pain from me.
I've come to know everything.
And I won't let you become
a sacrificial lamb.
You're wrong.
I'll do it. I want to do it.
Look at me!
Look into my eyes.
And now say that you
don't love Ravi.
That you can live without him.
And that you don't care for him.
Go on, say it!
Sit down.
Mona, did you give
a thought to Ravi?
He made everybody his foe, for you.
And you gave in so easily?
I'm not giving in, Raja.
But what can I do? Tell me.
If I don't marry somebody else,
the company people will...
You think if you ruin your life...
...the Company people will allow
this village to live freely?
If they can ruin this town...
...even if you kill yourself, they'll
do it. If not now, then later.
But, we'll fight. And this
fight will continue.
Look. Don't spoil your own life.
Whatever may happen,
I'll see to it.
Now wipe your tears. And listen.
Tonight I'm taking you to Ravi.
You both go away
very far from here.
Let's see who stops you!
Now, come.
And remember, don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
I thought Gods existed
only in stories.
Mona!
Everyone is not blessed
to be a human-being.
Some people have to become God!
Now go.
Go on, go...
But why are you doing this?
So okay, friendship is fine.
But I won't let you
risk your life like this.
I know you're feeling
very bad for me.
That's why you're saying this.
But whatever I'm doing...
...had Ravi been in my shoes,
he'd have done the same.
And when I had told him about
my love, accidentally...
...he had done the same.
May be, even more.
What can be more than this?
Don't I know, how you,
laughed off your lifelong love...
...in a mere moment?
And those two...
...thinking it a joke,
have already forgotten it!
Why don't you also take it
as a joke, and forget it?
You're telling me this?
Will you be able to forget?
No.
I love Mona, even today.
...and I'll always love her.
It has gone waste but hasn't ended.
It's a fact that I'll never
forget my love for Mona.
But neither can I forget
the love of Mona and Ravi.
Today I'll bring them
together... for good.
It's expected of me
and I'll do it.
But I think you should
take it easy.
Ravi will himself apologise.
- He'll not come.
He has his father's blood in him!
He'll give his life for her.
He'll commit suicide, but
he'll never come back!
I lost my own son once, like this.
But now, I can't lose Ravi too.
Go and tell him, I agree
to whatever he says.
He has won. And I have lost.
This is...
How was I to know that
the old hag will suddenly...
...get a spurt of love for Ravi?
- And what a fantastic spurt too!
But this doesn't mean I'll let my
lifelong hopes be drowned like this.
Kamladevi's property and
wealth, should come to me!
Only me!
And this will be decided...
...tonight itself!
You're not leaving forever.
One day you'll come to meet
us all, with Ravi. Isn't it?
If anyone sees you leaving
the village... Come on!
Well? Where are you taking her?
Look. Today I'm in a hurry.
And you people too...
- Hey, you girl...
Hold on.
You go, Mona.
Raja!
- You go to Ravi.
I'll tend to these people.
I should have gone away
much earlier. Anyway...
If not then, now at least.
- But, Ravi, you...
If it's Raja, I'm not here.
I've already gone.
Where is Ravi?
- But, who are you?
Don't ask questions, old
geyser. Just answer us.
Where's Ravi?
- Here I am.
What do you want?
Ravi...
Uncle...
Vikram!
Yes, Ravi. It's me.
But why be so surprised?
No, I'm not surprised.
I know you're a swine.
But I never knew you were
a rascal, and so cheap too.
Call me anything you wish,
but the fact remains...
...that the real heir to
Kamladevi's estate...
...is me.
But that adamant hag...
...wants to hand over all
her estate and wealth to you.
Because you are her blood!
Mona...
- Ravi...
Why do they want to kill you?
Don't kill him.
You're very lucky, Ravi.
Even your last wish is fulfilled.
Before dying, meet your beloved too.
Now you shouldn't feel
so very bad to die!
What are you saying? What do you
have against him? Why kill him?
Don't kill him... I beg you.
Don't kill him.
No, Mona...
My heart has melted
seeing your love for him.
Okay. I won't kill him.
Don't believe me?
Ravi, your Grandma thinks...
...that you love this girl
so much, that for her...
...you'll even commit suicide!
If you can really do it, then...
Turn around. Go to that revolver...
...pick it up;
Aim it at your temple...
And pull the trigger. Else...
No!
Raja!
- Mona, you're alright, aren't you?
But where's Ravi?
- Ravi?
There he is!
Come on, let's not waste time.
Before any further trouble,
you both get out of here.
And you?
- Forget it.
Look Ravi, you both
better get out of here, very fast.
Yes. I'm going.
But alone.
Ravi!
This afternoon I had
been to your house.
I heard you talking to Miss Joseph.
Raja...
What did you and Miss Joseph
talk about?
Nothing.
What matters is that you love...
- There's another matter too Mona.
Which if I hide from you, will
seem very dishonest of me.
Raja loves you.
Long before I ever did, and may
be much more than I do.
No. This is not true. Not true!
It is true, Mona.
The only truth!
We were lost in our happiness
and never knew Raja's heartbreak.
We laughed, and
he laughed with us.
We never saw that his laughter
crossed many a sea of sorrow.
You are Raja's hope, desire, life.
Only you, Mona.
But see, today also, he's handing
over his life to me!
No...
Make him understand, Mona.
It's not like that. Tell him, Mona.
I'm nothing in your eyes.
We're poles apart, Mona.
How can I even dare
to think that you...
And even if I did dare...
So what?
If a child cries for the moon...
...he hardly gets to hold it.
Raja...
One shouldn't be so very nice...
...as to make others feel
so very ashamed.
What didn't you do for me?
And I...
I just made you sad.
Why did you oblige me so?
- But I haven't...
I've not obliged anybody.
I just did what my heart dictated.
Now you also listen to your
own heart. Go with him.
Start a new life, with...
- We can't do that, Mona!
When I know everything.
Even if I get you, this guilt
will never let me live...
Forget me, and think of yourself.
Will you be able to crush his dream?
Will you be happy by making him sad,
and face yourself in the mirror?
No! No! No!
No!
What's wrong with you two?
Now that your goal is near...
...why are you punishing
yourselves in this manner?
Go...
Raja!
Vikram!
Come, Mona.
- No... Listen to me.
Oh no...
- No...
What life couldn't decide,
Death has decided.
No, Raja, No!
- You'll be fine, Raja.
Raja!
Son!
Miss Joseph!
Raja!
What happened to you, son?
What's wrong?
The arms that gave me life,
let death too come in them!
What more can I want?
- No, my son.
Don't say that... Don't!
Don't say that.
Miss Joseph!
Make the villagers understand...
Don't separate these
two from each other.
They both... love each other...
...very much...