Far from human habitat,
deep in the jungle, amid animals
live seven brothers.
This could be the reason
for their animalistic demeanor.
Here, headbutts are used to express
happiness, and punches, to express love.
Wake up!
These rascals plan to sleep all day.
Get up!
I'll count to three and
if you aren't up,
I will force... every single one of you...
to take a shower!
Alright.
One!
Two!
-No!
-We're up!
Open your eyes and look at me.
And listen carefully.
Som, you'll milk the cow today.
-What if she refuses to yield?
-I'll milk you!
-Chop the wood and load the warehouse.
-The axe is blunt.
Use a razor then.
Yes, Budh.
Clean the stables and the chicken coop.
Why? I love the scent
of cow dung in the morning.
Sniff your clothes
if you miss the scent.
-Irrigate the field.
-What's the point?
We can eat at the hotel
and be happy.
I'll beat the hell out of you!
Just follow my instructions.
Yes?
You'll cook... but first do the dishes.
Why would I touch the water?
Because if you don't,
I'll drown you in it.
Cut the grass and store
it in the backyard.
Why should I do that?
Let the grass grow.
The cattle can graze in the field itself.
Grains grow in the field as well.
Why do we cook it?
Why don't we eat it
directly in the field?
Go!
This is unfair.
You order us around every day.
"Milk the hens...
Chop the horse's wood
and clean the stable of the field."
And all you do is sit comfortably
in your chair and watch us!
I'm your elder brother.
An elder brother is like a father
and the sons must obey their father!
Does fatherhood prohibit a father
from helping his children out?
What is fatherhood?
It's similar to motherhood!
Tell me, does it stop you?
Yes, it does.
Of course it does.
Because I'm your commander.
The commander plans the war.
He doesn't fight the battle himself.
Fine, each one of us should
get a chance to be the commander!
Right, brothers?
-That's right!
-Just a minute...
Who wants to be what?
Each of us wants to
be the commander for a day.
All those who wish to be the
commander, step forward.
Stand in line.
-So, you want to be the commander?
-Yes!
-What if I don't let you?
-We'll protest!
We'll raise our voice against injustice!
-Fulfill our demands!
Now tell me, what is your response?
-You want an answer?
-Yes.
It's pretty simple.
One for all, all for one!
Go ahead.
These rascals wish to be the commander!
Lunch is ready!
Brother isn't here yet.
You'll get us all beaten up.
-I'm hungry!
-Get lost!
Are you alright?
I mean, is this all you'll eat?
This is for you guys.
I'll starve to death!
Fire!
We must teach Shani a lesson!
We always forgive him
because he's the youngest!
Yes.
He fools us every day.
Sometimes he faints...
At times, he fakes
a stomachache.
He fakes fever with
an onion under his arm.
-What will you do?
-You tell us.
What are you mumbling?
We have such a heavy head.
It must contain a small brain!
-Think!
-Brother, thinking is not our cup of tea.
-Try...
-I can't.
I got it! Come here.
Bravo! Bravo!
He's coming.
The flame has ignited, my heart beats
I can't believe Ravi would
give us such a great opportunity.
Why won't he?
We're his younger brothers after all.
We may look different
but our hearts are one.
Yes, you are right.
-What is the matter?
-I'll tell you.
Ravi has placed a bet.
The one who wins it...
He gets a break of seven days.
He'll get milk and cream
every hour and sweet fruits...
He gets to hog all day.
-Yes, eat to your heart's content.
-What's the bet?
-Very simple, tame an ordinary horse.
-Milk and cream.
That's it? Which horse?
Hope you don't mean
that white wild horse?
-Yes...
-Yes, that's the one.
But Ravi has prohibited
us from going near him.
He has asked us to stay away from
him until he is fully trained.
-He can break our bones!
-If I could get a week off...
I'd never get out of bed.
I'd neither wash my face nor
rinse my mouth or change clothes.
I'd eat there...
drink there, and I'd...
do everything right there.
I'd dream, get up and eat...
Go back to sleep, dream again
get up, eat and go back to bed.
But how can we get
a break for seven days?
How?
-It's my fault.
-I tricked him...
I'm to be blamed.
Get a wet cloth.
Open your eyes, my boy.
Who did this?
Who asked Shani to ride Raja?
Answer me!
Listen to me carefully.
If anything happens to my Shani...
I won't spare you!
If you hate your little brother
so much, I'll take him and leave!
You may keep this house,
farm, field! I want nothing!
I'll only take my Shani and leave.
Son... open your eyes.
-This...
-I'm absolutely fine.
Nothing is wrong with me.
Your little brother won't
die even if an elephant crushes him.
The horse is nothing.
Then why did you get us slammed?
Forgive me.
Actually, I was testing Ravi.
I was just checking the love he has
for us in his tender heart,
hidden beneath his tough exterior.
There is love. Loads of it.
But Ravi doesn't love us.
Yes, I don't love you.
Go die under the horse's foot...
then you'll see how much I love you.
Come here...
My sturdy brother cries like a girl.
Don't ever say you'll leave us.
You won't go? Right?
Where can I go?
Can the body leave the soul?
You are my soul.
We'll lead our lives together...
Singing our hearts out
We're the colors of a rainbow
That brighten up the world
We'll lead our lives together...
Singing our hearts out
We're the colors of a rainbow
That brighten up the world
We're the base of melody
The verses are sung about us
The sky sways
We are the seven wonders of the world
The world exists for us
We're the base of melody
The verses are sung about us
The sky sways
We are the seven wonders of the world
The world exists for us
We'll lead our lives together...
Singing our hearts out
We're the colors of a rainbow
That brighten up the world
We share joy
We share our sorrows
Why would tears blind us?
We'll go on with each other's support
We share joy
We share our sorrows
Why would tears blind us?
We'll go on with each other's support
We'll lead our lives together...
Singing our hearts out
We're the colors of a rainbow
That brighten up the world
We'll lead our lives together...
Singing our hearts out
We're the colors of a rainbow
That brighten up the world
-Hello...
-Good day to you Ravi.
10 tins of kerosene, 1 sack of sugar,
5 kg tea, 2 tins butter...
Ravi, one minute.
By the time you get your stuff packed...
-may we go for a ride?
-Okay.
Listen... no liquor, right?
-Not at all. We're going to have milk.
-Okay.
Come on!
Where was I...?
Yes, 10 kg of salt, 2 of red chili...
1 kg of coriander,
1 kg of cumin, 1/2 kg of bleak pepper...
Bleak pepper?
What's bleak pepper?
Go to the milk bar next door
and get 2 bottles of milk. Take it.
Milk?
-But sir...
-No...
When we go there,
we'll ask for your stuff.
Get 2 bottles of milk.
Need nipples?
Did you say something?
I said if kids ask for milk
in a bottle, give them a nipple.
Because either they don't have
teeth or the teeth won't stay.
Let it be.
They're kids.
Forget it or we'll
be cremated right here.
They are six and we're two.
No!
Not two, there's three of us.
One, two and three.
The 7-foot fellow has here!
Now turn into lions, you rats.
Grass eating lions.
No, milk suckling calves!
The bull...
The bull doesn't care about
the whimpering of small fry.
They have to clear the path for the bull.
But you look more like a
buffoon than a bull.
Buffoon.
-What do I look like?
-Buffoon!
-Whom did I ask?
-Him.
I asked him. You shut up.
-So, what do I look like?
-Baf--
They were calling a bull, a buffoon.
They see no difference between the two.
A bull is a bull while
a buffoon is a buffoon.
A bull is a bull whereas
-Mr. Bull, would you like some milk?
-Yes.
Open it.
Open it, fast.
What are you doing?
Leave me.
Ravi! Help!
Get some milk, Shani.
Scoundrel! I'll...!
Ravi... Milk!
-You drink it.
-Who can win against sorrows?
What did you say?
Who can win against me?
Not against me...
Shekhar?
What have you done to yourself?
-What is this, what's wrong?
-There's this girl I love...
with all my heart.
But she doesn't.
-Who?
-The one I pledged my life, my faith to.
But what happened? Where did she go?
No clue.
I have only loved two things in my life.
One the girl, and the other was my job.
-I've lost both.
-You can always get a new job
but you want the same girl, right?
Give me her name and address.
Let me handle it.
What the... who are you?
Later. First tell me
who do you think you are?
What?
What do you think of yourself?
Have you descended from the sky?
Are you the daughter of an emperor?
A princess?
Why are you so arrogant? Just because
you're blessed with a pretty face?
What right do you have
to play with a man's life?
I'm asking you.
-He's must be crazy...
-The poor guy is a gentleman.
If it was me, I'd have wrung your
neck like a chicken and dumped you!
-Who are you talking about?
-You made him an alcoholic!
The one who is drinking
his life away because of you.
I'm referring to my childhood
friend, Shekhar! Who else?
Yes! Go and see how he has
tortured himself!
Beggars give him alms when
they pass him on the streets!
Each time he'd meet me he'd say,
Sheela is my life.
Sheela has changed my entire life.
Sheela this and Sheela that!
And you cheat! Haughty woman!
You left him because he lost his job!
What are you glaring at?
Do you have an answer?
-You want an answer?
-Yes!
Now listen to me. If you say a word,
I'll throw the bed, chair...
and disfigure your face!
Firstly, I'm not Sheela!
Secondly, my name is Indu!
Understood?
I overheard everything.
I have realized my mistake. I'd like
to meet Shekhar and apologize.
-Where is he?
-Sorry...
He's drinking bar on
the hill at Alcohol Road.
What?
I mean he's drinking
alcohol in a bar at Hill Road.
Excuse me...
this friend of yours who just went...
Where's her room? I'd like to meet her.
-Even after that hard slap?
-Because of that hard slap!
The last room in this corridor, it's
hers.
Okay.
Thanks.
What is it?
Watermelon? Who sent it?
There's a tall man standing down.
He sent it for you.
-He also sent a letter.
-You may go.
This time I want to meet
you for my sake, not Shekhar's.
Please accept this small
token of our friendship.
Hello... I've come...
Is this the first gift you give a girl?
A watermelon?
What's wrong? Melons are healthy.
Strength won't help you
in winning her over.
Send her flowers.
-What?
-Flowers...
Flowers.
Watchman!
-Yes, madam?
-If I see this fool here once more...
-you'll lose your job! Understood?
-Yes.
Did you hear that?
Get out. Have you seen my staff?
Quiet! Repeat what
you said down there.
I was kidding. Put me down.
I'll lose my job if anyone sees me.
The flowers didn't work.
I must think of something else...
So, the patient is your brother?
-Yes, my elder brother.
-What's his problem?
He has many problems, sister.
First it was only his
heart that was affected.
-Now his whole body is affected.
-What do you mean?
I mean...
he fell in love and kept
his heart at the girl's feet.
But the girl kicked it
away like it was a football!
The innocent man's heart was smashed.
In the heat of the moment,
he tried to kill himself!
He jumped... from a high mountain!
What? What happened next?
Thank God, he's alive.
Did this affect the girl?
That's what we want to know.
Would it affect you?
Of course. I'm a human
I'd appreciate the person...
I'd have accepted his love
and apologized to him.
Ravi's job is done.
She's here! Go to your rooms
and don't come out till I say so!
Why should we go to the room,
if a girl is coming over?
It's a girl, not the military!
-Who is the girl?
-Yes.
Quiet! Get inside or be thrashed.
Wait.
Nobody will step out of their rooms.
-Okay.
-No.
Nobody, nobody will make a sound.
-Not a sound. Okay?
-Yes!
We'll shove a silencer down our throats.
-Your house is beautiful.
-You can't see it from here.
You should see our backyard, we have
such lovely trees and gardens...
-You'll be amazed at the flowers.
-Really?
Come.
-Now let's go.
-Son of a gun!
-Is she here for a guided tour?
-Even the cauliflower...
Oh my God!
-What was that?
-Your brother is in pain.
-Yes.
-Let's see him first.
Okay. Let's go.
-Please help me!
-Come in.
Oh my God!
Are you in a lot of pain?
My treatment will help you with the pain.
You'll should be able to move around soon.
-What's this?
-He's in a lot of pain.
If anyone touches him,
he trembles from head to toe.
Don't worry. I'll help him with it.
You're a man and you've
let a girl do this to you!
-What's he saying?
-He says...
If I don't get that girl,
I'll cut myself into tiny
pieces and throw at her feet.
How will that help?
What good is ruining
your life for another?
The real deal is, when you live
and she lives with your love.
-What is he saying?
-My brother says...
Thank you, but why are you
empathizing with a poor guy like me?
Why not? I am a human, too.
I have a heart and I know
what he must be feeling.
Can your heart really
understand what my heart says?
-You!
-Yes, I've gone completely mad!
I don't know what's happening.
I can't sleep...
like an owl, I stay up nights.
I sleep in the day
and see you everywhere!
In the doors, windows, pot...
I see you in the bread too.
That day, it wasn't just a melon,
I gave you my heart.
Cheat! Fake! Fraud!
You used suicide and this dramatic
brother of yours to get me here!
Do I look dramatic?
Quiet! What do you think?
I'd sympathize with you
on hearing about suicide?
I'd start liking you!
You can jump off from the sky
instead of mountain and die...
It won't affect me at all!
You're treating me like trash.
Trash! Trash is better than you!
Take a look at yourself
if you have a mirror at home!
If you don't, I'll lend you some money
to buy a mirror to look into!
Your face will scare you!
Filthy! Smelly!
Haven't showered for months!
I get scared as soon as you come close.
It is like if you've come from a stable!
Do you think a girl will like you
or fall in love with you?
You're not something to be loved,
You're something to be scared off!
-But...
-If you dare to follow me...
Or you try to trouble me...
I'll have you sent to prison!
Understood?
Don't!
You want to bring
a girl here to order us around!
We won't let this happen!
Have you ever thought,
if a girl joins this house,
our lives will be a living hell.
No way. We won't let
a girl enter our home? Never.
-We don't want her.
-Stupid jerks!
Can't you see I'm doing
this for you?
How is this gonna help us?
If a woman comes here,
she'll make tasty food for you.
She'll do the dishes
and sweep and swab...
-She'll cook...
-Yes.
-And clean too?
-Sweep...?
-Obviously.
That means no problems.
No problems at all.
We never thought of that.
Do something. She came in like
a cool breeze and left like a storm!
Don't worry,
I'll talk to her and get her back.
-Like the cool breeze...
-Really?
Yes. But for the
time being you get lost.
Let me think of a plan to coax her back.
-Go...
-Come on.
Ravi, what are you doing?
Deceiving a simple girl...
isn't the right thing to do.
I am a great actor, aren't I?
I said all this bullshit to stop
our army from revolting.
The truth is... I really love her.
You're looking exquisite. Beautiful.
The moon itself
won't be able to withstand such beauty.
I fear for your poor husband.
This is Indu, my best friend.
-Greetings.
Your best friend is
here but my best friend...
How has a flower bloomed
in the midst of a desert?
The suit, the perfume...
the clean-shaven look...
-Neat and tidy... Terrific!
-My good man.
Somebody told me that...
the beauty of one's heart doesn't matter,
what matters is the beauty of their body.
One's thoughts don't matter...
if the clothes they wear are smart.
So, I decided to give it a try.
-You seem to be in love?
-I tried giving a girl my heart, but...
she dumped it as if it were a watermelon.
My beloved,
How long will you torment me?
I'll light a fire in
Your heart that will melt you
My beloved,
How long will you torment me?
I'll light a fire in
Your heart that will melt you
One day... you will fall in love
I'll light a fire in
Your heart that will melt you
When you think of me
In your lonely moments...
You'll be surrounded by my memories
When you think of me
In your lonely moments...
You'll be surrounded by my memories
Your heart will beat
With anticipation and passion
My beloved,
how long will you torment me?
I'll light a fire in
your heart that will melt you
You'll bloom when our hearts unite
You'll be swinging in my arms
You won't be in your senses
You will fall in love
My beloved,
how long will you torment me?
I'll light a fire in
your heart that will melt you
One day... you will fall in love
I'll light a fire in
your heart that will melt you
Congratulations.
Yes?
One minute.
Congratulations.
Come.
What was that?
Nothing, I was just looking
for the firecrackers.
Why do you need firecrackers?
Use your brain sometimes.
Our brother is bringing
his wife home for the first time.
We must arrange a grand welcome.
I'm so happy.
I had never imagined
I'd find a man like yourself.
You and your younger brother...
just three of us...
far from the bustling city.
Peace and quiet all around.
Can't you see? Are you blind?
-Donkey...
-Mind your tongue!
I hate noise and yelling.
I see. You hate yelling.
Yes.
I'm in trouble...
How dare you beat up my little brother!
Why are you quiet? Say something.
What can I say?
Your thoughts worry me a little.
-Worry?
-Yes... worry with a little bit of joy.
Like tears of joy...
it's worry with joy.
You like cleanliness,
tranquility, hate fights...
and most importantly you're
happy that there's just the three of us.
I'm doomed.
What?
Groom... I can't believe I'm finally
a groom.
Sister-in-law, your dramatic
brother-in-law welcomes you.
Hello.
You know him... Shani,
my little brother.
And this is our home,
our little heaven, our--
Sister-in-law.
My brother.
This is my second
scoundrel... my brother...
Hello.
He's the third.
Hello, sister-in-law.
Let me show you my farm.
No... why would we go around...
our clothes have gotten a little dirty.
Mine too.
-Shall we... go in?
-Welcome.
Sister-in-law.
Come.
This is the living room where
this is where we--
He's my fourth brother, Som.
And the fifth...
-Hello sister-in-law.
-He's my...
I know!
-Your sixth brother.
-Yes, Budhu...
-Budh.
-Yes.
Is that all?
Or do you have a few more?
-There's just seven of us.
-Just seven?
My father wanted a family
big enough to pack stadiums.
But...
He named us after days.
Shani is the youngest and I'm the eldest.
Had you been more than seven...?
-January. February. March. April. May.
-Wow! Amazing!
What a calendrical family!
What is special about our bond
is the love that we share...
-I cannot explain it.
-I'm not asking for an explanation.
-We'd die for each other.
-I can see that.
What?
What is this?
-Kitchen!
-More like a mad house!
Whatever. This is all we have.
Call it whatever you like.
But make it as beautiful as you are.
Don't be romantic.
My head is reeling.
Let me clean up. Go out.
Listen to me, Indu.
Rustle up such a meal
that we eat up the plates too.
We haven't eaten well since mother died.
All we make is either under-cooked
or overdone. Salt in place of sugar...
Chili instead of salt.
Kerosene instead of oil...
Forget it. Go and relax.
I'll call you soon as food is ready.
Where do I begin?
Dinner is ready. Be quick.
What are you waiting for? Dig in.
I see... thank God,
you have some manners.
Stop it! I say, stop!
Animals! You are all animals!
Is this the way to eat?
I cooked for you with
such love and cleanliness!
And you're devouring the food like
animals.
You don't deserve it!
You're all animals!
That is what you'll always be!
Is she here to cook or to dominate us?
You said you were getting a maid?
Don't touch me! Go away!
You're a cheat! You lied to me!
You'd told me Shani
is the only family you have.
You feigned innocence
and brought me here!
You told your brothers that
you're getting them a maid!
She will cook and clean the house.
Am I here to be their maid?
I quit my job, my city
and followed you here to this madhouse!
This is very wrong. You cheated me.
You broke my heart. Ruined my life!
You are right.
I admit my fault.
I lied to you, deceived you.
I did try to tell you the
truth but didn't have the guts.
If I'd told you about my brothers,
you'd want to meet them.
You would never marry me
after meeting them.
I would have lost you.
I did this to win your love.
Really...
We are animals.
There's no difference between us but...
What could we do?
We were very young
when our parents died.
We were never scolded by a father
nor were we pacified by a mother.
There was nobody to hold
our finger and show us the path.
We just held each
other and came this far.
Living on this farm with the
cows and goats, we have become animals.
I realize my mistake.
I don't want to ruin
your life along with mine.
Tomorrow...
I'll take you back to the city.
You can go back to the
world of honor and etiquette.
You won't have to live with these animals.
Stay here... just for the night.
I'll take you back tomorrow.
Sister-in-law.
Please forgive your younger brothers.
We've all come to beg for forgiveness.
If our words have hurt you,
please hit us!
Beat us black and blue!
But don't leave us!
If you leave,
we'll all be lonely, very lonely.
Nobody has ever helped us.
Honestly. And we just look big,
but we're children at heart.
Won't you forgive your children?
If you leave, Ravi too will leave us.
Without both of you, we'll be orphaned.
Sister-in-law, please.
Forgive us!
Looks like my animals can cry.
Wipe your tears. Men don't cry.
I forgive all of you.
Now go and tell your
28 feet tall brother...
If he has any sense,
he must come up immediately.
It's our first day of marriage.
He must come with a smile.
Go on.
Get up! Wake up you bull!
-Thief!
-Get up.
Get up, you hippo!
Why are you yelling early in the morning?
I've been dreaming for six days.
Each time I'm about to grab the girl,
somebody wakes me up!
Take look around our room
and you'll all scream!
-Look...
-Our clothes!
Strut around in your underwear now!
-Hold on... where's Shani?
-Not here.
-No?
-He's behind this!
-Are you awake?
-Sister-in-law!
Yes. We are ready.
Get up. Your brother
is taking us for a picnic.
Yes.
We would get ready but that rascal
Shani took our clothes.
Shani didn't do it,
I took all your clothes.
Sister-in-law, you?
What will you do with our clothes?
I'll wash them.
Why are you ruining them?
Clothes should never be washed.
Your clothes were
so filthy and stinky...
that a rat would fall dead after
sniffing them!
I washed them in boiling
water yet they're dirty.
You have ruined our clothes.
Come out, shower and get ready.
-What?
-Shower and shave...
wear clean clothes and
join us for the picnic like humans.
Water makes me sick.
I faint if I see anyone showering.
God has graced us with such lovely hair,
why should we shave it off?
-Sister-in-law.
Will you come out or should I come in?
She's bluffing. We're in such a
shabby state. She won't come in.
Yes, you are right.
I'm asking for the last
time, are you coming out or...
-No! We won’t!
-Okay, then I'll come in.
No!
-Come out fast.
-Oh my God!
Sister-in-law...
Only you can change these beasts.
What I couldn’t do for years,
you did it in just two days.
I'm here to change all
seven not just these five.
What are you waiting for?
Out.
-Where to?
-Go take a shower.
I dry cleaned myself
the day we got married.
You'll have to jump
in the water and bathe.
Quiet.
Come on. Come on.
What are you looking at? Come on.
Clean and smooth
It's a Topaz shave
Nose.
Look at my face, Topaz, Topaz
Topaz
All ready? Let's get started.
Ravi, what happened?
Stomach... ache!
Press his stomach!
-What are you doing?
-Your leg ached the other day.
It was better once we pressed it.
So we're pressing your stomach!
Stop! Will you press
my neck if it hurts?
Yes.
Move aside...
-What's going on?
-His stomach aches.
No... everything seems fine.
I'm not faking it.
I can feel the pain deep inside my body.
Get the bags.
We'll cancel the picnic.
Don't cancel the picnic.
I'm feeling better.
No, Ravi.
We can't go leaving you here like this.
My sweets, my baby...
You go on.
Yes. Indu will take care of me.
How can we leave you here like this?
-They are right.
-You're funny.
They've really been looking forward
to the picnic.
Let them go. How can I stop them?
Leave right now! Go!
-Yes, let's go.
-Come on.
-Good.
Are you alright?
-Yes. I am fine.
-Let's go.
Finally.
-Your stomach...
-Excuse to get rid of them.
If the battalion stays here...
how can the commander enjoy himself?
Come here.
What a relief!
Girls!
Glorious weather, unknown destination
There's a tale waiting
To be told at some curve
Glorious weather, unknown destination
There's a tale waiting
To be told at some curve
Often, my heart starts pounding
The glow of youth torments me
When will my heart
Belong to another?
For the time being it's mine
Glorious weather, unknown destination
There's a tale waiting
To be told at some curve
Certain thoughts scare me
Nights full of
Love are around the corner
Certain thoughts scare me
Nights full of
Love are around the corner
Everyone knows fools fall in love
Have no fears for it is inevitable
Glorious weather, unknown destination
There's a tale waiting
To be told at some curve
You fool! Why didn't you run
when you saw the boulder?
These rich people need maids
to help them escape death too!
You are right.
Excuse me but she's not one of
those who can't move without maids.
In fact, she's one of those rich people...
...who can't move at all.
Can't move? Her feet seem alright.
Is she a cripple? Is she handicapped?
You are right. She can't walk.
We're sorry. We shouldn't have said
the things we did.
We didn't know about you.
We spoke nonsense.
Doesn't matter.
A cripple...
gets used to bitter medicines
as well as bitter words.
I'm used to it.
The thing is... we're all idiots.
There's no connection between our tongue
and our brain. The wiring is messed up.
Please smile...
What are your names?
I am Seema. This is Madhu.
This is Rachna.
This is Prema.
I am Guru.
We're so glad to meet you.
The Red Cross Society is having
a program on Sunday. You must come.
Of course.
Should I...
We... did it!
Quiet! I don't want
to hear you excuses!
All of you are useless!
Good for nothing!
I do everything for you!
I provide you with every possible comfort!
But the six of you can't
look after my poor niece!
-Shame on you!
-It's not their fault.
-I asked them to go.
-But why did they leave you?
They should always be
with you. That's their duty!
God forbid, if the
boulder would have touched you...
how would I face the world?
Everyone would say an uncle
got his rich niece killed...
because she's going to be 21...
and she's going to inherit millions.
None of you know...
how difficult it is to
be a trustee to a wealthy heiress.
People suspect you all the time.
I pray to God that you
complete your 21st birthday...
I'll hand over every
penny of your inheritance...
and...
I'll go far away.
If I have hurt you...
It's not my fault.
I swear, I did my best!
But...
I hate unprofessional men.
-Had it not been for the boys...
-Whatever, the girl is still alive!
Isn’t she?
Get out.
But darling,
we have time on our hands.
And she lives with you,
crushing her should be an easy task.
-Isn't it?
-No.
You are wrong.
-I can't do this at home.
-Why?
If she is killed outside,
they cannot blame me.
Only Babu can do this.
Who’s Babu?
A devil in a human form.
Where is he?
Serving his sentence in a prison.
Once Babu is released from the jail...
he'll release Seema from this earth.
No. No way!
None of you will go
to the Red Cross party!
Why not? The poor girls have invited us
so decently, with such love.
With love? With decency?
Do you know what love or decency is?
-Of course, we do.
-What is decency?
Decency... it means...
What is it? It's...
It's very nice.
Why are you looking at me?
Talk to her.
Don't embarrass yourself. Sit tight.
Have you seen how you walk?
You look like seven prisoners
released after life imprisonment!
When you speak, it sounds
as if somebody is throwing vessels!
If you open your mouth in the city,
all the girls will flee!
So the best thing is
to sit at home quietly.
Sister-in-law.
Nobody learns everything in the womb.
You learn it after birth.
From your own people
and all we have...
is you. Please teach us.
-Please...
-Very well. I'll try.
-Hey sister-in-law!
-Please teach us!
Play some tune.
Bow respectfully and ask her...
Not like this.
Please act it out.
Bow respectfully and ask her...
When she asks you, how do you do...
Just say...
Did you get it?
Bow respectfully and ask her...
When she asks you, how do you do...
Just say...
Really?
Let me see how you do it.
Not so soon, my love.
She'll blush, if she likes you
That's how, you'll know...
If the fish has taken the bait
She'll blush, if she likes you
That's how, you'll know...
If the fish has taken the bait
Look into her eyes and
Tell her that she's cast a spell on you
When she asks you,
What's the spell?
Tell her...
Why are you quiet?
Yes.
Now you're getting it!
-Shall we proceed?
-Just a minute.
Shut up!
I've some serious doubts.
What if she doesn't blush?
Silly.
If she doesn't blush, some other girl
will.
-Really?
-Yes!
Hold her hand lovingly
And take her to a corner
She'll be a little scared
Just like you
Hold her hand lovingly
And take her to a corner
She'll be a little scared
Just like you
Hold her and say...
Don't be silent.
-Where did I go wrong?
-At this point... say... I love you!
It's a fair of fairies
Every heart is alone
Let the hearts meet, the spring is here
Glorious weather
Unknown is the destination.
A tale waits to unfold
It's a fair of fairies
Every heart is alone
Let the hearts meet, the spring is here.
You think this is bad?
I've seen worse.
Sit tight! One word from you...
I'll burn your back with a flaming log!
I know you have a strong body!
I had taught these fools everything!
And you ruined it!
Those city boys... bred in the gutter!
I should have watched
them beating up my brothers!
-What honor would we have left with?
-Great. After what you've done...
the entire city must
be gossiping about you!
The cops could have locked all of us up.
What do you mean? We should have been
humble boys and asked them...
"Brothers, beat us up. You own us.
Tell us when you are tired
so that we can drop you off home."
What nonsense!
Fine. Do as you please.
And I'll do as I please.
-Don't say that...
-Let go. I'm furious!
If you get furious, what will we eat?
-Stop kidding.
-You were there.
Tell us did we pick a
fight or did they force us?
But I want to know why did you fight?
They were present. How could
we get thrashed in front of them?
-Who?
-They...
From the day we met those girls,
we feel something.
You guys have lost it!
You were already good for nothing
now you're doomed!
Is this how you read a book?
-I...
-No need to explain.
Everyone is lost. One meeting
with the boys has changed everything!
Where's Shobhini?
Madam, please add salt to the lentils.
Why are we suddenly leaving for Pune?
Tomorrow is the 3rd.
Babu will be released.
He'll do our job on the 4th.
And I'll be talking to the
lawyer regarding Seema's property.
If anyone suspects me of killing Seema...
the lawyer will testify
that I was with him.
Seema's inheritance will
be mine on the 5th.
Is this supposed to be
another one of your protests?
Why are you looking at me like
dumb fools?
Get on with the job or
you won't get food!
They're not moving
even after I mentioned food!
-What is it?
-Something’s happened.
Something has happened to the boys.
Are they drunk?
Have you seen them? They look sick!
As if they have no life!
What a great brother you are!
Don't you know anything?
-What is it?
-They are in love.
What does that mean?
What a nuisance!
You're equally dumb!
They are in love.
In love?
It was a spark in
you that made me love you
Explain it to me for I do not understand
When one falls in love...
the heart beats faster
And one feels restless
When somebody counts
The stars at night...
assume the man is in love
Look what love has done to you
The heart sighs...
Wishes somebody could guide
Look what love has done to us
The heart sighs...
Wishes somebody could guide me
Switch off the lights
Switch off the light
For I can't fall asleep
Switching the lights
Off will not help me to sleep
When will the girl come
Who will switch off the light?
Don't make noise
Or you'll wake up my wife
Look what love has done to you
The heart sighs...
Somebody please tell me the future
Look what love has done to us
The heart sighs...
Wishes somebody could guide
Want my guidance?
Let's get the girls.
Look what love has done to you
The heart sighs...
Wishes somebody could guide
Look what love has done to us
The heart sighs...
Wishes somebody could guide
Things aren't so bad
When the hearts are one
Why should there be distance
We'll get them
If we have the guts...
Even if the family doesn't allow
We'll get them
If we have the guts...
Even if the family doesn't allow
Look what love has done to us
The heart sighs
Wishes somebody could guide
Look what love has done to us
The heart sighs
Wishes somebody could guide
You!
Why aren't you sleeping?
It's pretty late.
I stayed up
to witness your deeds.
Let the girls go.
Untie them.
Save us!
These boys have kidnapped us.
Don't worry. I'll handle them.
So, this was your plan.
What were you thinking when
you kidnapped these girls?
I thought they were girls.
Do you know what a
grave crime you've committed?
Why are you standing with heads lowered?
-Answer me!
-Answer what?
You are the reason why
all this has happened!
What did I tell you?
I had asked you why the boys look lost.
You said they were
in love... with the girls.
-Yes.
-Quiet!
But is it right to forcibly
kidnap somebody from their homes?
We didn't force them.
We brought them with care.
What else could I do?
Look at my brothers.
Faces hanging down to their knees.
They neither eat nor
drink nor sleep or work.
I too have a duty towards my brothers.
Bravo! What a duty you've performed!
You should get a reward
from the government.
Quiet. Now hear me carefully.
It's late so the girls
will stay here tonight.
Inside. With me.
I'll take them back tomorrow morning.
And you'll sleep out in the stable.
Come on in.
-One for all, all for one!
I think the night's episode scared her.
I can't let her go in this state.
Let's inform her family.
Whom can we inform?
She has an uncle who has already
left for Pune for a week.
-Call the servant.
-Okay but with the boys...
How can we stay here?
With me around,
you need not worry.
As long as you're here,
none of the brothers will step in.
Not even my husband.
We'll send a telegram to Seema's uncle.
What is the Pune address?
Now I know why Babu couldn't do the job.
What do you mean?
How could he kill Seema,
when she wasn't home?
She's gone to the farmhouse
with her friends.
-They have sent a telegram.
-Now what?
I will have to meet Babu and
plan ahead.
But first I must go
and meet my sweet niece.
-No fever.
-But I feel weak.
Live here for a few
days in this fresh air...
eat the fresh produce
of this farm that I cook.
And you'll be fine.
Please don't tell your uncle
that my husband
and his... stupid clan kidnapped you.
No. Why would I tell him?
Actually, they're not dangerous,
they're just silly.
Tell him, he's not allowed inside.
He must leave or
there would be consequences.
Did you hear?
Tell this guard that I don't
harbor any desire to come in.
I'm going to the city for a few days,
so I wish to speak to my guests.
All that happened
yesterday was my mistake.
I saw my brothers were sad...
and made this stupid mistake.
So please forgive me.
The children aren't at fault.
It was my mistake.
You might not be here when I will return.
You would have gone home.
So, I came here to apologize.
If possible, forgive
this elder brother of yours.
Listen...
I'll be waiting for you.
Make sure you're back by Friday.
If I inadvertently hurt
you or your feelings...
forgive me...
The Devil is here.
Thank God, she's fine.
Her health is my biggest worry.
She's my elder brother's
child but I love her a lot.
-Thank you so much...
-What for?
She's like my younger sister too.
Seema hasn't recovered yet.
I'd like her to rest here.
But I can't stop you
from taking her home.
If she's not well, let her be here.
I won't let her move.
I can bear to be away from her.
But I can't bear that she's unwell.
You may keep her here for a few days.
If you need anything,
I'll send it from town.
By the grace of God,
we have everything we need.
Just send them some
clothes and medicines for the girls.
-I'll get them tomorrow.
-No, please...
my husband is in town.
He'll return in a couple of days.
-Give it to him.
-Where in the town?
He's with his friend, Shekhar.
Hello.
Speaking.
-Ranjit Singh here.
-Sorry, do I know you?
Seema is staying at
your farm with her nurses.
Yes, of course.
I'm her uncle.
Oh! What can I do for you?
I'd gone to the farm. Your wife
asked me to send some items.
I'll come to your home tomorrow
and pick them up then.
-Something wrong?
-No.
I hope you had no problems getting here.
No.
Have a seat. Drink?
Why were you staring at me?
You remind me of a very dear friend.
He's very much like you.
Tall and broad shouldered...
Young, handsome.
Are you left-handed?
You use your left hand?
Yes. My Dad would say...
use your left hand if you
want the world to treat you right.
No... this is too much.
I'm not used to drinking.
I don't drink.
You know why?
Because it ruins the liver.
-Here...
-I see.
So, I don't drink but that
day at a friend's marriage...
they forced me to gulp four bottles.
You told me about the farm
house but not your brothers.
My brothers! Each one is a gem!
I love them a lot.
The youngest is...
My youngest brother is so cute!
I love him a lot.
He's very hard working.
He works the hardest at the farm.
-Know why?
-Why?
Doesn't drink liquor.
Liquor ruins the liver.
I'm not used to drinking.
I went to this friend's wedding...
They forced me to drink four bottles...
-The others?
-What?
Shukra is elder to Shani.
He is sweet as sugar.
He's very strong.
He punches straight through the wall.
Very strong. He is a man of steel.
You know why?
Because he doesn't drink liquor.
-Liquor--
-Ruins the liver.
You're not used to it
but at this friend's wedding...
-you were forced to drink four bottles.
-Right.
You're too much.
I must kiss you.
Very good.
-The one elder to him?
-Elder to what?
Guru is elder to Shukra.
And Budh.
This brother of mine is a fool.
Like a cow. He's so docile.
Not a cow... buffalo.
No, buffaloes are black.
Cow, he's a cow.
He knows nothing about any vice.
You know why?
Because he doesn't drink.
Liquor ruins the liver.
-I'm not used to--
-Went to a friend's wedding
and he forced you to drink four bottles.
How do you know?
You're great! I must kiss you!
Wonderful...
-Who is elder to him?
-What?
Elder to the Budh... is...
Hangal is elder to Budh.
Not Hangal.
He stammers a bit.
Very strong... yes.
He can hit a coconut and
break it in five pieces.
-You know why?
-Because he doesn't drink.
-Liquor ruins the liver.
-Liver.
You're not used to it but
you went to a friend's wedding...
and he forced you to drink four bottles.
-Kiss...
-You're terrific!
-Good?
-Yes.
-Who is elder to him?
-Som is elder.
He talks a bit loudly.
But he's soft.
Soft nose, soft heart.
Soft...
that's it.
He too is very strong.
You know elephants?
-May I?
-Yes!
He flies and kicks elephants.
Elephant skull cracks,
the brains spill out.
You know why?
Because he doesn't drink.
Liquor ruins--
Hey driver, stop!
Here is Ravi's chain.
Why are you here?
Take him away and tie him up.
Did you really think breaking into
our house would be a piece of cake?
Do you think we would never know?
What... what do you mean?
We know everything about you.
-What do you know?
-Drop the act.
You know what we mean.
No, I don't know.
What are you guys saying?
Today is your birthday.
Where are you taking me?
Listen... wait.
Look at this!
Ravi gets a chance to go
in because it's his birthday!
-Go in.
-What's inside?
Your birthday gift.
-Gift...
-Yes.
You and your wife had a squabble
because of us.
As it's your birthday,
it's time for a fresh start.
The court exonerates you!
-But...
-Go in.
Open the door!
RAVI
On your birthday, I give you
the best gift a wife,
could ever give her husband.
I'm a bit shy to look you in the eye
and say this.
Hence, I'm writing it.
I am expecting a child...
-Child...
-Yes.
Why are you running away?
No... people say when
the hearts are one...
physical distance doesn’t matter
and our hearts are already one.
-Shall I switch off the light?
-What...?
Yes?
They can see our shadow downstairs.
No... I haven't come here for that.
-What do you mean?
-I mean...
-I must write accounts--
-Accounts?
Every moment is difficult
when you go out to work.
And you'll write accounts
the moment you get back!
Don't you care about my heart,
my feelings?
I do but...
-Down with Ravi and Indu!
-You stay in!
-While we are out!
There's some protest...
It's right. I'm in here comfortable...
they're down there battling mosquitoes...
it's not fair. Injustice...
I think I should be down there with them.
Your wish.
We won't tolerate any injustice.
Quiet! I'm coming.
I'm coming.
And I have some good news.
It would have been really shameful that
I sleep inside peacefully
while you're out here in the open.
So I've decided as long as
the girls are here, nobody goes in.
Come.
You had some good news.
What... is that?
I forgot...
all of you
are going to be uncles.
When I first got here,
this wasn't a home.
It was an asylum.
I went berserk trying to clean it up.
The eating habits of--
-Who is it?
-It's me.
What is it? Why have you come in?
We are freezing out here...
-Is it?
-May I have a blanket?
-Stand there, I'll get it.
-Please, let me do it.
So, where was I?
Is it really freezing?
Now that I've seen you...
I feel much better.
Coming.
So, I was telling you about the way
these brothers ate--
-Now who is it?
-It's me...
-What do you want?
-Girl...
Girl?
I mean a splinter hit
me while I was chopping wood.
-Want the first aid box?
-Yes. May I come in to take it?
No. Stand there, I'll get it.
Please let me do it.
-You remain seated.
-No, I'll give it.
-The first aid--
-Yes, come out.
I see. This is what they are up to.
What are you doing here?
You'll never learn!
We're thirsty.
Can we get some water?
-Water? In here?
-Yes.
If you knock again,
I'll throw you down the well!
You'll be drinking water
all your lives! Get it?
Get lost! If anyone
turns, I'll break your legs!
-Come. Let's go.
-We’ll drink water from the well.
What have you got today?
This is how things are. Everything's
a mess. The girls are equally stupid.
What more can I do?
You're making a mistake.
Indu is sleeping upstairs.
I thought she's probably here.
Forgive me.
What's the matter?
What is he doing here at midnight?
He's freezing too,
wanted to borrow a blanket.
But he's in the wrong room,
asking the wrong girl.
Water.
Looks like, he's run out of juice.
Why don't you kill Ravi?
His life could put us at risk.
No.
Ravi is useful if he’s alive.
The moment Babu returns
after killing Seema
I'll send Ravi back and he'll
be charged with killing Seema.
You... Indu isn't here.
She might be outside.
What's wrong?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Why... don't you say something?
You...
you're scaring me.
Stop right there!
Stop right there... please.
Why don't you speak?
What do you want?
It's alright.
What's going on?
How did you leave
the chair and come here?
How are you standing on your feet?
That's Ravi's magic.
He scared her with that knife.
-She ran out of her chair. Great.
-You're fantastic!
He's performed a miracle!
We'd thought Seema would
never walk in her life.
Brother, you're amazing!
We only loved you but
now we respect you.
Why are you crying?
You should be happy.
You can go anywhere on your own.
You are no more dependent on the chair.
Pray to God to give
you a husband like him.
Who sympathizes with others'
pain and fills their life with joy.
Forgive me.
You came to give me life,
and I thought you wanted to kill me.
I'll never be able to repay this debt!
You're an angel!
May God give you
all the happiness you deserve.
I pray that all your troubles come to me.
This family should always be happy!
Enough.
Enough, stop crying.
All your problems...
your struggle is now over.
Any obstacle in your path
will first have to face me.
I'll give my life to ensure your safety.
No sorrow will torment you.
Whatever be the cards
An ace or another card
If you look carefully,
Each one is merely a card
Finally it matters not
Nothing matters
Whatever be the cards
An ace or another card
If you look carefully
Each one is merely a card
Finally it matters not
Nothing matters
Are you the king of my
Heart or am I the queen of yours?
We are in each other's arms
Love is in the air
Creating love stories
Finally it matters not
Nothing matters
Whatever be the cards
An ace or another card
If you look carefully
each one is merely a card
Finally it matters not
Nothing matters
When destiny brings us together
If so destined, we will be together
From all directions
the hearts will meet
in spite of obstacles
-I am stuck.
-Why?
Speak up.
Finally it matters not
Nothing matters
Whatever be the cards
An ace or another card
If you look carefully,
each one is merely a card
Finally it matters not
Nothing matters
Giving your heart
Or falling in love
The tradition carries on
People fall in love
But leave the world alone
Finally it matters not
Nothing matters
Whatever be the cards
An ace or another card
If you look carefully,
Each one is merely a card
Finally it matters not
Nothing matters
-Where are you taking me?
-Come along.
-What's the matter?
-Come on
At least tell me what’s the matter?
Today is Karva Chauth.
-Karva Chauth?
-What?
Today, wives pray for their husband's
life.
May God keep her husband well.
No... I don't deserve it.
What are you saying?
The truth.
I'm not who you think I am.
I'm a criminal who spent
most of his life in jail.
I'm neither anyone's brother
nor anyone's husband.
This isn't true.
I’m not Ravi... I'm Babu.
If you don't believe me... have a look.
My name is Babu.
I resemble Ravi.
That's why I was sent here.
I must kill Seema the
moment I find an opportunity.
-Kill me?
-Yes.
Your uncle Ranjit Singh has paid
me one lakh rupees to kill you.
You die and he inherits all your property.
It'll all be his.
Cheat! Scoundrel!
You pretended to be our brother
and took advantage of our love!
-Don't spare him. Beat him up!
-Thrash him!
-Beat him up!
Get up, you impostor!
Don't spare him!
Beat him up!
-Stop...
-You stay out of this!
I say stop it.
I know he is our enemy.
He lived in our home and deceived us.
But he didn't cheat me.
He didn't deceive my duty, my honor.
He never touched me.
Don't think of what he's done.
Imagine what he could've done.
He lived with us but
never came close to me.
He could have easily gotten away
with anything he wished to do.
A sister-in-law is like mother
and you honored our mother.
Hence, we forgive you but
tell us where our brother is.
I will tell you but I have a request...
this story began with me
and I will bring it to an end.
Babu is your brother till Ravi returns.
He is with you.
I beg your forgiveness for my actions.
The truth is that my
origins are disgraceful.
I grew up in an environment
of deception and perfidy.
I stole to fill my stomach,
cheated to survive...
because that's what my world taught me.
A family, a sister...
a brother or a sister-in-law,
I've never known these relations.
After living with you for
a few days, for the first time,
I felt I was human too.
Apart from strength,
there's a heart in the body.
And the heart told me...
Babu, these people are like you.
Don't deceive them.
You have given me a new form, a new life.
I can never forget that.
I must say this,
whether Babu survives or not...
your husband will live.
I promise your love will live.
There's only one way to get in.
You wait here. I'll be back.
Your job is done. Seema is dead.
Now you may send Ravi
back to his right place.
Ravi is in his right place now.
Not only Ravi,
your right place is here too.
What do you mean?
Do you think I'm a fool?
If I can send you in Ravi's place...
Can't I send somebody
to keep an eye on you?
Now your life and Ravi's
will end right here.
Turn around.
Get him and Ravi upstairs.
Just a minute! Hold it!
Don't kill me, it's not my fault.
I don't know them!
He brought me here. Don't kill me!
I know nothing.
I don't want to die!
It's not my fault...
Stop!
Nobody will touch him!
He's my prey.
Promise me, you won't intervene.
No matter what.
Come on.
One for all... all for one!
-One for all... all for one!
-Yes!
-Fantastic!
Are you leaving?
-Why?
-I've fulfilled my duty.
Take care of yourself.
If you've some respect
for me in your heart...
never sit on this chair again.
Get up.
I say, get up.
No, I believed that my life
had finally turned around.
And I was happy.
But now I feel that it was all a lie.
I think I am destined to
be in this chair forever!
Get up!
Come into my arms, my love!