Who?
-
Who are you people?
What are you people doing in my
house at this time of the night?
Lotia Pathan has sent us.
Today was the last day
for you to repay the debt.
But you did not repay so
we have come to remind you.
Yes, there is no need to remind me.
When I have the money I'll repay it.
You had said that when
your daughter will start...
...dancing on the stage the
money will start showering.
She has already done
twenty five shows.
But you have not
paid us a single penny.
Do not talk too much.
And get lost from here otherwise...
...I'll call the Police and...
Listen Shyamlal, if by 12 o'clock
tomorrow the does not reach us...
...then remember we'll not spare you.
You are threatening me,
you scoundrels.
It is not a threat
but it is a warning.
And tomorrow this
threat will be carried out.
And we will not spare
you till your last breath.
Wow! Get on! Come on! 2... 3... Dip!
Hello! Oh! God! What
are you saying, daddy?
I've already given the number 1
and the number 2 money to you...
...and now you are demanding
50 thousand more?
Commitment is commitment, sir.
Krishnamurthy,
I do not know all that.
I am very frank, that if I don't get
50 thousand rupees...
...then Mohini will not
come for the rehearsal.
What are you saying, sir?
- What's the matter, Krishnamurthy?
You are looking quite hassled?
All is okay?
Sir, Shyamlal is demanding
50 thousand rupees more.
What? - And sir,
he is threatening to cancel the show.
Really?
Yes, Mr. Shyamlal,
now 50 thousand is nothing...
...in front of a great
artist like your daughter.
You can take it whenever you want.
This is absolute blackmail, sir.
- Shut up, Krishnamurthy!
Is this the way to talk to
a man like Mr. Shyamlal?
You go and get 50 thousand rupees.
Mr. Shyamlal you bring Mohini to my
residence and I will pay you the...
...50 thousand rupees there itself.
Here are your 50 thousand rupees.
At least count the money.
Saxena, Shyamlal does
not do the duty of a clerk.
If it is more or less
then I swear by Kashi's Vishwanath...
...you will repent a lot.
Okay then, I will take your leave.
Oh! Mr. Shyamlal, how can go
without taking any drinks?
Let Mohini go to the rehearsals,
but you sit down with me.
We will have a few drinks.
I'll be right back.
Dear Mohini! Dear Mohini...
...you go to the
rehearsals and I'll just...
And you'll sit down
here drinking liquor...
...and I'll dance there.
If someone else had said this to me,
I'd have killed that person.
You cannot kill me.
Because your liquor,
your gambling and enjoyment...
...is all because of me.
I am your source of income, father...
...and you do not have
the guts to kill me.
Come on Saxena, give me the glass.
Wow! Cheers! - Cheers!
- You scoundrel!
If you don't get the money then...
...Mohini will not come
for the show, is it?
Fifty thousand?
Lock up this old man.
And when the show starts throw him...
...backstage to hear
his daughter's song.
"Mohini! Mohini! Mohini! Mohini!
Mohini! Mohini!"
"Greetings!
- Greetings!"
"Tell me, what would you like to hear?"
"First you tell us,
where were you?"
"I? I was waiting for somebody."
"Who is it?"
"The one whom I love."
- "Oh! No!"
"And I plead with him again and again."
- "How?"
"Like this!"
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"I wait for you..."
"I count the days, one
by one waiting for you."
"Come darling the
spring has come."
"I count the days, one
by one waiting for you."
"Come darling the
spring has come."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"On the fourteenth day
I received your message."
"Said you'll come on
the fifteenth day."
"Neither did you come on the
fourteenth nor on the fifteenth."
"What did you gain
by torturing me?"
"On the sixteenth day too..."
"On the sixteenth day too...
...I'd adorned myself
with sixteen ornaments."
"Come darling the
spring has come."
"I count the days, one
by one waiting for you."
"Come darling the
spring has come."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"On the seventeenth day
I thought it was all over."
"On the eighteenth that
my heart was broken."
"I cried all day on the nineteen."
"On twentieth day the heart
was broken into twenty pieces."
"But still, no..."
"But still your love
did not go from my heart."
"Come darling the
spring has come."
"I count the days,
one by one waiting for you."
"Come darling the
spring has come."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"The days turned into weeks."
"The weeks turned into months."
"And the months
turned into years."
"You come and see for yourself."
"What is my state?"
"I am wandering
around like a crazy woman."
"Neither I am dead nor alive."
"In the lonely
nights I keep suffering."
"Come, come, come, come, come."
"Come, I am counting the days."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"I count the days,
one by one waiting for you."
"Come darling the
spring has come."
"I count the days, one
by one waiting for you."
"Come darling the
spring has come."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
Stop! Leave me, I said leave me.
Where did these goons come from?
Krishnamurthy, call the Police.
Leave me!
Brother Munna is coming.
Brother Munna is here.
Greetings, brother Munna.
- Greetings, brother Munna.
Greetings, brother!
Please sit here, brother Munna.
There was a Police raid at
Patil's den but still I could save...
...this material and come.
This is your share for today.
Today in the entire
day I could sell only ...
150 bottles, brother Munna,
that is why...
You know it is the end of
the month so nobody comes...
...to play three cards game.
The distance between your
life and death is not more...
...than the width of the
sharp edge of Munna's dagger.
If you ever tell a lie again...
...then you won't have any hands to
deal the cards with.
Come on, stand straight.
You jerk, Munna
does take money but...
...he also saves us from
all other hassles too.
Come on hurry up. Do not waste time.
I have to go to report
to the Police Station.
Hey you, Pakya!
You all are still here.
Are you all on strike or the
railways has gone on a strike?
Come here.
You are bruised very badly.
Were you involved in a fight?
- I'll tell you, brother Munna.
A new gang is operating in our area.
They roam in the Hanuman Lane near
the station and they rob your goods.
The same gang bashed up
Toped very badly and...
...snatched away all the
money from that poor fellow.
Whose gang is it?
There's a man called Mukut Bihari.
He has come from some other
town after committing a murder.
He is their leader.
Do you know their whereabouts?
No, I could not see
their faces in the dark.
And nowadays the Dandiya
dance of the...
...'Navratri' festival is
on at the Hanuman Lane.
So it is very difficult to recognize
anyone in so much of a crowd.
Dandiya!
Hey! Come here.
- Yes, sir.
Give me the yellow ice-cream.
Papa! Papa!! My ear.
What happened? Oh! No!
Somebody has snatched...
...away my daughter's ear ring.
Please help. Catch him! Catch him!
What happened? - Oh! No!
My daughter is bleeding profusely.
Somebody has snatched
her ear ring. Look around.
Oh! No! Where is my bag?
Where is my bag?
There was my salary in it.
He looks like a very rich man.
If this intoxicated man keeps
throwing around all his money...
...then we will incur a big loss.
Is it all over?
- Yes.
It is done for the night?
Either come to some
other place for Dandiya...
...or everybody go home.
- Let's go.
"Oh! I've forgotten
my paternal home."
"I'm in love with
my husband's house."
"Oh! I've... Oh! I've forgotten
my paternal home."
Who is Mukut Bihari amongst you?
He is not drunk at all.
To bring cowards like
you out of your hideouts...
...I have many more ideas.
Who is Mukut Bihari amongst you all?
Oh! So you want Mukut Bihari, right?
Hey Rashid! Give him the
address of Mukut Bihari.
Try once again.
Now I'll make you dance the Dandiya.
Now tell me,
why were you looking for me?
Mukut Bihari, you silently
transfer your ration card from here.
And you should not be seen
here after this morning.
Oh! Child, in my ration card
there are 12 murders registered.
How many? Twelve.
And the thirteenth will be yours
and then your thirteenth day...
Oh! Munna, you should've
come with some dangerous weapon.
Now listen carefully to what
I've to say, Mukut Bihari.
Otherwise, you'll not be
capable of hearing anymore.
Tell them to throw
down their weapons.
Whatever you've looted in my area.
Here it is, brother.
Come on! Walk ahead. Come on.
No acting smart.
Look there is brother Munna!
- Brother Munna is here.
Brother Munna has come.
Stop. Looks like their train has arrived.
-
Pakya, come on get onto it.
- I'll go right now, brother Munna.
Come on.
Now put them in the
Buffaloes' compartment.
And sent them to their
home town and how...?
As wedding guests.
- Yes. Come on.
Be careful.
After all they are our guests.
Come on shove them in. Oh! Oh!
All the purses and the wallets
that are in this bag return them.
Brother Munna!
- What is it?
There is a telegram for you.
Brother Munna,
please come home quickly.
There is a very big problem.
60 men, 16 women and
40 children are injured.
3 persons were killed
and 4 2 shops were looted.
And till date our police
force has not been able to find...
...out who they were.
We could only find out
that it was a gang of a...
...dangerous criminal named Lotia.
He is already wanted by the Police.
But where has he taken Mohini...
...we could not find out at all.
The motorcycles which were
apprehended from there...
...did you find out about their owners?
Sir, all those
motorcycles were stolen.
Sir, we've received a
message on the wireless.
A banished criminal has
entered our city limits.
Who is he?
- His name is Munna.
He was banished
from here a year ago.
This is his file.
He is Mahesh Deshmukh!
How did he become Munna?
Sir, he is known as
Munna in this area.
Before this he has served a years jail
for committing a murder.
The file says that he
is a dangerous criminal.
But my memory says that he
was an innocent, sentimental...
...but a zestful young man,
who was even ready to die for his country.
Do you know him, sir?
-
I knew him. Two years ago
I was posted at Nasik.
A bank was situated in the deserted
lane opposite to my police station.
Both his parents
were employed there.
I still remember that day
when I met Mahesh for the first time.
Daddy!
Daddy, I had told you that
I'll win the best Navy Cadet's Cup...
...and show you. Look at this.
The best Navy Cadet Cup?
Yes mother,
the best Navy Cadet's Cup.
I've done it dad, I've done it.
My dear son, I am proud of you.
Mother!
- Bless you son.
Inspector, our son Mahesh.
Congratulations!
- Mr. Deshmukh...
...now you'll have to give us sweets.
Your son has fulfilled
your heart's desire.
Yes my desire is fulfilled now
let Mahesh's dream come true.
What do you want to become Mahesh?
I want to join the Navy,
sir and become an Admiral.
Is it? That's very good.
I don't know what has taken over him.
Since his childhood...
...he has always been
talking of serving the country.
Definitely he must've been a
freedom fighter in his previous birth...
...who become a Martyr.
Mahesh, I am very happy to meet you.
Wish you all the best.
Thank you, sir.
- Bye! Bye! Deshmukh.
Bye. I had promised you that
I'll buy a bicycle for you?
Here is the money.
Thank you daddy,
thank you very much.
Ok. Mother, I'll leave now.
I'll see you at home at night.
- Yes.
Beware! I'll shoot everyone!
Give me the safe keys
you old man, you scoundrel!
I will not give you the keys.
Why do you want to invite your death,
come on give them to me.
Look here, I am working
here since the last 20 years.
It is my duty to
protect their money.
And I don't care even if I lose
my life in carrying out my duty.
That woman is going
inside the bank, sir.
And she also has a
small child with her.
Their life could be in danger sir.
You do one thing, you go from here.
And if on the way you meet
the Police then send them here.
Sir, my mother
and father are also trapped inside...
...and I should go from here?
Look, they are armed with guns.
They can shoot at anytime.
And your life could be
in danger, understood?
Why is it that only the
uniformed forces have the right...
...to fight against crime and
cruelty, and not us, sir? Why sir?
By the way I had written off
my name for the sake of...
...my country the day
when I wore this uniform.
Sir, it is very necessary
to stop that woman and...
...her child from going inside the bank.
If the dacoits see your
uniform they might start shooting.
I'll go and bring back that woman.
Sir, you order me. Sir! Please sir!
Please try to understand, sir!
Please sir. Give me the order.
Time is running out, sir.
Sir, order me. Give me the orders.
Please sir, please.
Ok. You may go.
Please, give it to me.
May God bless you!
- Ma'am...
Otherwise the youngsters these days.
- I want to tell you...
They do not bother to respect elders.
- Please listen to...
My Child!
Move away...!
Please somebody save my child.
Please save my child.
Take this, sir!
-
Mother.
My mother.
What have they done!
Sir. Look sir,
what they did to my mother?
Mahesh.
Father.
- Mahesh.
Inspector. Take him to hospital.
No, son. I don't have that much time.
If you want to do something
for me then fulfill my dreams.
You dream has become my dream.
Father. I will be very lonely without you.
- No, son.
The entire country is with you.
Take care of Jyoti.
- Father.
'The happiest day in Mahesh's life...'
'...had become the most sorrowful day
in just a few moments.'
'I've never seen life playing
a bigger joke than this...'
'...with anyone before.'
Mahesh went to Mumbai
along with his sister.
But after that day I felt
that my power of tolerating...
...pain has increased.
Anyway, search every
nook and corner of the city.
And block all the roads
going out of the city.
It is very important for me
that this man is arrested.
Because I want to know how did
he become Munna from Mahesh.
Jyoti.
- Brother...!
Brother...!
- Jyoti.
Jyoti.
What has happened?
What happened?
Has Lotia harassed you?
- No.
I am seeing you after
one year that is why.
Jyoti, there are four more days to
go before one year is completed.
I still have the stigma
of 'Banished' on myself.
And the Police are
hunting me like dogs.
And you are aware that
until I serve my sentence...
...I cannot come back to Mumbai.
Tell me, why have you called me?
For Mohini.
What has happened to Mohini?
Lotia Pathan's goons
have kidnapped her.
Then what should I do?
Who else can I tell if not you
to free Mohini from Lotia Pathan?
There are millions
of girls in his city.
I have not taken
everybody's responsibility.
But Mohini was the only
one amongst them who had...
...helped you in saving my honour.
Look Jyoti,
I am a banished criminal,...
...so I do not want to get
involved in any such thing.
This is the Police or
her father's job. Not mine.
So being her father he can
get her married to Saxena too.
Saxena? That theatre man?
Yes him. He wants to
get married to Mohini.
Let him marry,
she is not related to me or you.
As far as I am
concerned I have accepted...
...her as my sister-in-law.
She cannot become your
sister-in- law.
Unless you don't
marry someone else or...
...she doesn't marry
someone else till then...
...I have given this right to Mohini.
And as far as you are concerned...
...look into my eyes and
tell me that...
...you don't have any relation
with Mohini.
Then you can go from here.
Crazy! Go and bring a cup of tea for me.
- I will bring it just now.
Don't make me more furious, Saxena.
All this is because of you.
You are the root cause of all this.
Mohini is not going to come back
by blaming each other. - Leave it!
It is better that you
cool down Mr. Shyamlal and...
...think about Mohini's release.
We will find out some or the
other solution to this problem.
Shyamlal, the solution has
come to your door steps.
Lotia Pathan has imprisoned
your daughter in that place...
...where the crime is at its peak.
The police can't reach there but I can.
How can a young boy like you
lock horns with Lotia Pathan?
They will slash you and
throw you in the drainage.
Shyamlal, you have become so
blind in your selfishness...
...that you can't see your benefit.
My benefit! Listen to this!
He will be benefiting me.
Look Shyamlal, if I am not
able to bring your daughter...
...then think that one of
the thorn in your life...
...has gone out permanently.
Because you think
that Lotia and his men...
...will not allow me
to come back alive.
Yes, I think the same way.
And if I bring Mohini back...
...then you will get your daughter back.
Wow Saxena, wow! It is like
the story of the neighbour's son.
If he climbs on the tree,
then we will get mangoes to eat.
And if he falls down and
dies then we will get...
...the meal of the religious
ceremony after his death. Very good.
But what will you get by
endangering your life?
I will get fifty thousand.
- Fifty thousand!
You are going to strike a
deal with me for my daughter.
You scoundrel! Go away from here, go.
- Think properly.
Wait!
I will pay you the money.
Mr. Shyamlal, everything will
come back if Mohini comes back.
What will come back, Saxena?
What if she refuses to dance?
I am ready to take
this responsibility.
I will pay your debt
and not only that...
...I will make arrangements for you
to stay luxuriously the whole life.
Look dear,
I don't understand one thing.
He wants money in
exchange of my daughter but...
...what do you want
in exchange of money?
Mohini.
If you give us the blessings.
Why not Saxena?
I swear upon Kashi Vishwanath...
If I get a good amount
then I am ready to...
...sell my blessings too. Yes!
Okay Munna, we accept your deal.
So brother, what will you have?
One 'handi biryani',
one 'dandi Kebab'...
...one liver and fish fry
and the rest...
I understood.
- I hope you have understood!
What will you have brother?
- An Ice cream along with 'Pulav'.
Chocolate Ice cream, isn't it?
- Yes.
And you brother.
- One 'Chicken tikka'...
...one chicken Tandoori
and one butter chicken.
So brothers, we require
720/- rupees to...
...celebrate Chandi's birthday.
Then do something,
my hair has started graying...
...because of empty stomach.
See this! - Yes, my friend!
Then give some of it,
everyone will be able to have food.
Look at this! I have heard
that we find hair in food but...
...I have heard this
for the first time that...
...we will get food
because of the hair.
Do something quickly,
I am very hungry.
It seems that there is a party
in your destiny today, come.
Hey, clean the table over here.
- One minute!
Where are you going?
- To wash my hands.
Hey sit down! Clean it
with your neighbour's shirt.
But what if he
comes to know about it?
Did you come to know about it?
-
Don't make fun, I will beat you...
These boys that you can see are mine.
Let them eat whatever they want.
I will pay the bill.
- No problem.
Hey waiter, come here!
Hey waiter, come here.
- Yes sir.
Bring one cup of tea fast with
less of water in it. Go. - Yes sir!
I saw it first.
- I too saw it.
We will share it.
- This is Mumbai.
The one who has the note
is the owner of the note.
Okay, then this note should
go to the owner of the hotel.
Hey manager.
- Can't we compromise?
Compromise!
It is possible, just pay my bill.
- Yes, I will pay it.
Then it is okay.
Hey, move from here or
else all of you will...
...have to wash utensils
on Chandi's birthday.
Manager, my uncle will pay the bill.
What do you say uncle?
- Yes, I will pay the bill, let him go.
And uncle, don't leave it, catch it.
He loves me a lot.
- No problem.
This cock is very nice.
How much is the bill?
Hey Pandu, how much is the
total bill of all of them?
Six chicken soups of
48/- rupees.
Six vegetable 'Pulav',
Six chicken chilli.
Six 'Boti Masala',
six chicken special.
Twelve custard...
...and one fainted 'Marwadi'.
Today is okay but what
about tomorrow, bother?
There are many gullible
people wandering in this city.
We will get at least one in a day.
"The owner of the chickens,
save your chickens..."
Hey, this is Munna's cycle. Munna!
Take this advance, I return the
vehicle in two days. - No problem.
My friend,
I am very happy to see you.
But how did you come so suddenly?
There are few more days left
for your punishment to get over.
I had to come.
Have you come for Mohini?
- Yes.
Any information about Lotia Pathan?
His hideout is in the
slums of Kasara Ghat.
But how did you
come to know about it?
One can get the
address of every hooligan...
...of Mumbai in
Kafoor smoker's place.
Give anyone of them 10- 15
rupees to smoke drugs over there...
...and you will
automatically get the information.
But we will have to go there fully
prepared. There may be a brawl.
Just tell me when we have to go.
Just now. At this moment.
How is your life going on?
"The owner of the chickens,
save your chickens..."
Sir, you and here.
Though you have changed
your path and profession.
But I am still walking
on the same path...
...and my profession too is the same.
Mahesh, you are under arrest.
What is my crime?
- If you are banished my court then...
...surely you must have
committed some crime.
The law might have thought
of keeping you far from...
...the society for the
welfare of the society.
The same society had
banished Lord Ram too...
...for 14 years for their benefit.
What was his crime, sir?
But you are a
criminal in the eyes of law.
Don't you know what
are the consequences...
...of showing a knife to a police?
I know it, sir. Imprisonment
of 1 or 2 years, what else?
I am ready for it but now it is
important that I should go, sir.
Let's go, Baban.
Mahesh! Wait! My duty says
that I should arrest you.
And if necessary
then I should shoot you.
Then shoot me.
- No, I am not going to do so.
Because I what to know that
how the one who had taken...
...an oath to die for the country
has become its enemy?
I have forgotten my past life.
- You will have to remember it.
Because my duty is not only
to stop the criminals but...
...it is to stop the crime also.
And if I come to know
that how a talented youth...
...like you become criminals
then it is possible that...
...I might stop some youths
from becoming criminals in future.
You are talking about
stopping the criminals.
Your police made me a criminal, sir.
How? - I don't have the time
to state it now, sir.
You give me time of only one day.
I will surrender myself
to you within 24 hours.
And then I will tell you everything
that you want to know, sir.
And then you can give me
whatever punishment you want.
Look Mahesh, I cannot give you time.
But I can come with you.
- That is okay.
Yes Mahesh, tell me
that how you got banished.
After coming from Nasik
I joined a college here.
And started working in
Boat club's swimming pool.
One day I met a girl there.
Her name was Mohini.
Lift up your legs!
Isn't there any
lady teacher to teach?
Why are you trying to
terminate me from my job?
If you paddle your legs on the
water, you will learn to swim.
I would like to drown
before a man touches me.
As you wish, but I don't have
any problem in touching girls.
Come on girls, time is up. Come on.
Look at the attitude of this queen.
I would like to drown
before a man touches me.
In the swimming pool of his heart.
Wait fatso, I will show you
in whose swimming pool. Wait.
Someone help her.
Help...
Help me...
Come... let's see what has happened.
Not the learner but at
least the one who is drowning...
...should not have the
problem that the one who...
...saved her was a man or a woman.
Thank you for getting saved.
- Let's go!
Thank God!
Hey brother! How are you.
Hi!
You!
Hey guy, has the
college not started yet?
There is a lot of time left.
Take us to drink tea.
- Yes, sure.
What happened?
- Someone stole my purse.
How will you have a purse?
I had stolen someone's in the morning.
-
You found me only?
Look that is Guldasta,
let's praise him...
...we will get
breakfast along with tea.
That is good! Fantastic!
"The wind is blowing,
remembering of someone..."
"The wind is blowing..."
- Wow...
Great Guldasta!
- Please sit!
We want tea today.
- What a nice voice.
What will you have?
My heart is filled with joy!
- Have something.
Have something... Tea...
- Tea. - Tea.
What will you eat?
- To eat?
No brother, how is it possible?
- Okay!
Guldasta!
- Yes sir!
Sometimes it is
difficult for us to decide...
...whether your tea is more
sweet or your voice is sweet.
How come your tea is so sweet?
"You called me and I came
after you with my life in hands..."
I think we will not drink tea from
Guldasta's hands for a long time now.
If Laxmikant sees you.
- Not sees but hears...
If he hears you then you will
directly go to the HMV studio.
Look, one day we will sit here
at this tea stall...
...and listen to Guldasta's song.
Your friend is a music director,
isn't it? - Who?
I see, that one. - The one who
arranges programme in TV's.
The same one who give
chance to new comers. - Yes!
Introduce him with him.
- Yes.
How much should I pay?
- Don't make me feel embarrassed.
How can I take money from you?
- What else will you take?
No! At least once introduce me to
that music director, please!
Hey Guldasta!
- Problem is created.
Yes, sir. - Keep this sugar
and tea powder inside.
And listen! Keep in mind
to take money from them.
You always forget to
take money from them.
Actually sir, they are
the real appreciators.
And there are very few
in this world who...
...appreciates the real art.
Keep quiet!
Go and take money from them.
Sir, deduct money from my salary.
What did you say?
Hey, my band of boys.
Hi!
So boys, what is going on?
We are trying to impress the girls.
-
What will you impress girls?
You are just fooling around.
Just saying that red one is
mine and yellow one is mine.
If you have the guts
then go and talk to her.
Hey Munna master,
you go and propose a girl.
The Mumbai girls are very strict.
Girls are girls whether it
is Nasik or it is Mumbai.
One doesn't need a license
of the city to impress girls...
...he should have brains.
You are wrong at that point,
brother Munna.
One needs a heart to
love not the brains.
Do you remember Anand Bakshi's song?
"Love is not done! - It happens!"
"You cannot give your heart..."
"What is a heart,
take away my life..."
"Enough..."
- Enough. -
You all watch so many films
then too you don't understand.
The way situations
are created in films...
...to make one laugh or cry...
...the same way we can make one
to love us in life.
Oh! You mean, we can
make someone love us...
...by doing a drama.
No doubt of it. - Hey brother,
this is neither Nasik nor a drama.
You will have to get beaten up
with sandals.
No master, decision
cannot be made this way.
Show us the way to
use your psychology...
...then only we will know about it.
Not free of cost, if you
are ready to bet then talk.
Yes...
- Bet!
How much?
- Hundred rupees. - Hundred rupees.
Hey Baban, he is betting with me.
Yes, done.
- Done.
Do you know what she started
saying?
She started saying that wait...
Hi girls.
- ...I am Mrs. Singh. Hi.
What is the name of
the girl who was the...
...college queen last year?
- Nikita.
Yes, Nikita...
In which class does she study?
In my class.
- And in which class do you study?
In Nikita's class.
-
I mean I study
in your sister Jyoti's class.
It means that I will
have to talk to Jyoti.
You do one thing,
if you find Jyoti then...
...ask her to meet me in
canteen during lunch time.
I have an urgent work her, okay.
- Okay.
Bye.
- Bye.
I will go now.
Why have you come so late brother?
You wanted some money,
didn't you? Keep this!
Money! When did I ask for money?
You had not asked.
- Hi. - Hi.
Then you might have told
me about going for a movie.
Come we will go!
Why are you
buttering me so much today?
What is the matter?
Actually Jyoti, the one...
that girl in your class...
...who has blue eyes,
the one with brown hair.
The same one who was
the queen last year.
Nikita.
- Yes...
Introduce me to her, please.
Ouch! I am asking.
I will introduce you to Nikita.
But you too will have
to do one thing for me.
What are you saying?
Who else will come to help...
...except brother to sister
and sister to brother. Tell me.
She is my friend Mohini,
she has some work with you.
Tell him.
Speak up.
I wanted your notes
of psychology and...
...if you teach it yourself then...
Actually there is no
problem in teaching.
But the problem is of time.
He is going on doing the drama.
He is acting too smart.
There she is. Nikita!
Hi.
- Hi!
Hi!
Hello... Hi!
What she is looking!
I am sorry, I am really sorry.
There is no need for sorry,
I really enjoyed it.
Did you get hurt somewhere?
- No.
Will you please sit there?
- What?
There.
Sit...
- Thank you.
Are you comfortable?
- Yes.
Nikita, he is my brother Mahesh.
Hello, I am Nikita Sharma.
- I am Mahesh Deshmukh.
You are the one who passed
with first class in psychology.
Yes. - I was thinking that
if you teach it to me then...
Why not?
You've made my life.
I didn't understand.
Actually Nikita, I am very much
interested in teaching psychology.
And if I get a student like you then...
Did you understand it?
But do you have so much time for me?
Time, we don't have time
but we have to find time.
Thank you... thank you very much.
Why don't we start
from today onwards?
Far from this crowd,
somewhere in isolation.
The place where
there would be no one...
...except me, you and psychology.
Let's go to such place.
- You are gone Mohini.
Now go to Badri Nath
and worship god.
Let's go.
- Yes.
Your book.
Brother, what about us?
- Try to understand.
Bye.
- He has gone. Let's go.
It seems that she is
waiting for Munna.
It looks like they have made
plans to go out somewhere.
I will teach her a lesson now.
Nikita.
- Hi.
Shall we go?
- Yes.
The tyre of your car is punctured.
Oh God! What will happen now?
What is the problem in it Nikita?
We have this Indian
Impala, we will go in it. Sit.
Should I sit?
- Yes, sit.
Shall we go?
- Yes.
He doesn't look over me.
I think he must about Nikita.
What are you thinking Mohini?
Just jump.
What if he doesn't come?
So what! The one to give up
their life for love create history.
Jump Mohini, jump...
Help me, help me...
You come here to
practice swimming or...
...to practice how to drown.
If you drown a few more times then...
...you will get the
practice to drown.
Munna!
Hi!
- Hi! -
Help me. Help me.
-
Stand straight!
You just stand straight!
You are in just two foot
of water, only two foot.
When did you come?
- Just now.
I teach swimming over here.
Is that so? How many of
them have you drowned?
Just 30 to 40 of them.
-
How come you are here?
- I didn't swim for long time.
But when I found out that
you teach swimming here...
...I decided to start again.
Why not? Why not?
- Can you teach me, diving?
Diving! I got 30-40 medals in diving.
Come on.
- Ok. Let's go.
First raise your hand and then...
Hi, Jyoti. - Hi.
- Hi, Mohini.
'Here comes the spoilsport.'
Hi, Nikita. - Hi.
Have you finished your lunch?
Yes! We are just
waiting for my brother.
Shall I join you?
- Why not? Sit.
We will not be able to digest
our food if you don't sit here?
Yes, it is my affect.
Hey you,
Did you find this table only in...
...this canteen to show your affect?
If you want to show
your affect then...
...give everyone a bit of
opportunity to show the affect.
If you have any problem then...
I thought that Munna was here...
Munna, look how much
pain she has for him.
When that poor
hungry Munna comes here...
...then make him sit in
front of you and feed him.
Both of you will be satisfied.
You are crossing
your limits, Mohini.
You are talking about limits.
Even a witch leaves nine
houses before she attacks.
And you act as my friend,
talk very sweetly with us.
Hi Jyoti! Hi Mohini!
And on the other hand you
stick like a fly to jaggery.
In my culture, I don't give
answer to such cheap questions.
Who is asking for the answer?
I didn't swim for many days so
I thought of starting it again.
I do not know psychology,
teach it to me. -
Learn as much
psychology as you want.
If possible then learn psychology...
...for your next seven births,
so that you are fully satisfied.
If I would have known that
there are ill mannered...
...stupid and crazy girls like
you in this college then...
...I would have never
come here to study.
Munna, I am going.
- You are leaving the college.
No! I am leaving this city.
- Leaving this city.
You are leaving this
city just because...
...of some crazy girls foolish words.
Munna, after being
humiliated so much...
...I am not in a position
to show my face to anyone.
Nikita, how should I explain to you.
There is no need to
take it so seriously.
This is far more
serious than you think.
I am going.
Nikita, when will you meet me again?
Never.
- Not even by coincidence?
No, not even by coincidence.
I have stopped the love this
time which Mohini has awakened...
...in my heart for you. But I won't be
able to stop it the next time.
What? Nikita went away.
I wanted to ask for forgiveness.
I said a lot of
rubbish to her yesterday.
Munna, What is this that I have done?
I myself didn't know
what I was saying.
I only knew so much that I
started loving you. - With me.
Yes Munna, I love you.
And I can do anything to get you.
Mohini, I cannot believe that
a girl could love me so much.
And that too a girl like you
for whom...
...any boy from the college would
be ready to commit a murder too.
You just smile,
that is enough for me.
Mohini, I cannot believe
that the love for which...
...I was wandering around so
much would be so close to me.
That means... Munna, you
will accept me, won't you?
Yes, Mohini.
Look there.
"Heer got crazy calling Ranjha..."
"She got involved in
love in such a way that..."
"...she was neither able
to sleep or remain awake."
"She does not remember
anything except name..."
So Baban, saw how I enticed her?
- How you did it?
Not this way, first catch your ears.
We caught our ears.
And repeat along with me.
- What?
Whether it is Nasik or Mumbai.
The girls are girls, one
should know how to impress them.
Love doesn't happen,
it is made to happen.
Hail to psychology!
Hey Kaichi, where are you going?
Give me the money of betting.
Take it.
- Give it.
I am not running.
Now tell us the formula.
Will you give me a
party at Golden gate?
He is a greedy man.
- Do you agree?
Agreed.
Hello. - Mohini, I wanted to
tell you that Munna is fooling you.
What Munna?
He is using you just to...
He is playing with your feelings.
What is this fun going on?
If you don't believe
your well wishers...
...then go the
Golden gate hotel and...
...see it with your own eyes.
- But you...
So this is formula no. 46.
And its name is...
"See somewhere
and hit somewhere..."
If you want to impress a
girl by this formula then...
...give importance to
her friend so much that...
...she gets jealous.
And after that, when the
iron is really very hot...
...at that time...
- Strike the hammer!
Munna, leave this
thing and tell me...
...what had happened in
swimming pool? - Yes.
At the swimming pool,
she told me very openly.
What did she say?
- Munna, I really love you very much.
She said that?
Master, I too placed a
dialogue at that time.
What?
- Tell Munna...
Mohini, I don't believe it.
This is as if you got to eat
sweets by acting as a fool.
You spoke a bit more.
- Then?
And then I praised her a lot.
Praised her? - I told her that
I had never dreamt that...
...any girl would love me so much.
And that too a girl like you
for whom any boy...
...in college would commit a murder.
You have really
praised that female so much.
Then she said that Munna,
you just smile...
...once for me, that's
is enough for me. - Up!
Then I thought that I should do
full and final of that girl. - Yes!
You are great enticer.
- I caught her and said...
Mohini, I was blind till now,
I did not know that the love for which...
...I was wandering
around is so close to me.
Hey Munna, I am not Mohini I am Baban...
- She was so close to me...
Not in search of love, Munna.
And this girl who is standing in
front of you, Mahesh Deshmukh.
The girl who loves you.
You used her like an animal?
Just to win a
hundred rupees bet you...
...slashed her feelings
just to prove your formula.
You have no value for my love.
You too are one of them whom I hate.
But... but the day you understand the...
...difference between an animal
and a human being...
...that day you will
hate yourself the most.
Mohini... just listen to me.
I was craving from a long
time to meet you to talk to you.
Since the incident at the Golden Gate,
I have been waiting for you...
...outside the college everyday for you.
And then in the evening...
...the whole night I was waiting in
front of your house.
But you must have not
come out of your room.
Don't talk to me.
- Why should I not talk to you?
There my sister Jyoti
too is not talking to me.
And my friends... they too have
vanished without telling me.
Mohini... how should I tell you that...
...what I am going
through after that day.
Get side.
Mohini, I have
started hating myself but...
...I have really started loving you, Mohini!
- Shut up!
Mohini!
- All are watching!
Mohini, I know that after that day
you must have felt bad, very bad.
Please forgive me, Mohini...
Leave me! Let me go.
Mohini, how should I
make you understand that...
...how much I love you.
Should I kill myself?
I swear, I can kill myself
by jumping from this building.
Just say and see,
if you don't say then too...
...I will jump and kill myself.
Look, how dangerous it is.
If I die then there will be a problem.
You won't get the
chance to say sorry.
You will not be able
to forgive yourself.
If you are so much
interested in committing suicide...
...then jump from anywhere,
either from a six storied building...
...or from the Qutub Minar.
I have nothing to do
with your feelings.
Mohini, this is not
a hobby, it is love.
Look at me, this is not a joke.
How should make you understand?
You don't have to
make me understand.
There is no need to
explain anything to me.
Okay.
Get back! Munna.
Now tell me that you love
me as you loved me before!
Munna, come down.
Or else I will jump from here.
Munna, you are simply
wasting yours and my time.
Mohini! I will count till three
and if you still don't agree...
...then I will kill
myself by jumping from here.
You can count up to hundred,
I don't have anything to do with it.
One... Two,...
Go back! Come down!
Three...
"Tell me that you
are mine or else..."
"I don't want to live,
I want to die..."
"Tell me that you
are mine or else..."
"I don't want to live,
I want to die..."
"Look, don't ever
say such things..."
do such things..."
"Your these
qualities are a torment..."
"Listen, you have my oath..."
"Tell me that you
are mine or else..."
"I don't want to live,
I want to die..."
"I had hurt your
feelings the other day..."
"I am still sad because of it..."
"Forgive me thinking that
this is my first love, dear..."
"It is my love, dear..."
"These qualities of
yours is a torment..."
"Listen, you have my oath."
"Tell me that you
are mine or else..."
"I don't want to live,
I want to die..."
"Promise me one thing today..."
"You won't make
mischief in future..."
" As much as I love you,
you too will love me that much..."
"You will love me..."
"These qualities of
yours is a torment..."
"Listen, you have my oath..."
"Tell me that you
are mine or else..."
"I don't want to live,
I want to die..."
"Complaint and Criticism...
Complaint and Criticism..."
"Complaint and
Criticism are story of past..."
"Now I will never
be angry with you..."
"Now I am yours, just yours..."
"I will die but won't
separate from you..."
"Now I will never
be angry with you."
"Now I will not be a betrayer..."
"These qualities of
yours is a torment..."
"Listen, you have my oath..."
"Tell me that you
are mine or else..."
"I don't want to live,
I want to die..."
"Look, don't ever
do such things..."
say such things..."
"These qualities of
yours is a torment..."
"Listen, you have my oath..."
"These qualities of
yours is a torment..."
"Listen, you have my oath..."
Mohini!
- Yes!
We should stop these daily meetings.
Why? I have heard
that the wife looks...
...boring after seven
years of marriage.
And you have got bored now itself?
- Exams are nearing.
And if I get a first
class this time then...
...I will easily get a
job in the Navy this time.
You want to become a Navy officer.
Yes, it was my father's dream.
Mohini, this job is not
just a basic need but...
...a reason to attach
and serve my country.
And what if you become
a Traffic constable?
Then I will stop the
traffic and say that...
...wait, madam Mohini
is passing this way.
Shall we move?
- Yes.
Don't you feel ashamed to
wander about with scoundrels?
Father, you can abuse
me in any way you want.
This is not a mark of decency to...
...talk such rubbish
about unknown people.
Then is it a mark of decency to...
...fool around with
girls from good families?
You should be ashamed
to talk such things...
...with your daughter.
- Just keep quiet!
I used to feel like an orphan
even though my father being alive.
But I got peace
when Munna touched me.
I feel safe under his shelter.
Do you know the
status of the one with...
...whom you are in love with?
-
His father was a simple clerk.
He has a broken house to live.
To look after the expense
he works in swimming pool...
...for 500 rupees, just 500 rupees.
And his friends, all of them
are unemployed and loafer. Shame!
His father was a
clerk but he used to...
...feed his wife and
children with his own earnings.
He did not survive on
his children's earnings.
He has a broken rented house,
but it is better than...
...this bungalow which is mortgaged.
He works for just
rupees five hundred.
But it is better than the
one who is drowned in debts.
His friends are
unemployed and loafers but...
...they are not gamblers.
You taunt me.
How does it concern your father...
...if I gamble or drink liquor.
Yes, it does not concern my father...
...but it concerns my mother.
Shut up, first tell me that...
...why didn't you go
to your dance classes?
I won't go?
- Why will you not go?
I don't like these things.
I want to study.
Let your studies be aside,
you have to get ready for...
...the stage show within
six months, understood.
I do not want to do the stage show.
It seems that you won't
understand in this manner.
Keep in mind that if you
meet that guy again then...
...I will do the same thing that
I did to your mother. Understood!
You all go to the
office and sit, I am coming.
Lotia, I don't understand one thing.
You do not drink,
you do not smoke and...
...neither you go to the dance bar.
You do not have a bungalow,
you do not have cars and...
...neither you have
any luxurious items.
You have so much money that
it seems as it is pouring.
Why do you need so much money?
Money is not my need,
it is my weapon, Shyamlal.
Tell me, what you want?
My bottle is empty,
I need some money.
You have not paid the earlier debt.
Lotia, I will pay everything to you.
Just as soon as my daughter
Mohini starts dancing on stage.
I will pay all your debts,
believe me.
Lotia never depends on the
promise of his debtors, Shyamlal.
When Lotia gives,
he doesn't make any favours.
And when he takes he
doesn't spare anyone.
From when is your daughter
going to start her stage shows?
Lotia, if it had been in
my hands then I would...
...have made her dance now itself.
But what can I do? From the day
that guy is behind my daughter...
...her behaviour has
completely changed.
I don't want to fall in any trouble.
I want to live happily with
on my daughter's earnings.
So what is wrong in it?
You tell me, what is my mistake if
I got a daughter instead of a son?
You are absolutely right, Shyamlal.
Go and take money from inside, go.
Chhote Khan!
Chhote, give him
twenty thousand rupees.
Write it in his account.
Who is this sir?
I had never seen him before.
He is my brother, Chhote Khan.
I see... I am happy to meet you.
He just got released from jail.
He was caught in a bank
robbery case at Nasik.
He was caught? Oh my God!
There is no law left
in the country nowadays.
The visits to the jail and
out keep happening, Shyamlal
I am not worried about it.
I am worried that Chhote Khan
is the first Pathan...
... in our family to
become a drug addict.
He cultivated this bad habit in jail.
I will surely take revenge
from the one who sent him to jail.
Who is that unlucky person?
- His name is Munna.
Munna! Mahesh Kumar
alias Munna, the one...
...whose parents were killed
in Nasik bank robbery. - Yes!
Lotia, it means that our
enemy is one and the same.
He is that same Munna
who is after my daughter.
And he has made my life miserable.
Do you know his address?
Yes, I know it, I will just show you.
Come, you have done a
great favour on me by coming.
I was waiting you
from last three days.
I never waited like this
for anyone till today.
But like a crazy person
I used to stand here for 4 hours.
You should have at least called up...
...or should have informed Jyoti.
Munna, this is our last meeting.
I will not be able to
meet you after today.
What? What did you say?
I can't marry you, so
I have decided that...
Decision! This is the
decision of both our lives...
...then how did you decide it alone?
Don't forget that this is the
decision of my life too...
...and I have the right take it.
What do you think of yourself?
You have made a joke of it?
I will slap you in such a way that
you will come back to your senses.
Munna, there is no use of
these things now. I am going.
I will slash you into pieces and...
...I will slash myself too into pieces.
What do you think I am?
You will go away from my life
and I will just keep watching.
You rich girl,
if I can die for you then...
...I can even kill you too.
But I won't allow you to
go away from me at any cost.
I wanted to see this
side of your nature too.
I wanted to see whether the fear
I have of separating from you...
...do you too have the same?
I wanted to see whether you
are equally craving for me...
...as I am for you.
I wanted to see
whether you have got bored...
...of our daily meetings.
What happened?
- Nothing.
Who beat you, Mohini? Who?
Father.
He punished me for meeting you.
So I was testing you, Munna.
I have left everything
and come to you, Munna.
That hell which I
thought was my house.
Everything,
which I considered as mine.
I have left
everything and come to you.
I don't have anything
except these clothes.
I can't give you a
luxurious life but...
...I earn so much that we
can live our livelihood.
And if we can live our livelihood
then our life too would run.
Mohini, you have
taken such a big step...
...surely there might
be something important.
Does your father want
you to marry someone else?
What will he get me married?
He will never allow me to get married.
- Why?
He wants to make me a singer.
He wants to live
happily with my income...
...by making me dance on stage.
He did the same
thing with my mother too.
She used to sing and dance on stage.
And father used to play the drums.
They fell in love
and then got married.
After marriage he
never played the drums.
He left the habit of
playing the drums but...
...he got into the habit
of drinking and gambling.
Whatever mother used
to earn by dancing...
...he used to spend it on
drinking and gambling.
Whenever mother used to
fight with father because of it...
...he used to shut her
mouth by slapping her.
She used to live with the claps on
the stage and the slaps at home.
One day God knows how she
suddenly got the strength...
...to leave the house.
I am going, I will not
stay even for a second here.
Go, go away, the devils
in human disguise are...
...waiting outside
for a woman like you...
...who is alone and helpless. Go.
There are only devils present
in the world created my men whether...
...it is inside the
house or outside the house.
The devils inside the house
can protect you from the outside devils.
What is the guarantee?
The devils inside the house...
...can sell me to the outside devils.
I am not such a downtrodden person.
Until I can sell your art there
is no need for me to sell you.
What about the day when my
art will not be sold? Then?
Then? Then for that day my
beautiful Mohini is there.
How can my daughter bear to
see her father wandering...
...here and there and begging.
Don't leave me and go my child.
Beware, don't even try to
look at my child. Come, Mohini!
Beware, if you take
even a single step ahead.
Do you know what this is?
It is called an Acid. Acid.
If you take even a step ahead...
...then I'll not leave you in a condition
to sell your body or your art.
You can't do that as
I am your source of income.
The place from where
you get your liquor...
...and all the luxurious items.
You don't have that
much guts to finish me.
I will show you my guts.
-
Mother!
When the door of
her room was opened...
...in the morning she
had committed suicide.
But her death didn't
have any effect on father.
My mother's journey had got
over but mine was started.
I want to end this
journey of yours now itself.
You go home and come to
the temple along with Jyoti.
I will call Baban and
my other friends to...
...make the other preparations.
But why?
- Why! Idiot, it is our marriage today.
Now itself, let's go.
Tell me, where is Munna?
If he had been in the house...
...you would have been in hospital,
isn't it?
Take her to the 'Bangarkhana'.
Move.
Leave me.
They kidnapped Jyoti. Who were they?
I don't know about it but
it must be my father's move.
Do you know anything as to
where they have taken her?
Tell me, where have they taken her?
They were talking
about some Bangarkhana.
Baban, you go to the
police station along with her.
I will look after them.
Jyoti!
No, leave me.
You are under arrest.
This is not a murder, My Lord!
But just an accident...
...which took place while
saving my sister's honour.
The court and you
Mahesh Deshmukh alias Munna...
...would be happy to hear
that according to the...
...medical report no rape
took place on your sister.
You mean that when some
scoundrel tries to rape your...
...sister you should wait until
your sisters virtue is spoilt.
So that you can show
her tarnished virtue...
...in front of the court as witness.
Shut up.
The court doesn't
believe in such speeches but...
...it believe in evidences.
Where were you when
your innocent sister...
...was kidnapped from your house?
I was on the bed
along with your sister.
You scoundrel!
If the Public Prosecutor can get
so furious just at the thought of...
...his sister getting raped.
So can a brother
not commit a murder...
...when he sees his
sister being raped?
The court does not have
any doubt that Chhote Khan...
...was killed my Mahesh
Deshmukh alias Munna.
But taking into consideration
the age of the culprit and...
...the situation when
the murder took place...
...the court declares one
year imprisonment to Munna.
And releases the rest
of the associates of...
...the late Chhote Khan
on the basis of doubt.
This is a sheer injustice.
You are releasing the criminals...
...and punishing
an innocent man, judge sir.
What type of justice
is this, judge sir?
Do not add the stigma of
murderer on my name, judge sir.
Don't spoil my life,
don't ruin my career, judge sir.
Take back your judgment,
don't go... Judge sir.
Brother!
What will happen now, brother?
I had asked the same
question to myself...
...when mother and
father passed away.
And the passing time
gave me its answer.
How will I live without you
for one year?
This is just an imprisonment.
Tomorrow they can kill me.
What will you do then?
Till when will you keep crying?
Now stop this crying,
you are not a small child...
...that you always need me.
Be brave, be tough.
Learn to live alone.
- Who will teach me to live alone?
Life. Life, teaches everything.
Jyoti, the days of love
and affection have passed.
You will have to
live and fight against...
...injustice, betray and crime.
This is my punishment but
it is yours examination.
Good luck.
Just imprisonment of one year.
Advocate, only one
year imprisonment...
...for the one who killed
my brother whom I had...
...nourished for 26 years
as my child.
This is an injustice,
sheer injustice.
The punishment for this
murder in your court...
...might be just one year.
But only one law rules
in Lotia Pathan's court.
Eyes against eyes,
hands against hands...
...life against life and
sister against brother.
Amar! Amar!
Jyoti... what happened?
-
They.
- Who?
Idiots, get away.
Scoundrels, don't run,
I will not spare even one of you.
Cowards.
While going to jail
Munna had asked me to...
...take care of you so I came here.
Don't worry, someone will be
here everyday for your protection.
But bother, we can't stay
24 hours along with Jyoti.
And Lotia Pathan's men
can do anything at anytime.
There is only one solution for this Lotia.
- What solution?
Shut down all his
business and then...
...he will automatically run
away from here.
How is it possible? It is heard
that he runs many casinos.
The police too don't
know its whereabouts.
Then how can we find it out?
We will find out about that too.
Idiot! He said that to me.
Don't you have casino,
the place where cards are played.
Where is the casino in your hotel?
We don't have a casino in our hotel.
Sheikh is asking to me
buy this hotel.
He told me to buy this hotel
and build a casino over here.
He will play here.
- Sorry sir, it is not possible.
How is it not possible?
I will slap you with my slipper.
Hey, this Arab speaks Telugu.
My some friends are Telugu.
Go and do your work. -
Brother, can I help you?
I will take you to such a place where
all your desires will be fulfilled.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
Come.
Where have your brought us?
It looks like a hospital.
Prepare a casino,
where is the casino?
Sir, we will surely
play in the casino, come.
Brother, have patience, there is
a solution for everything here.
Someone might be
winning at every table.
This is our special room.
You can play how much you want,
there is no limit over here.
The Khan says that
this is simply great!
Great! Great!
Sheikh says that he will play here,
he will play now.
Sir, this currency
is from your country.
This currency will
not do in our country.
What are you saying?
This currency will not work?
You are insulting us, this
currency won't work here?
No, it won't work.
Come to the hotel at
11:00 am, we will bring...
...Indian currency
and will play here.
Yes, I will surely come, sure.
No one will go out. Understood.
No one will try to run from here.
It means that my doubt was right.
Catch him.
- What will you catch me?
Pandey, run from here.
There is a problem.
Hello, police station,
there is some fight going on...
...behind Jetabhai's store
near Hanuman street...
...you all come immediately.
Run away, the police have come.
Till now, I have seen the police
running behind thieves many times...
...but it is for the time
I am seeing that the...
...police is running
behind the police.
Move.
Hey, lift me.
- Fatty, you always...
Baban come, fast...
Yesterday
Chandanwadi police raided...
...many unauthorized casinos
and found 25 casino machines...
...and many other
unauthorized materials.
Lotia Pathan, the owner of
these casinos has escaped.
Police are searching for him in every
corner of the city. -
The news ends.
Lotia king, these
boys have destroyed us.
Where will we go now king?
They have ruined us completely.
Whatever Baban did
is my debt on him.
And Pathan can
leave this world but...
...cannot leave his debt behind.
Baban will have to pay this
debt by shedding his blood.
Mohini... whenever I go
to jail to meet Munna...
...he always asks about you.
Really.
- He is eager to meet you.
Mohini, you will
meet him, won't you?
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"I was... I was counting
the days for your return."
"Come my beloved it's spring time."
"I was... I was counting
the days for your return."
"Come my beloved it's spring time."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"I had informed
you on fourteenth..."
"I had informed you
on the fourteenth..."
"That I would be
coming on fifteenth..."
"And I had come..."
"But you didn't come
out on the fifteenth and...
...I was scared after
not seeing you..."
"On the sixteenth... I was eager
on sixteenth too from morning..."
"Come my beloved it's spring time."
"I was counting the
days of your return..."
"...come back my love
it's the time of spring..."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"I was not able to sleep for
the whole night on Seventeenth..."
"You were not seen
on Eighteenth too..."
"I got crazy on the Nineteenth..."
"And I went away from the
house on the Twentieth..."
"The voice of a crazy man
resonates in streets..."
"Come my love, its spring..."
"I was counting the
days of your return..."
"...come back my love
it's the time of spring..."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
Mohini... listen to me.
- This is a library and you are shouting.
Okay...
"You didn't come on the Twenty
first nor on the Twenty second..."
"You did not meet me on the
Twenty third and Twenty fourth..."
"Everyone explained
me on Twenty fifth..."
"Not to allow
Twenty Sixth to pass..."
"There are only four days
in this world left for me..."
"Come my love its spring..."
"I was counting the
days of your return..."
"...come back my love
it's the time of spring..."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"The days were
converted into week... '
"The weeks were
converted into month..."
"The months were
converted into year..."
"Just come and see my condition..."
"I am wandering
like a crazy man..."
"Nor I am living nor I am dead..."
"I am spending a lonely night..."
"Come... Come as I am
counting the days..."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"I was counting the
days of your return..."
"...come back my love
it's the time of spring..."
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
Saxena is waiting for
you for the practice.
All the girls have come.
And for whom are you waiting here?
Is your husband going to come?
- You are absolutely right.
Munna is being released from jail
today. He will directly come here.
He will not remain
alive if he comes here.
Get ready to go.
- I will die but I won't move from here.
You can die for your love but
you can't live for your father.
I will see how you do not come.
- I am not going to dance today.
How come you will not dance,
your father too will dance.
Leave me.
- Move.
Munna will never reach up
to this house, understood.
You will rot here until
you don't agree to dance.
I will see how many
days will you survive...
...without food and water.
Mohini!
Hey, how did you come inside?
What do you want? Get out.
Get side.
- Don't show your hooliganism here.
Mohini!
- I will trap you in such a way that...
...you will remember me.
Move from my way, take your money.
- My money...
Mohini!
- Why are you shouting?
You will never get Mohini.
- Mohini!
Why are you shouting for Mohini?
Answer me, Mohini.
Shout loudly.
- Mohini!
Mohini.
Mohini!
- Money...
Shyamlal, you can't keep us
away for long from each other now.
Even if you have
hidden her underground...
...then too I will tear off
the ground and find her.
Munna, you have come.
I knew that you would come.
Father used to say that you
would never be able to find me.
But I was sure that
you would find me.
Munna, you won't
leave me alone, will you?
You stupid girl, your Munna
is never going to come back.
What has happened to my Munna?
It is heard that someone has
killed him mercilessly. - It is a lie.
Munna is dead.
- No.
First of all his fingers
were slashed one by one.
If you had been there
you would have seen that...
...instead of his finger
there was only flesh. - No.
Then his legs were slashed,
he was crying for mercy...
...to not to make him disabled.
But just with a single
shot of an axe the...
...five feet ten inch Munna turned into
three feet and two inch. - No.
And at last when the axe was
slashed on Munna's chest...
...he was in agony and was
taking only one name and...
...that is Mohini...
- No.
If you had been there
you would have seen that...
...the blood from his
body spread on the road...
...and was wasted.
I removed him from here.
- Why?
That scoundrel destroyed my shop.
Everyone used to praise
him and used to have...
...tea and snacks free of cost.
He spent my hundred
and forty five rupees.
If I see him here,
I will break his legs.
Munna brother.
- You came back here again.
Look sir, I am here
as a customer and...
...If I ask for tea then I
am ready to pay for it too.
Take the money.
- Give.
Won't you have some breakfast, sir?
Give me two omelets.
- Ten rupees.
You will not get breakfast or tea.
Now the balance left is
one hundred and thirty five rupees.
Munna brother, I was searching you.
I had even gone to your house.
- Why?
You are searching for Mohini, isn't it?
- Yes.
I know where Mohini is.
- Mohini!
How did you come to know?
They have imprisoned
Mohini in the house...
...next to the place where I work.
Throw the card!
Take this brother.
- What is the point?
Twenty thousand cash... Credit
doesn't work while playing cards.
You have come here again to beat me.
Why don't you kill me?
I want to die...
The way you killed my Munna.
But I am not going to dance...
Kill me.
I don't want to live
without Munna, kill me.
I don't want to live,
I beg of you, kill me.
I don't want to live, I want to die.
Mohini...
- Don't touch me.
Mohini, I am Munna.
Don't touch me, leave me.
- I am your Munna, Mohini...
Munna! You are Munna.
- Yes.
Munna.
I thought that they killed you.
But how did you come to
know that I am trapped here.
That Guldasta... that man from
the canteen told me about you.
That singer.
- Yes.
But few days ago I saw him
talking to my father.
Guldasta.
- Yes.
Open the door.
- It seem that there is some danger here.
It is surely some one's plan.
- Wait I will see.
No...
- I will break the door.
I am scared. I have passed
one year in very difficulty.
If something happens to you then
I won't be able to live alone.
I will kill myself.
But how can I...
- I don't want to listen to anything.
Go, please. You have
my oath, go from here.
Hey girl, open the door.
- Go.
You go away.
-  Constable, break the door!
I will come back, Mohini.
You have literally
killed me, Mr. Shyamlal.
I did many things for you.
I continuously gave you
news about Munna and Mohini.
I trapped Munna.
But leave alone
Laxminikant Pyarelal...
...you didn't even
introduced me to an Orchestra party.
I will introduce you.
- What are you going to introduce now?
Yesterday night Munna
fooled the police and escaped.
It is heard that he is
after me to kill me.
Why are you so scared?
A case of robbery has
been filed against him.
And police is after him.
And if you are so scared then...
...take this money
and go to your village.
No Shyamlal, Guldasta will
not go to his native place...
...but he will be going
to the police station.
You have ruined me.
He is the proof that I am innocent.
Ask him what the truth is.
What is this?
- Sir, don't beat me. I am singer.
Sir, I will tell you everything.
Shyamlal has done all this.
Ask him...
Raj Gopal.
- Yes sir.
Take his statement.
Come...
- I will tell you everything.
Where are you taking me? - Have a seat.
- Sir, you don't know...
...what a rogue this Shyamlal is.
- Is it?
Last year he...
-
Inspector sir, this
is Guldasta shouting.
Don't shout! This is a police station
not a college canteen.
They are beating him,
this is wrong, sir.
We know very well that what
is right and what is wrong.
But is this a new law to
beat a witness while...
...taking his statement?
Shut up.
- How can you do this to him? How?
Sir, this is his statement.
And he has accepted his crime.
And this is the money which he stole
from Munna and Shyamlal's house.
What is this going on, Sir?
- Keep quiet.
Put this rogue behind the bars.
Idiot. - You scoundrel, you are
trying to trap me in a crime...
...which I have not committed.
You have taken bribe from Shyamlal...
...you have taken the bribe
from Shyamlal. Get side.
Tell me, whether you
have taken the bribe or not.
People like you are
destroying this country... Get side.
Inspector... I won't leave you.
- Leave him.
I won't leave you.
- Leave me.
Get side. Leave me.
I won't leave you.
Shut up, tie him up.
Inspector, you come out ...
You come out.
I will go out, you rascal!
Shut up! You come out and then I
will show you. - Get back.
I will show you, you are
raising your hands on me.
Tie him up.
You are raising your
hands on the police?
You scoundrel, you are
going to beat me with belt.
After the statement of witness,
evidences and investigations...
...the court has
reached the conclusion that...
...Mahesh Deshmukh alias Munna
reached Mulchand Kochar's house...
...on the night of 14th
February with an intension to rob,...
...where he
deceived the police and escaped.
Then on the 15th February in
broad day light he robbed...
...Shyamlal's house along with his
friend Abbas Ali alias Guldasta.
The court gives one
year imprisonment to...
...Abbas Ali alias Guldasta.
And Munna the one who is
a terror to this city...
...is ordered to be banished.
He will not be allowed
to enter this city...
...during this one year period.
Now at least you believe me that...
...why I don't have faith
in your profession.
But I will be happy
if I bring back your faith.
But you will have to
pay a price for it...
I am ready to pay anything
to convert banished Munna...
...into Mahesh Deshmukh again.
Then give me twenty four hours time.
You have faith in me and
I will have faith in you.
Okay, I will wait for you.
Stop the vehicle.
Best of luck.
It is very difficult to find
Mohini in such a big place.
I don't know in which
dark cell will she be?
We will do one thing,
we all will spread in this area.
The one who will first
get information about...
...Mohini will inform all of us.
- What is going on?
Sir, this boy tried to run
from here yesterday night...
...and was saying that
he won't lift the load.
You scoundrel, you
are beating a child.
They have found Mohini!
Catch him.
You wait here, I will just be back.
Pascal! Anthony!
Run childrens, run with me fast...
She might be somewhere over here.
If she runs from here then
I won't leave any of you. Go.
Come out...
You will not be able to
go alive from my place.
I will go, I will surely go and
you will take him out from here.
Come...
Hey, get back,
if you show your smartness then...
...I will kill the Pathan
with this knife. Move!
Hey boys, run from here.
Munna, your enemy too
will praise your bravery.
Because not even a needle
can go out of this city...
...without my permission
and you are taking this girl.
I am not only taking
this girl from here...
I will burn your kingdom to
ashes and then go from here.
Stop him.
The vehicle is not working,
it would had been better...
...if someone had
pushed it from back.
We have won, Hail to children's...
Is it so?
Go, you all are free, go fast...
There will be only one aim
in Lotia Pathan's life...
...from today and
that is Munna's death.
Munna!
I will not let you separate from me.
Not even for a moment.
You don't know how...
...tough it was for me
to pass this one year.
I was not able to
sleep even for a moment...
...as I got the habit of
fainting after the beatings.
I want to leave everything,
that dance, that song...
...that house, that fame,
that money everything.
Have you gone crazy?
There is nothing in you except...
...your fame, money and house
that I should take you with me.
What are you saying, Munna?
The same thing that
you are listening.
If you can't give me a
luxurious life then...
...what is the use of your love?
What?
Is it for this why you loved me?
If your own father
has the greed of money.
Then what is wrong if
even I have the lust for it?
What do you want?
The same thing what
your father wants.
You should dance,
sing and earn money.
I will have the right on
it as much I have on you.
You are lying.
- What is there to lie? This is the truth.
After completing one year
punishment of banishment...
...and staying along with rogues...
...I have understood the real
kind of this world, Mohini.
Nor the love and nor the
dreams come in use in this world.
I too loved my dreams
but what did I find.
I used to think that my
dreams are in my clutches.
But I didn't know when it
slipped out of my hand as sand.
This is the truth. The same
way your Munna too has changed.
His dreams have also changed,
this is the truth.
Now his dream is to be rich,
and to get all the...
...luxuries of this world.
And he will do anything to get this.
"The world is tranquil...
the sky is tranquil."
"All the destinations
have become quiet."
"This path too is silent."
"The world is tranquil...
the sky is tranquil."
"All the destinations
have become quiet."
"This path too is silent."
"The world is tranquil...
the sky is tranquil."
"As the night came, the
one who had shelters...
...went to sleep"
"As the night came,
loafers like us came out...
...and were lost..."
"This street, that street...
This place, that place..."
"Where could we go even
if we would like to go..."
"All the destinations
have become quiet."
"This path too is silent..."
"This world is tranquil...
The sky too is tranquil..."
"Listen something about me...
Tell something about yourself..."
"Don't be quiet
when close to me..."
"I am close to you
and even far from you..."
"I am free too and
even helpless too..."
"Why this season of
love passed away..."
"Why has the world
won against us..."
"My heart is always sad..."
"And the life is in
complete darkness..."
"All the destinations are quiet"
"This path too is silent..."
"This world is tranquil...
The sky too is tranquil..."
Hey, old man, take your girl.
- My dear has come.
And give me my money.
- Money? Which money?
Cash Fifty thousand.
Do you remember it or will I
have to make you remember?
What will you make me remember?
Shyamlal, there is no use of
quarrelling with such people.
Give him the money.
- Money! I should pay it.
From where should I bring the money?
That day I had given you
fifty thousand rupees...
...as he was going to
come with Mohini and...
...we had to pay him or
else he would fight.
Didn't I give you the money?
You might have given
but I have spent I now.
I don't have it now,
we will pay you...
...as we get it,
now you go from here.
Hey Shyamlal, enough of this drama.
You daughter has come,
now give me my money quietly.
What will you do if I don't pay you?
Unless I don't get the money
this girl will stay with me.
Give me the money and take her away.
Someone stop him.
- Wait.
I will pay you the money,
take this and count it.
You amount will never
be wrong, Saxena sir.
Do call me if you
have any other work.
Sure, why not?
You disgraced yourself so
much in front of Mohini.
Why are you
punishing yourself brother?
What else would I have done?
- You could have accepted her.
She would have got a house and I
would have got a sister-in-law.
This is impossible, Jyoti.
Okay, I will make it
possible which you...
...feel is impossible.
I will tell her the truth and
then I will see how you ignore her.
Don't act like a fool, you
want to give her a house.
Saxena too can give that to her.
I am banished, police is after me.
I don't have enough
space to run then...
...how come will I give her a house?
I will always regret that...
...I was not able to
give you a sister-in-law.
And what about love?
- There will be love...
As hatred in her heart
and as a wound in my heart.
Sir.
Sir, I have fulfilled my promise.
My lord, the one who
has been brought...
...in front of you has not
only violated the rule of...
...banishment order, but he
has done many other crimes too.
My lord, Munna has not
learnt a lesson even after...
...being imprisoned for
one year in a murder case.
An unsuccessful robbery in
Mr. Kochar's farm house.
Robbery in Mr. Shyamlal's
house along with his...
...companion Guldasta.
An attack on the
capable Inspector Gupta.
It seems that this
man is in a war with...
...the innocent and
good people of this city.
These murderers are of
such a type that their...
...customs and
traditions is to perform crime.
My lord, such murderers should
be kept far from the society.
He is such an acid that
if he comes out then...
...he will burn the whole society.
Yes, I am an acid...
I accept that I am an acid
but I want to ask that...
...from where did
this acid come from?
To you, to the
public prosecutor and...
...all of you who are sitting here.
I want to ask that where
did this acid come from.
My lord, this acid did not
take birth in my mother's stomach.
The one who had
taken an oath to die...
...for the society and
country in the uniform of NCC...
...the one who had fulfilled
those promise even after...
...endangering his life and
losing his parents that acid is me.
Mahesh Deshmukh was
not an acid, My Lord.
Julie, give me a glass,
here is mine move of Five hundred.
What is going on Gupta?
- Nothing, just a time pass.
When a duty becomes time pass and...
...a gambler instead of
being scared of a policemen...
...plays along with him,
then not only money...
...is placed in the bet but
the fate of the country too is placed.
What do you want to prove Gagan Singh?
- Nothing.
You had shown the
power of the police and...
...had proved the truth as lie.
Today I am going to
show the same power and...
...prove the lie as truth.
Which lie, which truth?
Look at this belt, do
you remember anything?
I don't remember anything, pack.
I will move now.
Wait Inspector,
you will remember everything.
This belt will make
you remember everything.
Inspector, I too have a belt.
Only a belt is not enough,
the hands which are...
...used to taking bribe
and betraying their duty...
...don't have the
power to lift their belt.
Which innocent boy you had
beaten with this belt? - Munna.
What you had done with him?
- I had trapped him.
How did you trap him?
- By false witness.
Whose false witness?
Guldasta's. - How did you
made him give false witness?
By beating him.
Gupta, you memory is sharper
than a wild elephant.
Keep this memory intact
till you reach the court.
It will be better for you.
My lord, I have told you
everything that I remembered.
Munna... is innocent.
But I proved him
criminal for the greed of money.
Taking into consideration the
witness of Inspector Gupta...
...the court takes back the
allegations made on Munna...
...alias Mahesh Deshmukh.
And orders to take action
against Inspector Gupta.
Look Munna, this country,
society is yours even after...
...all the injustice is done to you.
Your father sacrificed
his life for this country.
You can't go anywhere by
getting upset with it.
What can I do alone?
- Everything can be done alone.
Everyone waits that
someone else will do it...
...some organization will do it,
some society will do it...
...government will do it or
some society will do it.
And no one do
anything except waiting.
How is it possible for me
in this city along with...
...the stigma of murder,
robbery and banishment.
Not here, In Goa, my friend
has a shipping factory there.
I have spoke to him about you.
You go there and start a new life.
Come on Mahesh, cheer up.
That's better, come.
Guldasta you, come, come inside.
How come you came here?
I have come here to
ask for forgiveness.
Baban said that you are
leaving this city and...
...are going to Goa.
This city gave me the name Munna.
The same city gave
another name of Banished.
Getting free from that,
I am going to start...
...a new life with a new name.
Leaving Mohini!
- Everything which this city had given me.
Friends too and enemies too.
I won't let you go
without Mohini, no way.
Only relations stop a human being.
And I don't have any relation.
You have one relation
and I will surely try to save it.
There is nothing in
between me and Munna...
...to be saved, understood.
No Mohini, I have
seen in Munna's eyes...
...whatever is left
between you and him.
What did you see?
The desire for money.
I am not Mohini for him,
I am a girl of an old man.
And he made a deal with
my father for my release...
...and threw me from one
hell to the other hell.
I gave up myself to
him with lots of faith.
I loved him forgetting myself.
But he used me for his profit.
He trampled my feelings.
I hate him, I hate his thought.
I hate him.
-
This is what he wanted that
you should start hating him.
Yes Mohini, he knew that
how much he loved you...
...that much you too loved him.
And he knew that you
won't marry someone else...
...unless you don't hate him.
He was ready to see you as
a queen in Saxena's palace.
But he was not ready
to see you wandering...
...here and there with a
banished person like him.
Saxena! - Yes, he had come to
know that Saxena wants to marry you.
And what about the money
which he took in front of me?
He distributed it.
He distributed everything...
...between his unemployed friends.
I can't change
whatever had happened.
But I can try to stop the
wrong which is going to happen.
Mohini, when Lotia kidnapped you...
...there was only one man
in this city to release you.
It was Munna.
He is leaving this city
permanently to live an anonymous life.
And now there is only one hand
in this city to be with him.
And it is yours.
The only aim of my life is to
bring both these hands together.
And if required then
the aim of my death too.
Go Mohini, go.
Wait Mohini, you won't
go anywhere. Go inside.
Shyamlal, she won't stop now.
- Get aside you thief.
My body is not very strong Shyamlal.
But I have made my soul
strong by living in jail.
And sometimes the soul
is stronger than a body.
Go Mohini, go.
Where are you going?
Go Mohini go, no one
will stop you today.
Hey Baban, look the
customer is coming, turn it here...
Baban it is your old customer.
Hey Marwadi, don't leave
your vehicle, catch it properly.
Run away from here or else
he will sell away my vehicle.
Hey boys, don't look at my face,
get on with your work.
Lots of work is pending.
Take it... - Where is the
screw which I had kept here?
Nut bolt... - Take it from
here and place it over there.
Baban brother... A great
wonder happened. - What happened?
Lotia Pathan is back and he
is hiding in the dockyard.
And he was saying that he
will kill Munna brother.
Before killing Munna,
he will have to kill me.
Munna brother you.
- Hey Chandi, where is Baban?
Lotia Pathan is hiding in
the dockyard to kill you.
Baban has gone to
compromise with him.
I had to take
revenge with you too Baban.
It's good that you
came here yourself.
To stop you from reaching Munna...
...this Baban can
reach anywhere, Lotia.
Don't spare those scoundrels.
Wait, I have to take
my revenge with him.
Lotia, you are finished now.
- No Baban, no...
Leave me... I won't leave him,
I will kill him...
No Baban... he has enmity
with me, leave that knife...
Munna, your life has
just started now...
...you go away from here.
Baban, your life too
is waiting for you.
Munna!
Baban! Baban!
No Baban no...
- Munna, I had told you...
- Munna.
Lotia!
Learn to bow before the law.
Inspector, you are
showing me an act of bravery...
...by disarming me.
If you dare then keep
aside that pistol then...
...I will show you that how a
law can bend Lotia Pathan.
To bend a traitor like
you in front of the law...
...one doesn't need an
uniform or this pistol.
The youth of this country is
more than a match for you.
Mahesh.
I know that I allowed
you take law in your hands.
It is a crime but still I did it.
Because I felt that
this is the only way...
...to bring out the
acid present inside you.
Now my aim has been completed.
I am ready to bear any punishment...
...that law is going to give me.
-
"One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten...
...eleven, twelve and thirteen."
"I was... I was counting
the days for your return."
Come my beloved it's spring time."