SANSKRIT CHANTS
Look at the girl's fate! This
ramshackle house and this car!
Maya has found a wealthy groom!
They didn't even
have to give dowry!
Neither a music band,
nor any relatives.
As if it's not a
marriage but a robbery!
I think something is fishy.
There must a flaw in either the
groom's family or the bride's.
Mr. Anand, you've to
perform a ritual,
..before tying the
nuptial thread.
I'll utter the oaths.
Repeat after me.
I... - I...
This moment onwards...
- This moment onwards...
Take responsibility
of your livelihood.
To fulfil all your wishes and
to always keep you happy.
I promise you. - I promise you.
Accepting you as my wife,
I want to give you
this nuptial thread.
You say now.
I... - I....
I'll be with you through all
the ups and downs in life.
Following the religious path
laid down by the scriptures,
I won't tolerate any
unrighteousness.
I accept the nuptial thread,
..considering the sacred
fire as the witness,
..considering God
to be the witness,
..all the celestial
bodies as the witness,
..saints and sages
as the witness,
I promise you...
- I promise you,
..that I'll hold this nuptial
thread dearer than my life.
I'll hold this nuptial
Now put the nuptial
thread around her neck.
These 7 rounds around the altar
binds you both together,
..as life partners for
7 lifetimes to come.
Dad!
You are so bad, dad!
You got married alone!
Why didn't you take me along?
I've brought your mom.
She'll always be with you.
Greet her, dear. - Greetings!
Savitri!
Look! Anand has come!
He has brought lady luck home!
Come here!
May God bless you!
May you lead a good life!
Listen!
Anand's room... - It's ready.
Get up. Go and take rest!
What happened?
Ganesh! - Yes sir!
Open the dispensary! - Yes, sir!
What happened?
- I don't know, sir!
What happened to
daughter-in-law?
Nothing.
Son! - You stay here!
Ganesh, close the door! - Okay!
What happened to
daughter-in-law?
Is there anything to fear?
Will you say something?
Nothing serious!
She fainted due to fatigue
and will be fine by morning.
Don't mention it to mother!
She'll worry for no reason.
Both of you can go to sleep now.
No need to mention
it to anybody!
How are you feeling now?
Forget that we got
married tonight.
Consider me as your friend and
tell me what the problem is.
Look, I'm a doctor.
I've told everybody that you
fainted due to fatigue.
Nobody knows that you
consumed poison.
If a girl consumes poison
on the wedding night,
..then it's obvious that she got
married against her wishes.
Look, Maya! We have our
entire lives ahead of us!
Life will be difficult if we
keep each other in the dark.
Don't cry. Tell me
what the matter is.
Have you heard that joke?
A man came beneath a car
with an intention to die.
But he didn't die because
it was an ambulance.
They took him to the
hospital and he was saved.
You consumed poison in the
presence of a doctor?
It means God doesn't
want you to die now.
You're destined to live
a long and happy life.
What's the matter?
Whatever you tell you. I'll
listen to you patiently.
Tell me!
"Between us!"
"What a strange bond
is this between us?"
What is strange, boss?
You are from Patiala and
even I'm from Patiala.
This is our bond. What else?
Hadn't I met you, I would've been
running a gambling den in Koliwada.
Laxmikant-Pyarelal have composed
such nice tunes! Great!
Many have tried their hand,
but none could match them.
Enough! Music won't
fill my appetite.
I want food! Food!
Immediately!
Since yesterday we've been living
off a loaf of bread and tea.
I can't take it anymore.
Fool! Let's find a house first.
Then I'll cook for you myself.
Hot cornbread and spinach!
Oh my God! When will
you find a house?
When will you cook and when
will I eat? - What to do?
Nobody is willing to let out
their house to a bachelor.
Then say that you're married!
This is Mumbai!
You can't survive
without lies here!
I'll give you a tight slap!
We'll begin a new life with a lie!?
No way!
I'll die! But I won't lie!
Then we both will die! Finished!
Heard that? The conch is blowing!
We spoke the truth!
You're so foolish!
It's not a conch!
It's a factory bell!
- It's all the same!
We are searching for work and
this is the factory's bell.
Meaning a worker's conch!
Got it? Let's go!
Didn't I say our work
will be done today? Look!
There's no bell! What to ring?
Why do you need a bell? Are we
pleaders? Knock on the door.
Shout as well!
Why don't you call out
with your sweet voice?
Ma'am!
Ma'am! Ma'am...
Greetings! We've
come from Patiala!
Wait! I'm coming!
- But you are leaving!
We saw a girl's face.
It's a good sign.
But she went away.
- She will come back.
Don't you have any vessel?
What is the need for that? My
hand and mouth are sufficient.
Its okay! He's young!
You both sit here and eat in this!
- No! You are mistaken!
We've come to enquire
about the house on rent.
You've humiliated me. I have some
honour, tradition and values.
You tarnished everything!
- What? You didn't even let me lick i
We won't stay here. Let's go.
Listen! Grandpa has
called you in.
I told you!
The second sign is also auspicious.
Let's go.
The drawstring. - What?
The drawstring!
Greetings!
Maya! - Yes, grandpa!
I think you're right, Maya.
They look like them.
Like who? - You're hanging
this box around your neck.
So it looks as if
you're begging.
I won't answer back since
you're elder to me.
Even I have honour,
tradition and values.
Talk to me respectfully.
- What do you want?
Respect or room? - I'm already
respected. I need a room.
Look, I'm giving only
one room on rent.
This box won't even help
you to feed yourself.
How will you pay the rent?
Grandpa, I don't beg. I've come
here to be a music director.
Have you ever seen the
big music directors,
..playing music on the streets?
Is he your son?
No! - Yes!
What's this? One is saying no.
The other is saying yes.
What is this?
- Actually we desperately need a room.
Nobody is willing to give me a
room because I'm a bachelor.
And...
- Bachelors first take a room on rent.
Then they escape with,
..the landlord's daughter
and the rent as well!
Many even run away
with the wives.
Do you think I'm such a man?
- You don't look like one.
I'm telling you all this because
women live in this house.
No such behaviour will
be tolerated here.
Not at all! The
question doesn't arise.
Then listen. You won't enter the
house after 10 o'clock at night.
Then where will I go?
- You will come before 10 o'clock.
You won't cook in the room.
- Will we have our meals with you?
Shut up! You can have your meals
anywhere but not in the room.
60 Rupees is the rent and the
deposit is 300. -300 rupees?
We're leaving, grandpa.
Fine! I want to see the room.
- I want the advance first.
Where is the bathroom? - There.
Hey, you! Where is he going?
- To bring the advance.
Advance? In the bathroom?
- Yes! My boss is very smart!
His mother told him to beware
of the thieves in Mumbai.
So he doesn't keep the
money in his pocket.
He keeps it underneath.
- Meaning?
Here. In his underwear. How
will the thief steal it now?
Please take this. - Drawstring.
What? - Drawstring!
Keep it here!
Who knows what kind
of business he does!
Can I see the room now? - There!
How will we go up? By flying?
- Hey, fool! Don't fly!
Maya! - Yes!
How is it? - Good. Will do.
What? - This stairs.
Patiala guy! Talk to me clearly!
Else I will not spare you!
Got it?
Show them the room and
come down quickly!
Look how she's opening the door.
Here's the room. Buy a new lock.
- No. Give me this key.
I too will practice with this.
Get another lock. You will get
the key. - Give this to me!
The boss won't go to the
toilet again for 5 bucks.
I will teach you a lesson!
You've humiliated me once again!
Come!
Boss, the luggage is outside!
No!
Boss, it's better if you
shorten this drawstring.
If grandpa sees it
again, he'll pull it.
Don't taunt me early in the morning!
I warn you!
Chotu!
- What happened, boss? Who bit you?
Chotu, there is a hole.
But no latch!
Boss, hold it from inside with
the drawstring. - Shut up!
Guard the door.
You know that I
bathe in the nude.
How do I know? When did
you take a bath with me?
Don't talk too much!
Just do as I say!
Remain seated!
- What if I stand?
Don't let anybody in
under any circumstance.
I'll be in trouble
if anybody comes in.
Naked?
Boss, its better if I
inform everybody that
..there's no latch
in the bathroom,
..and the boss is bathing naked.
Don't be a fool! Remain seated!
And don't move! If
you dare to move...
Chotu!
Boss! No! I won't do it! Sorry!
Boss! Forgive me!
The guy is one in a million!
He has his own house. 3 bedroom
and a hall. Attached bathroom!
As far as good deeds
are concerned,
..not just his father, but even his
ancestors were social reformers.
His age is around
25 to 26 years.
The dowry is only
25,000-30,000 rupees.
They're demanding a dowry
despite being social reformers?
Being social reformers won't change
the outlook of the scoundrels.
I'm against dowry!
This is what I'm saying!
She is a girl,
You would've demanded a dowry
if you had a grandson.
What did you say, Gangu?
She is such a virtuous girl!
She's my eldest granddaughter, Maya.
I was talking about her.
God bless you!
She is the other granddaughter.
- God bless you!
She is my daughter!
Gangu, you are blessing everybody
as if you'll even get me married.
That's what I'm trying to tell you!
Why not?
Dye your hair! Shave
off your moustache!
Remove your spectacles.
You'll look like a hero.
Shut up! Come!
Age is 49 but not yet 50.
Right eye is working fine.
All his 32 teeth are intact.
That too golden!
Maya will be rich!
Are you mocking me?
- Sir, I'm not mocking you.
You are mocking yourself.
Look at your state!
Your son-in-law left your
daughter and children,
..at your house and went away.
This house is mortgaged.
How much money do you earn?
Not much.
You can't afford to give dowry
but you want a nice groom.
Lower your expectations
and then talk.
I'll lessen the amount if you
compromise with the situation.
Are you Ganga Prasad?
- Why? Any objections?
No. The postman was asking. I
think it was your money order.
My money order?
I told him there's no
Ganga Prasad here.
Where did the postman go? - He must
be at the corner of the street.
Oh my God! Postman! - Listen!
Your album!
- You have put me in trouble! Postman!
What is this, Maya?
I neither like this man nor
the alliances that he brings.
Sheela has not even
completed her education.
She has to learn typing
and shorthand as well.
How can I marry until she gets
a job and Prakash is cured?
Don't worry about these never
ending household problems.
I said what I had to say!
I won't marry now!
"What are you doing
in my courtyard?"
Chotu! Quickly get limestone!
Can I get some limestone?
To apply on boss's thumb.
Apply some ointment!
Limestone won't heal it.
I don't know that but the boss will
only apply limestone as it's free.
Fire is free too.
Shall I give that?
I've seen many misers!
But none like your boss.
Ma'am, you don't know the boss.
He doesn't talk about his problems.
But I'll tell you.
The boss' family is in Punjab.
He has an old mother
and young siblings.
She works as a
maid to feed them.
But boss has to bear other expenses.
Do you know what he did?
He donated blood a few days
ago and sent the money home.
Chotu! Knock the door.
- You do it.
Chotu! Look my thumb...
What happened? - We have come!
So what should I do?
- Move aside and let us go in.
Grandpa had asked you to
be back home by 10pm.
My watch is not working.
So I didn't know the time and
I forgot that grandpa...
You won't forget it if you
sleep outside for a night.
We're sorry! It
won't happen again.
Good! You go in!
Apologise and I'll let you in.
- Fine. I apologise.
It won't happen again. Sorry!
Don't say it with a sullen face.
- Sorry!
The first one was better.
I need a needle and thread
to stitch boss' pants.
I'll stitch it.
How is your boss's thumb?
- Not good!
The thumb has swollen badly.
Move!
Take this! Tell him to apply it.
Else he might have to amputate it
in his bid to save a few pennies.
Miser! The milk's getting burnt!
Boss!
Did you get the needle and the thread?
- I got it stitched, boss.
Great!
Who gave you this?
- This? That...
What joke is this! I don't like it!
Let me tell you!
Where are all the family members?
Why don't you come out?
What happened? Why
are you shouting?
Look at her shamelessness! She
dares to ask what happened!
Why did you send
your stuff to me?
You are a strange man!
It's for your own good!
You will feel better
after using it!
Will I use this? Am I a
woman that I'll use this?
What happened? Why
is he yelling?
Do you expect me to be quiet?
Prem Pratap from Patiala
won't tolerate this!
Beware if you uttered a single word!
I'll burn this ladder!
You'll hang there like a
monkey all your life.
Hey you! Why are you getting angry?
What happened?
What happened? Why
is he yelling?
He was saying,
..that he was a high and low jump
champion in school. – Really!
So he's going to jump. - Great!
Will you jump from this height?
Jump!
Yes! Jump! Please jump!
You! - Boss, let it be!
I think he's mad!
"Call me lovingly!"
Wow!
Chotu!
Hey! What are you doing here?
I'm returning from office. But
why are you wetting that cloth?
This? This is my boss's lunch.
Midday meal.
Midday meal? - Yes.
Different types of hunger
in the world have,
..different ways
of satiating it.
My boss knows all these
tricks very well.
When you're hungry and you
don't have anything to eat,
..the only solution
is to wet a cloth,
..and tie it tightly
around the stomach.
Your hunger vanishes
in 3 minutes.
This is the boss'
lunch thrice a week.
Then why is he in Mumbai?
Tell him to return to his
village and do farming.
Tell me something, Chotu.
Does he know music?
What does that girl think?
She's no match to me!
I am Prem Pratap from Patiala!
My family...
Now what to say, boss?
I told her that my boss is
not less than any Beethoven.
Beethoven is nothing. I'm no
less than his father too!
I'll mesmerise her with my music.
Pick up that drum!
1, 2, 3, 4!
"Don't fall in love with me,"
"if the heart starts
beating, what will happen?"
"There's a delicate
veil in between,"
"what will happen if it slips?"
"Don't fall in love with me,"
"The heart is a sinner,."
"the body is wounded!"
"The anklet is tinkling!"
"The heart is a sinner,."
"the body is wounded!"
"The anklet is tinkling!"
"If any bell of your anklet...."
"What will happen if the bells
of your anklet tinkle?"
"What will happen
if it tinkles?"
"Don't fall in love with me,"
"Don't fall in love with me."
"I'm afraid of your
kohl and the clouds,"
"the thunder in the clouds...."
"What'll happen if the thunder
in the clouds struck?"
"What will happen
if it strikes?"
"Don't fall in love with me."
"Don't tease me,"
"my desires might get aroused!"
"My heart is a glass,
it's brittle,"
"what'll happen if it shatters?"
"Don't fall in love with me!"
What happened?
Take this. Give this to your boss.
- What is this?
Snacks. The sauce
is packed inside.
It smells nice! How many? 100 or 200?
- Shut up!
Give it to your boss. Ask him
whether he liked it or not.
No, ma'am! If boss loses his temper
he'll throw the snacks on my face.
Nothing will happen. Tell him that
I've made it especially for him.
What are you saying, ma'am?
You don't know.
Boss will starve. But he won't beg
to anybody. - You are a fool!
It's right that you shouldn't
take anything from others.
But what's the harm
taking it from one's kin?
Kin? What do you mean?
I mean to say that
I'm not a stranger.
Look, isn't boss like your
elder brother? - Yes.
So that makes me your sister-in-law.
- What?
What are you? My sister-in-law?
So what will be your
relation with the boss?
I mean to say...
I see! So this is the issue!
I'll tell him! Sister-in-law!
Snacks?
- Rice cakes weren't available.
I gave you the money
for just 2 rice cakes.
Where did you get so
many snacks from?
I didn't bring it from the hotel boss.
Sister-in-law gave this.
Sister-in-law? Who?
The girl downstairs!
No, boss! I didn't accept it
willingly! she didn't listen.
She said boss won't
say anything.
What is this? - Snacks!
I don't like it!
Let me tell you!
If you don't like it then throw this on
that fool's face who gave it to you.
That's what I'm doing! Your dear
granddaughter has sent these!
Ask her!
Maya!
Grandpa, what happened is that
the small boy came to me...
Not in Marathi! - Shut up!
How did the snacks go up?
Look, grandpa! Don't
abuse me in Marathi!
If I start abusing in Punjabi,
..you won't be able to
understand anything!
What nonsense is this! You came to
give me alms as if I'm a beggar!
I forgave her
thinking she's a kid!
Today again you sent it!
This is the limit!
I live in your house and pay the rent.
I don't live here for free.
I admit that I'm poor.
I don't have money.
But I toil! I don't come to
you for alms! - Listen to me!
I'm telling you and her
for the last time!
Prem Pratap from Patiala has some
honour, tradition and values.
If you do it again, I won't
tolerate it. Beware!
So you had given him snacks!
No, grandpa. Chotu
was very hungry.
I took pity on him
and gave him some.
Maybe he gave it to his boss too.
This fool got infuriated.
Look at this! We're giving
him food with love,
..and he's abusing us!
That too in Punjabi!
I see! He doesn't
have a single penny,
..but talks like the king of Patiala.
I'll teach him a lesson!
You! - Let it be, grandpa!
Shut up! I won't spare him!
Let it be, grandpa. He's mad!
He doesn't understand anything.
You'll tell him
something in Marathi.
He won't be able to understand
anything. Sit down!
Have your breakfast.
He will pay for this.
Did you see? The fruits of your
honour, tradition and values.
This banana! If you had
listened to that producer,
..we would've had good
food and ice-cream to eat.
But what did you do?
You refused!
If he wanted a film song, then
you should've given it to him.
Why do you act so smugly?
Why will I sell
somebody else's music?
Boss, we all are in
the same profession.
Give and take goes
on in business.
Just think. You ask for
sweets from a vendor.
He gives you snacks instead.
Will you take it? - Why will I?
Don't I know the difference
between sweets and savoury?
Won't I throw the savoury on
that shopkeeper's face? - Yes!
Similarly the producer threw
the offer on your face.
Look, Chotu! I can't
imitate anybody!
We can't starve all
our life either!
Let it be! Knock the door!
No, boss. You shouldn't wake
up the sleeping serpent.
She'll bite you. Listen to
me and sleep here only.
Am I scared? I pay the rent.
I'll daringly knock on the door.
Praise the almighty!
Chotu went in!
- Let him! You talk to me.
Are you nuts?
Don't you even understand,
..why a girl secretly
sends snacks to a guy?
I can't make music secretly. How
can I eat snacks sent secretly?
Lower your voice.
You'll wake up grandpa.
I'm not scared of your grandpa. As
if he is not grandpa but a lion.
Call your grandpa! Call him!
Call everybody! What is this?
At times you send snacks,
at times something else.
Don't lock horns with
Prem Pratap from Patiala!
I have honour,
tradition and values!
Wow! What a scene! What form!
I'm blessed!
CHANTS
Wow! Beautiful!
Lovely! Beautiful!
Look this is 'Danashvi' raga.
You shouldn't use 'Shuddevat'
in this Use 'Kovatdevat'.
If you will use 'Shuddevat',
it will change the raga.
Stop that!
Stop that noise, I'm trying
to teach music here.
"The anklet is tinkling!"
Stupid! Fool! Idiot!
Don't be angry! Use 'Shuddevat'!
It's okay!
"Fool!"
"When a fool plays a
game, he ruins it!"
"If the tracks are damaged...."
"If the tracks are damaged,
the train will be derailed!"
"When a fool plays a
game, he ruins it!"
"People who don't have a heart,"
"Why should I meet such people?"
"Such people..."
"If you meet such people...."
"If you meet such people,
the meeting is ruined!"
"When a fool plays a
game, he ruins it!"
"If the light and
the wick stay away,
"how will there be light?"
"There will be darkness
the whole night,"
"the oil will be wasted!"
"When a fool plays a
game, he ruins it!"
"The bird is eager to fly,"
"how to open the cage?"
"If the prisoner ran away,"
"If the prisoner ran away,
what'll be the use of the cage?"
"Fool!"
"When a fool plays a
game, he ruins it!"
Idiot! - You are right!
I've been observing your
attempts for a long time.
Had a girl been
after me like this,
I would've already
roamed around with her,
..and took her to a
nice restaurant.
Shown her a movie and
settled the matter.
Aren't you ashamed to talk
like this at this age!
Aren't you ashamed to talk about
this to an innocent child?
What can I do? I can only
tell you my problems.
Do one thing, Chotu! Convey
my feelings to your boss!
I'll do that. What's the big deal?
I'll quickly tell boss.
Boss too will come down quickly
and tell your grandpa.
Will that be fine with you?
- No.
That fool is unpredictable! He'll
surely do something like that.
Then grandpa will thrash him.
What's the use?
What is this? Can't you
talk from a distance?
I won't bite you! Why are
you so scared of me?
Scared? Why will I
be scared of you?
I've already paid the
rent to your grandpa.
I haven't come to
ask for the rent.
Will you be able to
compose the music,
..if someone gives
you the lyrics?
Again the same thing!
Do you see this, Chotu?
This Marathi girl is again challenging
Prem Pratap from Patiala!
Boss, you're always
eager to fight.
You should first ask
which song it is.
Tell me. Which is the...
Is this a song or a horoscope?
Won't you read what's written?
I don't want to read it. You read it.
I'll understand.
Look, I want you to hear it properly.
Understand it properly.
Engrave it in your
heart and your mind.
Let it course through your veins.
Let it be a part of your blood.
Chotu! Look what she's saying.
Boss, she's telling you to
understand it properly.
Once you understand the meaning,
everything else will be fine.
Fine! Read it out!
This is a love song. We
both love each other a lot.
I understood!
Really? - Yes!
A girl and a boy are
best of friends.
Not a girl and a boy!
You and me!
Fine! What's the situation?
It's midnight. Everybody at
home is in deep slumber.
Only I can't sleep.
Because I love you a lot.
I can't live without
you even for a moment.
So I quietly get up and come
to meet you on the roof.
You are here all alone.
It's a moonlit night. There
is silence all around.
I run to you and embrace you. You
hug me tightly in your arms.
Warm breaths, fast
beating hearts,
Smouldering bodies,
souls in pain!
Actors like Amitabh and Rekha
will be apt for this song.
Why did they come in between
you and me! You ***!
Just watch! Their
acting and my music!
The song will be a super hit!
Even the children will sing it!
Chotu, pick up the drum!
Read it.
I can't live without you.
You can't live without me.
Love can't exist without us.
Without love, we can't exist.
What? Repeat it. Let me
understand the meaning.
Boss, the meaning is that you and
Maya are made for each other.
Made for each other! - I see!
Meaning without me,
even you can't live!
Now you've understood it boss!
Just look there.
Fine! Start the beat!
"I can't live without you,
you can't live without me!"
"Love can't exist without us,
without love, we can't exist!"
"I can't live without you,
you can't live without me!"
Liked the tune?
Nice.
Chotu, I have a doubt.
When you, me or
love doesn't exist,
..who's singing this song?
Why is he singing and where?
What do I care? Continue!
Boss, you are a fool! Stupid!
Are these the words?
No, the actual words
are I'm a fool.
I'm stupid, idiot.
Sing it like this.
Let's start. 1-2-3-4!
"I'm a fool, stupid an idiot!"
"I am a fool!"
Prem Pratap!
Prem Pratap from Patiala!
Why are you screaming?
Will you hear it if I
say call out softly?
Here's your money order receipt.
Money order? I didn't send any money.
What is this receipt for?
Is your name Prem Pratap? - Yes!
Do you recognise the
signature of the receiver?
This is my mother's signature.
Chotu! I didn't send
money to mother.
Then how come this receipt?
Boss, what do I know
who sent the money?
Where are the bangles? Why
don't you say anything?
I gave my necklace and
made bangles for you.
So that it'll prove
useful in your marriage.
But you don't even bother to
tell me where you lost it!
Why are you yelling? Had I known,
I would've brought it myself.
I'll teach you a lesson! Where
are your bangles? Tell me!
Go and bring Maya's bangles.
- What bangles, boss?
Give it to Maya.
Didn't you hear what I said?
I won't go! Go and give
it if you want to.
Chotu! - Are you a man?
You always talk about music!
But you can't understand
what's in a girl's heart.
How can you become
a music director?
Fine! Now go and return it!
- Return it!
Will returning the bangles
set everything right?
Will her wounds heal? Will
she be relieved of the pain?
If you want to return, then
return her smile, her love.
Have you ever thought why that
girl mortgaged her bangles?
For your sake!
Why did she send money to your mother?
Why did she quietly endure the
beatings? For your sake, boss!
Poor girl! She fell
in love with a fool.
Shall I tell you
the truth, Chotu?
Even I love Maya a lot.
But I don't express my love.
I can't tell it to anybody.
Because Maya's family
won't accept my love.
I'm a poor man, unemployed too.
There's only one option left.
To elope with Maya.
Do you know the consequences
of that, Chotu?
Maya's humiliation. Her
family's humiliation.
She has a younger sister, too.
Who will marry her?
Maya is a nice girl. She's
beautiful and virtuous.
If she gets married
in a rich family,
..all the problems of this
family will be solved.
I keep quiet because of all this.
- Forgive me, boss.
That poor girl asserts her
love for me in different ways.
But I feign ignorance.
I even sing that I'm
a fool, stupid.
What to do? I'm helpless.
And you...
I heard your helplessness
and your heart too.
Your helplessness is
true like your heart.
But even I'm helpless.
Hear it out.
No girl should fall in
love before marriage.
But I've committed that mistake.
Now I can't love anyone else.
If I marry someone else,
..my life will become miserable.
"If I could keep
quiet, I would have,"
"but it's difficult
to keep quiet!"
"Read my eyes and understand
what lies in my heart,"
"it's difficult to express it!"
"I'm innocent, I don't know
the language of eyes!"
"Innocent!"
"Bangle!"
"Damsel, your bangles
stole my slumber,"
"Bangle!"
"Damsel, your bangles
stole my slumber,"
"Beloved! Some day I'll come
to your house wearing this!"
"Beloved!"
"Forget this fervour,"
"talk to me comfortably!"
"Who told you to
love me so much?"
"We can't control love!"
"Bangle!"
"Damsel, your bangles
stole my slumber,"
"Bangle!"
"If we can't unite in this
world, let's die together!"
"Flowers will blossom through
this earth, if we die together!"
"My heart is tormented,"
"I can't sleep the whole night!"
"Bangle!"
"Damsel, your bangles
stole my slumber,"
"Beloved!"
"Someday, I'll come to
your house wearing this!"
"Beloved!"
Datta, the guy looks
like a Prince!
He's a rich doctor. This
family will prosper.
It's fine. But Gangu, it's
the guy's second marriage.
So my heart doesn't agree.
Let me see! His first wife
is not alive, father!
His age is also around 30.
- That's what even I'm saying.
Only you can make Datta see
reason now. - Shut up!
Father, I think the guy is fine.
He's rich too.
It'll be good for our children.
- That's what I'm saying.
The guy's mother is
on her death bed.
She'll soon die. Maya is
going to rule after that.
Then you go and fix the alliance.
- The guy's family is in a hurry.
Tomorrow is an auspicious day.
The marriage can be conducted
tomorrow. If it's acceptable to you.
How many times should
I say that its fine!
That's what even I'm saying. It's
great! Congratulations Datta!
Wow! The girl too has arrived.
It's a good sign for the marriage.
God bless you!
What was he saying? What good sign?
Whose marriage?
Your marriage, dear. The
date is fixed for tomorrow.
So suddenly? How can you fix
my marriage without asking me?
We've confirmed it after taking
everything into consideration.
Yes, Maya! We've thought
well and selected this guy!
No matter what your decision is!
I won't marry!
What did you say?
Have you gone mad? We've
fixed everything!
Your marriage is tomorrow.
- I don't want to marry!
Aren't you ashamed
to disgrace us?
We've given our word! If you refused,
our image will be tarnished!
Let me be! Listen to me!
I won't marry!
How can you refuse?
- Come inside! I'll make sure you do!
Come in! - Come!
Chotu! - Yes!
Go and see what Maya is doing.
I've checked 5 times
since evening.
She's sitting on the window
sill like a prisoner.
She's crying inconsolably.
I'll wait at the corner of the street.
Quickly bring Maya.
What's in this bag?
Some clothes, money that I've
saved and some jewellery.
We are not eloping, Maya. We'll
get married in the temple.
Then we'll take our
elders' blessing.
Go and keep the luggage.
No, Prem. You are naive.
If you returned, grandpa will
behave very badly with you.
It's okay. We're not
doing anything wrong.
I don't fear anybody except God.
But Prem...
- Go and keep the luggage.
Look, Chotu. The shops
will open by 4:30.
Buy two garlands and thread and
come directly to the temple.
By then, the priest
too will wake up.
Maya!
I know that every girl desires
her marriage to be conducted,
..with great pomp and show.
She should wear the bridal attire.
Henna should adorn her hands.
But you have to get married like this.
Secretly! Covertly!
But Maya, if everybody's
desires got fulfilled,
..then temples
wouldn't be built,
..and nobody would
come here to pray.
No, Prem. I have no
complains with God.
I have no complains with you, too.
I'm angry at myself.
Because of me, your image
is being tarnished.
A self-respecting man like you,
..has to secretly accept an
unfortunate female like me.
Instead of my family's blessings
you'll only get their curses.
Maya, you shouldn't say that.
Elders do get annoyed
with children.
But they never curse them.
Your family will forget
all this very soon.
They'll shower their
blessing on us.
Prem. – Beat him!
You come with me.
- Don't beat him!
Want to do love marriage?
Don't beat him!
- Keep quiet! Come!
I’ll teach you a lesion.
Please don't beat Prem! No!
Please don't beat Prem!
Take this medicine.
Take this medicine
and try to sleep.
You need rest.
Please.
Have it. It'll flush out
the remaining poison.
But I don't want to live.
I don't have the courage
to lead dual lives.
Get some poison for me.
I want to die.
Look, I told you that I'm a doctor.
It's my profession to fight death.
It's very easy to poison
somebody to death.
But it's difficult to
save somebody from death.
Death can't solve any problem.
I won't pressurise you.
But I too have a problem.
Hear it out. Then you can
do whatever you want.
Shanta, my first wife, died
while giving birth to Chanda.
Her photo is still in this room.
This is proof enough
that I still love her.
She died 6 years ago. But
I didn't marry again.
My mother was very
worried for me.
Gradually this sorrow took a toll on
her health and she got bedridden.
She had only one wish. She
wanted a daughter-in-law.
So that the motherless
Chanda gets a mother.
You've seen how ill mother is.
As a son, I want my mother
to live a long life.
But as a doctor, I know that she
won't live for more than a few days.
I agreed to get married to
give some happiness to,
..my mother during
her last days.
When mother applied
vermillion on your forehead,
I saw the joy on her face.
I hadn't seen such happiness on
mother's face for the past 6 years.
I know that I'll never
get to see it again.
In order not to hurt my
mother during her last days,
I request you to live in this
house for a few days, as my wife.
I promise you that
I'll find your Prem.
I'll hand you over
to him respectfully.
I don't want you to
stay here forcefully.
If you live as my
wife for a few days,
I'll forever remain
indebted to you.
I hope you'll think
calmly about this,
..and reach the right
decision by morning.
I'll take leave now. Goodnight!
Dad! Grandpa said that from today
my new mother will look after me!
Then why are you
giving me a bath?
Dear, this house is
new for your new mom.
She doesn't even know
where the bathroom is,
..where the soap is, where
Chanda's clothes are.
After she learns all this,
she'll look after you.
Don't trouble your new mom.
First find out whether she's
in a good mood. - But...
But why will her
mood be bad, dad?
I've brought her here away
from her home, her mother.
So she must be missing them.
I see! Then send new mom
back to her house, dad!
I'll send her, dear. In a week or
so, I'll send her back to her home.
How are you feeling now?
You didn't take the tablets.
Please don't be careless.
You've to take it twice, in
the morning and evening.
I'm going to the hospital.
I'll find out about him.
He must be somewhere
in the city.
We'll find him and all your
problems will be solved.
I'm leaving.
I have a small request.
Mother must be eagerly waiting
for her daughter-in-law.
If not as a daughter-in-law,
then for the sake of humanity,
..if you sit with my dying
mother for sometime,
I'll be indebted to you.
What is this, son?
It hasn't been a day since your marriage,
and you're going to the hospital?
What will that poor girl think?
It's important to go, father. I
have to perform 2-3 operations.
Why should the patients suffer
because of my marriage?
Why to put their life in danger?
Anand, you refused for 6 years.
But you've finally married again
for the sake of your mother.
Because I won't live for long.
Am I right?
Don't say that, mother.
You're getting better.
In a week's time you'll
start walking, too.
Talk to your mother like a
son, not like a doctor.
Tell me. Did you like the girl?
She's good. She was
about to come down.
She saw some books lying around.
So she started arranging them.
She'll come to meet you
after taking a bath.
Have you both gelled well? Have
you both liked each other?
Yes.
Son, I know that you can
never forget Shanta.
I don't say that you should
forget people after their death.
But you should not
hurt those who're,
..alive by mourning
for the deceased.
What have I done, mother?
Promise that you'll
always keep her happy.
Promise me. - Yes, mother.
I'll do everything for
Maya's happiness.
I promise you that I'll
fulfil all her wishes.
I heard that day before, a
couple came here to get married.
Yes. I'm asking about them.
Can you tell me where that guy is?
- I told you. I don't know anything.
Kishan! Was there a
fight here that night?
Sir, it was great! They bought
two garlands from my shop!
That guy was a Punjabi!
Look at his guts! He was flirting
with a girl from my locality!
People thrashed him
black and blue!
I quietly watched
from behind the door.
Nowadays people shouldn't interfere
in all this. - Then what happened?
Sir, I fled. Who'd want to
get involved with the law?
Wait! I'll answer it! Go!
Hello! This is Chanda
Anand speaking!
Hello, Ms. Anand. This is Dr.
Anand speaking.
Yes, doctor.
Did mom have her breakfast?
- No!
No? Did she have her medicine?
Did she go down to meet grandma?
- No!
I see!
Listen, dear.
Tell mom it's fine if she doesn't
want to go to meet grandma.
But ask her to take her medicine.
Fine?
Oh! I see!
Dad called up and said its okay if
you don't want to meet grandma.
But have your breakfast and
do take your medicine.
That is most important.
'Mother must be eagerly waiting
for her daughter-in-law.'
'If not as a daughter-in-law,
for the sake of humanity,'
'if you sit with my dying
mother for sometime,'
'I'll be indebted to you.'
Did you like this house, dear?
And my son?
Did he talk to you?
His nature is a bit
different, dear.
He doesn't talk too much.
Don't feel disappointed. Ok?
The honour, respect, peace
and harmony of this house,
I'm handing over
everything to you, dear.
The day I had come in this
house as a daughter-in-law,
..my mother-in-law had given
me this responsibility.
I'm doing the same thing today.
Though you're young,
but from today,
I'm giving you the responsibility
of three children.
Father, son and granddaughter.
You'll have to be the
mother of all three.
Anand didn't marry for
6 years fearing that,
..maybe the step-mother won't
take good care of the child.
But I judged you at first sight.
That you are not
such kind of a girl.
Promise me dear, that
you'll look after Chanda.
I knew that you'll
be kind at heart.
Your arrival will bring back
the happiness of this house.
Mom, dad had called again!
He was asking whether
mom had her breakfast.
I said mom hasn't even
touched her breakfast.
So dad said, I see!
So Chanda, tell mother
to have her breakfast.
I can't eat so much!
The other plate is mine, mom.
I thought if I eat,
you won't eat at all.
So I too didn't eat.
If I starved my whole life
will you do the same?
Yes! But mom, I'm famished!
- Is that so? Come!
You are very sweet, mom!
Now you eat, mom! - Okay.
Maya!
Chotu will wake up! - Boss, I won't
wake up. I'm in deep slumber.
He's talking in his sleep.
- Yes. I'm talking in my sleep, boss.
Leave! - C'mon!
What? What are you doing?
Leave my hand!
Otherwise I'll raise commotion!
- What commotion?
My honour is at stake!
Won't I raise a commotion?
Then shout! Whom will you call?
Chotu?
Why have you come up alone
so late in the night?
Should I bring grandpa along?
Fool!
Fool? Have you come at midnight
to tell me that I'm a fool?
Then what! Guys plead so much!
They implore so much! Only then
does the girl agree to meet!
Does a girl come all
alone at night?
Then why have you come?
I've been mad enough to
fall in love with you.
Had it been some other guy then...
- What would he do?
He would take advantage
of this opportunity.
It's a cold moonlit night.
We should hold each
others hands and romance.
Talk romantically now!
- Oh my God!
Look, I've already
crossed my line.
Now if we are caught, we'll
be thrashed black and blue.
We won't be thrashed any
less if we sit apart.
Sitting close won't help us escape
a good thrashing as well. Got it?
What should I do now?
Now you'll place your
head on my lap and rest.
No! Not on your lap.
- Look! Just do what I say!
Otherwise I'll scream
and tell every one,
..that you called me here and
you're trying to rape me.
No! - Now quietly lie down here!
This is my knee, not my lap!
Now turn your face!
What happened?
Maya, I'm telling you!
Go away otherwise...
Otherwise what?
- You'll catch cold!
You could catch cold if you stayed
out in the moonlit night for long!
Sit properly!
Tell me! - Kiss me!
What? - A kiss!
No, Maya! - Yes fool!
Look, if you don't kiss me,
I'll stay here the whole night.
Kiss me!
Where? - Kiss me here!
No. – Its fine. Do it here.
Will you leave if I kiss you?
First kiss me, I'll think about it!
- Then I won't kiss you!
Fine! Give me a kiss!
Look at your face!
Are you loving me or drinking poison!
Smile!
Is this a smile!
Do it with style!
Maya!
Now the boss will be thrashed!
Father! Get up! Look!
Maya is not in her bed!
Look down. Maybe she
fell down in her sleep.
Don't joke, father! I'm worried!
Don't worry. She's not a kid. I
mean she must be in the bathroom.
Go and find her! This
house is not a Taj Mahal!
Go! - How do I go? Mother
is standing down there.
Then go from here!
Climb down! - How? Shall I jump?
Jump! - Jump!?
I'll break my bones? - Grandpa is
going to break your bones anyway.
Father! She's not in the bathroom too!
God knows where she has gone!
She is not a child to get lost!
Search properly! She
must be here only. Go!
What are you doing?
Why are you looking
at me like this?
Aren't you ashamed! My
honour is at stake!
What are you doing? I'll die!
You are not even
telling me to stay.
Let mother come! Let
any storm arrive!
I can fight the whole world!
Just hold my hands!
Right now you are
holding my wraparound.
Has Maya gone up?
She must have gone to dry chillies.
- Are chillies dried at night?
You mean to say that guy from
Patiala That music director!
He's a young guy. Maya is a child.
Did that loafer entice her?
I'll thrash that ***! You go up!
I can't climb the
stairs in this old age!
Maya!
My wraparound! Give my wraparound!
- Don't shout!
Throw it up!
Where are you taking my wraparound?
Give it back!
Oh my God! Why did I see this?
Doctor! - Yes, sister.
I've called all the hospitals
and nursing homes.
Mr. Prem has not been
admitted anywhere. - I see!
Sister, do one thing. Call up all
the charitable homes and lodges.
He must be somewhere.
I'm very happy today, dear!
It's a full moon day today
and a Thursday too.
The priest says that today
is an auspicious day.
We'll replace your nuptial
thread with a necklace.
Till now you were a
guest in this house.
Today, you'll bond with
this family for a lifetime.
These are our
ancestral jewellery.
You might find it old-fashioned.
But wear it for
sometime for my sake.
Touch Anand's feet and
take his blessing.
No! I don't like this old
tradition of touching one's feet!
Anand! Look, don't leave.
Daughter-in-law, wear this
dress and the jewellery.
No! It's not necessary
for you to obey mother.
Prem Pratap from Patiala.
6/26, Old Colony, Patiala.
Sir! The photo has arrived!
Shall I hang it in the hall?
No! The frame is not right.
I'll have to change it.
Keep it aside for now. I'll
decide later. - Okay, sir.
Hello! 7468! Patiala!
Is Dr. Singh there?
Hello, Mr. Singh! This
is Anand from Mumbai!
Yes! Everything is fine! I
troubled you for an urgent work.
I want to find Mr. Prem Pratap!
Yes, I'll give you the address.
Send somebody to find him!
Book the ticket and send him
to Mumbai on the first flight.
No! He hasn't stolen my things.
Actually I have something
that belongs to him!
I want to return his belongings!
Please write it down!
Prem Pratap from Patiala!
6/26, Old Colony, Patiala.
I came to Mumbai 25 years ago.
I looked so fine at that time!
So many girls flirted with me.
But I too didn't budge! I
didn't look at anybody!
Otherwise would I
have had this garage,
..this truck and 6 cabs today?
But sir, you came here
to earn your livelihood.
My boss came here for love.
This love affair has been going
on since we arrived in Mumbai.
Snacks were sent in the morning,
..and the girl would
come upstairs at night.
He's giving her bangles.
They are singing songs.
Romantic! - Shut up, Chotu!
You brought the snacks! You
made me compose songs!
Now you're acting smart!
You are the root cause of all
the problems! Wait! Come here!
Stop fighting and
concentrate on your work!
What work do you do?
- He's a musician.
That's fine! But
what work do you do?
Isn't composing music
for movies, work?
Arrange for your
basic needs first.
You can pursue music after that.
Find a good job first.
Nurse!
Mangala! Laxmi!
Mangala!
Laxmi!
Where's Mangala?!
- What's the matter, mother?
Where has everybody gone?
Please call the nurse.
Nurse has taken a leave. Tell me.
What do you want? - No! I...
Tell me!
- The bedpan... I'll take it.
No, daughter-in-law! Let it be!
Thank you Maya. Thank
you very much!
Even the real daughter-in-law
of this house,
..would've hesitated to do this job.
But you...
Mr. Prem is a lucky man.
Boss, let's begin!
You look there. I'll look here.
Let's see who is
destined to find work.
Buy this! At a cheap price! Only 50
paisa! You won't get it tomorrow!
It's a steal! Have tea in this!
The tea will taste delicious!
You'll look like a hero if you use
this comb! At throw away price!
Mom!
What happened, Chanda?
How did you fall?
I climbed up to
switch on the geyser.
The bucket slipped and I fell down.
- Come!
Who told you to climb up? What
if you had hurt yourself?
Why didn't you call me?
- Dad wants me to do my own work.
Because you'll return to
your house in a week's time.
As long as I'm here, I'll
do your work. Understand?
Thank you, mom.
You're very sweet!
Good morning, boss! No need to
get dazed! This is our own shop!
It was difficult keeping
the goods on the street.
So I made a new arrangement.
Sit here.
Quickly get 2 cups of tea.
My boss has come!
I will just get it! - Sit boss!
Don't call me your boss!
I'm ashamed to think that you've
learnt this after being with me!
To steal and cheat!
You've started preaching again!
Look, boss. No man is a born thief.
This merciless world,
merciless situations,
..turn a boy like
me into a thief.
This is the norm of the world.
Commit sins and then
pray in the temple.
All your sins will be cleansed.
I'll slap you back
to your senses!
Fine, boss. Nobody
can reform you.
You have capability, but
only to face rejections.
You turned out to be so stooped!
My servant is coming. Don't
talk like this for sometime.
It will tarnish my image. Talk
to me respectfully for now.
Here! - Give it to boss.
Sir!
Boss!
Ganesh! - Yes sir!
Where's Chanda?
- She's in madam's room, sir!
Chanda!
Chanda! Get up, dear!
Dad is calling you.
Dear, come and sleep in your room.
- I'll sleep here with mom!
Don't trouble your mom! Get up!
Go to your room!
I'll be no problem to mom, dad!
Am I right, mom? You too
come and sleep with us.
Don't talk rubbish! Quickly
get up and come with me!
I won't come! - Chanda!
Didn't you hear what I said!?
Didn't you hear what I said!
- Shameless!
How dare you mimic me! Get up! Come
to your room! - No, I won't go!
I'll sleep with mom!
- Chanda, keep quiet!
Now come!
Dad, I'll sleep with mom!
- Listen!
Was it necessary to vent
out my anger on the child?
Yes!
Because she was insisting for
something which I couldn't give her.
If Chanda gets used
to a mother's love,
..then how will I give it
to her after you leave?
I can't marry again.
My time's bad! I'm being
forced to listen to you.
Boss, you've ruined your life
and now you are wailing.
If you couldn't take any responsibility
then you should've told me before.
I went to have lunch and here
you played the harmonium.
All the goods disappeared and
you didn't even realize it.
Amazing!
- Stolen goods are bound to be stolen!
What else will be the outcome?
You say that your entire
goods are stolen.
Look at this! Was this drum stolen?
No! What does this mean?
It means, no matter
how much I try,
.. I won't reach great heights
till you are with me.
Chotu, it means you share
a deep bond with music.
It's an unbreakable bond. That's
why your drum wasn't stolen.
Oh my God! - There's never a
loss in honest deals, Chotu!
Forget this shop
and come with me.
I'll take you to the
glamorous world of music.
Oh my God! What sin
have I committed?
We haven't committed
any sin, Chotu!
So someday we'll surely shake
up the world of music.
Even children will take Prem
Pratap from Patiala's name.
Mr. Prem.
Greetings! How do
you know my name?
Not just yours, I even
know Chotu's name...
I know Chotu's name, too. I
was looking for you people.
Did I steal your goods?
Actually, I'm a film producer.
I know you are the musician who had
refused to steal somebody's music.
I'm Anand.
I want you to compose
music for my movies.
Give me your address. I'll
send a car to pick you up.
We can give an address
only if we have a house.
For the moment, the
footpath is our address.
Fine! No problem!
I'll arrange for your accommodation.
Come with me.
I won't be able to come today.
Cancel all my appointments.
If there is any urgent
work, call me on 545281.
This is our first chance.
I'll play such tunes
for the producer,
..that he'll sign us as the music
director for all his movies.
Boss, don't worry. I'm with you.
So will you play something?
- What do you want to hear?
Anything. A love song?
Look how can I play anything?
I should know what the story is,
what the situation is. - Fine!
The situation is that a girl
and a boy love each other.
The girl's family forced her
to marry some other guy.
Wow! Your movie is a hit! What
a story! People will go crazy!
Shut up! Fool!
What's so great
about this story?
It's a common story. This
happens in all the movies.
This isn't the whole story.
This is just the beginning.
The heroine consumes poison on
the first night of her wedding.
You mean to say the heroine
dies in the first reel itself.
No. She was saved because
her husband is a doctor.
On asking the reason
for consuming poison,
..the heroine speaks the truth.
She was forced to get married and
that she loves somebody else.
Wow! The girl is so courageous!
Her husband promises the heroine
that he'll find her love anyhow.
He'll unite both of them again.
- Wow! Great!
That husband is not human.
He's God!
But this husband
too has a problem.
His mother is sick.
She's on her death bed.
So he requests the heroine,
..to play the charade of being the
daughter-in-law for 6-7 days.
On one hand, is the mother who
will live for 6-7 days only,
..on the other hand, the wife
who is eager to meet her lover.
In all this, what must
be the husband's plight?
Then what happened?
- The end has to be written.
I'll narrate it to you
as the story progresses.
You've left me in suspense. When
will your story get completed?
Very soon.
Till then, you
compose a love song.
For the beginning, when the
hero and the heroine meet.
Such a serious story,
such painful turns,
..and you're asking me
to compose a love song?
Fine!
"You don't..."
"You don't fall in love
deliberately, it just happens!"
"You don't give your
heart, it gets stolen!"
"You don't fall in love
deliberately, it just happens!"
"You don't give your
heart, it gets stolen!"
"You don't fall in love
deliberately, it just happens!"
"You don't give your
heart, it gets stolen!"
"There's no pressure on love,"
"You lose your sleep over it!"
"Listening to the heart,"
"in long twilights,"
"lovers don't sleep!"
"That's why it's said,"
"You don't fall in love
deliberately, it just happens!"
"You don't give your
heart, it gets stolen!"
"The bond of the heart is such,"
"don't ask about the
plight of my heart!"
"I'm in grave trouble,"
"I miss you!"
"Tears brim in my eyes!"
"That's why it's said,"
"You don't fall in love
deliberately, it just happens!"
"You don't give your
heart, it gets stolen!"
"In the season of
these flowers,"
"in the season of
"love pierces thorn, and
it hurts the heart!"
"We endure everything
with a smile!"
"That's why it's said,"
"You don't fall in love
deliberately, it just happens!"
"You don't give your
heart, it gets stolen!"
Nurse! - Yes, doctor.
Quickly arrange for the glucose.
Tell Saxena to come here quickly.
Arrange for the oxygen, too.
- Okay.
You're a doctor yourself. You know
what the patient's condition is.
The effect of the tranquilizer
given will last for sometime.
It's difficult to say what will be the
patient's state after she wakes up.
Anyway. Let's hope for the best.
If possible then get out
from this atmosphere.
Boss, the producer has come.
You've kept me in suspense. You
narrated half the story and left.
Here, I'm tensed thinking
what will happen next.
I shouldn't interfere
in your matter.
But I think till the time
the mother doesn't die,
..your story won't proceed.
After the mother dies, the
doctor will face the real test.
Anand speaking.
This is Ganesh speaking, sir.
Your mother is no more.
Just 5 minutes ago. Sir, we
are waiting for you only.
Hello! Doctor!
You didn't tell me. Did
the mother die? Tell me!
I think she should die!
What do you say?
She died. - What?
Yes. She died.
Wow! Now there will be
a twist in the story!
But don't add a song here. Everybody
adds songs on the mother.
But in this situation, I'll give
such a background music that,
..everybody will tear up.
I'll play it. Come on, Chotu!
Pick up the drum!
Look, this is a sad tune.
I'll thrash you if you laugh. Got it?
- Fine.
Not so fast. Play it slowly.
Boss! Boss!
The producer is crying.
This is the effect of our tune.
I've only played the harmonium.
Watch the effect when it's
played with 50 piece orchestra.
Each person in the theatre will cry.
Come on!
Prem Pratap from Patiala!
Music director!
Hello, Mr. Prem.
- Greetings, sir.
I was waiting for you since morning.
- Do one thing.
Take a cab and come to
my house immediately.
The address is Savitri villa.
10th Road, Juhu Parle Scheme.
I'll come immediately, sir.
But at least tell me. What have
you decided about the climax?
Mr. Prem, I'll decide the climax
after taking your opinion.
So please come here immediately.
Dad, what is a climax?
Separating two bodies
and uniting two souls.
Greetings! - Greetings!
I've come to meet Mr. Anand.
Prem Pratap from Patiala.
Music director.
Come, have a seat.
The producer is rich.
He's an influential man.
He'll surely complete the movie
by selling his house if needed.
Sit. You've reached
the right place.
Greetings, sir! - Greetings!
I was waiting for you.
Sir, you look tired. Are you fine?
- Yes. Just like that. Come.
I understand, sir. I
understand your dilemma.
When a man is in deep thought
and he can't decide anything,
..he feels distressed.
- Come. Sit down.
To tell you the truth. I'm too
thinking about the climax.
I can't even eat properly.
- Please sit.
Then you must have
reached some conclusion.
What should be the climax of
this story according to you?
Look, sir. There are only
two ends to this story.
One is that the heroine
forgets her lover and,
..spends her life happily
with her husband.
The happy ending.
The other end is that the
heroine forgets her,
..lover and her husband
and leaves this world.
Again she consumes poison.
The sad ending.
Mr. Prem, I think you're
a heartless man. - What?
You're forcing that girl to
spend her life with a man,
..she married
against her wishes.
This is injustice! This
happens in all the movies.
Secondly, why should she
consume poison again?
What is her fault?
But sir, there can't be a third
climax to this story. - Why not?
If that husband is a noble man, he
can unite the separated lovers.
No, sir! That's
absolutely wrong!
Even I thought of this.
But people won't accept this climax.
- Why?
Because sir, we have some
tradition, values and feelings.
According to that, once a
man marries a woman and,
..gives her the nuptial thread,
then she belongs to him.
That woman becomes his wife
for the rest of her life.
Once the 7 nuptial rounds of the
fire are taken with the oath,
..it can't be broken.
If 2 people married
according to the rituals,
..can't maintain the
relation for some reason,
..then the law gives them the
permission to seek divorce.
Foreigners resort to a divorce, sir!
We are Indians!
In our country, a
woman has to spend,
..her life only with her
husband once marriage.
So Mr. Prem, why doesn't this rule
apply on the men of our country?
Even after marriage, many
marry for the second time,
..or have extra-marital affairs.
Then how does your tradition and
value accept them in the society?
Why only women have to
obey the marriage rituals?
Why not men?
- Sir, you have confused me.
You have put me in a dilemma.
My intention was not to
put you in a dilemma,
..but to solve this problem.
Sit.
Killing that girl or
forcing her to live,
..with someone she doesn't
love is sinful! It's wrong.
The right thing to do is to unite
that girl with her lover again.
Am I right? - Okay.
Very good, sir!
Are you saying it for my sake or
do you really think so? - No, sir!
You've explained everything
so clearly that,
I think this is the
right thing to do.
It will be a new climax.
Novelty!
Very good, sir! It
will be revolutionary!
People won't even be able
to think of this climax!
Good that you agreed with me.
Come upstairs.
Upstairs?
You have given your consent. Now
let me fulfil my duty too. Come.
Sir, do you mean
advance payment?
Yes! Assume it's an advance.
Come.
Advance? Good! Very good, sir!
You have thought of a fine climax!
Very good!
Lovely story! Unexpected twists!
Your movie is a hit!
With Goddess Saraswati's grace,
..the music will complete
a silver jubilee.
Why silver jubilee?
Golden jubilee, sir!
Sir, it has really been
a pleasure meeting you!
What character! What a
theme for the story, sir!
Wonderful! Beautiful...
I'm sorry, Mr. Prem.
But if I had told
you this earlier,
..that Maya is the girl
who had consumed poison,
..on the first night
of the wedding,
..and that I am her husband,
..we wouldn't have been
able to talk clearly.
We would've never been able
to reach the right decision.
That's why I had to
play this drama.
Forgive me if I have hurt you.
Maya, I'm fulfilling my promise.
Though for my own
selfish reasons,
I made you stay in this house for 7
days. I'm sorry for hurting you.
The sad story that began
with this marriage,
..has now become the happy
story of two lovers' union.
I'm happy. My best
wishes are with you.
Goodbye! Good luck! - Sir! Sir!
This isn't right!
Your climax is not right! It's wrong!
- Why?
Just a while ago you
only had accepted it.
Yes! Everything is fair in movies.
But this is real life.
Such endings can't
happen in life, sir!
But Mr. Prem, stories,
novels, movies,
..all this should
portray real life.
I don't want to argue whether they
should or shouldn't portray life.
I accepted your climax because
I didn't want to lose my chance
of being a music director.
Otherwise I can never accept
such a derogatory thing.
Maya is your wife. She has
to spend her life with you.
But how do I accept your climax, Mr.
Prem?
Knowing that the girl who
has come in my house,
..as my wife loves
somebody else.
She loves you.
I can't torment myself
by making her my wife.
Life will become hell. For
me as well as for Maya.
There's only one solution to this
problem. Take Maya with you.
No, sir. This isn't possible.
If you will leave her here, she'll
surely consume poison again.
Will that be acceptable to you?
Can you let your beloved die?
What kind of a man are you?
What kind of a lover are you?
Fine, sir.
I'll take Maya with me.
But not this Maya,
..return the same Maya, I
had fallen in love with.
Mr. Prem, do you doubt me? - No,
sir! I am not such a stooped man!
I'll never doubt you!
I mean to say that Maya is wearing
the nuptial thread given by you.
If I touch her, I'll feel as
if I am committing a sin.
As if I have brought home
somebody else's wife.
If this nuptial thread is
removed, I'll get my Maya back.
Maya, give this nuptial thread back
to the doctor and come with me.
What happened, Maya?
A nuptial thread is nothing but
an ordinary yellow thread.
It's like a golden license.
Remove it and come with me.
Why are you thinking so much?
It's just a display.
Remove it! Remove this worthless
thing! What does it have?
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
'I accept this nuptial thread,'
'considering the sacred
fire as the witness,'
'considering God
as the witness,'
'the celestial bodies
'considering the saints and
sages as the witness,'
'I give this oath,'
'that I'll hold this nuptial
thread dearer than my life.'
'I'll uphold its
dignity all my life.'
Dad called and said its okay if
you don't want to meet grandma.
But have your breakfast and
do take your medicine.
That is most important.
If Chanda got used
to mother's love,
..then how will I give it
to her after you leave?
Today you're going to bond with
this family for a lifetime.
Maya is an Indian girl with
orthodox thinking, sir.
She's still in a dilemma
about the nuptial thread.
She doesn't know of this new
world and the new revolution.
You explained that to me
and I've understood too.
Sir, I think you should do it.
You remove the nuptial thread.
Do it!
You are a man. What
are you afraid of?
You have the right to
disobey this old tradition.
Pull out this nuptial
thread from Maya's neck.
So that I can take her with me.
What are you thinking, sir? These
orthodox rituals are of no use!
Break these bonds! Go ahead!
Yes, mother.
I'll do everything for
Maya's happiness.
I'll fulfil all her wishes.
I promise you.
No!
This is our story, sir.
The story of our country's
tradition and values.
I'm not an educated man.
But I do know that my lover
may become somebody's wife,
..but somebody's wife
can never be my lover.
The heart of an unmarried
woman is like a mirror.
It reflects the one
who stands before it.
But after marriage, that reflection
gets converted into an image, sir.
A husband's image. Your image.
This will never change.
This can be the only
climax to this story.
Nothing else. Never!
You might find my
thinking orthodox.
It is very old. But
sir, old is gold.
I'll take your leave now.
Goodbye, Mr. Anand.
Sorry, Mrs. and Mr.
Anand. Goodbye!