©
© P
© P@
© P@r
© P@rM
© P@rM!
© P@rM!N
© P@rM!Nd
© P@rM!Nde
© P@rM!NdeR
© P@rM!NdeR M
© P@rM!NdeR M@
© P@rM!NdeR M@n
© P@rM!NdeR M@nk
© P@rM!NdeR M@nkÖ
© P@rM!NdeR M@nkÖÖ
© P@rM!NdeR M@nkÖÖ ™
Mobile - +919815899536
EMail - parminder222536@hotmail.com
What have you got?
- Stuffed breads.
Pickle?
- No.
Why?
- I forgot.
You want me to dip it in grass and eat it?
If you want to.
Idiot.
- You.
Fool.
- You're a fool.
Eat it if you want to or dump it in the canal.
You're going to get whacked today.
You'll be walking around with a big red scars.
Sattu was searching for you.
He was angry.
Very angry. Red with anger.
He wants to send you to London to a boarding school.
As if mom will let him.
He wants to send me to London.
Idiotic Sattu.
Why are you staring at me?
Go, get some water.
Get it yourself.
Are you getting it or should I whack you?
What will you do?
- I'll bite you.
I'll scratch you.
I swear, Sattu.
I didn't smoke.
Why are you hitting me?
I'm your Father, not Sattu.
But grandma calls you Sattu.
- She's my mother.
But even my mother calls you Sattu.
Sattu.
Why are you hitting me?
Don't look at me.
Was your teacher lying when he told me you smoked?
Make up your mind about why you're hitting me..
..for smoking or for calling you Sattu?
Keep quiet.
He's going abroad, Kaushalya.
That's final.
He'll die without us.
He'll bring us shame if he stays here.
Unmannerly.
Calls his own dad by his name.
What do I do?
When I call you 'my own dad' Kaushalya glares at me.
Shut up.
Pack his bags, he's leaving tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Be grateful that I've given mother and son one night..
..to do all your emotional 'give and takes.'
Sattu's gone mad.
- Shut up.
Sattu.
- Insane.
I'm growing bigger day-by-day.
How big?
Big enough for you.
Mummy says, get marry or else, someone will take me away.
You don't agree.
I was about to say that I won't allow
anyone to touch me before Dev.
Paro, I am going insane.
I'm losing it too.
Come back soon.
You're losing it?
I've lost it.
Yes, I've lost it too.
You just said you were losing it.
Yes, I was, now I have lost it totally.
Paro.
Do you..
Do you touch yourself?
Tell me.
Paro.
Send me your photograph.
You have it.
A naked one.
Have you completely lost it?
If you ever tell me again to do such a..
..crazy thing I'll kill you.
You know how difficult it was?
I had to go 17th Sector, Chandigarh to send them.
My heart was pounding like an engine.
As if they all knew what's in my bag.
And that photo shop guy was staring at me..
..like he has never seen them before.
Like his wife applies pimple-removers.
Rogue.
Tell me how to use the scanner.
I'll do it myself.
Madam, why do you take the trouble when I'm here?
I'll bring the photo so alive that
people would want to touch it..
Don't you get it, fatso?
Paro, I'm coming back.
"Come away now.."
"You cast your spell and went away."
"Left me wanting more each day."
"The rhythm's taking over."
"A longing's bloomed inside my heart."
"Like a bird chirrups in zest."
"The rhythm's taking over."
"I swing, I sigh, with a heady high."
"Give me your hand now.
Give me your hand now."
"I think I'll fly and touch the sky.."
Yes, he's come. Here.
Throw this in the dustbin.
Son, it's your brother Dwij's 'Haldi' (pre-marriage ritual) today.
"The rhythm's taking over."
"A longing's bloomed inside my heart."
"Like a bird chirps in zest."
"The rhythm's taking over."
"Oh my beloved..."
"I'm coloured in your hues.."
"..bathed in desire, I'm your muse.."
"Our joys stacked up will make a hill.."
"..on it we'll sit, you and I.."
"..and rejoice."
"Madness will your love evoke."
"You'll wrap around me like a cloak."
I'll surrender myself towards you.
"With you it all feels so right."
"With you it all feels so right.
With you it all feels so right."
"You cast your spell and went away."
"Left me wanting more each day."
"The rhythm's taking over."
"A longing's bloomed inside my heart."
"Like a bird chirps in zest."
"The rhythm's taking over."
"I swing, I sigh with a heady high."
"Give me your hand now."
"I think I'll fly and touch the sky."
"Come with me now."
"My anklet shivers to the beat."
"My bindi (adornment) shimmers in its forehead seat."
"We're all drowning in the lake of love."
"My anklet shivers to the beat."
"My bindi shimmers in its forehead seat."
"We're all drowning in the lake of love."
"My anklet shivers to the beat."
"My bindi shimmers in its forehead seat."
"We're all drowning in the lake of love."
"My love."
"My love.."
What happened?
Dev, how are you?
Manager uncle.
Top form.
Haven't seen you since ages.
Son, what's that on your shirt?
I don't know.
It looks like Turmeric (haldi).
It smells like turmeric.
It is `turmeric.'
- Yes.
Paro.
What are you searching for on the floor?
Well.. my earrings.
What's on your ears then?
- On my ears?
Well.. earrings.
Paro, come out.
- Yes.
What's on your hands?
It looks like turmeric.
It smells like turmeric.
It is turmeric.
Paro, go out.
Welcome, sir.
I'm Sunil.
Come along.
Please come.
Sir, the sugarcane juice crystallises and comes here.
And this is where we check if it has turned into sugar.
Hello, son.
First time?
No.
You can't put your hands in.
- Why not?
My dress is too tight.
- Shall I rip it?
So that I go around without clothes?
Let go of my hands.
- I won't.
I am a Jatni (caste).
- Even I am a Jat.
I love you.
Paro.
- Yes. I'm coming.
What are you doing there?
- Don't come here.
I'm coming.
Your father will surely die one day.
What were you doing there?
There's a long queue outside the toilet.
What?
So that the dogs don't come and eat the food.
Paro. Paro.
Open the door..
There's a long queue outside the toilet.
Hey, you.
- Paro.
Do something.
What do I do?
- Find a solution.
So desperate?
Yes.
That's good.
Paro..
Hello.
Hi.
I'm Rasika.
I'm Dev.
I know that you've studied in London.
Even I'm going there.
Oxford.
Are you?
- Yes. - Very impressive.
I'm from Delhi.
- I'm from here.
Aunt Kaushalya wants us to get something from the farm.
Is it?
- Yes. Shall we?
Come on.
I was so bored there.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Yes.
Have you guys done it?
Done what?
S. E. X.
Listen.
- What?
I'll be back.
- Okay.
Tell me.
I need the keys to your room.
Why?
- My Dev is back.
So, why should I give you my room keys?
Give it to me.
I love you.
If you want to do it with Dev,
why don't you do it in his room?
Why don't you get it?
Heavy crowd is here.
It's a wedding.
Have I ever said no to you?
I love you.
Look at your status.
Loves me.
Be grateful that..
Get lost.
Aunt, you've given the servants a free hand here.
Look at him.
- What happened?
What happened?
Look..
Listen, Paro is the most sensuous girl in this village.
You're right.
- She can break the bed.
She can bake you to death.
She can murder you.
Just murder you.
Hello, sir.
- Sir..
Sorry.
It's okay.
Where were you?
- I had gone for an outing.
Alone?
- Yes.
Brother.
- Here she is.
Papa. When did you come?
- Just now.
How are you?
- I'm fine.
Are you all right?
- Absolutely.
I swear on my dead mother.
She's insatiable.
I was so worn out and sore..
couldn't get up for two days.
I was hurting.
By God, sir.
No one can beat Paro.
You're lying.
Sir, may my dead mother die again if I'm lying.
She wanted to do it just a while back.
I refused.
I said, "No."
Why are you glaring at me like that, sir?
All you have to do is just ask and she'll come running to you.
But I'm very surprised, sir.
You haven't done it with her yet.
I'm shocked.
Hey.
What did you do?
What happened?
Please go out.
- But what happened?
Leave me alone, please.
What happened?
- Nothing.
London has ruined his head.
At least find out what happened.
Let's go out.
I'll tell you.
What are you doing?
You asked me to do something.
So, here I am.
Put your hands up.
You're so hairy.
You're such an expert.
How many have you done it with?
Get your hands off.
I said take your hands off.
Where are you going?
- Let me go.
Tell me what happened.
I said let me go.
You..
Characterless.
Have you come, Paro?
Where were you?
Aunt had asked for it.
She was falling short of mattresses.
Come, dear.
Your dad wants to talk to you.
Let's go inside.
Yes, tell me.
Sit.
- No. Tell me.
See! Have you met the Delhi businessman Bhuvan Singh..
..who's here for the wedding?
Bhuvan Singh who?
That girl Rasika's brother.
He likes you.
He wants to marry you.
So what if he likes me?
They're very well-off.
I will marry only Dev.
And will wait for him till he marries me.
Have you gone mad?
Why should Satpal marry his son to you?
Why shouldn't he?
I've made lassi (buttermilk) for him all my life.
He loves me so much.
That's okay.
We're not in his league.
And Dev's studied in London, you've studied here.
I'm the college-topper,
Dev barely scraped through his exams.
At least, try talking to him.
I don't want to embarrass myself.
You can't embarrass yourself,
but you can embarrass your daughter.
Meet Bhuvan once.
Bring him close to me and I'll chop him into pieces.
Paro. Dear..
Paro. Paro.
Listen to me, dear.
Where are you going?
Move aside. Let go.
Paro.
- Father is losing his head.
He needs treatment.
He's right.
Why should Satpal marry his son to you?
Even Dev has grown up.
Who knows where his heart is.
I know where it is.
He gave it to me when we were kids.
The bucket is overflowing, my dear.
- I know. I know!
Paro. Paro, where are going?
What kind of a chef is he?
Look what he has done to the flatbreads.
He has burnt them.
Do your own job.
Don't interfere in his.
Is everything all right?
- Yes.
Finish this work fast.
We've to sing and dance too. Keep it here.
Paro, come here.
Take this cup of tea to your uncle.
I don't know what is wrong with this girl..
It's very tasty.
- Please, take it.
- No, enough.
Paro, come join us.
Come.
Eat something.
Later.
- Where are you off to?
She's very strange.
You are Bhuvan's sister, right?
Please don't tell my brother anything.
Get out.
What were you doing with her?
The same that you do with Sunil.
With Sunil?
What did I do with Sunil?
Tell me.
Is that why you broke his head?
You just go from here.
- I didn't do anything with that lousy man.
I know everything.
Sunil told you?
When did he tell you all that?
Exactly before I broke the bottle on him.
Leave or else I'll do the same to you.
You hypocrite.
You broke the bottle on him after
taking Rasika out in the car?
What you do is right.
And if I do..
Will you please leave me alone?
I'm leaving.
I came to tell you that
I have received a marriage proposal.
Good.
Go ruin someone else's life.
Anyway, you're not good enough to get married to me.
A manager's daughter will always remain so.
Look at yourself.
Unkempt hair..
..lousy clothes.
Wants to marry me..
Illiterate.
"My dear.."
"I don't think I want.."
"..this love thing any more."
"My dear.."
"I don't think I want this love thing any more."
"I don't think I want.."
"..this love thing any more."
"My dear.."
Brother.
- Yes?
Your heartthrob.
You idiot.
What did I do with you, you idiot?
Tell me, what did I do with you?
- What are you doing?
Get out of my way.
I'll dump you in the well.
Have you gone mad?
- You idiot. Come here!
What did you say to him?
What did I do?
What are you..
- You idiot.
Stop. You idiot.
Where are you running to?
Stop.
- Run. She has gone mad.
Paro, what are you doing?
- Idiot.
Wait.
Sunil, run.
- Stop.
I won't spare you.
Why are you running away?
Stop.
Stop, you idiot.
She has gone crazy.
Paro..
Paro, what are you doing?
Have you gone mad?
Hey, Paro.
Give the matchbox.
- You'll tear my shirt.
Let go.
Give the matchbox.
- That's the only spare shirt I have..
Paro, don't burn it.
Please.
Paro, don't..
- He burnt my dreams.
I will burn down his house.
- Paro..
Forgive Sunil.
"I could embrace you, give you my life always."
"Shot at my heart by your double barrelled gaze."
"Shot at my heart.."
"I could embrace you, give you my life always."
"Shot at my heart by your double barrelled gaze."
"My heart's like a child's though you treat it not so mild."
"I don't know what to do about it now."
"I should've watched that thing,
side stepped your beauty sting."
"You must be the breeze that
blew from the Chenaab (river)."
"You must be the glory, the beauty of Punjab."
"Let's do it."
"You must be the breeze that blew from the Chenaab."
"You must be the glory, the beauty of Punjab."
"You came into my life and left me a sweet ruin."
"Your sweet smile will now be my undoing."
"When you sway that hip or pout that precious lip."
"You unleash another storm, sink another ship."
"I should've watched that thing
side stepped your beauty sting."
"The way you look, the way you move, leaves me in a whirl."
"I don't know what to do about you, dizzle-dazzle girl."
"I don't know what to do
about you, dizzle-dazzle girl."
"You're the heady brew from the fields that gets us high."
"You've got every boy in town dying to catch your eye."
"You're just like Juliet, beauty so renowned."
Bhuvan's getting married?
"I should've watched that thing,
side stepped your beauty sting."
Congratulations.
No, no. You won't lose your job.
I am sorry.
I had gone mad.
I am ready to fall at Paro's feet.
You won't do any such thing.
She will be getting married soon.
You got it?
I know she is getting married, but I might lose my job.
How much have you drunk?
You're ranting continuously about your job.
"Shot at my heart by your double barrelled gaze."
"By your double barrelled gaze."
Paro's looking very beautiful.
Yes.
She's getting married.
Did she tell you?
- Yes.
I don't know which fairy you're waiting for.
I always had this dream..
Of bringing her from that house to this, as a bride..
..so she would always remain my daughter.
But London has ruined your taste.
You prefer vodka over whisky.
Fish over chicken..
Waif-like stick figures over a real curvy woman.
You are a hopeless case.
"I'm all tangled up in this spinning wheel of love."
"Crumpled with the pain, from under and above."
"You spun that wheel, I tottered, had a fall."
"Now I think I'm finished, I think I've lost my all."
"I don't think I want this love thing anymore."
"God knows what all this spinning around was for."
"I don't think.."
"Your eyes intoxicate like opium smoked."
"You glow and smolder like embers stoked."
"What we shared is pieces, what answers can I give.."
"There's nothing more to say, no reason left to live."
Hello.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
- Uncle, where's Dev?
- Dev?
No idea!
Paro, what are you doing here?
Come, let's dance.
Paro.. Paro..
"My heart croons.."
Careful.
"One, two, three, four, six."
"Could I melt this heart into a tune?"
"Get my heartbeat to croon."
"Am I smoking hot or what?
"In my chest is a fire."
"My desire's on a pyre."
"Darling, I don't know what to say."
"I saw dreams of heaven."
"But they all went to hell."
"It's all gone up in smoke.
To my world I bid farewell."
"God help whoever gets bitten by this bug."
"The devil takes your beauty, the devil takes your love."
"The devil takes your emotional torture from above."
"Go away, oh, love."
"Oh, love."
"The devil takes your beauty, the devil takes your love."
"The devil takes your emotional torture from above."
"This heart is torn by a tragedy, tragedy."
"A paradise lies plundered.
Its roses dried and dying."
"This heart is torn by a tragedy, tragedy."
"A paradise lies plundered.
Its roses dried and dying."
"Say why did you ditch me?"
"Now take my life too, kill me."
"Go away, love."
"The devil takes your beauty, the devil takes your love."
"The devil takes your emotional torture from above."
"Go away, oh, love."
"Oh, love.."
"The devil takes your beauty, the devil takes your love."
"The devil takes your emotional torture from above."
What happened?
What happened to him?
- Dev.
Leni.
Wake up.
Baby, wake up.
Good morning.
"1 , 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 1 0, 1 1 ..
12, 1 3.."
Leni!
- "1 , 2, 3.."
"The seasons set on my lashes."
"I drink the moment, each drop splashes."
"A sun-drop on my forehead falls."
"To myself I make whispered calls."
"This is what my life's about."
Leni, you're the best.
Hey, stop.
Why are you filming me?
Just for my personal use.
However is your fate and heart...
- Your the best, Leni.
"Green branches in a blossomed daze."
"I've splashed colour on all my dreams."
"My heart shines a thousand gleams."
- Leni, you're the best.
"Nature smiles.."
"To myself I make whispered calls."
"This is what my life's about."
Leni, you're the best.
Characterless girl.
Helen..
Helen, it will be fine.
Taran Yadav, the 28-year-old who made the..
..objectionable MMS involving a student of..
..Mathur International School, New Delhi has been arrested.
Taran claims the student is his lover.
The girl caught in the storm is a minor studying in..
..class 12 of the same school.
Go inside.
- Papa..
I said go back in.
Helen.
- Leni.
Come inside.
Mom, I'm just going for a walk.
Look, I'm sorry for what I did.
Okay?
I'm not going to go and do it with everybody.
How dare you.
Mom.
- No more Delhi.
Helen, no.
Helen.. No..
I saw what she did.
She knew what she was doing.
How could you watch it, Dad?
Did you get off on it, you sick man.
Leni.
- Just shut up.
I didn't sleep with him.
- Shut up.
- I didn't sleep with anyone.
I'm still a virgin, you hypocrite.
Shut up. I told you, shut up.
Do you want to hit me?
- Please..
Come on, hit me.
You coward.
How could he watch it?
- I know.
"Every beat of my heart.."
"I follow the dream I have in my heart."
"Life plays a cruel game of hide and seek."
"Sometimes near and sometimes far."
"It makes us laugh."
"It comes and goes, comes and goes, does life."
Aunt, don't worry.
I can understand.
Even I've seen it.
But I still want
to marry her.
She's only 1 7.
- I'll wait.
My mother..
She got married when she was just 15.
I swear.
Hello.
Natha Singh.
What are you all doing?
You haven't sent the potatoes yet.
These weird books in English that
you keep reading are spoiling you.
Why don't you mind your own business, Grandma?
How dare you answer back!
First, you killed my son, now you want to kill us all?
What happened?
Look at her staring at me, like she will kill me too.
I tell you.
Let's just bury her in the field..
..only way to save whatever respect we've got left.
Look down or I'll gouge your eyes out.. witch..
..and parade you naked in the village blind.
Understood?
Mom.
I miss you.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I don't want to be here.
I'll go anywhere you want me to.
I'll do anything.
Mom, please.
I know you're there.
Please pick up the phone.
Mom, I love you.
Mom, please pick up the phone.
I know you're there.
Please.. please.
Please pick up the phone.
How much?
"Every beat of my heart."
"I follow the dream I have in my heart.."
"Life plays a cruel game of hide and seek."
"With a trinket, with an anklet in my leg.."
"..I'll dance with zest."
"Here swings.."
"Here swings my heart."
"Life plays a cruel game of hide and seek."
"It disappears and then gives us a peek."
"It makes us laugh."
"It comes and goes, comes and goes, does life."
Hi. Hi, Tara.
It's Leni here.
Yes, I'm back in Delhi.
Listen, I've nowhere to go..
Yes.. sure, I understand.
Hello.
Yes, Leni here..
"Makes us dance, does life."
"Makes us cry, does life."
"Makes us cry, does life.."
"Makes us dance, does life."
"Life is like a flower that blossoms."
"Some are fortunate to be happy and some to be sad."
"Life plays a cruel game of hide and seek."
Hey.. Stop. Stop.
Listen. Hi.
I know that you're hungry.
Come, come.
We'll eat something together, okay?
Why?
Are you throwing a party?
- Don't worry.
Come.
Come with me.
We have women from all over the world.
Easy money.
And you're beautiful.
Come.
This way.
The biggest room here.
It's been vacant for the last three months.
This room is our way to tell customers that..
..she is numero uno (the best).
Exclusively for connoisseurs.
And we're in no hurry.
You're still a minor.
You don't have to do what you don't like..
..and till you don't wish to.
Want some?
It evaporates bad memories
Stay here. Complete your school.
Take your exams.
Join a college, study what you want to.
A number of foreigner girls study here.
And also work with us.
And here, everybody has fixed time for studies and work.
How wonderful.
Hey. Congratulations.
See.. see..
12th board, first division.
"Lead me dancing to my lover's drums."
"My anklets.."
Look ahead.
"It hit me."
Did you think of a name?
Yes, Chandramukhi.
"My anklets tinkle, throw tantrums."
"Lead me dancing to my lover's drums."
"Anklets say.."
Leni...
"Anklets.."
Excuse me.
© P@rM!NdeR M@nkÖÖ ™
"Anklets.."
"My God!"
"Its stubborn pleas ring a restless beat."
"Clung in hope to my helpless feet."
- Chanda!
"Lost in a daze, with a rhythm crazed,
it calls out to my love."
Come down.
Come.
I brought this..
For me?
- Yes, for you.
"It calls out to my love.."
You're naked..
Why are you naked..
"A restless beat."
..you were thinking of me and?
"Anklets say.."
Happy birthday!
Oh, I'm sorry, baby.
It's my birthday.
Will you be my cake?
Oh, yes.
I will eat you up.
Wow, that's a nice present.
Oh, my God!
Chanda!
Carefully.
Welcome home.
Paro..
"A scream rose inside."
"Loud, thick, strong it cried."
"It sizzled, coursed through every vein."
"Yesterday stood so tall."
"Today had a fall."
"Now to meet my own gaze is a pain."
"All things I lay eyes on turn to soot."
"My heart is ashes, I crash and burn."
"This moment hides a scalded truth."
"Leave me now, leave me, leave me now far from my sight."
"Leave me now leave me, leave me now.."
"Leave me now leave me, leave me now far from my sight."
"My heart is ashes."
"I crash and burn."
I need some, Charlie.
- Okay.
Excuse me.
Here you go.
Thanks.
How are you?
- Fine.
The keys?
- Keys.
He's addicted to foreigners.
Not easy to give up, is it?
I know.
Rich spoilt kid.
Understood?
Why are you taking your clothes off?
No?
Okay.
Who are they?
Would you please put that back?
Yes, sir.
- Coke?
Thums up (cold drink).
With vodka.
What?
- With vodka.
Give me a light.
Thank you.
- Welcome.
Vodka with Thums up.
Your bill, sir.
Can I get one more?
- Sorry sir. Closing time.
Excuse me.
- Yes.
Where are you going from here?
- Ghantaghar.
Will you get some there?
You'll get nothing.
If you want to drink, you'll have to drive to the border.
What are you doing, brother?
Don't go there.
Why are you going there?
No..
- Let go my hand.
Fine.
Brother, they'll get you drunk.
They'll strip you.
And leave you naked in the garbage.
Till the municipality truck picks you up.
Thirsty?
- Yes.
- Come.
Come with me.
What's your name?
- Dev.
Chunni.
- Chunni?
What are you doing in Delhi?
- Nothing.
Any illness or ailment?
Why?
- Just asking.
There's no tax for asking questions, right?
What's the name of the place?
Good watering holes don't have names.
How is it going?
- Come, sir.
Come in.
Come here.
You've come after a long time, sir.
- Where's my table?
Your table's ready, Sir.
Over there.
Sit.
Relax.
Your order please.
- Ask him.
- Thums up?
Coke.
- With Vodka.
Yes, sir.
- Do you do relay?
- Sometimes.
Shall we?
I'll drop you home if you lose.
Note...
Whisky, Vodka, Black Rum and White Rum.
- And Gin.
Okay, sir.
- No. No.
Gin causes impotency.
No Gin.
"That's how we do it."
O Stranger...
"Feel a luscious fever slowly rise,
I'm your beautiful stranger."
O Stranger...
"Lord save me from this surprise,
I'm your beautiful stranger."
"Time did me in and fled."
"God knows what lies ahead."
"That's how we do it."
"My mind echoes like an empty well."
"Runs this way.. that, headless, pell-mell."
O Stranger...
"A thousand dreams inside these eyes,
I'm your beautiful stranger."
"Okay.."
"Your hair hangs sentinel over eyes of stone."
"Beautiful stranger.."
"Feel a luscious fever slowly rise,
I'm your beautiful stranger."
O Stranger...
"Lord save me from this surprise,
I'm your beautiful stranger."
"That's how we do it."
Welcome home.
Beautiful stranger.."
"That's how we do it."
Paro.
So, how was it last night?
This is Delhi, my friend.
Here you enjoy a girl..
..relish a girl, but never keep one.
You have to pay dearly for it.
It can cost you your life.
The watch.. it's nice.
Sattu, I want a car.
Please tell the manager.
Hey. Pause. Pause.
Hello.
- I'm in Delhi.
Let's meet.
Where can we meet?
Where do I meet you?
It's him.
- Your brother's back from his honeymoon?
Yes, long back.
Should I pick you up from your place?
Give me the address. See you.
"A luscious fever slowly rises."
"This desire hides no surprises."
"Your name's dug deep on Delhi's throne."
"Your hair hangs sentinel over eyes of stone."
"Beautiful stranger.."
"Feel a luscious fever slowly rise."
"I'm your beautiful stranger."
O Stranger...
"Lord save me from this surprise."
"I'm your beautiful stranger."
"That's how we do it."
Where are you?
You could've told me.
I could have got the car..
You could've told me, I'd have brought the car.
Where are we going?
To my hotel.
What will we do there?
Can't we just go somewhere where we can sit and talk?
Do you even care about me?
So, all that you want to do is sleep with me.
- Don't you?
You know what?
I really regret everything that we shared.
And I think that you're the biggest jerk ever.
Sick.
"Leave me now leave me, leave me now, far from my sight."
"The splinters of my fractured pleas."
"Stab into my memories."
"And blood flows out where tears should."
"My eyes are now deceit, just like your devil love."
"The devil takes your emotional torture from above."
Yes, sir.
Tell me.
Chunni, I need a girl.
Where did you take me that night?
Leave your credit card here.
It's Saturday today.
Come.
I've reserved a suite for you.
Booked in advance.
Come with me.
Sit.
I'll be back.
Relax.
Baby.
She's already busy with somebody.
Do you want the regular ones or someone exclusive?
Keep patience.
My God, no.
Yes.
Please come.
Come.
- I'll be there in 15 minutes.
Yes.
Hello, yes.
Of course, it's me speaking, baby.
How are you?
Wow.
Sit. Why are you standing there?
Are you ready for a wild night?
Yes, you are soon going to be with me.
Yes, I will do everything..
In Tamil?
Okay. I'll speak in Tamil.
I'll put my hand in your shirt.
Is it enough or you want more?
Go little down.
What're you saying?
It seems you're very fast.
We will do it slowly.
That's how you like it, right?
In French?
I'll be waiting outside.
You take your time.
Enjoy yourself.
Baby, was that good for you?
Okay, baby.
Bye.
Hello.
He took 11 minutes.
Yes.
Hi.
Last time you passed out before we could..
Yes.
I'm Chanda.
I'm Dev.
Can I get a drink?
- Why?
I'll bathe in it.
- Shall I bathe you?
Vodka.. if you have it.
The mini-bar charges are extra.
Why are you so angry?
I can calm you down in a couple of minutes.
I'll rip you apart.
- That too..
Let's start?
No.
Why not?
Because I don't like your face.
Am I that ugly?
- Uglier.
Then where's the pretty one?
Do you want some?
Why are you dressed up like a school girl?
All-American Girls.
Have you seen the series?
No.
Would you like to watch it?
Erotic.
Want to watch it?
Have seen a lot of them in the UK.
Is it? Were you in the UK?
London.
But you don't talk like that.
How old are you?
Old enough to go to bed with you, darling.
I'm sure you're an animal in bed.
Will you shut that lousy accent?
Your bird must be really chuffed.
Oh, Dev.
Yes, Dev.
Don't stop.
Oh, Wow.
My Dev..
Oh.
You're hot.
Superman.
Don't tell anyone I did that..
I don't want a queue outside my suite.
My God.
Looks like you got your money's worth?
What did you do, Chanda?
Not much, but I was about to..
Shut up.
Move.
What happened?
What happened, Chanda?
Tell me.
- What happened? Chanda..
He went inside..
What happened?
- Chunni.
- Just a moment.
Don't bring him back or I'll fall in love.
Chunni.
- I think I'm already falling for him.
What?
Chunni.
- Coming. Coming.
Why do they let drunkards enter the bus in the first place?
Sir, ticket.
You are so young.
You booze, get into fights.
Don't your parents object?
Ticket.
If I had a son like you, I would
have thrashed him black my blue.
I would have knocked some sense into him.
What are you staring at?
Haven't you ever seen a woman before?
- Here.
Madam, ticket.
- He just ate it.
What?
I got it.
Go to the showroom and select the colour you like.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
When you have time, do come and meet us, son.
Let me talk to him.
I'm keeping the phone down.
He hung up.
Why didn't you tell him you're sick?
On top of that, you bought him a new car.
It's okay.
He is young.
Let him be..
You're needlessly spoiling him.
You spoilt him when he was a kid.
Let me do it now.
What's wrong with him?
Hello.
I want to speak to Paro.
Dev.
It's 11 at night.
This is important.
She's sleeping, Dev.
- Wake her up.
Dev, I need to speak to
you too.. about Rasika.
Should I speak to you or your dad?
I'll call later.
"These eyes crave.."
"These eyes crave..
horizons unseen."
"These eyes crave.."
"These eyes crave.. from both, a stream passes."
"For paths long lost..
these eyes crave."
"These eyes crave.."
"Lost my way, I've lost my way.."
Hello.
Dev.
Yes.
- Yes.
What do you want?
I want to meet you.
Are you in Delhi?
- Yes.
Where are you?
Yes?
Open the door.
What's that?
You were drinking?
This place is such a dump.
When did you last take a shower?
Paro, I love you.
You're stinking.
Go take a shower.
Then we'll talk.
I made a mistake.
Go take a shower first. Go.
What a filthy towel.
I'll ask for a fresh one.
Don't you have housekeeping?
Ma'am, he never leaves his keys at the reception.
Or else he just says 'later'.
Madam, bed-sheet.
- Take these.
- Yes, madam.
And bring a carton.
And take all the other bottles.
- Yes, yes.
What's this?
- It's cream.
Yes, that's fine.
Wait. Stay here.
The washing powder is green.
Only this one item is blue.
Anything else?
- Nothing else.
Take this.
The clothes haven't been washed for long.
How can you be so dirty?
Paro.
Yes?
I love you, Paro.
Rasika told me everything.
She's lying.
- I know everything.
I'm happy, I got married.
Or I would've had to wait for you endlessly.
Are you happy?
- Yes.
Mr. Bhuvan is a gentleman.
Mr. Bhuvan?
Had I married you, I would have called you Mr. Dev.
Let them soak for a while.
So..
I guess you make love to him.
What do you want?
- I told you that I love you.
I want to love you.
What do you mean by 'want to love'?
Make love to me.
What now?
Do what you want to, but I'm not taking my clothes off.
Paro..
When will you meet me, next time?
Next time, you want to talk, call me in the day.
Are you really happy?
He has two children.
Lovely children.
And they love me a lot.
You don't love me.
You can't love anyone except yourself.
You should marry either this mirror or the one in the toilet.
Don't feed me that psychological nonsense, okay?
Never take so much of drugs.
Some things look too good, the rest too bad.
I'm leaving. Get over me..
..and go back home, get a life.
Why don't you go home to your old man?
He might be old, but he's quite good in bed.
Then what are you doing here?
Go ride your superman.
I don't need to ride him.
You are humiliating me?
No, I am showing you what you really are.
Get out.
"It's raining now."
"It's raining now, a fevered shower."
"It's raining now, little jabs that scar."
"It's raining now.."
"The song's a wail, its raining now."
"Its raining now."
"Lost my way, I've lost my way.."
"The devil takes your beauty, the devil takes your love."
"The devil takes your emotional torture from above."
"Devil takes your love."
What's wrong?
Will you say something?
What are you?
Florence Nightingale tonight?
Your Romeo is so trashed.
He threw his wallet at me.
Don't let him go.
Keep him with you.
Keep him with you for 1 0-1 5 days..
..while I max out his wallet.
I witnessed the climax to his love story.
A lot of violence.
Give me his wallet.
- Why?
Hope you are not falling for him.
You'll get your money, give me his wallet.
Have you lost it?
Shut up, broker.
His wallet.
You need to talk.
When you feel pain, you should talk.
What do you know about pain?
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
There's some coffee in the coffee-machine.
What's your story?
- Story?
I mean..
how did you become..
you know..
How I became a strumpet?
No.. - Call girl? Escort?
Flesh trader.
I've a client.
The NGO type.
He has trouble calling me a 'strumpet'.
So, he calls me C.S.W.
Commercial Sex Worker.
It's out of fashion to say 'strumpet.'
She's right.
- How's she right?
You don't love her.
- I do love her.
If you really, really loved her, you would've been with her.
First, you made a mistake and
when you realised your mistake..
..you should've apologised.
But how can you do that?
Big male ego.
You didn't ask her even once not to get married.
Why should I shut up?
Stop feeling sorry for yourself.
You can't love anyone.
Just accept it.
It's men's toilet.
Do you mind getting out?
Ever since I accepted what I am, I have been okay.
You're okay?
You think I'm not?
You like to believe that I'm hiding a lot of pain.
Are you not?
- Not anymore.
Liar. - Okay.
What's okay?
Whatever you say.
You're the boss.
Why are you all 'happy and glee'?
What should I do then?
Whatever, just don't irritate me.
Idiot.
I heard that.
- Thank you.
Why are you justifying her?
- Because she's right.
What's so right about what she said?
She's happy. She has moved on.
I like that word, you know..
'moved on.'
It's so easy.
People do move on.
I've done that.
Yes. To coke.
That's your solution to everything.
Is it?
Goodnight.
Stop it.
Why are you filming me?
Go away.
Did you get off on it, you sick man.
Just shut up.
- Let's kill her and burry her.
Mom, I know you're there.
Please pick up the phone.
Come on, hit me. You coward.
They would stare at me as if..
..I was some kind of a serial killer.
No one spoke to me.
How is it my fault if the whole world saw me doing it?
And how did they know it was me?
They didn't show the MMS on TV..
..nor was my photograph published anywhere.
They all downloaded it.
They enjoyed it.
Half the country got off on that clip..
Then they turned around and called me the 'strumpet.'
I want to get smashed tonight.
Let's go out.
I've to pick up my car too.
"My heart desires.."
"To drown in dreams."
"Fill up my arms with sky, clouds, streams."
"A rhythm holds my breath aloft."
"A song that's whispered so soft."
"Everything's a sweet haze."
"I seem to own the world these days.
I seem to own it."
Come on.
"The bee buzzes between flowers."
"Humming songs of summer showers."
"Sometimes that way, sometimes this.."
"The world's a swirl of coloured bliss."
"Drenched is this open sky."
"Bathed in its colours will I.."
"..hum a tune of happiness."
"The breeze blows in little laughs."
"Hugs the seasons, kisses each draft."
Instead of holding me like a father would..
..and telling me, 'It's okay, my baby."
"Forget the past.
Forget whatever happened."
He shot himself.
Look at me.
- What?
Come here.
It's okay, my baby.
Forget the past.
Forget whatever happened.
When I feel sad, I come here.
Steaming momos (Chinese food), sir.
- Thank you.
How much?
- Rs.60 only.
Take it. No.
Keep the change.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hot..
Paro is very beautiful?
- Yes.
I love her to death.
Still?
Forever.
Chanda, I love you too.
You're such a jerk.
"Anklets.."
Sleep more if you want to.
Where are you going?
- To college.
Bye.
- Bye.
Will I see you when I get back?
- Yes.
Do you know something?
- What?
You're not so bad.
I love you.
I love you, Chanda.
Chanda.
I love you.
"Its stubborn pleas ring a restless beat."
"My anklets plead for a sight of him."
Her name is Paro.
- I know.
He's crazy about her.
He doesn't care for you.
He just sleeps with you.
Why are you doing this to my business?
"Haunting me by night and day.."
"Lead me dancing to my lover's drums."
Hello. - Sir.
When a woman discovers the witch in her..
..then she is not worth bringing home..
to your heart..
What do you mean?
- Remember I told you?
This is Delhi.
Here you can enjoy a girl, relish a girl..
..but never keep one.
You end up paying very dearly.
Chanda.
She's out.
She'll be back after noon.
It is afternoon.
Who are you?
- I spoke to you.
You asked me for a photo.
By what time will she be back?
Do you get protection here?
By the way, my medical certificate is also quite clear.
Chanda.
"It's all burnt down to ash."
"To dust this life's been dashed."
"Where have those little smiles gone?"
"These sighs are charred, this breath is smoke."
"Charred.. charred.."
"Can't revive a hope that's choked.."
"The night's a coiled snake, its fangs drawn.."
Please come, sir. Welcome.
Welcome.
- Sir.
Cheers.
This is for your girl.
And what is this for?
Sir, you left your room open?
Your box..
"Where have those little smiles gone?"
© P@rM!NdeR M@nkÖÖ ™
'Seven people were mercilessly mowed down..'
'..by a BMW reportedly been driven by Devendra Singh..'
Drunk driving, road rage as well as a rich boy with toys..
Do you think this is going to be an other incident?
It could possibly be that the father was very rich..
Last night, a black BMW maimed
seven people on Tilak Bridge.
Everyone died on the spot.
The BMW was located in the Paharganj area of Delhi.
The BMW is registered to famous businessman of..
..Punjab Mr. Satpal Singh.
What do you remember?
Sattu.
Read your statement and sign it.
We'll discuss everything else on the way.
Now, listen to what I'm about to say.
You need to understand something very clearly.
Can we make a stop on the way?
I have some work.
What work?
I want to tell my friend that I am fine.
He doesn't carry a phone.
Make it quick.
Chunni?
Who's this?
Chunni.
- What are you doing here?
Go inside.
What are you doing here?
Don't come here again.
I don't want trouble.
Just need a gram.
I'll pay you later.
Wait here.
Here.
Thank you, pal.
- Don't come back again.
I don't want the money.
Your job is done.
Now, go.
This is your medical report.
The court can cancel your bail any time..
..but because of your father's death
there is a lot of sympathy for you.
The press feels sorry for you..
..doesn't mean you take advantage of it.
You're allowed to leave the city only for four days..
..and be back after his funeral.
Thereafter you cannot leave Delhi.
And yes, you will have to visit the
police station every morning..
..to sign the register.
I've stood as your guarantor in the court.
Do you understand me?
Listen. Dev.
Mother. Dev.
Why did you do it?
Why?
You were such a nice kid.
Why are you doing it to yourself?
You have everything.
I hope he rots in jail.
Here.
Money for the lawyer.
And for me?
You can take him please..
'You don't love me.
You can't love anybody except yourself.'
'Go ruin someone else's life.'
'Anyway, you're not worthy enough to get married to me.'
Are you humiliating me?
'I'm showing you what you really are.'
'You know what?
You are not so bad.
I love you.'
What's your name, sir?
- My name is Satpal Singh, sir.
Do you drink, Satpal Singh sir?
Like a fish.
Then let's do one thing.
Why don't we skip Delhi and go on a tour?
Let's drink in solitude.
I'll pay for everything.
But why?
- Just like that.
"This world's so round."
"What's up, comes down."
Sir, try this out.
What's this?
- Have it.
Pure village opium..
"You're a fortune now, next week you're crap."
"Free this minute, the next you're trapped."
"Come watch the show.."
"Yes, yes, yes.."
"This world's so round."
"What's up, comes down."
"Loopy, loopy, sideways skewed."
"Sugary, spicy, both ways messed."
"The real is unreal, a real fake.."
"Yes, yes, yes.."
"It comes and goes, dip by dip."
"Hide and seek, finger on lip."
"Boils, bubbles, hid behind.."
"Yes, yes, yes.."
"This world's so round."
"What's up, comes down."
Stop.. stop..
What happened, sir?
Have some water.
You'll feel better.
Keep this money, pal.
Take me back to Delhi.
"It tempts, pleases.."
"Then cheats and teases.
Smacks our faces in the mud."
"Sings a lullaby."
"Then screams out high."
"Grinds our faces in the mud."
"No bump, no jolt along the way."
"Without warning it all gives way."
"Yes, yes.."
You are dropping me to Delhi, aren't you?
- "Every corner,
every street."
"This way, that way, hands and feet."
"God, help us.."
"Yes, yes, yes.."
"You're a fortune now, next week you're crap."
"Free this minute, the next you're trapped."
"Come watch the show.."
"Yes, yes, yes.."
- Keep this money.
Sir, are you all right?
- Yes, I'm fine
I'm sorry.
Hello.
Is Paro very beautiful?
Yes.
I love her to death.
Still?
- Forever.
Here's your bill.
You too take it.
What happened?
- Give the money.
It's time to close the bar.
Can I get another drink?
Not any more.
Please, leave.
- Okay.
200.. 300..
Keep this.
What happened?
Looking for your wallet?
No.
- Someone must've picked your pocket.
Check his bag.
- Yes.
There's nothing.
- Give it to me.
- See.
It's expensive.
- Doesn't look like one.
Show me the jacket.
Check it.
- Yes.
Nothing in this too.
You can get your money by selling them.
No, it still won't cover.
Throw him out.
Come on, get up.
Come on. Get up.
Out. Get lost.
Don't come here again.
Come on, get inside.
Hey.
Do you have anything to drink?
What's your name?
Okay, then.. I'll call you Dwij.
Yours or mine?
Yes, hotel reception.
Hello.
- Dev?
Is Chanda there?
- She has left.
Open it. Take him out.
'You are lucky.'
'There's still time, straighten up or..'
'..you'll end up like that Tilak bridge guy.'
"This faint drumbeat in my heart awakes.."
"A tremor inside.."
"The fog-veil parts, the sun fires up."
"Throbs with life a tremor inside.."
"As far as the eye can see."
"An illusion of the truth maybe.."
You must have got some photograph of hers?
Where did you meet her?
Must be some place she arrived from
when you found her at the station?
There must be some place she goes to.
Thank you, sir. Rs.20.
Hey.
I'll go for a smoke.
Hello, sir.
Sir, do you remember me?
Steaming momos.
Steaming momos?
"It makes you want to live again."
"A tremor inside.."
"It enlivens death, the tremor inside.."
What are you looking at?
She'll come.
Meanwhile, serve these momos..
..in the rickshaw.
"A tremor inside.."
"Throbs with life a tremor inside.."
"Feel these moments."
"Touch these moments."
"These moments.."
Chanda..
I don't love Paro.
I never saw her for what she was.
You were right.
I am a jerk.
When did you leave that place?
The same day you left me.
Why?
- You bought this for me, didn't you?
"Do something timeless this time."
- Let's go.
I told the Police Inspector that we'll be there by 12.
"Fill yourself with the light sublime."
"Light up a torch for your heart."
"As far as the eye can see."
"An illusion of the truth maybe..
Yes, it's true.
It's true."
"My heart croons.."
"One, two, three, four, six."
"Could I melt this heart into a tune?"
"Get my heartbeat to croon."
"Am I smoking hot or what?
"In my chest is a fire."
"My desire's on a pyre."
"Darling, I don't know what to say."
"I saw dreams of heaven."
"But they all went to hell."
"It's all gone up in smoke.
To my world I bid farewell."
"God help whoever gets bitten by this bug."
"The devil takes your beauty, the devil takes your love."
"The devil takes your emotional torture from above."
"Go away, oh, love."
"The devil takes your beauty, the devil takes your love."
"The devil takes your emotional torture from above."
"This heart is torn by a tragedy, tragedy."
"A paradise lies plundered.
Its roses dried and dying."
"This heart is torn by a tragedy, tragedy."
"A paradise lies plundered.
Its roses dried and dying."
"Say why did you ditch me?"
"Now, take my life too, kill me."
"Go away, love."
"The devil takes your beauty, the devil takes your love."
"The devil takes your emotional torture from above."
© P@rM!NdeR M@nkÖÖ ™
Mobile - +919815899536
EMail - parminder222536@hotmail.com