Keep it.
Is the cocaine in the case?
No TJ.
I'm here to give you
my birthday card.
Where is my money?
Right here.
Here's your full and final payment.
Now...
Put your hands up.
No...
Put them up.
Relax sweetheart!
I said 'No' because TJ...
...forgot to say 'Please'.
Please... put your hands up.
You think you're very smart.
But not this time.
This time I keep the case for free.
And because I know that you will
want to avenge this day...
...you'll have to die.
TJ!
Do you know that there are
36 points on the human body...
...if struck right...
...could prove fatal.
Is that so?
Its just that I'm in a
dilemma now.
About what?
About who, between
the two of you...
...I should I kill first!
I always liked you Don.
Me too, TJ.
I've also always...
...liked me.
Don't shoot don't shoot...
If you kill me...
...my men won't let you live long.
You will get caught.
No, TJ.
Not only is it difficult to
catch Don...
It's Impossible!
I want to thank you...
...for your help on behalf
of our government.
We know the gang
we're looking for...
...has made Kuala Lumpur its base.
Our Chief Investigating Officer Mr. De Silva
will give you all the details.
Sir...
Thank you Verma.
Gentlemen I'll come to the point.
Firstly, let me tell you all we know
about this gang.
Verma...
When the Soviet Union split up in 1990,
a number of small nations were born.
Selling arms to terrorists and
fundamentalist groups...
...became a lucrative business for
a few people in these countries.
One of the new empires built with this money
was headed by a man named Boris.
Verma...
When these empires crumbled under
international pressure...
...Boris disappeared.
And when he wasn't found
after years of searching...
...he was presumed dead.
But Boris was not dead.
He had gone to India.
He invested the money he made
selling arms into drugs.
He bought drugs in bulk from
Afghanistan, Pakistan and India...
...and started distributing
them in Europe.
His two invaluable lieutenants
in this business...
...Vardhaan and Singhania.
We don't have a single
photograph of Vardhaan.
Nor do we know who or
where he is.
Reason?
This is Singhania.
It is rumoured that Boris wanted to
hand over the business to Vardhaan...
...but Singhania murdered Boris.
Did he kill Vardhaan too?
Perhaps he did...
Because there's been no trace
of Vardhaan since then.
And this is Don.
...who manages Singhania's
business here.
Given the information we have,
it is clear...
The most dangerous and cunning
criminal among them all...
...is this man.
Good shot.
Yeah, Narang.
Hello Anita.
Mr. Singhania had called.
He wanted to know how the
police knows so much...
...about our operation.
It's hard to say.
All our men are very loyal.
Is that so?
What madness is this, Don?!
Narang... this is a good shot.
Did you see Kumar's feet?
Terrible shoes!
I didn't like his shoes!
Ramesh...
This loyal man of yours was
actually a police informer.
The next time before you
recruit anyone...
...please get him to meet me once.
Or check his shoes, at least.
Kumar.
I don't understand.
How did they find out
he was our informer!
Good question!
You...
Vishal Malik. I'm with the Interpol.
I see.
- I am...
- DCP De Silva. I know.
And now I'd like to know how a fact that
only top Indian officers knew...
...came to Don's knowledge?
I don't know.
By the way...
Who told you?
Excuse us.
I'm sorry, Mr. De Silva.
I wasn't pointing a finger at you.
Then who?
Inspector Verma.
See... he is young.
Recently inducted into the force.
Newly married.
Its quite possible...
Mr. Malik. I wonder if you're
actually drinking coffee?
Just checking.
I trust Inspector Verma.
Anything else?
Yes. I too am involved in this
investigation from now.
Hi Kamini.
That's great news.
Where are the two of you?
That was quick.
I am so happy, Kamini.
If my brother wants a better life today,
it's all because of you.
Thank you.
Anyways, our hero is in a
pretty bad mood.
Why?
Hi Roma.
I know a lot about them.
If Don even suspects that
I am leaving him...
...he'll kill me.
Ramesh...
By the time Don finds out
we'll be long gone.
Anyway, I am gonna see you
at the airport tonight, okay?
I know that after Mom
and Dad died...
...whatever you did was, to an extent,
for my happiness.
But I wasn't happy...
...nor did I feel that what you
were doing was right.
...until today.
I am proud of you.
Yes, Narang.
Poor... Ramesh.
Ramesh...
Very sad...
Very sad.
I always thought of you as reliable.
But unfortunately, you didn't
think the same of me.
All you had to do was tell me
you wanted out...
...and I'd have arranged it
all for you.
Don! I...
Don, I...
Yes... what?
I made a mistake.
Why are you saying that?
Your love for that girl...
What's her name?
Kamini.
Kamini!
Your love for Kamini isn't a mistake?
Anyway...
I am here to say goodbye.
Ramesh...
Have a nice life.
Yeah.
One dirty fish can make the
entire pond dirty.
But if that pond...
...is to become mine.
It becomes necessary to kill it.
Ramesh...
People don't leave Don.
They leave this world.
Kamini, I need to ask you a
few questions.
What do you want to know?
Ramesh was always with Don.
Is that true?
Yes.
Do you remember any particular place
that Ramesh used to go often?
Yes.
Tell me.
This information can help me
to catch Don.
It's not my desire to
get him caught, Officer.
Kamini, don't do anything that...
...could put your life at risk.
I don't care whether
I live or die now.
But the police department cares.
I'm trying to quit...
It kills you.
This camera... this pistol...
Why do you need
all this security?
Because a "Do Not Disturb" sign
doesn't work in this hotel.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking that...
...I don't like two types of girls.
One, who take too long
to succumb to me.
The second, who succumb
too quickly.
And I succumbed too quickly.
What did you say your name was?
Sonia.
Sonia, the time between us meeting
and you being in this hotel room...
...is just half an hour.
That's because, when I
saw you I felt...
...it was you I've been
searching for.
Romantic talk bores me, Sonia!
Shall I get it?
No...
It's mine.
Why don't you go inside...
...and get into something more...
...comfortable.
Sure!
Yes... Anita.
Kamini...
Thank God you're okay.
Where are you?
There isn't anything else to wear.
I know.
Who were you talking to?
I'm sorry!
Oh that!
To my Aunt.
She worries needlessly,
if I'm slightly late.
I can't tell her the truth,
can I...
...about where I am...
...and who I'm with.
Bring your Aunt along next time.
She's not your type, Don.
Oh... yes.
Why the hurry?
Why else would I want
to be here?
This heart of mine,
is crazy for my love.
His love is like a flame...
...burning in my heart.
I am willing to let this
flame engulf me.
You can't escape from
it's intensity either.
This heart of mine,
is crazy for my love,
is crazy for my love.
My heart always gets
what it craves for.
But my love can take my life
if my lover requests it.
My heart always gets
what it craves for.
But my love can take my life
if my lover requests it.
I gift you my life
in return for yours.
This heart of mine,
is crazy for my love.
His love is like a flame...
...burning in my heart.
Every moment that passes,
A storm rages in my heart.
As the goal I desire...
...is coming closer.
Every moment that passes,
A storm rages in my heart.
As the goal I desire...
...is coming closer.
You will never forget the day...
...our hearts collided.
This heart of mine,
is crazy for my love.
His love is like a flame...
...burning in my heart.
I am willing to let this
flame engulf me.
You can't escape from
it's intensity either.
This heart of mine,
is crazy for my love.
Your Aunt is outside, along with
a bunch of uncles!
May I know the reason
for this family reunion?
Ramesh was my fiance.
He had never mentioned you.
I can understand why.
It's been a pleasure
meeting you.
The pistol is empty.
You're right!
Let's go. The police are
waiting for you.
The police of many countries are
waiting for me. But...
Sonia...
Not only is it difficult to
catch Don...
It's Impossible!
Really...
You know what!
You know this pistol is empty.
I know the pistol is empty but...
The police don't know
the pistol is empty.
And wait for my call,
is that understood.
Sir...
Verma...
Hold it right there.
Surprise... surprise...
Officers, please. Put your
guns down. Or else...
It would be wise to
surrender, Don!
I don't think so.
It'd be wiser for you
to move back.
I'm asking for the last time.
Or I'll be forced to...
Stop.
Okay...
Down...
Good.
Come nice and easy
everyone down...
...and move back. A little more.
I just want to get out of here.
If you help me, this girl...
...will be grateful to you
all her life.
Thank you.
Good night... Gentlemen.
Listen to me... Don.
First, call the lift.
For the lady.
Go on.
Quickly.
Don, I'm unarmed.
I can't stop you even if I want to.
Let the girl go.
Of course I will. Once
I get out of here.
Trust me.
No...
Damn it...
Verma...
What's going on!
Who are you?
Questions later.
I have to get out of here first.
Put the pistol down.
You have no idea who I am?
Mr. Narang, Police...
Move...
Stop that car.
Put your hands up.
And step out of the car.
Out... of the car!
Wait, Vikram!
Let's go.
Go.
Who is this girl?
Roma.
She can be useful to us.
Or is she useful?
If you had seen her shoot
two cops a while ago...
...you wouldn't be asking that.
Really...
Yes, Vikram...
I'll be there right away.
Come, Roma.
Go ahead Narang.
I'm in no danger from this girl.
So, the police is after you.
Why?
I'm charged with murder.
But as usual, the truth is
somewhat different, right!
Wrong. The charge is true.
What was his name?
Rajiv.
He was my sister's husband.
Your sister must have
felt terrible.
My sister is dead.
He killed her.
So you killed him. Good!
What do you want from me?
Nothing.
Narang Saheb said...
Oh, Narang...
Come closer.
Come on.
You know, what I think...
I think...
I think Narang wants to start
a new sort of 'trade' which...
Very good.
I like wild cats a lot.
Wild... cats...
What happened?
What did you think?
She tried to kill me.
Relax... Narang.
You will work with us
from today.
Thank you Don.
Jairaj called from India.
He wants more cocaine.
I know.
Did you speak to Jairaj?
Yes...
I didn't say anything
to him. but...
...you are asking for more money
than Mr. Singhania had said.
This deal will bring us
profits in millions.
Don't you like such a huge sum?
It's not that but it's not your job
to make this decision...
...it's Mr. Singhania's!
Singhania makes the decision.
I do the work.
So what do you do?
I don't talk like a child.
Such arrogance isn't good.
Don't forget, this business
was set up by him.
Then tell him to come here
and manage it.
What's this?
Your wedding DVD!
This disc has information of all
our business and contacts.
The next time Mr. Singhania is here,
you can give it to him!
Don, I'm not saying your
intentions are wrong.
All I'm saying is...
...you're moving very fast.
For what I want to achieve...
...this speed is essential!
But turning your friends into
enemies for this quest...
...would be a big mistake.
The biggest mistake, Don's
enemy can make...
...is to make an
enemy of Don!
You have forgotten
what happened yesterday.
If I ever find out that
your memory has returned...
Then remember this too...
The bullets will be real
next time.
Yes... Verma.
I just got information that
Don is going to India.
When?
Day after tomorrow.
For a deal with someone
named Jairaj.
We'll leave tonight.
And find out where
we can find Jairaj.
Deepak, come here.
It's not nice seeing you
empty-handed, Jairaj.
Where's the money?
In the car.
Hand over the case to me.
Nobody says please anymore.
As you like...
Here you go!
Sir, he's driving very fast.
Sir, he's very close but
he's moving very fast.
Sir, we can't see him any more.
Get out of the way, damn it!
Sir...
Come on...
Enough. You've run
quite a lot.
You!
Still angry about the
girl's death, Officer!
Shut up.
If you want to shoot...
...go ahead.
...but don't even think
about arresting me.
All right.
Have it your way.
Any luck... Verma?
No Sir.
This place is so huge that Don
could be hiding anywhere.
Sure, but for how long?
All the highways and stations here
must be under strict surveillance.
Have our men posted in
the hospitals nearby.
He won't be able to get out of here
even if he wants to.
Is that understood?
Right Sir.
No one knows where Don is
after the police encounter.
Not even the police.
I'm afraid that Don...
Don what?
I think he is dead.
Or, do you hope he is dead?
You know Mac...
I feel that he wanted something
to happen to Don!
- Oh! calm down Anita.
- No, I will not calm down.
What was your problem with him?
Was it that Don had become more
important to Singhania than you?
Mac...
Take her away from here.
I'll go myself.
But remember...
If what you're saying
turns out true.
I'll hold you responsible.
- Good morning Sir...
- Good morning Feroz.
Feroz!
Yes... Sir.
Come here.
Perhaps you remember.
It was about a year ago...
A man had barged into my office
along with a small boy.
The boy's parents had
disappeared and...
...he found him on the street.
I had asked you to
file the report.
Yes Sir.
Bring me that file.
Vijay...
Every moment, every day...
...I long for you.
O Lord!
You must reveal your glory,
once again.
You must return next year,
You must reveal your glory,
once again.
You must return next year,
I will wait for you
with longing eyes.
Heed me, heed my plea.
Come back again.
Hear your devotee's plea.
Only when I look upon you...
...will my heart be at peace.
Lord O mine...
Dear Lord O mine!
Be it happy times
or days of sorrow...
Our hearts chant just one name.
Because of you,
life is comfortable.
You dwell in our whole being.
Every second...
...I think of you.
I am your fan.
I chant your name in prayer.
Heed me, heed my plea.
Come back again.
Hear your devotee's plea.
Only when I look upon you...
...will my heart be at peace.
Lord O mine...
Dear Lord O mine!
You must reveal your glory,
once again.
You must return next year,
One, two, three, four!
Hail Lord Ganesha's glory!
Five, Six, Seven, Eight!
Lord Ganesha is with us!
Lord O mine, Ganpati!
May the next year
bring you soon!
Is it fresh?
Here you go, Deepu.
Done counting?
Yes, uncle.
How much is it? Grand total?
3000 Rupees including the
last three days.
Yuck! What are you doing?
Sorry very much.
What is the world coming to'?
My voice has gone hoarse singing
for three days and what do we get?
3000 Rupees!
- Don't worry, Vijay Uncle.
- How can I not!
We'll make a lot of money over
the 9 days of Navratri festival.
Wow, Deepu...
We'll have to make money...
I worry constantly about enrolling
you into a good school.
Just want you to
pass high school!
But what can I do?
There's no money left after
rent and stuff, is there?
Hey, don't feel sad.
Imagine what your Daddy
would say if he met me?
"Why thank you! You've got my son
onto the street!" Isn't that right?
You don't know my Papa.
He'd never ever say that.
Really! Then what will he say?
Vijay...
How does your he know my name!?
Vijay!
Oh! I don't want Ice cream
Please go!
I'm not selling Ice cream!
DCP Saheb.
I consider myself pretty smart.
Actually I am.
But when you are keeping things
even from your own department...
...why are you telling me?
I mean... this Don Sir?
What's he got to do with me?
Look at this first.
You'll understand everything.
Okay.
This is ME!
You're joking, aren't you?
No.
No! You're... not joking!
So then?
In that case I'm feeling...
...that you want me to
take Don's place...?
Yes.
Don't mind please.
Okay.
You just told me...
...Don Sir killed one
of your informers.
To say yes to this job
after hearing all this...
...you get what I'm saying?
DCP Saheb.
Look at Don Sir! He uses his
gun without thinking twice...
...and me?
Forget a gun!
I can't even use a bicycle!
Vijay, I agree this job
is dangerous.
You don't say?
But if we plan
each move carefully...
...it can be easily done.
Sure... sure...
Sir, I'm not afraid of jumping
into this well, but...
...you tell me...
If something happens to me?
Where will Deepu go?
I understand Vijay.
You must understand.
The people I want to catch
with your help...
...find it easiest to get kids,
like Deepu, hooked onto drugs.
God forbid, if tomorrow...
...he gets addicted to this poison...
...how will you forgive yourself?
Look Vijay. If you agree...
I'll take full responsibility for
this boy's education.
It will give Deepu the choice
to be whatever he wants...
...a doctor, an engineer...
or a police officer like me.
All this is possible
if you want it.
Okay, DCP Saheb.
But tell me something...
If Don Sir's gang find me out
and you find me in a coffin...
Deepu's name won't be cut from
the school register, will it?
Deepu education will be
looked after.
I promise.
Ok... ok...
One more question...
The fact I am Vijay...
...not Don Sir.
You alone will know that, right?
May God give you a long life
but what if you pop it...
I mean...
Don't worry.
Nothing will happen to me.
Stop... Papa.
Where's Mummy?
Making breakfast.
And she sent you as her
alarm clock, did she?
Well, where's the button to
switch this alarm off?
No...
Thank you Sir.
So... what's the problem?
Just a moment, Sir...
Sir, is this the password
you entered?
That's the one.
F09AK74.
If you remember, while installing
the program I had told you...
...the password recorded in this folder
will be shown backwards for safety reasons.
So your actual password is...
...47KA90F.
Oh God! Yes... I'm sorry.
Will that be all, Sir?
Stop! right here.
Is anybody there?!
Hello Jasjit.
I hope you are comfortable.
Who is this?
The man who can rescue you.
But you will have to
do me a small favor!
This is a strange way of asking
someone for a favor!
I like you, Jasjit.
Tell me something...
Isn't it true that Joshi's computer alone,
can unlock his safe?
I don't know.
Oh really!
That means you were lying to Joshi...
...or are you lying to ME!
Look...
Think what you want.
But, just get me out of here.
Why?
Is it very suffocating?
If you want, we can send your
wife Geeta to be with you.
Take it easy Jasjit. Relax!
All you need to do is one job.
There are diamonds worth
10 million dollars in Joshi's safe.
Get them and I'll release her.
I want to talk to Geeta.
Of course.
Jasjit...
Geeta...
I am so sorry... Geeta.
This is all my fault.
Forgive me.
I love you.
I love you too.
That's very sweet but
I've got diabetes.
Now lets talk business.
The diamond company
Joshi works for...
...is on the 25th floor
of Belcourt Towers.
The security on the entire floor is the kind
required to safeguard diamonds worth 10 million.
We can get you to the roof
via the service lift.
Rest... is up to you.
Hold it.
Right there!
Take the bag off your shoulder
and put it down.
You must be wondering how
the police got here.
I'll tell you.
Mrs. Wadia lives in the
building across the road.
She and her husband
quarrel pretty often...
...and the poor lady comes out
to her balcony to calm down.
Guess what she saw
from her balcony tonight?
Inspector De Silva, please listen
to me very carefully.
I'm being forced to do this.
Some people have
kidnapped my wife.
You think I am a fool...?
What's your name?
Jasjit.
You're under arrest.
Shinde...
Jasjit... Stop.
Inspector...
They will kill my wife!
I must go. Do you understand?
I'm telling the truth!
May be...
But I am not authorized
to sympathize with you.
Take him away.
Any idea where Deepu is?
De Silva...
Your days are numbered!
Wow! Isn't this something?!
He's handsome!
You know, sir... seeing a picture is one thing.
To be face to face like this...
...Don Sir is alive, isn't he?
Yes.
The doctors have kept him in
a sedated state.
I personally believe that a person
like Don has no right to live.
But I need him now.
Vijay, I want you to study
him properly...
...understand him...
Learn his habits,
his mannerisms, everything!
I will learn everything.
What's the big deal?!
Let him wake up at least!
As soon as your work is done,
I'll hand him over to the police.
I get it.
First...
All the marks and scars that
were on Don's body...
...need to be made on you.
Sure.
On me...!!
Yes.
The doctors here can
do it painlessly.
How can it be painless?!
Hi... Ashok.
He's all yours.
Vijay, this is Dr. Ashok Khilwani.
He will operate on you.
Everything ready as plan?
Yes, just a few
preliminary tests and...
...we are ready to get started.
I'll check everything.
Thanks Ashok.
What's the matter?
I've never heard that a
bullet mark on a shoulder
or a scar on the head
can be made painlessly.
- Don't be afraid.
- How can I not be!!
I was about to tell you...
I got Deepu admitted to
Malaysia's International School.
Inter... Int...
With that name, it must be good.
- It's one of the best.
- Best.
Now you stop worrying about Deepu
and concentrate on your work.
Okay... okay...
Look, I'll tell you all I know
about Don.
Besides that, I've thought of
another plan.
When Don, that means you...
...go back to your companions,
you'll be ill and wounded.
You will have lost your memory.
The more you learn about
Don's life...
...the closer I'll get to
regaining my memory.
Thank you.
You think exactly like the
comic book hero, Chacha Chaudhary!
You Know Chacha?
Brain working faster
than the computer.
I'll tell you a
great story. Listen...
One day, Chacha Chaudhary took
his dog Rocket out for stroll...
You want it?
- Don never ate paan (betel leaf).
- Never ate paan!!
That wasn't very
nice of him, was it!
Well, I guess that
I must quit too.
Fine.
Come on Vijay.
Is this a binocular?
Neha...
Yes Doctor...
Start monitoring the blood
pressure of the patient.
- Why?
- Yes Sir.
Anand...
Patch me through the face map.
Doctor... sir...
...it won't be too painful, will it?
No, it...
How long, before he comes?
Well... Just another 48 hours, Mr. De Silva
and then he is all yours.
Good job Ashok.
Doctor, please come
immediately to room no. 2.
It's an emergency.
My God!
What happened Ashok?
Don is admitted in that room.
What happened?
Heart seizure, doctor.
Have you given the patient
anything to stabilize him?
Yes Doctor... 2 ml of adrenaline.
Get me a cardiac injection, Quick.
- What's the blood pressure?
- 210 by 120 doctor.
I said hurry up.
No...
God damn it...
Ashok...
You and your team know
nothing about this incident.
This operation never happened.
Is that understood?
OK.
The success of my plan is linked to
this secret remaining a secret.
Ashok...
It's only a matter of a few days.
Hello...
Yes...
Where have you seen him?
- Where did you see him?
- Over there.
The doctors are saying that
he has lost his memory.
He doesn't remember anything.
Still, we must get him back
at any cost.
You're right... but how?
The passport they found in his
car was Malaysian...
...and they must send Don back.
Don't worry, Mr. Singhania.
It will be done.
Go back!
Welcome back, Don.
That's right.
Your name is Don.
I am Narang.
She is Roma.
All of us here, work with you...
and you work for Mr. Singhania.
You remember Mr. Singhania
at least?
I don't believe it!
In spite of all the security,
they took Don away!
Don's testimony could have exposed
the entire crime ring.
But what can he tell us when he
doesn't remember anything?
I don't think he's of any use
to them now either.
Who is them?
Mr. Malik, whoever did this either
works for Singhania or for his enemy.
Like who?
Like...
...Vardhaan.
Vardhaan...
Where is Vardhaan?!!
Have you seen him?
Do you know where he's hiding?
Do we even have a single
picture of him?
No.
Please...
And by the way Mr. De Silva.
Memory isn't something that
once lost, can't be found.
It's just a matter of time.
Is this...
...mine?
Yes...
For me, Don isn't Don...
...without this.
How do I look?
You look very dangerous.
Mr. Mallik...
It's been 3 weeks since
Don's escape.
Why can't the police catch him?
You tell us where he is and
we'll go catch him!
Please... Mr. Malik...
Look, until we get the right information,
or a witness comes forward...
...we must follow police procedure.
What's in it?
Our contacts, bank account numbers
and passwords are all recorded in this.
You had made it yourself
and put it in the safe.
Yes.
Yes, Vijay. Tell me.
De Silva Saheb...
I know enough about Don...
...my memory can return now.
Good.
We must do this with
utmost care.
I agree.
If you can't lose your
memory without reason...
...then it shouldn't come back
without reason either.
I've got a solution for that.
Tomorrow, make some excuse...
...and come to the place I've fixed.
Who are you waiting for?
Maybe... you.
Oh that...
You have done a lot for me...
I won't forget that.
There's a lot more left to do.
That there is.
Don...!
It was like this the
other day too.
I was in my car...
...and the police
were chasing me.
They were shooting at me...
And then I...
I remember everything.
Who I am!
Who all of you are!
I remember each and everything!
Mac...
Remembering your friend's
names is one thing...
...in our business, it's important to
remember our enemy's name.
Which enemy are you
talking of, Narang?
Vardhaan or that officer De Silva?
Maybe TJ is the one you
were thinking about...
...or the man who betrayed
us all... Ramesh?
I really enjoyed killing them all.
- This calls for a celebration.
- Oh yes, it does.
I am... back.
The people in this world...
...have clutched their hearts again!
I have returned...
...bringing back with me...
...a lot of excitement!
Look who's here.
Back to rule your world.
Who's got you mesmerized?
For whom do you wait
with open arms?
Who is this charming man?
Recognize me.
I am Don.
I bid my life...
...and gamble with death.
I have no regret...
...nor do I care...
...who I make my enemy.
No enemy of mine,
will live too long.
I am very dangerous.
I am very dangerous...
...and forever cunning.
Who is back to win
the world over?
Recognize me.
I am Don.
Their eyes inviting...
...many women have
wanted me for themselves.
That are glancing into mine...
...have mesmerized me.
These eyes...
...tell me...
...that they are hiding
an intoxicating secret.
I am getting addicted to them...
...and my heart is falling
under it's spell.
Who is here that has
fallen under this spell?
Recognize me.
I am Don.
Yes, Vijay?
A deal is on at 7 tomorrow morning,
outside the city.
If you could come there...
...I'll bring the disc with me.
I'm sure...
...it has all the information
the police wants.
Can you come there alone?
Rest assured.
There'll be no one with me.
Mr. Narang, don't you think it's
unsafe for Don to go alone?
I mean, this deal could
also be a setup.
Don won't go alone.
You will go with him.
Don't be silly Narang...
Are you telling me that
I can't do this job alone?
No. I know that you can
do it alone.
But Mr. Singhania has personally
ordered me to do this.
Mr. Narang...
Can't Vikram or Mac do this job?
Why is it important for Roma
to go with Don?
Because Mr. Narang knows
me very well...
...and when, where and
who to shoot...
...is something
I know very well.
Singhania...
Your time is up.
Tomorrow, the disc will be mine
and you'll be finished!
Tomorrow...!
This one word separates me
from my success.
And don't worry.
The police will never find out
that I have the disc.
Because neither do they know
that I am Vardhaan.
Nor is my photograph in
any of their records.
Is this a joke?!
No, its not!
What is this madness?
I have felt this mad since...
...you killed my brother Ramesh
and his fiance.
Ramesh! Your brother?
Yes...
And I didn't kill you
till now because...
...I wanted you to remember
why you were being killed!
You don't know this but...
I didn't kill your brother.
Good bye Don.
Stop! That's enough...
Look! Look at me.
Listen carefully.
You didn't kill me
all these days...
...and for that, I thank you.
Thank you very very much.
Now listen to the truth.
The truth is...
He...
...is not Don.
Who can say that he is not Don!
Besides Vijay and me now...
...only you know the truth.
Where is the disc?
Vijay...
I'm sorry.
I thought that...
No, it doesn't matter.
Anyone in your place...
...would have been deceived.
Mr. De Silva...
Your work is done?
No...
My work isn't done yet.
That too will happen.
Singhania is coming here.
Singhania?
Yes, sir.
He is coming to Kuala Lumpur
for a meeting.
I'll inform you of the location
as soon as I know.
Good.
Vijay...
You may have done this
for Deepu's sake but...
...neither me nor the police
will ever forget this favor.
Who is Deepu?
Vijay uncle...!
Don't you recognize me?
How can I not recognize you?
My... Deepu!
But, honestly...
...for one second
I did wonder,
"who is this smart young gentleman
running towards me?".
This new uniform!
New shoes.
Well uncle, you aren't the
same either!
What can I say, Deepu?
Your Vijay uncle...
...had to change.
But what about your paan?
Paan is gone!
Just a minute...
Roma, this is Deepu.
Hi Deepu.
Nice to meet you.
Hello... me too...
And Deepu, this is Roma aunty.
- Uncle, is she your aunty too?
- Hey! Is that anyway to speak!
Vijay...
The things you are doing
for this boy...!
Who does this in today's time?
If anything would have
happened to you today...
...I would never forgive myself!
Please forget all about it.
Anyway...
...I don't know...
Should I be grateful to Don for
making it possible to meet you...
...or I should hate him.
Because I wonder...
...how you can even
sit beside a man...
...who constantly reminds you
of your brother's death.
I can't punish you for a crime
committed by someone else.
And please.
Stop addressing me so formally.
What do I call you then?
Aunty?
Excuse me...
Hello...
There is some Mr. Jasjit Ahuja
here to see you sir.
Jasjit...
- How are you, Haatim?
- Very well.
What a surprise?
My God, it's been ages
since we met!
Bangalore 2002.
Before you came here.
Really! .
How time flies!
Unbelievable!
What brings you here?
DCP De Silva is in this
city right now.
Yes...
I heard about what
happened to you...
...I'm sorry.
I couldn't do anything for you.
But you can now.
I want his address, Haatim.
What do you plan on doing?
What time is the meeting?
And Singhania will be there?
Good... I'll see you then.
Vijay...
Well done!
Welcome back!
Perhaps you don't know
who I am'?
I know you very well.
DCP De Silva.
Who are you?
Think back!
9th January, Belcourt Towers?
10 million dollars worth
of diamonds?
No!
Well, maybe a bullet could help
sharpen your memory.
Hang on!
Jasjit?
Yes...
Jasjit.
What do you want?
I want to kill you!
I hope you won't mind too much!
Look, Jasjit...
Maybe what happened
to you was wrong...
I was only doing my duty.
I'm a police officer...
...and right now it's crucial
for me to be somewhere.
Or else some big criminals
will get away.
Let me go!
How can I let you go?
Look at these faces!
One of them is my wife...
...who is dead because of you.
The other is my innocent son!
Who knows where he is now?
Look at them...
This boy...
Deepu...
Is your son?!
You know Deepu?
Yes. I also know
where he is...
...but will tell you that,
only after I come back.
Wrong!
You will tell me right now!
Jasjit...
You can kill me and
take your revenge...
...but then give up the hope that
you'll see your son again!
I don't hate you as much...
...as I love my son.
Go.
I will wait for you here.
Leave that here.
You do have to come back,
don't you?
Night and wine have met
we are intoxicated.
Body and heart
are both ready to melt.
Celebration surrounds us...
...but yet I am anxious.
Why does my heart beat faster?
Why does my heart say...
"you fools do not know this yet?".
Tonight...
Who knows what will happen?
What will we gain?
What will we lose?
Tonight...
Who knows what will happen?
What will we gain?
What will we lose?
What will happen
in just a few moments?
What was always mine
will be mine again.
The night will decide
who resides in who's heart.
The decision has been made...
...that I will be victorious.
You fools do not know this yet.
Tonight...
Who knows what will happen?
What will we gain?
What will we lose?
Tonight...
Who knows what will happen?
What will we gain?
What will we lose?
Come, let me tell you
something, secretly.
Soon, the night is going to
change its hue, secretly.
Then I will take you away
with me, secretly.
Where will you go?
Look! Here I am.
You fools do not know this yet.
Tonight...
Who knows what will happen?
What will we gain?
What will we lose?
Move it...!
Put your gun down.
Open the door.
Let him go.
Shoot, Mr. Malik!
- Mr. Malik! Shoot him!
- Shut up.
Let him go. Put your gun down.
Shoot, Mr. Malik!
Get into the van. Move!
Malik! Shoot him.
Do you want me to shoot him?
Relax...
Malik...
Close the door.
Shut the door.
Stop!
Turn the engine off!
Now...!
I mean it.
Now!
Yes...
OK... Thank you.
What do you think, Verma?
Is this man telling the truth
that he is not Don?
Don is very clever, sir.
Claiming that he is Vijay,
Mr. De Silva's informer...
...is surely a plan to
escape punishment.
Hmm? Lets do this...
Bring Narang and Mac here.
Let them hear what he's saying.
Perhaps his words...
...can break them.
Mr. Malik, how many times do
I have to tell you I'm not Don!
I'm Vijay...
De Silva Saheb's informer.
If Singhania's men are behind bars
today, it's all due to me.
And why don't you go ask
De Silva Saheb who I am?
DCP De Silva is no
longer with us.
He's dead.
Dead?
Just a minute!
Then...
Where's the disc I gave him?
What disc?
I had given him a disc that contained information
of Singhania's contacts and bank accounts.
I'm sorry but he didn't mention
any such disc.
But it must be somewhere!
...In his apartment or
somewhere here...
...in his desk... or...
Mr. Malik!
If I were Don...
...how would I know that
he had this disc?
DCP De Silva's informer has
told us quite a lot about you.
Now if there is anything,
you two would like to say?
What are you saying, Mr. Malik?
This man is Don.
And he is doing what
he knows best.
What's that?
Making police officers like you
look like fools.
Shut up.
Take them away.
Verma, take a small team to
DCP De Silva's apartment.
If that disc is there...
...it's possible this man is
speaking the truth.
He is telling the truth.
He is not Don.
Malik Saheb, I'm telling the truth...
I gave De Silva Saheb the
disc with my own hands!
You don't believe me, do you?
Don, I gave you a chance...
But now even you can't deny
the fact that you are Don.
I'm sorry.
Verma... just send
the guards in!
Wait...!
There is another proof...
Dr. Ashok Khilwani!
He operated on me to
make me look like Don.
Please...! He knows the truth.
Please... Sir...
Thank you, Feroze.
Malik Saheb...
...did you talk to
the doctor?
- He is not alive.
- Not alive?!
Last month, he and his assistant
died in a car accident.
Malik Saheb...
Please believe me.
I'm not Don!
The Court will decide
this matter.
Please listen to me!
I'm Vijay, Malik Saheb!
I'm not Don, I'm Vijay!
Try and understand...
Hello Vijay!
We heard everything.
Don't be silly, Mac.
I am Don.
I only said that to
confuse them.
What's happening?
Stop it.
Narang...!
- Please make them understand.
- Shut up.
You are Vijay...
But if they attack you here...
...the police will realize...
...are not Don.
Get back.
Get back...!
So...
Behaving a bit too smart,
weren't you, boy?!
Now get ready to die.
The punishment for selling
drugs in Malaysia...
...is death...
...and the court will surely give
Don the death sentence.
If it doesn't...
...we'll kill Vijay in jail.
What happened, sir?
They say that, till we
get a date in court...
...it's not safe to keep these
dangerous criminals here.
So what is their intention?
They have a high security jail on
an island, five miles off the coast.
They'll all be flown there
first thing tomorrow.
Excuse me...
I need to use the
toilet please...!
Very badly...!
Hey...
Okay.
Come through!
- Hey... hey...
- Easy!
Okay... okay...
Sorry.
Come through.
Hi...
Give me your gun, Please!
Just stay there.
Come on...!
Now the handcuffs...
Go on...!
Quick!
The other one...!
Quick...
Now give me his gun, Please...
Quick... quick...!
Take him with the others.
Move it!
Fast...!
Go on...!
No...!
Congratulations! Jasjit.
The information on this disc...
...is like a winning lottery ticket.
I know a man who can get you
a lot of money for this disc.
Jasjit...
De Silva said that he knew
where Deepu was.
Perhaps, the buyer we find
may have known De Silva?
Haatim...
If he can lead me to Deepu,
I'll let him have all that money.
I see...
And you have this disc.
No problem.
It'll be done.
Malik...
What!
What happened, sir?
Who was that?
An incident on board forced the
pilot to make an emergency landing.
Don has escaped!
Thanks...
Thanks for coming!
Thank God you're all right!
You call this being all right?
Vijay...
I know what the truth is.
The truth...?
Why will the police
believe you, Roma?
Only the disc can prove
my innocence now.
We'll get the disc.
The man who stole the disc...
...cannot be honest enough
to return it to the police.
He's sure to try and sell it.
Just a minute, Roma.
Singhania has an agent here...
...who kept him informed about
the cops and our enemies.
He could be of use.
Try and contact him somehow.
But if you are found meanwhile...
I mean, the police will be
searching everywhere for you.
I know!
But where can I go?!
There is one place.
Where is Ramesh's place?
Close by. To the right.
Stop please.
Yours, sir?
All units respond...
Wait...
We have a fugitive situation.
Suspect's name is Don.
Last seen wearing a dark jacket,
trousers and a grey shirt.
He is of Indian origin.
Who are you, Saheb?
What do you want?
How does one explain who he is?
Just know that we are
in big trouble...
...and need shelter for a while,
that's all.
It's not a police affair, eh?
Should we tell them?
Uncle...
It's a police affair and...
...an affair of the heart too!
Well! I get it now.
You've run away?
No, uncle. I haven't run away...
I've been kidnapped!
That's great!
Where do we witness
love like this nowadays?!
Come this way, Saheb.
Come, madam.
Sit down, Saheb.
Uncle...
Saheb! Bhaang! (Milk brewed
with Marijuana plant extract).
Bhaang?
Tonight is Mahashivratri...
(Indian festival in honor of Lord Shiva)...
...it is a holy offering
to Shiva. Drink!
Oh, the lord will bless you for
drinking his favourite brew!
You also try it.
Cheers...
Happy Mahashivratri everyone.
It's all right, brother!
Honestly speaking, uncle...
If I had listened to my mother
when I was a boy...
I wouldn't be seeing these days!
Why? What did she say?
When I never listened to her,
how can I tell you what she said!
If you're done,
can we please leave?
Leave! But where do we go?
De Silva...
DCP Saheb!
You set up a good way to get me
up there before you left"!
Well done!
Saheb... paan!
Hey buddy!
I don't want it!
Eat it. It's from Benaras.
Really?
But Don didn't eat paan.
Never...
Don, who?
Don... Who??!
Don means me, meaning Vijay
a.k.a Don, meaning...
- Paan!
- Pawn!!
I didn't understand a thing.
How do I tell you, brother?
The plight I am in.
Tell us... tell us...
I set out to eat "halwa"...
(hot Indian dessert)...
...and ended up burning my mouth!
What can I say?
How can I explain?
I'm in a bad situation...
...that's hard to escape.
It's like a violent storm!
It's like a raging wind!
I've had to...
...run for my life!
Along and winding...
...chase has been on!
Day and night,
I've been awake...
...running helter skelter.
Sometimes this way!
Sometimes that way!
Ran this way once
and that way next!!
Then you gave me this paan...
...and life has returned
to my tired body!
Eating a paan from Benaras...
...unlocked my benumbed brain.
Now watch the things I'll do...
...to straighten up everyone.
This boy...
...this boy from the
banks of the Ganges!
Eating a paan from Benaras...
...unlocked my benumbed brain.
I've been cursed!
...to be caught up in
this maze, alas!
My life is in limbo...
...I'm at the hangman's mercy, alas!
So honest and simple,
So innocent... yes I am.
Don't know how I ended up
amid this educated lot!!
With a sweetened knife...
With a sweetened knife
they've slit my throat!
This boy from the
banks of the Ganges!
Eating a paan from Benaras...
...unlocked my benumbed brain.
A lovely lass,
unique and desirable...
...her enrapturing charm
turns all heads...
...wherever she goes...
...and her body sparkles
like precious stones.
Her dazzling eyes carry
a world of dreams...
...her lips, youth's nectar.
A flirtatious swagger
in her walk...
...sprinkles the air with her
sandalwood-scented body.
The vision of her
sets your heart aflame.
Her face is moon-bright.
Her eyes like a gazelle.
She is beautiful...
...as sweet as honey.
A beautiful maiden...
...has fallen for me, alas!
A sweetened skewer...
...has pierced my heart, alas!
So bright and fair
she's a spicy lass.
A fighting spirit to match
she stole my heart.
Now that I have her love...
Now that I have her love
my life has blossomed!
This boy from the
banks of the Ganges!
Eating a paan from Benaras...
...unlocked my benumbed brain.
Now watch the things I'll do...
...to straighten up everyone.
This boy...
...this boy from the
banks of the Ganges!
Yes...
Yes, it's me.
There's a buyer for the disc here.
Yes, ready to pay in dollars.
Just a minute.
You should speak directly.
We have Deepu.
If you want to see him alive,
bring the disc...
Jasjit...
If you want to see your
son alive...
...bring that disc at 5 pm sharp
to this address.
Jasjit...
- Haatim Qureishi?
- Yes?
May I come inside?
Who are you?
I've nothing personal
against you.
But if you don't hand over
the disc to me...
...I'll be forced to...
...change my mind.
What disc?
The one you wanted
to sell Roma...
Remember?
Sorry...
The disc is with my friend, Jasjit.
And where is your friend, Jasjit?
Where's the disc?
Where's Deepu?
Deepu will come.
Call me when he does...
...you already have
my phone number!
Jasjit...
Seeing your punctuality...
I must say...
...I'm very impressed!
De Silva...?!
No...
Vardhaan.
Vardhaan...?
But you...
...are dead?!!
Right?
For a man who can keep the
police in the dark for years...
...creating the drama of a mere
accident is no big deal!
Do you want me to shoot him?
Relax...
Malik...
Shut the door.
Let's go.
Stop!
Turn the engine off.
I mean it.
Come on.
You're very cunning.
Thank you.
Now all I want is the disc...
...which you will give me.
I don't believe it.
Now I get it!
Why the police didn't find
the diamonds in that basement.
I recognise that ring.
What did you think?
I brought the disc with me!
Do you think I am a fool'?
Remember?
That night, you had asked me
the same question!
You have a very good memory.
It'll help in
recognizing your son.
Daddy...
Deepu...
Vardhaan...
If anything happens...
Relax Jasjit!
I don't enjoy bloodshed.
All I want is...
...the disc.
All right...
You'll get it.
Jasjit here.
Bring the disc.
My man will reach here at 7.
You and your son will...
...remain my guests till then.
Phone please?
Take him away.
Kill them when you
have the disc!
Are you okay, son?
Deepu...
Listen carefully.
As long as they do not get
what they want...
...our life is not in danger.
- But daddy! At 7, when your...
- Nothing will happen at 7.
Nobody is going to come.
That phone call was
to buy us time.
I'm scared, daddy.
Don't be, my son.
I'm with you now.
Nothing will happen to you.
Nothing will happen.
Yes, Mr. Vardhaan.
Nobody has come so far.
Okay.
Find them.
- Now where, daddy?
- Keep it down!
Just a minute.
Let me see.
They must be hiding close by.
Keep looking.
There, he is.
Don't shoot.
Only he knows where the disc is.
Daddy...
Vijay uncle...!
Daddy, stop!
This is Vijay uncle.
He took care of me when
you went away.
Vijay uncle, this is my Daddy.
Take it.
Vijay...
But for you, I don't know
where Deepu would be today.
Please Jasjit...!
Whatever I did for him...
Deepu is a lovable boy.
Anyway, why do you need
this disc so badly?
Just know that the only way
out of the mess I'm in...
...is this disc...
...and your testimony.
I don't understand.
Your testimony will prove...
...that this disc was
with DCP De Silva.
DCP De Silva?!
Yes.
He was the only one in the
police department who knew...
...that he is not Don,
but Vijay.
But after he died...
He is not dead!
His real name is Vardhaan.
And just a little while ago...
I met him!
No!
This can't be.
I mean...
...your eyes must have
deceived you!!
No, I have not been deceived.
DCP De Silva is Vardhaan!!
He made me pose as Don...
...obtained the disc...
...and a chance to kill Singhania.
Then faked his own death...
...and left me to die as Don.
DCP De Silva... Vardhaan!
You've played a big move!
But he must never have thought...
...that I'd steal the disc.
Give the disc to Vardhaan!
Vijay! What are you saying?
Yes, Roma.
A final meeting with DCP De Silva
is very important.
Don't worry, darling.
Today will be the last day
of Vijay's life.
I've reached the place
you told me to...
...alone.
Good.
Buy a ticket from the counter.
There's a bridge on level one...
...come there.
And yes...
...don't forget the money...
...or you'll have to
buy the ticket again.
You seem to be in a great hurry.
Now where do I go?
Throw the bag down.
What!?
I can see you, Jasjit...
...but I don't see the disc.
You'll get what you want.
Throw it.
Looks good.
Where's the disc?
Upper viewing platform.
Silver briefcase.
Damn!
Poor DCP De Silva!
You!
What are you doing here?
I should be asking you that!
You're dead, remember?
- What do you want?
- Answers to some questions.
Please! This is no time
for interviews!
All right then. Here's
the second reason.
I'm going to kill you today.
You have the guts to shoot?
You've trained me pretty well.
What will you gain
by killing me?
There are some deeds in which
profit and loss doesn't matter.
They just have to be done.
Very good!
But how will you prove your
innocence, if you kill me?
Only I know your real identity.
Perhaps that disc can be of use.
What do you think?
You have the disc?
No...
It was my love for you that
dragged me here!
Give me the disc.
I'm ready to send you to
any corner of the world.
Think it over.
You must be exhausted
running from the police!
Not as much as from thinking
over and over...
...why you betrayed me?
Come on, get over it.
What betrayal?!
This is the real world.
You think Singhania asked me
before seizing Boris' entire empire?
I created the entire business!
With my intelligence and guts.
And now to get it back,
I can use thousands like you.
All right.
I betrayed you.
You want an apology?
I'm so sorry, Vijay!
Happy?
Feel any better?!!
Use your head, Vijay.
There's still time...
Join me.
You will gain from it...
...and so will I.
That's the signal!
All teams move in.
I repeat all teams move in.
Good boy! Come...
Put your gun down.
This is the police.
I repeat...
Put your gun down.
Stop, Vijay!
Don't make this mistake.
Hand him over to us.
Please kill me!
You will be making a huge
mistake if you let me live.
Don't listen to him!
He is trying to set you up!!
Shut up!
Remember! Wherever you go...
someday I will find you...
And that day will be the
last day of your life!
Don't listen to him, Vijay.
After that, Roma.
Then, Deepu.
I'll kill them both...
...unless you kill me now.
In that case, Vardhaan...
...I'll be waiting for you.
Hurry up!
Take him quickly!
Vijay?
Hold on please.
You finally did it.
You proved your innocence.
It wasn't possible without you.
Thank you.
Sir, we must take you to
the hospital right away.
Yes, of course!
Come with me Roma.
Excuse me?
Can't she come along with us?
I'm sorry sir.
Ma'am, please step aside.
Don't worry,
I'll see you at the hospital.
Vijay!
I love you.
Even I like wild cats a lot.
Come closer.
I like wild cats a lot.
Wild cats!
- Mr. Malik, where's that ambulance going?
- One minute sir...
To the hospital.
Why, what's the matter?
He is Don!
"I like wild cats a lot...".
Don had said that to me...
whispered it in my ears!
If this is Vijay,
how did he know it?
Diazepam (a sedative)?
Yes Sir, Giving it right now.
Good.
The doctors have kept him in
a sedated state.
All the marks and scars
that were on Don's body...
...need to be made on you.
Sure.
On me!
I was about to tell you...
I got Deepu admitted to
Malaysia's International School.
When Don, that means you...
...go back to your companions...
...you'll be ill and wounded.
You will have lost your memory.
The more you learn
about Don's life...
...the closer I'll get to
regaining my memory.
Thank you.
You think exactly like the comic book
hero, Chacha Chaudhary!
Weren't you trying to quit?
What all can I quit?
I've quit everyone...
except you.
Really Don.
I thought that you would
get caught today...
...or that I'd lose you.
To whom... Roma?
- What about the disc that the police...
- That's fake.
What's on it means nothing!
Don't worry, sweetheart.
Now the reins of Asia's
underworld is in my hands!
I am the king!
As for catching me...
Always remember this!
Please...
Not only is it difficult to catch Don...