"Let me go home, beloved.
Let me go home. "
Dreams are sold differently
in different cities.
Because the city and it's monotonous
life needs the vision and color...
... of a beautiful dream to make itself big.
A city like this, where a dream of...
... becoming an international super model...
I, Meghna Mathur dreamt and lived.
The only difference was that
my dream was bigger than the city.
Since you were tired of eating
the potato pancakes for breakfast...
... so I made radish pancakes today.
- Mother, this has a lot of butter.
- Have it.
I told you I am on a diet.
Having one won't make a difference.
Of course, it will.
I am trying to lose two kilos.
I got my portfolio done.
I was thinking of leaving
for Mumbai on Monday.
Monday reminds me, I have
spoken to Mehra Associates.
They have agreed on an
internship with them...
... while you finish your chartered
accountants course.
In fact, you can start with
them from Monday.
Papa, you didn't hear me.
I want to go to Mumbai...
to become a model.
I don't want to do an internship.
Meghna, I've told you earlier also.
Never mind.
Listen, dreaming isn't bad but...
But what father?
Fulfill only your dreams?
Can't I have my own dream?
I have decided...
I am going to Mumbai.
In that case there is
nothing left to discuss.
Do as you wish...
... but don't expect anything from me.
A little encouragement perhaps...
Encouragement for what?
You have lost your mind after
winning a small beauty pageant.
It was my fault.
Wants to be a model!
Though I have spoken to
your uncle Baldev...
... call me as soon as you reach.
Father...
Don't worry.
Everything will be alright
Love you...
You were much younger during
cousin Kuldeep's wedding.
Divya is very happy ever since
she learnt you were coming.
Sister...
Mother was mentioning
that you want to model.
It will be great to watch
her on television.
Divya...
Come Meghna, I will show
you to your room.
Of course and be comfortable.
Thank you.
This is Divya's room...
You will have to share it with her.
Sure.
It's a little small...
... but you won't be here for long.
Maybe a month, until I get work.
Alright, freshen up,
till then I will serve breakfast.
Thank you.
Okay, not today. Alright,
I'll talk to you later.
- Hi.
- Hello gorgeous, welcome to Mumbai.
No, no, darling.
Lesson number one...
... never kiss the cheeks, okay?
Sit.
I'm sorry I'm late
but what could I do.
Vinay wouldn't let me go.
Now before you jump into any conclusions,
Vinay Khosla is my boss.
You know the famous
Bollywood designer.
This evening we have to
do fittings for Duggu...
- You know last minute changes.
- Duggu?
Duggu... Hrithik.
Anyway, enough of blabbering.
You tell me how you are.
I'm okay.
When I saw you in that silly
beauty contest in Chandigarh...
I just knew that you
are going to be a star.
Thank you, Rohit.
I'm here because you
showed confidence in me.
Now everything is in your hands.
Don't worry, darling.
I am your man.
- Do you have your pictures?
- Yes, of course!
Okay, let me have a look.
What's the matter?
Nothing. Nothing. Fine.
Interesting, I'll handle it, okay?
Who are you looking for?
Your casting agent.
Here?
Shomu, hot shot co-ordinator,
a Godmother to the newcomers.
Don't be too fussy.
Have you ever travelled by
plane before?
I'm sending you to a foreign location.
So what if the role is small?
You will suffer one day.
And Shweta, you have a two dayjob.
No one gives more than 25,000 rupees
for a Punjabi dance number.
I would have done it,
if I were taller.
Ma'am, you are being called inside.
Who is it?
Are you new?
- Are you from the north?
- Yes.
What size are you?
Small, medium, large?
Listen, I am not interested.
It's the client who wants to know.
I wasjust about to call you.
I'm sending a girl for the catalogue.
Check her out.
What? What is your name?
Meghna... Meghna Mathur.
Her name is Meghna Mathur.
Bye.
Okay, listen, You have
an audition tomorrow.
B 409, Adarsh Nagar.
Be there at eleven o'clock.
Take the number from this chick.
Chick?
An audition? Tomorrow?
Yes, and listen if it works...
... I take a twenty per cent cut.
Is that clear?
Okay.
Stop here, I think this is the place.
How much is it?
Fifteen rupees.
Take this.
I recently did two advertisements.
What about you?
I'm an airhostess.
I got bored of serving people...
... so now I want to be a model.
Do you have a problem with that?
- No.
- Then stop bothering me.
It is a soap commercial, isn't it?
Alright, I will be there.
I am at Adarsh Nagar right now.
I will be at Famous studios in an hour.
Okay, pal, I'll be there, bye.
New?
Yes.
Auditioning for the first time?
How did you guess?
Only novices walk around
with their portfolio.
Seasoned models, like us,
send it in earlier or email it to them.
- By the way, I'm Manav... Manav Bhasin.
- Hello.
A veteran struggler.
Since nine months.
- And you?
- Who is Meghna Mathur?
That's me.
- Please, come in.
- Yes.
- All the best.
- Thank you.
Saira Khan...
give me your left profile...
Right profile...
Hi, I am Saira Khan. Age 22...
You can contact me on 98...
Hi... my name is Meghna Mathur.
My mobile number is 9820131139.
Have patience, darling.
You can't be tired in
just three orfour auditions.
It takes up to three
hundred auditions at times...
to finally get a break
Nowjust relax, okay?
Have your coffee. It's not easy, dear.
Okay. I'll call you later.
One week is over...
Will you do a lingerie advertisement?
Shomu...
I have told you a million times,
It's lingerie not lin-guh-ree.
The same thing.
Will you do it?
Shomu, just behave yourself,
okay? Meghna is a star.
Meghna won't do such
degrading commercials.
Why are you getting angry?
What is so degrading in
a lingerie advertisement?
Haven't you seen commercially
successful models in calendars?
They wear whatever they are told.
Attitude walks in before stardom.
And you go to Bandra.
I'll give you an address.
Don't take her seriously.
She just talks nonsense sometimes, okay?
Look, just relax, darling.
I've got a surprise for you.
- We are going for a fashion show tomorrow.
- Fashion Show?
That too Rahul Arora's fashion show.
Rahul Arora! I have only
seen him on television.
So tomorrow evening it is
Rahul Arora's fashion show. Live!
Love, I have told you so many times
not to keep your phone switched off.
Because I get worried.
You know, you are becoming
impossible now.
Not the same thing again!
I am not being possessive.
I should at least know where you are...
... and what you're up to.
That's nonsense and
you know it is not true.
We've been together
since six months...
... and I know you quite well.
No, I don't want to discuss it?
Now what?
Behave...
Come on, Rahul, just once.
- No...
- Please baby, say it. Please, darling.
- Not right now.
- Please, darling. Please say it, once.
- Try to understand.
- Darling, please.
Okay, I am hanging up the phone.
- One minute. We are meeting tonight, aren't we? - Yes.
- I'll see you soon. Okay? Okay. Bye.
- Rahul...
Yes mother...
What can I say?
The whole world is talking.
Everyone is laughing at me.
They say I don't want
you to get married.
Let them talk.
How does it affect us?
How can I bear it?
We can't go against society.
It's high time you got married.
Your uncle Kishen from
London had called.
He sent some pictures through email.
Mom! I don't want to see
any pictures of girls.
- At least look at them.
- Mom, please...
At least don't bother me today.
Tomorrow is my show
and I'm really nervous.
"I know baby that you need me. "
Oh Jassi, what are you doing?
Look straight. Yes.
That's good.
And turn.
Make a note. Third sequence.
Dinaz is first.
Girls, walk faster,
this isn't a garden.
Couturier, lets see it.
Now listen quickly get ready for it.
We don't have much time.
And please, concentrate.
Couturier, what is this?
This is the show stopper outfit.
Increase the length of the slit.
There are only three hours
left for the show.
Please leave.
Don't stress me out.
Please, quickly.
Rahul, pay attention now okay?
We have a run through, alright?
Yes, but where is Shonali?
When is she ever punctual
that today will be an exception?
She is your show stopper
and your favourite.
Why aren't we sitting in the front row?
It's absolutely empty.
Are you nuts?
That's reserved seating, darling.
Just watch what happens
there in a while.
Hi... come on, Jack.
Sir... sir... this is reserved, sir.
Are you mad? Listen,
this is not the first row like this.
I am leaving, okay?
- You know where?
- Yes, sir.
Now come on, speak to Rahul
and arrange for it fast.
Okay, sir. Give me two minutes.
I'll arrange it.
Hello, J. P, I have a situation out here.
Relax, dude.
Sweetie, this is my number, call me.
Hi.
- Meghna...
- Yes?
Look there.
There in the front row,
that's my boss Vinay Khosla.
He is Rahul's biggest rival...
... and his most loyal audience.
He doesn't miss a single show.
That guy?
- Don't you point!
- I am sorry. - This is cheap.
There, right hand corner...
That's Ashish Suri...
Rahul's boyfriend.
He is so cute, isn't he?
I hate Rahul.
Look, front row center.
That's the fashion power list.
She is Shelly Duggal, the editor
of a famous fashion magazine.
Sitting to her left, there... can you
see the lady in the animal print?
Anisha Roy, the owner
of Profiles Agency.
Every top model since the past
six years is from their agency.
Oh, here come
Mr. and Mrs. Abhijeet Sarin.
She is a hi-flying socialite, but he...
he is the big daddy of the fashion world.
The owner of Panache.
His brand is the biggest
status symbol in the fashion world.
Everyone dances to
his tunes. Everyone.
Ladies and gentlemen,
can you take your seats?
The show is about to begin.
"Charm. Charm. "
"Charm. "
"C'mon, sing with me!"
- Look my dear.
- Shonali Gulral.
That's right. The Diva.
"Charm. "
"The charm is of the body. "
"This charm is famous. "
"This charm is also a goal. "
"Get lucky here. "
"Charm. Charm. "
You idiot!
I'm in the middle of the show...
I told you not to call me.
That was Mohsin, isn't it?
God knows how many times
you'll break up and patch up.
- Shonali, your next change.
- Yes, I know that.
"The fire in you. "
That's Jassi, isn't she?
"She walks in style. "
"It lights up fire in love. "
"Charm. Charm. "
"It's the charm...
... of Fashion. "
"Charm. Charm. "
"It's the charm of fashion. "
"This Charm. " "One's sake."
- Go. Go.
"Guess what?"
"Charm. Charm. "
Start dimming the lights.
Now ask them to stand back.
"It's the charm of fashion. "
Ladies and gentlemen, put your hands
together for Rahul Arora!
"Charm. Charm."
"Charm. Charm. "
"Charm. "
"It's the charm of fashion. "
I would like to thank Mr. Abhijeet Sarin...
... and Panache India for showing
so much of confidence in me.
And I look forward to this.
What about your next collection?
Well, you will have to wait forthis.
Spoke to Manish, you're on
for the Delhi show. Okay?
- Hi, Christine. Hi.
- Hi.
- The show was fantastic.
- Yes.
- We just loved the music.
- Thank you.
- Christine, this is Meghna.
- Hi. - Hi.
She is here to be a model.
- Isn't she gorgeous?
- Yes, sure.
You know, you really must use her.
She'll dazzle the ramp.
Okay, send me your pictures.
- No. No. It's okay.
- So cute... do it.
Excuse me, girls. Hi.
- Hi, lmmi...
- Hi.
- You are looking great.
- Yes.
Can I show you my photographs?
I have them here with me.
- Here.
- Bye.
- Okay.
Excuse me.
I agree you may not like the pictures
but you needn't throw them.
Attitude! Doesn't come
through in your photographs.
You need a good
photographer, baby.
Who would you go to
if you were in my place?
Darling, I'd never be in your place!
Kartik Suri, he's your man.
You know Rohit, Kartik is
very busy these days.
Traveling, international
photo shoots, you know it.
Okay, Come on, Sonu, look at her.
She is a star, you know it.
What difference will
one photo shoot make?
I'm sure if you put in
a word he will agree.
Look, please.
He charges 50,000 rupees,
along with make up and styling.
And separate charges for costumes.
Can she afford it?
Of course.
But Meghna...
- Wait.
- Well then, 10,000 rupees advance.
Will 7,000 rupees do for now?
I only have that much
with me right now.
But how did you...
I'm making an appointment for...
... the 20th of next month
at eight in the morning.
If you cancel you forfeit
the advance. Okay?
- Yes. That's fine.
- Actually...
- Okay.
- Seven... here is the advance.
Manav, I told you earlier as well...
... if you want to progress in this industry...
... you have to compromise.
Come on, do you think
that all the successful models...
... found workjust like that?
They also had to compromise.
I can't do what others do.
I want to be successful
on my own terms.
Not like this.
Well, suit yourself.
Anyway, thank you for your time.
Have a good day.
Hi Amar, where are you?
Hi, Mrs. Agarwal...
Rohit here, from
Vinay Khosla's office, ma'am.
Ma'am, I'm here with
the outfits for the trial.
- Yes, that's right.
- Manav!
- Yes. Oh hi.
- Ma'am...
- Hi, how are you? Good.
- Good, how are you?
What are you doing here?
Did you have a meeting?
- At lunch, ma'am?
- Yes, a kind of... - I didn't do it till now.
That's what I came here for,
but it didn't work out.
- Anyway. - I'll see you after lunch.
- I'll see you later.
- Okay, bye.
- Okay.
- Who is that?
- Just a friend... model.
You should have at least
introduced me to him.
- He's quite hot.
- Rohit.
- Now what?
- Lunch.
Enjoy, Meghna.
I only have mineral water.
Especially when someone
else is paying the bill.
But how can we eat out here,
it's so expensive.
Just relax, okay?
Mrs. Agarwal is an NRI.
She is very rich.
She told me to have lunch
and add the bill to her account.
- Shomu called today. Yes.
- What?
She said there is
a party at some hotel.
If I have to make contacts,
I must go.
Should I go?
Of course, you should go Meghna!
Networking is very important.
What fun!
Lunch and dinner both
at a five star hotel.
You are on a roll.
"Hey baby!"
Sorry. Hi, Janet here.
Stop fooling around.
The girls have been waiting in
the lobby since long.
Listen, there are three girls...
... one of them is new.
Just explain it to them.
Properly, okay?
Yes, I'll be there in five minutes.
Sorry, Sameer, I have to go.
Working, you know.
Love doesn't provide food.
Sameer?
Not Sameer, honey, Sohail.
Oh, it's my fault. Sorry. Bye.
- Stay together, okay?
- Okay.
Where is Bajaj?
- Hello Janet!
- Hello!
Welcome to the party,
how are you?
- Very well. How are you doing?
- Come. Come.
- Let me introduce you to my friends.
- Sir... Janet, meet Mr...
- Hi.
A young businessman from Oman.
- And sir, meet Ms. Janet.
She is a very well-known
model from Mumbai.
- Hi... very nice meeting you.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice meeting you.
- Meet my friends, Shaheen.
- Hi. - The music video queen.
The 'Kanta laga' type.
- She is Meghna.
- Hello.
The famous super hit
Bollywood item girl.
- She is Anita, the famous calendar girl.
- Hello.
Hi!
One vodka with coconut
water on it. Vodka?
No thank you, I don't drink.
Drink up. It's free and imported too.
Shomu said that I could
make some contacts here.
- Drink ma'am.
- Contacts? And that too here?
Just smile and look pretty
for the photographs.
And then ourjob is done.
That's it!
- Thank you. - Janet!
- Yes Bajaj, coming.
Good party, isn't it?
Mukesh Tyagi.
I run an ad agency.
Talent Unlimited and you?
Meghna Mathur...
You are a model, right?
No, not as yet but hopefully...
Come on, you look professional.
Send me some of your photographs.
I suggest that you
drop in to my office.
I have good contacts...
perhaps I can help you.
- Sure...
- Do one thing, this is my card and...
- call me up on my mobile.
- Okay?
Janet, Meet Mr...
Mukesh Tyagi.
He runs an ad agency. Yes.
Talent Unlimited.
"Send me your pictures. "
Or "drop into my office. "
He says he has a lot of contacts.
He has been doing the party
rounds since the past five years.
Listen, fraud...
- ... with those old lines, you won't
catch any fish. - Go from here.
What's the problem with
you small town girls?
Anyone who speaks halfway decent English,
can get anywhere with you.
Come on, let's go.
You want to make contacts.
Janet, Reema, Meghna.
Dolly, that's your 15,000.
I've cut five for the advance.
- There are 10,000 in the packet.
- Okay, fine.
And here's your 18,000.
Don't ask for conveyance.
We've got a party like this
after a month. Get it.
And Meghna...
It's yourfirst time so
I'm paying you 12,000.
What are you looking at?
Here take it.
Don't want it?
No... but... money?
You're paid for the work you did.
Work?
Didn't you pose for the camera?
People like having girls
at such parties.
Mr. Bajaj is an event manager...
... he contacts me for the models.
It's like this...
... pretty girls increase the glamour
quotient for such parties.
High society calls this
eye candy, understood?
Here take this.
Here.
And here, Reema.
- What's this? Where have you been?
- What do I do?
Don't you want your money?
What should I do?
The world of glamour is strange...
... you are so desperate
to achieve success...
... that the difference between
what's right and wrong begins to blur.
To be honest, there's barely
any time to think about it.
As the date for the portfolio got closer...
... my hopes began to diminish.
Meghna darling,
why are you so tense?
Everything will work out,
dear. I promise.
How is it possible, Rohit?
Only six days to go for the portfolio...
... and I still don't have the money.
You know what he said...
If I don't pay the entire amount...
... then I forfeit the advance.
And I still have 30,000 to go.
Meghna, if you don't mind...
Shomu's offer is still open.
I don't know.
You could give it a try.
It's worth a shot.
Lingerie?
"Beautiful lady. "
"Drive me crazy. "
Janet, show some more skin.
I've shown enough for
what I've been paid. Get it?
Fine, let's get on with it.
"Come on. "
"Beautiful lady. "
"You drive me crazy. "
Don't feel shy.
It's weird for the first ten seconds...
... after that, you will get used to it.
Come on madam.
Take off your gown.
There are other models
waiting for the shoot.
Quickly, there are three more to go.
Come on madam, make it quick.
Just feel free, do not stress.
- Take this.
- Meghna, relax.
Archana... very good.
- Have some tea, you will feel better.
- No.
Okay, left profile now.
- Janet, your cheque.
- Thank you.
Meghna, that's yours. You remember
my commission, right?
Yes, but Shomu are you sure this...
... advertisement won't be released here?
I told you that it won't get released here.
This advertisement is only for Sri Lanka
and Bangladesh. Is that clear?
Don't worry.
You've done the advertisement now, so...
- Now chin up.
- Just have a smoke and chill.
Thanks. I don't smoke.
Meghna, don't think so much.
The lesser you think,
the more you will make.
Thanks Janet.
Oh yes. Tomorrow is
your portfolio shoot, isn't it?
- Yes. Thanks.
- All the best. I know you'll rock.
Okay guys, let's get this done.
Alright... just look up a bit.
Relax, yes. Okay.
Now look at me. Smile.
Yes, nice. That's good.
Look at me and chin down.
Chin down.
- Chin down.
- Chin slightly down. Relax now.
- Okay. Do it again!
- Sorry.
Smile... yes. Much better.
Okay, great.
Look at me. That's a nice smile.
Hold that.
Hold that pose.
Superb!
Anisha, didn't I mention that...
I haven't seen a striking
impressive face recently.
And I finally found one.
She is unbelievable.
- Irene.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Send in the Kartik girl, please.
- Okay.
Meghna Mathur!
That's me!
So you want to be a model?
No ma'am.
A super model.
Ambitious.
Do you know the city gets
two hundred girls everyday...
... who aspire to be a model.
I know.
But... how many of them...
... get a chance to sit across you?
- Kartik was right, you have spunk.
- Thank you.
But that will not suffice.
What did you tell me your name was?
- Meghna...
- Yes, Meghna.
Meghna, in the fashion industry...
... even a little talent will do.
But if you have the wrong attitude...
... nothing will work.
You have attitude.
Use it with prudence or
it will be mistaken for arrogance.
That won't happen.
Really!
Yes.
Won't you be there to guide me?
I like your confidence.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Nothing yet.
Not good?
Oh, horrible.
Actually, I don't know
a lot about wines.
Don't worry there are
very few over here who do.
At least you are honest.
Ross, two glasses of Merlot, please.
- Try this, you'll like it.
- Okay.
Still the same.
You've either tried wine for...
... the first time or had a lot of it.
That's why you can't tell the difference.
- By the way, I am Abhijeet Sarin.
- I know you, everybody knows you.
- I am Meghna Mathur.
- Now I know you.
Want to try something more interesting?
- Yes... - Come, let's go.
- Okay. Come.
Cheers.
These models are so thin.
I've heard they do drugs?
I don't know. Not all of them,
maybe a few.
And guess what, Sheetal...
I heard that designer
Varun Ramani's wife is...
having an affair with her gym instructor.
Then you know the latest.
Rajan Sodhi has hidden
cameras in his wife's bedroom.
- And?
- And guess what, she got caught.
What are you saying?
I just don't understand. How can
people get into such situations?
Does she know this?
You seem quite intelligent.
So what's this craze for modelling?
You too are intelligent and
are also in the same business.
So the comparison is with me...
It's not like that...
It doesn't matter.
I judge people by their ambition.
Really, so what do you think of me?
You've hardly told me
anything about yourself...
What can I say?
Like thousands of girls...
I too want to be a successful model.
- But there's a small difference.
- What's that?
That I'm better than the rest.
That you are.
- Come, let's go.
- Yes.
You know you're very lucky,
Meghna... What?
You've been meeting these people...
Kartik... Sarin.
The formula to this business is...
the right timing, knowing the right
people and the right publicity.
I've thought about it.
I will feature you in Leena Mehta's show.
- Really? Yeah.
- It is a big show.
Everything is happening so quickly...
... don't get overconfident.
This is just the first step.
Everything depends on what
you make of this opportunity.
And, where you want to go from here.
I know where I want to reach.
- Shona...
- Ritu? Why is she calling you?
- Shona my phone...
- You told me she doesn't call you.
Shona, give me my phone...
- Why did you lie to me?
- Leave my phone.
- Why is she calling you? You fool! You lied to me?
- She needs help.
- Shona, give me my phone.
- Why? - What are you doing?
Are you the only one who can help her?
- Shona...
- You bastard, you are doing it again. You are lying to me.
- Let me talk to her. I need to talk to her.
- Shona, leave it.
Shona!
You fool! I have a show tomorrow.
Come on, Shona. I told you
there is nothing like that.
She just needs help.
This is my Avant-garde collection.
It's completely different
from my earlier work.
I mean, this collection is inspired
by my childhood memories.
My mother, my grandmother!
You will see influences
of those images.
I don't know how it is going to be...
... accepted, but it is very special to me.
What's this? Made in Bangkok.
At least she should have taken
off the label before the show.
She gets it from the
Indra market in Bangkok...
and calls it her
Avant-garde collection.
Some designer.
Darling, you are looking beautiful.
Look here...
- Slowly, it hurts.
- Sorry.
Salim, darling.
I am the show stopper.
Come overfor my make-up
or should I stop the show?
- Can you just finish it by yourself?
- It is okay.
Thank you.
Yes, darling.
- You look sad.
- Not at all.
Would you like to go back?
No. Let'sjust do your make-up.
Please, show me. Show me.
Next... next.
- This?
- Yes. Print this.
- Okay.
- Thank you, bye.
Okay, ma'am. No problem.
Chandu, why are you
clicking a nobody?
Fool, do you know how
big a socialite she is?
Socialite? Once upon
a time she was a B-grade actress.
Today she is a self proclaimed
socialite and designer.
Are you kidding me?
She is at every function:
Weddings, parties, awards...
She doesn't even spare baby showers.
Are you kidding me?
Baby shower?
Yes, even baby showers.
Delete her pictures. Terrible!
- Oh hi!
- How are you?
I am fine. What brings you here?
Well, I came to meet Leena.
Networking, you know.
I got to know that it is yourfirst show so...
- I came to wish you luck.
- Thanks.
- All the best. - Thanks.
Thank you. - And... - Thanks.
Don't be nervous,
you'll bejust fine, okay?
Pooja... isn't that Madhur Bhandarkar?
What's he doing with Rita?
He's probably doing his research.
He's making a movie on fashion.
He makes realistic films.
He won't even spare
the world of fashion.
Now remember, I want a lot of drama.
- Is that clear?
- Look at the clothes. They are so dramatic.
No expression. I just want you
to look straight, look strong...
... no smiles. Am I clear?
Binal, walk tall and beautiful.
- Meghna. This is a huge show for you.
- Yes.
I want lots of attitude.
Do you understand that?
- Yes... yes, ma'am.
- And Shonali... Shonali.
Yes, yes. I know, I am listening.
Alright. Great. Okay girls,
let's go out there and kill them.
Are you ready?
Come on. Let's go.
Okay girls, come on. Stand in a line.
Come on, we are ready
to start the show. Come on.
Yes, okay. Okay, she is on. She is on.
- Get out!
- Go Shonali, go.
Please, go.
"I shall give up my life. "
"For your love, I shall give up my life. "
"Your Kohl enchants me. "
"It's the time to fall in love. "
"I shall give up my life. "
"For your love, I shall give up my life. "
That was such an impressive show.
You were fantastic as always, Shonali.
Thank you so much.
Panache is extremely proud of you.
You are the face of Panache.
We'll have to extend your contract.
Oh, come on Abhi,
stop discussing work.
Shonali, join us for a drink.
- Come on...
- Yes, come on.
- Come on, let's go.
- Okay.
No. Really. Really.
Wasn't that amazing?
- She just walked on.
- Thank you.
And beyond looked at...
- You were fantastic, fabulous.
- Really?
- Really.
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
What grace... what poise... oh my God.
I was so nervous. Janet Sequeira!
- Rahul Arora!
- Oh my God.
- How long it has been?
- Six years.
Look at you.
How much weight have
you lost since college?
I had to diet to become a model.
And dieting made me like this.
You and diet?
- You know... Rohit, right?
- Yes.
- You know... when we were in college...
During college she used
to carry a box of sugar candy.
Sugar! Calories!
We all used laugh at her.
Should I reveal your secrets?
- Oh... no secrets, okay?
- Okay.
- Besides I am very upset with you.
- Why?
You are a model now and
you didn't even bother to call.
Rahul, you know this business.
You are an A list designer
and I'm a struggling B list model.
How could I call?
- You know it is not like that with me, right?
- Yes, I know...
- Give me a call.
- I will.
Okay, by the way meet my friend, Meghna.
- Hi... - Nice meeting you.
- Rahul Arora.
- Yes, of course. I've heard...
- You were great on the ramp.
Good confidence.
Good presence. Right?
- Thank you. Thank you so much. Bye.
- I will. Bye.
- You know him? You never told us.
- Yes. Well...
- Hi Christine.
- Hi, Christine.
Well done, Meghna.
Such good confidence in yourfirst show...
- ... l'm really impressed.
- Really?
I am sure, you'll go a long way. Bye.
Did you hearthat Meghna darling?
You will go a long way.
Very well done. Very well done.
- I told you so.
- Imagine.
After many trials and troubles
I reached a place...
... where I could see my dream
taking shape clearly.
But myjourney ahead went
through strange phases.
Old relationships though
near seemed far away.
And new relationships
started growing closer.
This restaurant is really posh, Meghna.
We are going to get a huge bill.
Just relax and order.
- It's very...
- Its okay.
- Hey Rahul! Hi! How are you?
- Hi!
- How are you doing?
- Very well.
- Do you know, Meghna... Manav...
- Hi.
- Rohit...
- Hi... this is Ashish.
- Hi. - Hi. - Nice meeting you.
Why don't you guys join us?
Yes, sure. Sure.
- Sure.
- Okay.
- Excuse me. Two chairs, please.
- Yes.
- Sure, sir.
- You haven't changed a bit.
- Why do you say that?
I wasjust being polite and
you actuallyjoined us.
- How rude.
- I can't believe this.
You know, throughout college,
I used to foot her canteen bills.
So I thought it was payback time today.
- To say...
- By the way...
Unfortunately, it's Meghna's treat.
- Oh, I am sorry.
- Yes, this is my treat.
Come on, let's order starters guys.
- Hi...
- Hi.
- Can I ask you something?
- Sure
Do you have a brother
or cousin who looks...
... just like you do.
- Sorry, bad luck.
- No... - Oh no!
Listen, you do know that...
the venue for tomorrows rehearsal has
changed, don't you?
It's Four Seasons now.
- Anyways, thanks for telling me.
- Oh no, not at all.
- Bye.
- Bye, take care.
- See you. Bye.
Santosh...
It's two in the morning, Meghna.
You've been coming in late every night.
You should be a little more responsible.
Even the neighbours are complaining.
This can't continue here.
I'm sorry, aunt, but my job keeps me...
I know what it keeps you at.
Divya brought this to
show us from the neighbors.
What influence will it have on her?
Meghna, we can't let your career be...
... a negative influence on Divya.
I suggest you...
... look for alternate accommodation.
Santosh, it's so late in the night...
She doesn't need to leave immediately.
She can leave after a couple of days.
It's okay aunt...
I'll leave right away.
- Janet.
- Hi, how are you?
- Hi... sorry to call you so late.
- What?
I'm on my way to Goa.
Is everything all right?
Anything urgent,
message me, darling.
No. Nothing at all.
- Okay, yes. Bye.
- Okay. Bye. See you.
I left home in a huff but
I didn't know where to go.
Janet is in Goa and
Rohit stays with his parents.
I don't know anyone else in Mumbai.
I'm really sorry but...
There is no need for an explanation.
I'm glad that you called.
It's only fortonight.
I'll look for another place tomorrow.
Meghna, this is Mumbai.
You may find God but not accommodation.
That too, a single woman...
... a model, no way.
Yes, there is one place though...
... where you can share an apartment.
- Where?
- Here.
Actually, I was looking
for a room mate.
I don't have regular work...
... and the rent is too high.
So, if you don't mind.
We can share this apartment.
But Manav, both of us...
... in the same apartment...
... won't it be awkward?
Come on Meghna,
this isn't Chandigarh.
I mean, no one cares.
Rent, provisions...
we'll share the expenses.
We can share everything...
... but the bedrooms will be separate, right?
Of course! They will be separate,
you can be sure of that.
- Okay.
Okay, great! Welcome home.
Anisha, I'm sorry I had to call you.
Where is Shonali?
The entire unit has been
waiting fortwo hours...
... there is no sign of her.
This has become a habit.
- Please, help me. Please do something now.
- Oh no!
Tony, give me two minutes.
- Shonali...
- She is in there.
Shonali... come out of there.
Come out, right now!
What's your problem Anisha?
The entire unit has been
waiting fortwo hours...
It's a big ad film shoot,
for heaven sake.
And you are back
to this awful habit.
You better buck up, Shonali.
This is the third complaint.
Our clients pay a lot of
money for your time.
It's only because of
my agency and my reputation...
... that's the reason you
stand here today.
If you don' take control of yourself...
... then there are several others
who are eager to replace you. Got it?
- Don't worry...
- Megha, Gauri...
If she misbehaves,
call me up again.
"Temptation next. "
No... don't argue Koko.
I know exactly...
... what's going to be good on you,
okay? Trust me.
Vinay, isn't this a bit over the top?
I mean... just look at this.
You are about to do
Bobby Chopra's film in Europe.
- And today everything is about looking glamorous. Okay?
- Yes, but.
You guys do very realistic films and...
Yes, I mean, this is mainstream
cinema and you have to look hot.
I am the only one who can make
you look hot. Okay? Period.
I don't know, Vinay.
- According to my character graph, I mean...
- Dear, no...
Ranveer, just help me. Just look.
Koko, the amount the producer is
spending on your clothes...
exceeds the total budget
of this film production.
So if you're done arguing,
can we rehearse?
The entire unit has been
waiting fortwo hours...
... and a lot of people work on daily wages.
- Wages.
- Okay, Vinay, whatever.
Come on, roll the camera.
- Its fine, I surrender.
- Baby, trust me. You'll rock.
- Really?
- You doubt Vinay Khosla? Come on, baby.
Come on, take it.
Hey Manav, whom are you paired
with in Anamika's show?
I have been paired with Rajneesh.
Not anymore.
What do you mean?
Now your entry is along with me.
We open the show together now.
Really? But how come?
Because our choreographer believes...
... that we make a great pair.
And I agree.
"It's special. "
"It's an unusual feeling. "
"Some distance, closeness...
... keeps my loneliness away. "
"Is it love?"
"Is it trust? Maybe it's love. "
"This is blossoms. This waiting... "
"Maybe it's love. "
"It's special. "
"It's an unusual feeling. "
"Some distance, closeness...
... keeps my loneliness away. "
"Is it love?"
"Is it trust? Maybe it's love. "
"This is blossoms. This waiting... "
"Maybe it's love. "
"What to say?"
"Show your heart someone close to you. "
"I had a condition. "
"I feel I have won this lost round. "
"This is impatient waiting... "
"Maybe it's love. "
"It's magic. "
"Something is special. "
"It's an unusual feeling. "
"Maybe it's love. "
- Just see...
- Let me read.
Forget what you are reading.
Just look at that.
- Please give me the phone.
- No.
- Give me the phone.
- No way, please.
Forget your phone.
Oh hi, Anisha.
Where are you?
At home.
Sarin wants to see you immediately.
Right now?
No questions Meghna.
Please go over right now.
Okay, I'll go. Bye.
- Meghna, please come.
- Oh... come.
Anisha told me... I had to rush...
to come to see you... in the office.
I've brought my portfolio along.
I also have it on CD.
If you want to have a look.
There's no need forthis.
Would you like to be a show stopper?
It's for Vinay Khosla.
The show is in four days.
You think you'll be able to do it?
- Vinay Khosla?
- Yes.
- Oh my God, you mean 'The Vinay Khosla? '
- That's right.
Yes, of course. Thank you.
For the first time,
- I don't have a single Bollywood
starlet in the front row. - So sad.
Half of them are doing shows and...
- ... the other half are abroad.
- Oh what a pity?
What's happening with
the new girl? Is she ready?
- Just two minutes. - No, no.
You go and check. Go. Go! - Okay.
I've got a very huge offer.
Ladies and gentlemen,
kindly take your seat.
The show is about to begin.
Darling, you look gorgeous.
And you are biased.
No, no Meghna. It goes over.
But it looks so much cooler here.
She is an absolute new girl.
And a show stopper?
- And handsome looks. Handsome looks, okay? - Okay.
- I just hope she is good. I just hope.
- Okay.
- I am so stressed. I am so stressed. This is not funny. - Relax.
Sarin's recommendation and all that.
Anyway, I'll just... where is Rohit?
- Just you know...
- Where is Rohit?
Meghna, you should... because...
- Meghna, I was telling you...
- Rohit.
Oh what the... who the hell
has done it like this?
It is supposed to go
above the head, no?
- Rohit... Duffer...
- Yes...
You know how particular I am.
Actually... It's not his fault.
I told him.
You?
I thought that if...
Hold it. You thought?
Darling, you are a model.
You don't need to
use your brains, okay?
Spare me the horror.
- Fix the lousy thing, Rohit.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
It's such an insignificant thing...
What did you say?
An insignificant thing?
This is the show stopper outfit.
Do you understand that?
The media will be watching.
All of them.
And even if you sell yourself,
you can't afford this dress. Alright?
And listen,
I really don't care about...
... your relationship with Sarin.
I don't want supermodel nonsense.
My relationship with Sarin?
- You have no right to say that.
- Oh yeah? Really?
I don't have a right?
In my show?
Do you even know, who I am?
Vinay Khosla...
and nobody talks to me like that.
Rohit, tell Christina I am
replacing this girl right now.
Change the whole thing.
Send four girls in the end.
Change the finale. I don't care.
And you! Out of this outfit and leave! Out!
- But sir... No... no...
- What! - Nothing, sir.
Come on, now all of you get on with it.
Come on, back to work.
No wonder we models are
treated like hangers.
Okay girls, listen. Quickly listen.
There's been a change, alright?
I want the last four girls
to end the sequence.
The last four girls being Geeta...
you right?
- What about that young girl?
- Don't know about her.
Thank you. Excuse me.
Sir, there is a problem backstage.
I think you should come.
Okay. Excuse me.
What the hell.
She has ruined the whole show.
- What's the problem, Vinay?
- She's arrogant.
Why don't you ask him?
- Don't believe me, then...
- Alright. - Sarin...
Meghna!
Meghna, you still have those bangles...
We need them back...
I am sorry. I am sorry.
- I am really sorry about this.
- It's okay.
How could he think that I...
Calm down, Meghna.
People say stuff when they're angry.
You could've controlled yourself.
So it was my fault?
Do you even know what he said?
Listen, I know it wasn't your fault.
Besides he is a veteran designer
and you are new to modelling.
Does that mean he can say
whatever he wants?
So what if he is a reputed designer?
I'm no average model either.
Come on, I know, Meghna.
You'll never understand.
Tell me Anisha...
... when is Shonali's contract up for renewal?
There is time yet.
Five months I think, why?
Terminate her contract.
Right now!
But Sarin, we can't do that.
Why not?
Panache is my company
and I can do whatever I want.
But... it's a contract.
I mean...
... it hasn't expired as yet.
Give Shonali full compensation...
... in fact give her a little more...
... so that there are no complaints.
- But...
- No questions. Just do it.
But on what grounds?
Come on, Anisha.
You are smart.
You'll think of something.
I am sure.
I don't understand,
why, Anisha? Why?
I warned you a couple of times earlier...
... but you didn't listen.
Three official complaints!
Ultimately professionalism counts.
Come on Anisha,
I know this profession.
Three complaints and I am out?
It's not just that, Shonali.
Your lifestyle...
... your boyfriends...
... your addiction and
misbehaviour at parties.
It's affecting the brands,
especially Panache.
This was bound to happen someday.
Anyway...
I didn't want to be unfair.
The compensation is higher.
If there is anything that
you want to add to the termination
clause, go ahead.
Just one question.
Who has replaced me?
Meghna Mathur.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen
and my friends from the media.
This is the moment we've
all been waiting for.
Allow me to introduce to you,
the sensational new face
of Panache... Meghna Mathur.
- So glamorous. So nervous.
- I know.
- But he was so good...
- Excuse me.
I am going to take her
away for a minute.
- Yes, sure. Sure.
- I'll just be back. - Yes, sure.
- Hi.
- I want to introduce you to...
- Avantika... Meet Meghna Mathur.
- Yes.
- This is Avantika Sarin.
- Oh hi.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Lovely to meet you Meghna.
All the very best and
welcome to Panache.
Thank you so much.
In no time my dreams
turned into reality...
... and they reached the sky.
My new image as a super
model everywhere...
... gave me a new high.
I felt like the whole world
was interested in no one but me.
I got lost in myself.
Knowing what I wear...
what I eat... what I think...
possibly made people think
that they know me.
I too was lost in myself.
But I... I just had one obsession.
What would be my next
move to attain more success...
- What's so different in the soup?
- I have no idea.
On the salad.
- Hey guys. I am really sorry.
- Hi.
- Hi...
You are so late, baby. You knew
this dinner was planned, right?
Yes, but the campaign is about
to begin and you know how it is.
I am sorry guys, I'll be right
back from the loo in five minutes.
There she goes.
Come, come. Sit, sit.
We'll be here.
Hi Shonali.
Congratulations... for Panache.
Thanks, Shonali.
Look, I hope you understand,
there's nothing personal.
- I didn't know that, its going to...
- Don't worry.
Neither did I...
It's this industry...
... you never know when
the designs are outdated.
- No thanks.
- Smart, but be careful.
You're still new.
Everything feels good in the beginning...
... the novelty eventually wears out.
I can see it in your eyes.
You will neither recognise
yourself nor anyone else.
Be very careful.
Thanks Shonali, but I recognise...
Myself...
and others as well.
We'll see.
- It's really taking... - As I told you,
Meghna, this is just the beginning.
- Yes...
- See, how things go.
- Hi, Mr. Sarin...
- Nice to meet you.
Our new face of Panache,
Meghna Mathur.
- Meghna, that is Manohar Grover.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Meet Mr. Stevens. That's his beautiful wife.
- Hello.
- Hello. - Hi.
- Mrs. Chang, Meghna Mathur.
- Pleased to meet you.
- How are you doing?
- That's Mr. Harper.
- Hi. - Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- He's a whiz kid.
Oh!
Cheers.
Alright, then.
If we wait any longer...
I'll have to head to
office from here only.
- Let's go.
- Yes. Come.
No, that's it. You can stop here.
- Thank you.
- You are welcome.
I'll get down.
- Thank you, good night.
- Good night, bye. - Bye.
Bye.
I know... I know.
Even I know the time.
- Meghna...
- Look Manav not now, I am really tired, okay?
Meghna, I was worried.
I tried calling you all night.
The phone was on silent
and in the bag.
I don't know. Oh God, Manav...
You knew I was with
Mr. Sarin at a party.
Listen, but you could have
sent me a text message.
- I would have if I could have.
- You are right.
Meghna, this is the fourth time.
I am a model too. I know.
Exactly! You're a model too,
so I thought you would understand...
but obviously not.
There were so many people at the party...
Sarin was introducing me to
the media, so I was... I couldn't.
And you forgot that
someone's waiting for you...
Manav, these are really important people.
You won't understand the pressures.
- Really? So make me.
- How do I?
You aren't in that league.
You are still struggling.
Meghna, I am really happy
that you are in the big league.
But have you thought about
the price you're paying for that?
A lecture at four in the morning!
I am lecturing you because
not everybody can handle success.
Is that so?
Then tell me...
... why are those
who preach about success...
... only those who haven't tasted it yet?
Because they don't run after it insanely.
And what if Mr. Sarin were promoting you?
Why would he?
He's promoting you, isn't he?
Who knows what he is getting in return...
I can't believe you just said that.
How typical, Manav.
I don't know why,
but I thought you were different.
I'd also thought the same about you.
"Something is special. It's close to me. "
"It's an unusual feeling. "
"This closeness has a distance. "
"There is loneliness in the air. "
"The love we have, the trust... "
"Maybe it was love. "
"It was blossom. "
For Meghna, I am the final word
Mr. Agarwal. Okay, bye.
So many signatures, Anisha.
Is it necessary to read everything?
- Just go through it once.
- No way.
No way. It's your agency's
contract. I trust you.
Where do I need to sign?
Okay. On all these pages, initials.
- What?
- And here... full signature.
It is a tough task ahead for you.
I am warning you.
What's the point?
I am the best.
And you know that.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Oh hi. - Listen, I am sending you a car, come over immediately.
Right now?
- No questions do as I say.
- Okay.
- Sarin?
- Yes.
Sign it later.
Thanks.
Come. Come...
This way.
Come.
Surprise.
It's fabulous.
I hope you like your new house.
It's yours.
I...
Mr. Sarin. I'll take it.
"Abode. "
"I have got it. "
"The goal of my destiny. "
"Why are you common?"
"I have no complaints. "
"A little intoxicated is my life. "
"This is my abode. "
"It's my youth. "
"I have no time for myself. "
You should come to the Gurudwara
occasionally, it feels good.
- Gurpreet?
- Kuldeep?
- How are you?
- I'm fine.
- Greetings.
- Greetings, dear.
What happened about the photographs
that Mrs. Sethi had sent?
No aunty, I don't want to
get married right now.
Don't want to get married?
My daughter mentioned...
that these fashion designers
don't get married.
Is it true?
So are you also...
Aunt, these days, people
sayjust about anything.
How is Dolly, your elder daughter?
The one that got married in London.
I heard she is divorced...
... and now she's living with you.
Is it true?
Come on, let's go.
You'll run out of answers
but their questions won't stop.
- Mom...
- Yes...
It's your life, your decision.
Mom?
Rahul, I'm nervous.
I never thought I'd be the show
stopper for such a big show.
- And today thanks to you...
- Enough now.
Now don't get into your
teenage drama queen mode...
You very well know that you can do it...
... or you wouldn't have agreed.
Rahul... you know...
I agreed because
I can never say no to you.
Thank you forthat.
- You look lovely. - Thank you. - Okay?
And you rock! - Thank you.
Ria! How are you doing here?
Ladies and Gentlemen,
please welcome Rahul Arora.
Who has brought us
the lovely brand La Perla!
It was very funny.
- You're back.
- Yes.
So, what did you ask of Him?
I wasn't here to ask.
I came to thank Him.
Janet, yesterday, backstage
you told me something.
Did you really mean it?
What?
That you can never say no to me.
Of course Rahul, you know that.
- Janet Sequeira.
- Yes. - Will you marry me?
You are such an idiot.
I thought you were serious.
I am. I am serious.
Janet, will you marry me?
Listen, I don't know
whether it's right or wrong.
But I do know this...
... if anyone can understand me...
... it's only you.
What about your boyfriend?
I have spoken to him.
When you can't come
out with the truth...
... it's time to live a lie.
There are a lot of people
who live like us.
So shall we.
And as they say...
it is difficult to find
a good friend in a husband.
But you will surely find
a good husband in a good friend.
So?
You know my answer.
You know I can never say no to you.
Oh God, you scared me.
How sweet?
- See you. Let's go.
- Let's go. - Please, come.
- Hi Leena.
- Hi Leena. - Hi!
- Hi Meghna.
- Hi, Mr. Sarin.
- Hello Meghna.
- Hi.
So, everyone is talking about you.
Don't worry, they're
saying good things.
Abhi is taking good
care of you, isn't he?
After all, you are
so important to Panache.
- Of course. Bye.
- Bye.
- See you, Meghna.
Bye.
What was that?
That it. For you.
Attention. Attention, please.
Attention, please.
Ladies and gentlemen,
attention, please.
I... I want to raise a toast.
Today is Rahul's wedding...
... and I'm very happy.
I want to congratulate Rahul
and his beautiful wife.
Thank you.
- Hi wife... wife...
- Janet.
Janet... Janet, right.
Janet is a beautiful girl
and Rahul is a great guy.
- Cheers, guys!
- Cheers!
Cheers!
Kartik, this is the kind
of look I want, okay?
Vinay, you will get any look you want,
but please call your model.
Come on, guys. I am ready.
- Does anyone want to shoot or not?
- Yes, of course.
- Vinay.
- Yes.
I thought of holding
the drape like this.
I know you are very particular
about your drapes.
If you don't like it we can change it.
- No. It is absolutely fine. You are looking gorgeous.
- Thanks.
- Don't be silly.
- I thought so.
What are you standing here for!
- Go and get the next thing
ready duffer. - Sir... - Go!
Come on, Vinay, let's hurry up.
It's been two hours and
we haven't taken a single shot.
Meghna... darling are you ready?
Why are you getting
so hyper, Kartik?
Anyway, what do you have to do?
Except change the background colours.
Oh God. Just ignore her, okay?
Okay guys, come on guys.
Come on, let's get ready.
Anybody for some more drinks?
I think that's enough, baby.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Shona... Do you love me?
- Yes, I love you.
- How much?
- A lot...
- Really?
She loves me.
Drink this.
Come on, drink it.
Come on, Shona.
Are you joking?
I am serious, Shona.
Come on. Come on.
- Listen... Come on.
- Please, pal.
She loves me. Don't you, baby?
Come on now, drink it.
Don't be shy. Drink it.
Drink it, Shona. Come on. Drink it.
Get lost from here!
- Hey!
- Don't touch me, you fool!
- Stop being a lousy woman! I was joking!
- You were joking!
You insult me in front of your...
... friends and then say you were joking.
You fool!
Who funds your expenses?
Who pays all your bills?
Do yourfriends know about this?
Have you told them?
- Or should I tell them?
- Listen man!
You don't do me any favour
by funding my expenses.
Who gets you your dope?
I do.
Who handles your craziness?
I do!
You are a crazy woman,
you know that?
A crazy woman.
Don't call me crazy, you fool!
Get lost!
What rubbish,
I don't need a Bollywood...
... star when I have you, come on.
This is your place.
Make yourself comfortable here.
- Okay?
- Thanks Vinay.
- And...
- Oh. - Who has done this?
Sorry, dear. Yes, I've organized
some wine for you, I'll just check.
Yes? Alright, thanks.
Salim, leave everything right now
and attend to Meghna.
Come on, fast.
- Shonali... you first change.
- Yes.
- Kuki...
- Hi.
I told you I want more
options for earrings, right?
I won't wear such tacky earrings.
Meghna, everyone has the same look.
All the models are wearing
the same earrings.
So... I am the show stopper tonight.
- Make it happen...
- Fine.
Yes, thank you.
Move... move... please move aside.
Shonali is here, help her.
Please, get me a stole. Quickly.
Please, get me a stole, someone.
Swati, will you please get me a stole?
Right now!
Come Shonali, sit. Sit.
What's wrong with her?
Girls, will you please go
for yourfinale? Line up, please.
Calm down Shonali. Calm down.
Stop the media from coming inside!
Just relax.
- Oh God...
- Calm down, Shonali.
Shonali, please. Just relax.
It will be okay. Just calm down.
It has to be my rivals.
They are trying to sabotage my show.
This is not happening to me.
No. No. No media bites.
No, please.
I'm not in a frame of mind to comment.
Spare me the horror.
Please, no. No.
The media should
show some restraint.
Shonali is really disturbed.
No, I don't think Shonali Gujral...
... will do something like this for publicity.
It's very unfortunate,
but it is only an accident.
There is no need to hype it
and create an issue of it.
Down with fashion shows!
Don't ruin our culture!
As far as Vinay Khosla's
show is concerned...
whether this was an
accident or publicity stunt...
Only Shonali can confirm.
You havejust seen what
Meghna Mathur had to say.
She herself is a model
the same Meghna Mathur,
who is the brand
ambassador of Panache.
Could this be a personal conflict?
Or anything else?
Let's see again, what
Meghna Mathur has to say...
... about her rival Shonali Gujral.
Whether this was an
accident or publicity stunt...
Only Shonali can confirm.
Did you see the story about Shonali on TV?
Don't know for how long
she will have to stay there.
- Really sad.
- Yes.
Janet, have you given it a thought?
Rahul, I am still thinking.
To adopt a child considering our situation?
Janet, but...
Yes, Rahul.
It's a huge responsibility.
I promise, I'll think it over.
- Take your time.
- Yes.
How is Ashish doing?
Rocking.
He's gone off to Chennai...
- ... to do a show with Manish.
- Lovely.
- Your drink.
- Thank you.
Why can't you come with me
on this three city tour?
Abhi, after all,
it is a Panache event.
I mean, we will be together too.
What's wrong with you, Meghna?
You know it is not possible.
Where did this come from?
There's something I want to tell you.
Go on...
- I am pregnant.
- That's all.
Not to worry, it can be handled.
And what if I tell you...
... that I want to keep the baby.
Sure... I am okay with it.
I don't have a problem...
... but Anisha might have a problem.
You have signed a contract.
Abhi, at times you are really funny.
I wasjust kidding...
... and you took it seriously.
I am a really successful model.
I won't ruin my career.
Come, I'll make you another drink.
Yes, my love.
I'm on my way home.
No. I dined with the client.
Have the children slept?
Yes, see you soon.
Page 20, clause 22 A.
We will get twenty percent
of your earnings.
Clause 31 C.
You can't do any endorsement
or make an appearance...
... without our permission.
And finally Clause 36.
Officially you can
neither get married...
... nor get pregnant.
Till the contract is valid.
You know what... I don't care!
Whom are you calling?
Sarin?
It is no use, my dear.
Sarin put in these clauses in
the contract himself.
Are you okay?
I am fine.
I went back to being a middle
class girl for a while.
But I am fine.
I am fine.
Whose pregnancy do you
want to get terminated?
Mine.
- Are you married? Okay.
- No.
- Just fill up this form.
- Can I borrow your pen?
Stop! Stop!
Madam, you are driving
without the seat belt.
License?
Listen, I don't have much time, so...
Alright. Take the car aside.
Sir, license.
Surekha, take the test.
I am not going to take that dirty test, okay?
Who knows how many people
have put it in their mouth.
Listen madam.
It doesn't matter whether you are
a model, an actor or anybody else...
I don't care.
Surekha, take the test.
Our daughter has done us proud.
The one who climbed
the stairs of success so soon.
Why are you crying?
Look, your daughter is now a super model.
Now our neighbours will come
with flowers, to a proud mother.
Meghna, your reckless behaviour is
not only damaging your reputation...
... but Panache's too.
I know you are upset.
But learn to keep your personal life
apart from your professional life.
Really?
Tell me something, Abhi.
What about our relationship...
... is it personal or professional?
Don't worry.
You don't have to answer that.
It is time to get truly
professional Mr. Sarin.
- Yes... - Had you been to his last season?
- No, I haven't, but I...
I am telling you, the food should...
- No thank you.
- Yes, she is very charming.
- I will.
- Cheers.
That's not fair.
- Lovely!
- Exactly.
- Hey, I'll be right back.
- Sure.
How I managed to put this show together.
- It was hell...
- Whatever, third big launch of the year.
Thank you very much.
- Tony...
- Hi.
Congratulations.
I am so sorry I came late.
No, it's alright. You made it at least.
- Cheers.
- Bye.
- Excuse me.
- Yes. - See you.
Johnny, hi.
- Hi Meghna.
- Abhi...
I think you have taken
my words too seriously.
You have become so professional...
... that you are uneasy greeting me.
Behave yourself. You are drunk.
I am drunk?
- Hello, Meghna.
- Mrs. Sarin.
So, how are you now?
I saw all that drama on television.
What happened?
You look so stressed out.
Didn't you tell her?
Actually, I wasn't well.
I was in a clinic.
I had an abortion.
Abhi will give you the details.
After all... he paid the bills.
Oh! She got offended.
I'm telling you again Meghna,
it's still not too late.
Avantika is very upset...
... but I think we can handle it.
Just meet her once and apologise.
If she forgives you,
everything will be sorted.
I should apologise to her?
Are you kidding me?
Who is she, Anisha?
Just some lousy trophy wife...
I don't need her.
Of course, you need her, Meghna.
You're in this position due to Panache.
You are signing brands courtesy of Panache.
You need them!
Wrong, Anisha.
I am the freaking face of Panache.
I don't need Panache,
Panache needs me. Okay?
Anything else?
- Yes.
- What the hell is going on, Anisha?
- Where the hell have you been?
- Shut up!
I just read the paper.
Come on, Meghna.
This had to happen.
I told you so.
Oh, cut the crap, Anisha.
Gauri Anand is from your agency.
I've been replaced.
Don't be such a lousy woman.
There's no need to get personal, Meghna.
Personal? I can't believe you did this to me.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
When we replaced Shonali...
... you didn't ask me this.
I really think you should...
The sound of a shattered
dream never hurts...
... as much as it's lasting echo.
My career started falling
like a pack of cards...
... and I stood there,
a mere spectator.
Everything changed...
home, relationships...
... and along with them I changed too.
Commitment, sincerity, professionalism...
I ran away from all of them...
... and reached a place so loud...
... that I couldn't even hear myself.
What I was doing, why I was doing it...
I had no clue at all.
Shonali was right,
I couldn't even recognize myself.
Go easy, Meghna.
You've had a lot to drink.
You're saying that, Janet!
Look, I don't know how to lecture.
But I can say this much,
you're ruining yourself.
You are right.
You don't know how to lecture,
so please don't try.
Meghna, everyone I meet is
talking about your arrogance.
It is not arrogance,
baby. It is attitude.
It's important to have an
attitude to be successful.
- Okay?
- Oh, really?
What about unprofessionalism?
Is that necessary too?
Listen, if you continue to...
... behave like this no one
will want to work with you.
Unprofessional?
Did you just call me
unprofessional, Janet?
What do you know
about professionalism?
You don't become a model by doing
a couple of small assignments.
Listen... I know I didn't make it big.
But I have spent more time in this industry.
I know why your reputation is getting ruined.
That's why I'm telling you...
... straighten up before everything crumbles.
Straighten up?
How?
Should I beg Sarin or Anisha?
I know what I can do.
I should marry a rich gay designer like you.
How about that?
Leave. Just leave.
- Hey.
- Hi babes. Where are you?
We all are waiting for you.
Come to Dhiren's party fast now.
Yes, I'll be there.
- Give me 20 minutes.
- Okay.
"Charm. "
"It's the charm of the body. "
"It's the ladder to success. "
"Charm. "
"It's the charm of fashion. "
"It's intoxicating. "
"Charm. It's the charm of the body. "
"Here love is on fire. "
"Charm. "
"Charm. It's the charm of fashion. "
"It's the charm of fashion. "
"It keeps asking. It's amazing. "
"No one could undo it. "
"This charm. Heavens bow to the earth. "
"This charm. "
"It sparks fire in the heart. "
"It's the charm of fashion. "
"This charm. It's the charm of fashion. "
"Charm. "
Meghna...
Dear...
We become totally isolated...
... when we lose our own company.
I came back home to Chandigarh...
... but I could never be myself.
Leaving all my relationships behind...
I descended into my inner darkness.
I neither felt happy nor sad.
The psychiatrist advised...
... that nothing is possible until...
I rediscover myself and
my inner self confidence.
But as easy as it is to lose oneself...
... it is even more difficult to forgive oneself...
... to find oneself again.
Have you heard anything about Shonali?
I heard that she's run away from rehab.
No one knows her whereabouts.
Yes, that's really sad.
Hey Rahul.
Who is your show stopper for the Delhi show?
I heard thatjust like Vinay Khosla,
you too have roped in a film star.
No, no. I like film stars.
But if there was a model...
- ... for a show stopper for this show... that's best.
- Yes.
You know I... really miss a good model.
- Like Shonali...
- And, Meghna.
Meghna.
Dear...
... the one who loses...
... isn't the one who falls.
But a failure is one...
... who still doesn't rise to the occasion.
My daughter is not a loser.
I'm sorry, my dear.
It was my fault that I...
... didn't trust my daughter's dream...
- ... and how high it could take her.
- Papa...
I had trust in my daughter...
... and I still do.
Go ahead, pursue your dream again.
Yes, my dear.
Go back, my dear.
You will achieve success.
Yes, dear.
Go dear, go back.
Thought I'd come and apologise.
But I can't.
Look Janet, I know I really hurt you.
I was wrong.
But when I decided to come back...
I couldn't think of anyone else but you.
So, I came right here.
I did the right thing, didn't I, Janet?
Welcome back.
I am so sorry.
So, you know what... I've now
specifically told all the actors...
You may borrow clothes for
a function, but do return them.
Yes, you know theyjust...
Typical.
Oh my God. Oh my God... listen, listen.
Guess, who is back in town.
Meghna Mathur.
- Wow...
- Back from the dead or what?
Hi Vinay, I am back in town.
I would like to meet you.
Please, let me know
when I can call you.
Spare me the horror.
Who wants to speak to her?
- Guess what?
- What?
Same message.
She's sent it to everyone.
- Desperate.
- I tell you.
You know, she always
compared herself to Shonali.
Mark my words, someday
she will lose it, just like Shonali.
- Bye... - Bye. I'll see you.
- Yes. - For dinner? - Yes.
- Manav, that was excellent.
- Thank you.
- We need a close up.
- Okay.
- Go to the rest room.
- Alright.
- Well, be back in half an hour.
- Sure. - Mahesh!
Set up a trolley.
Make it fast, come on.
You went through a lot in your life...
... but the good thing is
that you have come back.
Listen... don't worry.
Everything is going to be okay.
I am sorry, Manav.
I know I've hurt you a lot.
It's okay.
I'm really happy for you,
today you're in the big league.
- I am really happy...
- Well, hardly.
- Hi baby.
- Oh, hi.
Am I disturbing you?
No, no. Come in. That's fine.
- Meghna, that's Ria.
- Ria, that's Meghna.
- Hi... Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
She is my fiance.
We just got engaged last month.
I heard a lot about you.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you. I... I should go.
- No, no. Please...
- No, really.
Please stay for a while.
Some other time.
- Okay? Congratulations.
- Thanks. - Thanks.
It is said, the people you meet
on your way up to success...
... you encounter them again
on your way down.
It felt really weird.
The relations I left behind in
arrogance of my success...
... have left me and gone way ahead in life.
Everything had changed.
But thank God...
some relationships in life...
don't require an invitation for acceptance.
And this is going to be
your outfit for the show.
- Nice?
- Nice.
It's beautiful.
- Rohit... thank you.
- For what?
For giving me this opportunity.
I know that you didn't have to do it.
And everyone must have
advised you not to.
Who cares...
No one knows you like I do.
Look, if I could have my way,
you would be my show stopper.
But Meghna... the sponsors...
you know how it is.
I know... Rohit I know.
The fact that I'm even in
your show, means a lot.
After all, it is my first show
on comeback and...
Trust me... you are going to rock. Okay?
Hey, are you nervous.
Don't worry... want to drink?
No thanks.
"Some distance is...
... fighting loneliness. "
"Is it love?"
"Is it trust?"
- Meghna...
- Hi.
Meghna, are you okay?
Yes, of course.
Look, don't worry.
You'll be absolutely fine. Okay?
Are you sure?
You are looking gorgeous.
- Sir.
- Yes... - Thanks.
Look, the show stopper has come.
I'll be back in a minute.
- Okay?
- Bye.
Hi, Fabiana. You just tell me,
my assistants are there to help you.
And let's go to the lounge,
yes. Okay, come.
Guess what? I had no clue
and I walked in and then...
... i was...
Okay girls, let's stand in order.
Meghna, you are not here.
You are after Brinal.
- Brinal, stand here...
- I am sorry.
Meghna... Sucheta...
Move... move.
"Something special. "
Okay, listen.
Meena is the next girl, right?
Okay, tell her to come on the head
ramp and take Meghna away.
Listen, this is second
change for Meghna.
Just leave her,
I'll handle her.
Okay, just do the same.
Meghna, just relax, okay?
Meghna, just relax.
Meghna, it is alright. It happens.
It's alright?
I ruined everything, Janet.
I froze on the head ramp.
Do you even understand
what it means?
That means nothing at all.
It happens sometimes.
It doesn't happen, Rahul.
I don't think I have
it in me anymore.
Oh, come on, Meghna.
You were nervous then, that's all.
I mean, you walked
the ramp after a year.
Meghnajust think,
how will your dad feel?
Meghna, relax...
you have to be very strong.
You have to believe in yourself.
You know how this industry works.
There is no room for weakness.
Alright.
- Listen... isn't that Shonali?
- The model?
Just see.
Isn't that Shonali the model?
- How long have you been here?
- Shut up.
- Madam.
- Shut up!
Go away!
Madam, do you know anyone here?
Madam, please tell us.
Do you know anyone here.
People say that she has
been here for the last two days...
and isn't talking to anyone.
Shonali Gujral's distressing story...
highlights another truth
of the fashion industry.
It is evident...
that the profession isn't
as glamorous as it seems.
With cameraman Mahesh Pakhare...
... this is Umesh Kumawat
for Star News, Mumbai.
Listen, Inspector...
... instead of roaming
on the streets...
... instead of making a mockery
in front of the media...
... it is better that
we take her along.
Our NGO will
take good care of her.
Madam, it's a procedure.
Until her family members don't come...
And don't take her along or...
... she doesn't say anything.
We can't let you take her.
Madam, do you know her?
Yes, I do.
Meghna, it's a huge responsibility.
You yourself are struggling.
Can you afford to look
after her as well?
I haven't thought about it, Janet.
All I know is...
I'm not doing it for Shonali...
... but for myself.
I really need to do this.
Okay.
After bringing Shonali
home I realized...
... that our lives were quite similar.
Both of us had lost ourselves.
The happiness I achieved in helping...
... Shonali come back to a normal life...
was more important than the happiness
of professional success.
As she got better, I regained
the self confidence I had lost.
Listen, listen.
Breaking news.
My darling Rahul has bagged
the finale at the fashion week.
- Cheers.
- That's fantastic.
- Wow, Rahul. That's fantastic.
- Cheers.
- The biggest show ever.
- Thank you. Thank you.
In fact everything was
finalised yesterday.
Tie a line of top models
and a surprise show stopper.
Who is the show stopper?
Like Vinay Khosla's...
Rohit... you know in fact
she is the best right now.
Ms. Meghna Mathur.
Surprise!
Yeah.
Guys, I don't think that's
a good idea. I mean...
After what happened
at Rohit's show...
I don't think that's a good idea.
We've given this
a lot of thought.
I know you'll are doing this for me.
I mean, I really appreciate it.
I do, I am really grateful, but.
But... I... can't do your show Rahul.
I am sorry. I am sorry.
Why don't you want to do the show?
Please.
You do know how important
this show is for you, don't you?
Come on, Shonali.
You do know what happened
during Rohit's show?
This show is very
important for Rahul.
I can't let the same thing
happen to him too, you know.
Meghna, you aren't
worried for Rahul...
... but you're afraid of failing again.
Rahul has so much confidence in you...
... isn't it fair...
... to prove him right?
You can do it.
We have lost a lot here.
I know there's no hope for me.
- Shonali...
- But if this show helps you make a comeback...
It is worth the risk.
I have never interfered
in your decisions.
So why do it now?
Because, I am concerned.
To make Meghna the show
stopper for such an important show...
... it's foolishness!
And you know
what she did at Rohit's show.
I don't think she has
it in her, anymore.
Look Rahul, try and understand.
The situation is different.
People from the Paris Fashion
Week are coming to see the finale.
If there is any problem in this show.
Then Paris is out of the question.
It could be disastrous
for you and for my brand.
Abhijeet, I know you
care about me, but...
I think you are overreacting.
Nothing of that sort will happen.
Maybe you are right.
But is it necessary to take
such a big risk forthis show?
There are other shows,
give her a chance there.
No, Abhijeet. It'll be too late then.
I mean, Meghna needs
our help right now.
Look, I know what I am doing.
Just trust me.
You think about it.
Oh!!
The Kimaya Fashion Week
has begun with a controversy.
Bollywood's ace
designer Vinay Khosla...
has accused upcoming designer
Zulfi Khan with stealing his designs.
Zulfi has copied all my designs.
I had designed them for a film,
which he has stolen from there.
I can show you the DVD.
Side... side, please.
Rohit's driver will come
to pick you up from the airport.
- Come directly to the venue. Okay?
- Did you have dinner?
No, I havejust returned
from a fitting session.
Okay dear, take care of yourself.
We will be there.
- Okay.
- Bye. - Bye.
Shonali!
Oh no.
Shonali...
- One second.
- Okay. - Yes, Meghna.
Janet, Shonali isn't at home.
The house is a mess.
Don't know what to do?
Relax, Meghna. Take it easy.
- What is it?
- We'll be there soon.
Who are these people?
Who are they?
Hi. Biren...
Hi... have you seen Shonali around?
Did she come here?
Why would she come here?
Desperate woman!
She hasn't paid me five thousand
for the stuff as yet.
She's probably lying
around on the streets.
Okay, thanks.
Let's go.
Shinde, pay attention.
If you get any information,
call immediately.
Alright.
We've sent out a search party.
Look, don't panic.
We have your number.
If we get any information...
... we will call you.
- But...
- Relax.
Sir, please try your best.
Meghna, let's go.
- Thank you, inspector.
- Thank you.
Meghna, enter...
"Don't know ifl am... "
Walk properly, Meghna.
What are you doing?
You forgot your turn, Meghna!
Meghna, come on.
Concentrate on what you have to do.
Sorry.
Don't worry.
We'll find Shonali.
We've informed the police.
Everything will be alright.
You just focus on the show, okay?
And I promise everything will be fine.
- Got it?
- Yes, got it.
Okay?
Okay. Full.
Now where will we...
No but... that's okay.
Great... Iook, it looks cute.
Come on, you can have this straight.
Okay girls! Ready? Let's line up
and have a great show.
How is it? Sure?
No, turn around, stand up.
- Are you okay?
- I am okay.
- You need something?
- No. - Okay.
- Janet, please come here.
- I'll just be back.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
kindly take your seats.
Go, Diandra!
Alicia.
"I shall give up my life. "
Ask him to call Meghna Mathur.
"It's difficult. I shall give up my life. "
"My dreams. "
Meghna, you are next,
come on. Come on!
"I shall give up my life. "
Lets go.
"It's difficult. I shall give up my life. "
- Ready? You are next.
- Yeah.
Meghna, your phone is ringing.
- Hello...
- Are you mad, Shruti?
- Hello, Miss Meghna.
- Yes.
This is Inspector Gighe from
Bandra police station.
There's bad news.
We've found Shonali Gujral's body...
... at Khar East.
We suspect that the cause of death...
... could be drug overdose.
Please come to Bhabha Hospital
and claim the body.
Hello, Ms. Meghna.
30 seconds to go for Meghna.
30 seconds.
Ready? Okay? Stand by and send her...
Go.
Send her in quickly.
Meghna, you have to go now.
Come on, go!
Move.
Meghna, walk!
Come now, walk!
Walk, it's your turn! Go for it!
Meghna! Walk!
Come on Meghna, walk!
Meghna!
Put the lights.
Meghna! Walk!
Come on, Meghna, walk!
Go.
Meghna walk.
What are you waiting for?
Go for it!
Come Meghna, quickly.
Meghna, now!
When we dream, nobody tells
us what we'd have to...
... give up to achieve them.
I lost Shonali in the same
moment I achieved success.
I was pained by her loss.
But I had the feeling that
she gave me a reason to dream.
Even after everything
I went through...
life provided me another opportunity.
To find myself again.