You and I..
Because I love you
Boys get together and go out
Girls get together and chat
How will we get together?
Deep in my heart you and I
You and I..
Daylong of longings
whenever you're nowhere near
Who all were you with?
So if you love me?
Why didn't you profess your
love and you fought me off?
Now come into my arms
Boys get together and go out
Girls get together and chat
Deep in my heart you and I
First of all God created the word.
Then he went off to sleep over it..
and He conjured up a
guy and He was glad..
..that he rested for some more days-
That's when He made
His biggest mistake
He created a Girl-
Which done He lost his sleep.
So we lost our sleep too. For good
And the world was
split into two halves
girls and guys like you and I
You and I..
So what do we do about .. you and I?
Renowned cartoonist Karan
Kapoor's debut novel "Hum-Tum".-
is a national bestseller
First week sales crossed 10 000 copies
Publishers say that they have
orders of ten thousand more.
Karan Kapoor joins the press in
a first look after this grand success
Vedika from Mumbai for NDTV India-
How does a cartoonist
turn into an author?
Tried cartoons now I'm trying words
hoping to understand .. women someday
Come to grips with that understanding?
Hopefully after a few more books
And you'll write only on women?
Anything better more interesting?
Notwithstanding your digs at girls..
- indeed..
I think your novel is woven around..
your real life experience.
Look.- when love is requited..
there's no story left to be told.
A failed romance
isn't worth talking about
And unrequited love..?
True love never goes unrequited
it's consummated one day or another-
Because life's a long while
Many such romances in your life?
Only one object of romance-
But the romances she sparked were many
Mamma!
- Silence
Mamma enough
- Rhea stop it
My daughter is going abroad.-
Who else in the family ever went?
Who else in our colony?
And listen.. I've packed
lots of snacks for you
Spiced grams pickles sweets
Eat almonds every day
sharpens your brains
I'll miss you Mamma
I will also child
Your attention please..
..this is the last and final call
for passengers traveling..
Hey gorgeous
Karan where have you been?
Well.- - Something forgotten back
in the car? - Yes
Oh car keys
You see.-
- Don't even start
I don't care whoever she was.
Who said I was with any girl?
Hey who said I was with some girl?
Karan listen have you kept
your passport and tickets carefully?
Mom I'm going to America. To study.
I think I can take care of myself
Rubbish
Oh no! Hey brother
Don't hey brother me okay?
I got your passport tickets
What would I do without you Mihir?
Grow up okay?
Sure Karan grows up someday
Hear that?
Thank God Shalini is in New York.
She'll take care of you
Don't remind me.
- She's your girlfriend
So? Never take girls too seriously
Girls are like buses.
There's one every two minutes
traffic permitting
Karan I have told you many times.-
..I disapprove of your
attitude towards girls.
And I've told you that before Girls.-
Are mothers sisters- I know.
But not my sisters
Karan You will learn to
show respect to women.
Says who that I don't respect women?
I respect you
I respect Indira Gandhi
Mother Teresa
Mother India Miss India
Miss India. Ooh miss India.
- Karan.
Keep Him on your desk.
Lord Ganesha Thank you for
sparing me that melodrama
Look
One minute Rhea..
Mamma enough. I'm off
- Listen
I'll be late for my flight
You always do that- - if you
won't stop I'll beat you. Wait.
Oblations from our Goddess of Succour.
Give it to the poor in America
Mamma!
- Never argue my child.
Do one good deed then
you'll deserve a good in turn
My tigress- Bye wish you good luck-
Hoist those pants
Hello! Yes one minute.
Your dad
- Your husband-
I wish you'd mention him with a smile
Hello hey dad.
Yes I am all set-
Yes I got the passport.
What is with you guys man? Hey dad..
..I was thinking
this time for a change
..why not holiday with me in New York?
Yes okay great.
I'll see you there bye dad. Bye.
is it on time?
- Yes I think.
The way he talked
I think he misses you
in all these seven years
did he care to call me up even once?
Anyway Better for you if
you stay out of this mess.
Concentrate on your studies-
- Yes studies
Bye mom-
- Bye dear. Take care.
Mihir you'll take care of mom?
Like you always take care of her?
Come on. You make
nice-sounding parting shots
like take care of Ma etc.. etc.
Bye Karan-
- Take care
Mom-
- I love you dear-
I love you too mom. I love you-
- Yes yes. I love you- - I love you.
I hope he does fine
You're worrying about him?
I pity the girls out there
They don't know
what's coming their way.
Not bad. Do good and get good.
All the best Karan.
There is vermillion on your forehead-
Thanks.
Don't say hi out of the blue
Wait a minute in fact
don't even glance at her.
She might be watching you only.
Oh my oh god shit.
Praise the name of The Lord
Preserve the name of The Lord
Whatever hundred sardars say-
Sorry
Not one nice airhostess
Boring.
"I.. I and you.-"
Excuse me-
- Sorry sorry.
you know beer-dinner-playing
hard to get was a waste of time
When it's too late to even say hi..
Then you ask for a magazine
Excuse me can I
have a magazine? Please.
Yes sure-
Thank you.
Know what for three hours we've been
only two inches from each other..
..without knowing each other's names.
Strange?
Why didn't you ask before?
Rhea Prakash
Bond James Bond. No sorry.
Karan Kapoor You can call me Karoo
Hi!
The makings of a highly
interesting acquaintance?
You and I
Not as in yourself and me You and I-
My cartoon character.
Excuse me sir- Would you
like to have tea or coffee?
Let's make a guess.
You're the tea type
One tea for the lady.
- Okay sir.
One coffee please with very
little sugar brown sugar..
..and just about two spoons of milk.
Okay madam I'll just get it for you.
Nice you avoid tea.
You know tea types?
My mother prefers tea
Correct.
Just what I was
about to say. Tea types
are conservative mothers
grandmothers
Coffee- Coffee is
a modern girl's drink.
Today's woman prefers coffee not tea
I am glad you are a modern girl.
I like modern girls.
Modern girls are modern you know.
Hello.- sleeping beauty. Do you
want to come to Khandala? Hello..
Excuse me- Hi-
- Hi.
Our New York fight is six hours away
Airport squatting is boring.
Let's take a tour of Amsterdam
You got a visa-
- How did you know?
I checked your passport.
- What? You rifled my bag?
You were asleep. I was bored-
So I thought how I'd kill some time
How dare you.
You don't open a lady’s handbag-
Why what's inside a lady's handbag?
Okay I stand corrected.
I'd never do it again
I am sorry.
I can't believe you rifled my bag-
- I said I'm sorry
Where are you headed?
- I thought we'd sight see Amsterdam
"I and you.."
So where does our story end?
- Story? Ours?
Yes Everyone has a story-
So when we meet others
our stories meet
We'll spend lots of time together and
We'll look each other up in New York
Or we might say
goodbyes and never meet again
Yes..
No matter how long or how short
There's a tale of the two of us
Keep. Euro 1 .40
- What was that?
My fare.
- Don't be silly. Only 75 Rupees
Fifty-fifty- Why must
you spend on my tickets?
Yes how are we related?
it was a bad joke-
- Very-
No. I was about to
tell one more bad joke.
Here's where we are.
And there's where we're headed
Sorry
Why do people smoke?
You don't know. Oh come on Rhea.
Unless you try how will
you know? it's amazing
You are right.
Why do people smoke?
Can I have some gum?
Only one.
- Can I have one more?
"I and you.."
I thought we're
taking this tour together
So? - Why do you guys
always walk ahead of girls?
Why are girls always a step behind?
We walk ahead to show you the way
and we follow so we can support you
Okay that is quiet sad.
"I and you.."
Museum!
- Oh no Rhea.
We decided not to see boring museums.
Excuse me- When did we decide?
Okay we're deciding now.
Oh come Rhea don't be such a girl.
Museums are for kids
school teachers and old people.
Okay I am going. You are on your own.
You'll leave me all alone?
You will leave a girl
all alone in Amsterdam?
How will I get to
the airport on my own?
Fine.
- Fine. - Fine.
You go your way. I'll go mine.
it is an art dear. it is good-
Done with your museum?
Now let's do something.. Fun.
God
- What have I done?
Why were you staring at that girl?
Your x-ray eyes see through dresses?
- I wish
What? Rhea man..
Karan how would you feel if
you were ogled at by a girl?
Wait don't even bother to answer me-
Thank God not all guys think like you
Okay what? Rhea.. Not all guys think
like that? You seriously think so?
You mean every guy is looking
for the same thing from a girl?
Right.
And what if he doesn't get it?
- We cover up with lies
Lies?
So what's your lie?
Your lies
When a girl smiles at me..
I tell my friends look she
gave me her telephone number
When she gives me her
telephone number
I'll tell that I took her out
When I take her out
I'll say that I held her hand
When she holds my hand I'll say..
I kissed her
After I've kissed her I'll say..
We've done something. You know what.
And talking about us what
lies will you tell your friends?
I didn't mean you. I meant.-
- You guys are sick-
You guys are sick!
- But I didn't mean you-
Why does she take
everything so seriously?
You'll never figure why..?
She thinks harder
but she knows lesser
Whatever her heart tells
she'll do quite something else
I'll never figure why
she isn't like a guy
She thinks harder but she knows lesser
Whatever her heart tells
she'll do quite something else
I'll never figure why
she isn't like a guy
There's romance lurking in her heart
but she wants you to make a start
And when she's ratted
it's her locks that she ruffled"
I mean you're all the same
We're nice friends I
never thought of you that way
Sounds fine but it
never came to my mind
Up close she says you're so special
and soon nothing
about you is good enough"
What an awful shirt What a haircut
Stop speeding
Stop hogging
Give me a break
Up close she wants to change your life
the spell she casts
can ruin your life"
You'll fall for her
words then you'll know why..
what started with a
laugh ends in a cry
And you'll never figure
why she's so unlike a guy
if happiness is being alone
what makes you such a flirt?
The thousand gifts you shower on
her for what were all those flowers?
You didn't tell me your name
How about a coffee?
Can I drop you home?
When do I get to see you next?
it's a wayward life you've
lived living like a tramp
But you'll insist you're
different why are you so vain?
That wet towel on the floor
Cap of the toothpaste tube missing
Wear used socks inside out
Never knows how time flies?
How to live a life she shows you
She makes something human out of you
Not one moment can
you live without her
And she knows what you can't tell her
That's just why no
girl’s are like a guy
All sorts of strange dates
she'll always call to mind
Love can be forgotten but
forgetting a date is crime
On 1st March we looked at each
other. 4th April I went to meet you
May 21 . You touched me
June 6. I felt something stirring
Can't trust a guy
these guys are so fast
Now he's here now he's gone
no telling how long he'll last
Your Mummy-Daddy aren't at home?
Great! Can I come over?
Your friend is going home alone.
Poor thing shall I escort her?
She'll lead you up the
street before she says yes
She's enjoying herself
while you're getting harassed
She's shy that's why she hides.."
But if she said yes ever
she's is avowed forever
That's just why a
girl’s different from a guy
That's just why a girl's different
from a guy - Someone shut her up
All right what's the quarrel?
Like a bee he comes singing his song
then he's busy I got the
timing wrong" - Oh come on Rhea
Please I'm busy or I'd never..
So what you'll live
in my heart forever
The beauty he fell for once is now so
boring..- I am not listening to you.
and before you know it his..
..eyes have begun philandering
- I am not listening to you.
You can't live on love and fresh air.
Why not take up interior decoration?
Okay that's it.
"I and you.."
Rhea hey wait up dear-
Rhea come on stop. Look.-
..I kissed you. You
slapped me. Scores settled?
Come on dear.
Now you're going to listen
I thought you're a nice guy only a
little stupid but a respected guy.
And you got me all wrong
Because it was I who
broke the ice on the plane?
I went out with you in Amsterdam
tried puffing a cigarette..
you thought I was
all laid out for you?
How true. Guys like you expect
only one thing from any girl
You are sick. You have
no respect for woman.
Such strange notions
You wanted to know?
How our story ends?
There's no story about us
There's only "The
End" and this is the end
Understand and good bye.
No bye's Rhea-
Life's a long while
You and I.. unlike other
guys and girls we won't fight
Okay cool.
- I like that.
Stop whistling- it's not nice
I'm not whistling at a girl
You go whistling after girls?
Gosh you are sick-
You go whistling at
girls and you say I'm sick?
I never whistled at anyone and
I didn't say I wouldn't fight
You girls are totally
confused silly girls.
No point telling the truth to girls
- Meaning?
For example in that
dress you don't look fat
What? I look fat in this dress?
I don't look fat for the dress.
it's the pink. Pink makes me look fat
Neither you nor your
dress is to blame.
Pink takes the blame.
Oh God.
I'm serious. I look slim in blue
I'll be back.
- Where are you going?
Where am I going.. hot dog
Hot dog? One for me.
- Okay
I knew! it's.- you
I knew too. I'm avoiding you
Avoid? What do you mean avoid?
You're still angry? Rhea I was only..
You transpired. it's bound to happen-
- Forget it. Now we meet..
After 6 months in New York.
Like I told you..
between us there's a story.
- And what about your other story?
Which story?
- The one behind the tree.-
in which you were doing whatever..
- Who me..?
Rhea..?
- No man.. - Shalini
Rhea! in New York?
- Yes studying fashion designing
Fashion designing wow- Wonderful.
And you..?
- Columbia University
Rhea have you met my boyfriend?
- Hi!
Karan is your boyfriend?
- Yes- Ever since college. in Delhi
Rhea and I were classmates in school.
Your friend from school? That's nice
We never saw each other
after we went to college
How do you know each other?
Karan. He's your boyfriend
Rhea is your friend from school
if one of you doesn't
tell me How you met up
No baby no
- I'll scream- Right now
Excuse me
- Come darling I'll tell you
When we met in Amsterdam.-
Shalini was still your girlfriend?
You went to Amsterdam?
- I.. I..
Come I'll tell you everything
Wait a minute wait a minute.
Shalini I'll tell you
how we met up in Amsterdam
I've got some work. I'll see you.
- What work..? Karan!
I'll tell you when I remember
- Come here
He's a real jerk. I swear! He
actually kissed me. I slapped him
What?
- He is there.
Look dear I am sorry.
I hardly met this girl-
Listen!
Thanks.
Somebody has told it right that..
..behind every
successful man there's a woman
Of course
That's because girls never run
after guys who don't succeed
You must rig the tent in four days
Mr. Mishra we've organized
so many weddings together..
I've given you so much business.
And today on the right time..
no you must do something. Please
Assurances and assurances-
Nothing ever seems to happen
Why are you staring at me?
Get on with your jobs
Good morning mom.
Nothing for breakfast?
I only got to ask for
breakfast and you break into tears?
The tent isn't up- Mr.
Sharma's wife is in labour
And even that cow is sick!!!
Why haven't you taken a haircut?
This is my Tom Cruise look
- Tom Cruise look!
I told you stop organising weddings.
- Karan please leave me alone
Ok I'll make myself breakfast.
You want anything?
Karan what are you doing next week?
- Next week?
I don't know about today and
you ask me about a week ahead
I've never planned so long ahead
Wait a minute. Why?
Because you're going to
help me out with this wedding
Oh come on mom. Am I
supposed to organise weddings?
- I'm not asking- I'm ordering you.
Do you understand? That's it-
No way! I can't do all this
I won't get into all this
I am sorry but the answer is No.
Sahib what goes in between?
white flowers? Greens or marigolds?
What do you feel?
- Marigolds could be better
I used marigolds for my wedding.
- Then go ahead why ask me?
Oye! - Not Oye. My name is
Jhallo Ram. - Take your basket away
Hello! Susie don't believe Natasha
She and I are just friends.
Nothing happened between us
I don't care. I just called to say
that boss has cancelled your leave
if you don't report for
work today you're fired
Let him do that
He was very serious
- Even I'm very serious
The Times of India
has made me an offer-
They'll carry my
Hum-Tum cartoons daily
And the money is good. So who
cares for this nine-to-fiver?
Right Tuka Ram?
- No. Jhallo Ram
The bride's people have arrived
Susie the bride's people have arrived
Suji.. the stuff for
making sweets? (Suji: semolina)
Jhallo Ram- Unload the stuff
Where is the electricity generator?
Nothing's on time if I'm not around
This is nice.
Remove that basket
Nice venue for a wedding
Thank you very much.
A wedding villa is a fun place-
How far away is your bridegroom?
Hum-Tum! I always browse the
strip in the Sunday Times of India
Hey that's cool.
My Hum-Tum is so popular among girls?
- Yours? Hum-Tum are very cute
Right. You and I are cute
Hi I am Pooja.
Hi Karan.
Karan Kapoor?
- That's right.
No way. Rhea.
Hey well done dear-
You are looking like a girl.
- Don't touch me.
Damn tent. Oh Jesus.
Something awful always
happens whenever I see you
Whatever happened to your hair?
- it's my Tom Cruise look
You won't understand. Not
your level- This is fashion
What? - You loser!
What are you doing here?
- What are you doing here?
I'm in charge of wedding plans here
That's obvious.
- Actually it's my Ma- I'm helping her
That's so sweet.
- Right? See so sweet
What are you doing here?
- You're organising the wedding?
And you don't know who the bride is?
- Who..?
No way you.
You're marrying so late?
You could've mothered
three kids by now. Have you?
Come on tell me how many.
- You are really a loser Karan.
3 years on I thought my
slap would’ve mended your mind
I guess I was wrong-
Some guys never change
My bags are inside the car.
Have them delivered to my room
You think I'm a porter?
- Likewise
Bye Karan-
I hate that chick-
What's up?
- How many kilos of candies?
Who wants candies?
I hate them. Who asked for it?
The bride's mother.
- Who chooses sweets for the wedding?
The bride's mother? Or I..?
- You're the boss
Get ten kilos of pastries-
- Done
Greetings.
- Greetings
I'm the bride's mother. Sorry
you should've said you hate candies
I'd never have asked for those
Aunty I was only..
Aunty? How can you call me aunty?
Jhallo Ram where are you going?
- To buy your pastries
I was just joking. What did
the bride's mother ask for?
Candies.
- Then candy it is
Buy 10 kilos. No 15 kilos
5 kilos from my side
Many thanks
You're Anju's son?
- Yes Aunty
What's this cursed Aunty-Aunty?
in our times we married
early we had our babies fast
if you insist..
..you can add a Bobby with Aunty.
The name's Mrs. Parminder Prakash
But everyone calls me
Bobby Aunty- it is my pet name
if I may say so
you're as beautiful as the
legendary danseuse Umrao Jaan
I've been noticing you all along.
Your poise your grace..
today's girls have none of it.
Now take your daughter
Son.. even I've been
noticing you all day
striding like a tiger.. showing off
your stripes to the girls.- Not I.-
Come off it. Wish you good luck
Please..
- Karan..
Yes Bobby Aunty..?
- Shut up
I think this shut up
problem is from their ancestors.
Hey hi Priya.
- Hi.
Not Priya. Pooja
I think Priya suits you more.
- No
Can I call you Priya?
- No.
Thank you.
Jhaloram. Hey Jhalo.. tell any
of your friend to get me a car.
Your friends and family
just hijacked all the cars
And my designer wants me to
try out my wedding gown right now
Get me a cab
Here's a village.
You won't spot a cab
in a 12 mile radius
Well! There's a way
Why aren't you attending the ritual?
You aren't supposed to meet your
fiancé two days before the wedding
Obviously you don't know.
is it an arranged match? Or love?
What do you think?
- I don't know arranged?
Oh love.
- No both.
What do you mean by both?
Sameer and I went to college together
We became good friends.
He proposed.
I said okay.
- Just like that you said okay-
He's smart sensitive successful
mature..
unlike you- Find-my-towel-type.
- What's find-my-towel-type?
Like someone who'd
scream from the bathroom..
Where's my towel my shoes.-
where's the newspaper?
Just peas and potatoes?
in short find-my-towel-type.
You expect your Sameer..
..won't ask you to find
his towel after the wedding?
Oh you poor thing.
in New York you lived with Sameer?
- Before my wedding? Are you mad?
Oh come on Rhea..
Don't tell me you never..?
- What..?
You know what I mean ding dong?
Why should I tell you that?
That means no.
I knew it no ding dong.
You don't know anything ding dong?
Rhea this looks fantastic on you.
- Thanks Mailni..
..but don't you think it should be
slightly more fitted here.
Just a little from here perfect.
Rhea Pooja said your
Sameer is some computer engineer
Sounds quite serious and quite boring
Being a computer engineer
doesn't make him serious and boring
Unlike you he isn't an immature fool
Had I been more mature
you would've considered me..?
Shut up Karan- I'm getting
married in two days. You're sick
Did I ask you to marry me? She
takes everything so seriously
Hello.
- Hi.
I don't see your husband.
He's in the catering business?
You're in the weddings' business
he's in the catering business..?
Wonderful! Wish you good luck.
- No he's a photographer
Even better! He's going to
shoot the wedding photos?
No he's a fashion photographer.
Besides he doesn't live in India
in fact we've separated.
- So what?
I've separated from my husband too.
it was a matter of life and death
Bobby you're a
wonderful example of perseverance
Somewhat true- But Anju
you've got it going for you
You run a thriving wedding business.
And all you have is one son
You haven't a worry in life
Of course I worry. Mention
marriage and Karan runs scared
Oh! Why..?
Marriage is the end
of love and romance
Taking a potshot at marriage? Does
he know what love and romance is?
What would she know?
She's getting hitched
You tell me did Adam and Eve marry?
- No..
They didn't and they
basked in their un-marital bliss
Look at legends. Romeo
and Juliet- Did they marry?
No.
- They didn't
Did Heer marry Ranjha?
- No
Did Shirin and Farhad marry?
Ever wondered why?
- Why..?
I'll tell you why.
Marriage would’ve
spelled doom for their romance
They could never have
become legendary lovers
So I tell you if you wish
to find true love never marry
Fall in love like me
What rubbish Nonsense
Yet every romantic legend
stopped short of a wedding? How come?
You ever heard a story told about
the romance of any married couple?
Of course. And
everyone in the world knows
Emperor Shah Jahan
gave his wife Mumtaz..
..the finest tribute
to love. Taj Mahal
Chocolate heroes
They're screaming for love..
these roadside romeos.-
but they'll duck the wedding
Chocolate heroes
Deep down inside whatever he is..
he'll put up a heroic posture
All day he's ogling books..
full of girlie posters
He'll say life's a carnival.-
but marriage is trouble
So show him the door
Chocolate hero
Chocolate heroes
Talk of marrying..
and he throws a fit
- Really?
Talk of living-in.-
you'll find he swears by it
in every girl he finds romance
But commitment not a chance
He'll never find Juliet
so Romeo loses his shirt
Chocolate heroes
Chocolate hero
He'll grow up to
become an ageing beast..
and the coughing will
rack his ancient chest..
he won't find a helping hand..
then he'll miss love’s caring wand
When he is abandoned
then he will repent
And then finally he will remember me
Chocolate hero
Chocolate heroes
They're screaming for love..
these roadside romeos.-
but they'll duck the wedding
Chocolate hero
Chocolate heroes
The bridegroom has come.
What's all this excitement over?
fetching the bridegroom?
He's bound to turn up isn't he?
if he fails to turn up.-
then you've reason for excitement..
the bridegroom is missing..
Come on Rhea come on.
What a naughty boy
Where ends our story?
Story? Ours?
- Yes
A story is happening around every one.
When we meet others our stories meet"
There's no story about us.
There's only The End.
The end. This is the end-
Bye
- Bye-
I wish Mamma was here
You know she's busy at home.
if she could’ve come she would
Carrying prayer candles
What.-?- Always
transpires with prayer candles
Mamma? Mamma! Mamma I
thought you wouldn’t make it
Yes dear-
Actually I was totally stuck.
I thought I'd miss your flight.
But Karan took care of everything
He is a very helpful boy dear-
- Karan?
Friend's colony? I
live in Friends Colony too
is it? Which block?
- 'M' I am in K 42
Sorry I lied. Actually
I live in Kailash Colony
But now that we've
met Let's meet up more
Yes sure-
- Nice meeting you. - Yes- - Bye-
K 42 in friends colony. Yes.
No use
No use. You'll end up taking her out
You'll spend money take
her for a long drive..
..and when you're dropping her home-
you'll hope she asks you in for coffee
She won't
How can you say?
Even I did my bit- But don't worry
my success rate wasn't hundred percent
Many a times I was
left thirsting for coffee
What happened? You think
I don't think like you?
For you as many girls as you wish?
For me only one for a whole lifetime?
Don't worry Rhea
didn't make a wrong decision
No boring scenes as
in when I suddenly..
..realise that
you're in love with Rhea
No!
- Even if he does too bad
We need women more than they need us
And somewhere inside all of us guys ..
..there's a kid who refuses to grow up
No matter.- how
feeble she might seem.-
..but in here we're far weaker.-
But you won't understand now
The day you find
your Rhea you'll know..
Take care.
- Bye bye.
You always appear just when
I've forgotten all about you
Which means you think of me
all the time when I'm away
I never meant that
if you wish never to see me again.-
you must think of me always
Because when you've
forgotten all about me..
I'll make my appearance
- Yes
But if you're thinking of me always
you're actually wishing you'd see me
Right? Yes.. no.-
That's why a boy and a girl
can never be friends- Why?
Because you girls always
end up talking about love
Then you and I will never be friends
Too bad.
- Too bad. - Bye. - Bye.
Dad will you ever be on time..?
Excuse me madam- - Yes please- -
Can I get a beer? - Yes sure.
And one Cognac-
I'm no poet
But my pretty one..
..ever since I've seen you..
poetry just dawned upon me
I'm no poet
He is my son. Cheers-
I had heard of love no doubt
But I didn't know what love was
I remained confused as
confusions generally are..
and remained an enemy among friends
Yet I'm no foe..
..but dear pretty one..
..having seen you.-
I've learnt to make friends
And I was no poet
Hi dad-
- My dear son. - Thank you.
Wow!
- is it good or bad?
Dad it is in the front
cover of Vogue. Mind blowing.
Your Dad isn't an international
photographer for nothing
I am so proud of you dad.
- Thank you.
Could I find her phone number?
Now Paris? Aren't you tired of
shifting base every year or two?
What's tiring about it?
in the last eight years I've
done New York Milan and now Paris
Who are you running from?
- Your mother
Okay done dear-
I won't talk ill of your
mother in front of you
Dad! Not even behind my back
A man has a right to
live his life no?
if not my wife whom do I criticize.-
..my neighbour's wife?
Even after all these
years of living apart?
You still consider her your wife?
There is something.
I don't know but I love Bombay.
Mom was upset when
we shifted from Delhi.
She's settled down.
Hey nice house dad-
Your room is over there-
- Thanks
Wow amazing dad-
Nice pictures dad-
Nice pictures.
- Relax boy relax.
Part of my last
year's photo exhibition
That is why they are there.
Snacks?
- Yes please
Your wife is fine Dad-
Did I ask how she is?
Not in many words.
Good day mister- Coffee or tea?
How are you?
Nothing thank you.
Good day madam. Coffee or tea?
- Coffee.
Milk very little just
about two spoons. Sugar.-
..brown sugar. That's it.
Like I said life's a
long while. We keep meeting
Karan.
- Hi.
I am sorry madam.
That was bound to happen
Oh come on how can you forget?
Every time we meet
something always goes wrong
You haven't changed a bit
What are you doing in Paris?
- I run a little boutique here
Nice.
- What are you doing here?
I'm pursuing love between" You and I"
Remember my cartoon
characters Hum-Tum?
You won't believe it the whole
country is raving about Hum-Tum
I mean from like newspaper clippings
T-shirts caps no words dear.
I mean it is really very successful.
Very good-
- Thank you.
Publishers wanted me to write
a novel about Hum-Tum.. in which..
they fall in love-
Because Paris is the most
romantic city in the world..
here I am catalysing their romance.
And it's so awful you're walking out?
No it's my station. All the
best for your Hum-Tum Bye.
Hey Riya! Say hi to Sameer.
Sameer is no longer part of my life
I just want to talk to her.
Have your food is
it to eat or to see?
Should I call her up Dad?
- Certainly not
Wait till the next summer
I want to talk to her-
I want to know what happened to her
I just want to make her feel better-
She isn't the same old Rhea
But I haven't left a good impression
Hope she doesn't get me wrong
if you wish to do good
do it. Don't hesitate
Take my mobile and call up.
if you keep mulling over it
you'll end up nowhere? Now be a man.
You keep thinking just do it.
Who will eat that food? Your Dad?
Not a bad idea who wants to diet?
Hello Can I speak to Rhea?
Who's calling? I'm
hearing Hindi after ages
By the way who are you?
Umrao Jaan is that you?
- Umrao Jaan?
Aunty I'm Karan- Karan Kapoor-
Mrs. Kapoor's son
is that you Tiger?
Where are you calling from?
I'm calling from Paris.
You needn't raise your voice
Shut up I'm tired of
talking in hushed tones
Blast their diction they always
seem to be conspiring in whispers
if you're in Paris aren't
you coming over to see us?
Give me your address and
I'll be over in a flash
Address? You know
how these names sound
.. I went to school till 8th standard
Yes I can manage English
But it is not like that.
but this language..
never heard anything like it
French.. never speak what they write.
More like they are gargling.
Aunty address.
I'll give it a try. Write.
Apartment
- Red brick building..
it's a red building on the street.
I can't manage the name of the house
Made of olden type red bricks
Sometimes in life some things
happen and you lose faith in God
Did Sameer and Rhea hurt anyone?
Just after their first anniversary..
..like everyday Sameer
was leaving for work
Some college students jumped a
traffic signal for the fun of it
And in a moment's time
Rhea's life changed forever
There was a time when she lit up
my life whenever she came home
Nowadays she's so quiet.-
Sometimes I don't realize
that we are in the same room.
She left America
India.. and now she's here..
where she knows that no one knows her
I think she wants to
get lost in the crowd
Now it's as if Rhea has lost herself
My Rhea lived life on her own terms;
in life’s hands she
suffers her defeat
Just met your mother
Can I share your umbrella? Thanks.
You know Rhea..
Sometimes whatever happens to us.-
God what am I saying.-?
Whatever I say what use..
You're home
And you couldn’t even say
how you liked the conversation
Thank you Karan
- What for?
For what you've been
trying to say Bye-
Hey Rhea can I borrow your umbrella?
Oh sure-
Thanks bye.
"You looked at me and gifted me.."
Mamma phone.
Hello. - Hello could I
speak to Rhea please.
One minute.. your phone.
Who is it?
- No idea
Hello!
- This is such a problem.
I grasp Neither the
language nor the cuisine
I end up eating what I never ordered.
Listen have lunch with me tomorrow-
And I get to return your umbrella
No Karan. Not lunch.
I'm busy tomorrow
Are you sure.
- Yes-
Anyway thanks bye.
He only asked you out for lunch
You could've said dinner
All day you sit at home.
You could do with an outing
What a life. Home-to-boutique-to-home
Mamma.
- What am I saying?
I'm only watching my
movie 'Teesri Manzil.'
Shammi Kapoor is a star
My darling baby
What do you think about this?
it is good.
- it is very soft..
..and this color
looks very nice on you.
it is so soft.
Finding that Chinese
restaurant was tough. - Karan.
You said you'd be busy.
So I thought let’s have lunch here
Would you like to join us?
- No thanks I will have it later-
I want this.
- You want to take this?
Come on I am famished
You want to eat this?
- Why are you doing this Karan?
Why this expression of sympathy?
This is the reason
why I didn't return to
India after Sameer died
I hate seeing people pitying me
Why can't you people
be just normal with me?
The food bill. 32 Euros
Your share is 16 Euros-
Remember? You only said fifty-fifty
Can we eat? I'm really hungry
Lovely food
How did you find out I like Chinese?
I never knew- I love Chinese
Come on start eating.
Excuse me- Oh I am sorry I didn't
know you were closed for lunch-
No no it is fine-
Come I'll help you.
Eat in peace. Let me take care of her
Hi I am Karan-
- Hi I am Nicole.
Hey nice doggy.
- Thank you.
I want an overcoat.
- Okay what type?
Pretty child.
- Thank you
Something about me?
- I only said she's a pretty child
Not bad. You picked up French so fast?
Must know the language where you live
I seem to be able to make do
with Hindi anywhere in the world
if they don't know Hindi I
make sure I teach them some
Hey look at them.
if I don't teach Hindi
to those French kids..
..you can change my name to
something French All right.
But if I succeed you'll do as I say.
- Do what..?
Chuck up
- Chuck up every woe
- Chuck it I'm with you
Try and smile once
Let hues of the
Spring blossom once again
Try and smile once
Let hues of the
Spring blossom once again
Sing a new song strike a new melody
it's a new season it's a new day
Chuck it.-
chuck every woe
Chuck it I'm with you
Chuck it.-
chuck every woe
I'm with you-
Unleash new joys sing a new rhapsody
Let loose your moorings
ride new waves of ecstasy
Unleash new joys sing a new rhapsody
Let loose your moorings
ride new waves of ecstasy
Get the bounce on your feet
let dance the sands at your feet
Feel your spirits rise
and reach for the skies
Chuck it. Chuck every woe.
Chuck it. I'm with you-
it's the only life you ever had
through twists and turns good or bad
Hug every moment get life's feel.
Smile life's joys you can steal
Chuck it.-
chuck every woe
Chuck it I am with you-
Chuck it.-
chuck every woe
Chuck it I am with you-
Try and smile once
Let hues of the
Spring blossom once again
Sing a new song strike a new melody
it's a new season it's a new day
Chuck it.-
chuck every woe
Chuck it I am with you-
Chuck it.-
chuck every woe
Chuck it I am with you-
Chuck it.-
chuck every woe
Chuck it I am with you-
What are you doing? My bags..
I don't run a hotel.
if you're living with me
you'll socialize with me
if you're seeing only
Rhea find someplace else
Get lost don't stay with me. Out!
Dare don't stay with me!
Dad- These dramatics
don't suit you. Open the door
Spending so much time with a
girl doesn't suit you either
By the way is it serious?
What an awkward monologue with a door.
Please open the door.
On one condition.
You'll introduce e to Rhea
Rhea has invited us to lunch tomorrow-
Really? Come in.
- But.. - Come in-
The door was open?
- Then what?
You think I'm a bad dad who'll
lock his son out in the cold?
No I am not so bad.
I'm a bad boy
Excuse me..
is Karan in?
I am Arjun Kapoor- Good day.
- Good day. I'm Nicole
Nicole-
- Welcome
Greetings. - Greetings. - My father.
- Greetings uncle.
So you are Karan's "bau'ji"..
- "Bau'ji"..? - Dad?
Myself Mrs. Parminder Prakash.
You can call me Bobby
I'd rather call you Dimple
the actress who played Bobby
Your Bau'ji is very colourful Karan.
- Dad..
Flowers for my Umrao Jaan.
- Lovely flowers. Nice boy
I wish I had carried those flowers
Oh chocolates for you.
- Thank you.
Please come in
- Do come inside
Nice house.
- Thank you
So you've taken after your father
Son..
I want to see Rhea married again
You ought to talk to my mother
She organizes weddings
Silly I didn't mean that
You aren't talking about me..?
- I love my daughter dearly
Would I ever want her to
marry someone like you?
Thank God. I was scared
Life is meant to be lived..
to the fullest
I know what loneliness means
At least I had Rhea
After I'm gone who stays with Rhea?
Everyone of us needs someone..
For company love support
But I have a feeling That
Rhea will refuse to agree
That's why she is living here.
But whom will she find here?
But son if we can find a
nice boy I think it'll work out
So you're looking for
someone conservative homely..
in other words a very boring guy.
Because interesting boys like
you Never make for good husbands
Thanks aunty. I am not interested.
Okay now give me a nice smile.
Smile smile. Hold it there!
What happened uncle?
Nothing just remembered someone
I met her a few years ago.
She's very beautiful
The only beauty I could
never capture in my camera
nor into my life
I should not be asking but..
- Then don't ask
Caught you.
- Come in I'll tell you
I was just back from London
after a course in photography
You know I was part of
this very glamorous life..
Then I met Anju
Anju's world was very
different from mine.
She was a plain simple girl.
With a strong mind
That's the quality in
her that sets her apart
You may have conquered
the word but..
..you want to come back home
to a woman like this.
We married
To make each other happy
initially we made our compromises
Then followed the questions..
Like where-are-you-going..
..who-is-she? Maybe I was
not prepared for marriage
Afterwards questions that had
never been raised cropped up
I guess I was not ready for marriage.
With time there was more work
more quarrels. in a fit of rage..
I took up a six-month
assignment in America
She didn't ask questions
I gave no answers
For six months I
waited for a call from her;
maybe she waited for mine
Then six months became a
year and years became ages.
We never.. On one
count I'm grateful to her
She never let Karan feel
the distance between us
I don't know why I'm telling you this
.. I never even confided in myself
Neither to me
Wish you had tried at least once..
So neither have you
been able to forgive me
I forgave you long ago Dad.
But I never got over what you did
I am sorry son. I am
really very sorry.
Maybe you ought to say
sorry to someone else
I am sorry Rhea.
You must think I'm evil.
No one's evil. Evil
are the times that befall
You're saying I've
fallen into evil times
There you are. Come inside.
I don't serve a bad lunch
Come inside first eat and see. Come.
- Come please.
I never could bring up
this topic with my dad
Thanks Rhea.
- it is okay.
if you tell anyone I cried
I'll kill you. No I am serious.
I'll kill you. Remember it.
Okay thank you very
much for the lunch.
Wish you good luck.
Thank you very much.
You are here again?
- Hello is it Karan's dad? - Hi.
Hi Nicole hi sweety.
Hi do you stay here?
The one with the dog?
No no she is saying
she loves your dog.
Thanks.
- Welcome. - Have fun. - I'll try.
You are a brat you'll never progress.
- Aunty don't say that. Greetings.
Bye dad see you.
- Bye.
I wonder what her mother's like.
- What..?
Bye uncle.
Rhea father and son will
never progress. Come on let's go.
Mamma.
- is that son and father..
Let's go in.
Karan.
- Just 2 seconds Rhea. Coming.
You aren't dressed yet? Not
going to the airport? Get dressed
Spare me.
- Why?
I can't bid goodbyes
Sorry.
Getting late I should make a move
Take care of yourself.
I love you.
Have a nice flight bye bye.
Remember we met at the airport
After that first meeting..
I really hated you.
I know same here.
- Not at all.
I really hated you.
You hated me.
That's why you tried to kiss me
Only tried?
- Shut up. - Thank you.
Then I hated you so much all because..
you didn't know how to talk
you had no respect for women..
..you were so ill-mannered
and irritating - Not Bad.
After all these years you
remember everything about me?
Did you hit upon a
story for your Hum-Tum?
I have something in mind. in the end
who knows Hum-Tum may fall in love
All the best.
- Thank you.
You know Karan I didn't think
I would ever admit this to you.
I think I'll miss you
We're going to see each
other very soon. Guess why?
Because though life's a long while
we have very little time
Are we going to be friends now?
Friends? But you always said
you'd never make friends with girls
Pretty girls are the exception
And I am not pretty!
- When did I say that?
Are you saying I'm pretty?
Actually..
- listen. - Yes. - Shut up! - Okay.
Rhea is coming after 3 days?
- Yes
Whose friend is she yours or mine?
- Mine
And am I your chauffeur or secretary?
- Neither
Then why do you want me to
pick her up from the airport?
Because I want you to marry her
You want me to marry Rhea..?
- Exactly
Come on Mihir you're
perfect for each other
if Rhea is perfect why
don't you marry her?
Hey don't talk rubbish
dude. I can't marry Rhea. - Why?
I'm the sort a mother
would warn her daughter about
You agree with me
thank you very much.
I know Rhea. She needs a mature
experienced guy
Which is you so shut up
and trust me. - I trust you.
in three days Rhea is coming.
Pick her up at the airport
if you don't like her you
needn't see her ever again
Okay so you are going
to pick her up. Thanks.
When did I say yes?
- You didn't say no
I can't believe it ..
I'm doing your bidding
Oh come now Mihir stop all this.
if Rhea realizes that I'm
introducing the two of you
She will kill me alright?
After the wedding can I
tell her we're married?
Not bad! Already
contemplating the marriage?
Rhea is putting up with her aunt.
She knows the address all right
Come on I'm busy. Hang up
Nice sport. Australia fields
so well even in video games
You Rhea.
- Yes.. you..?
Hi I am Karan sorry Mihir.
So you are Mihir. Myself Mrs.
Parminder Prakash
How handsome You're just
like Karan described you
Karan described..?
No.. he didn't. He only said
Mihir would receive us instead of him
You couldn't tell me that before?
- Such a long fight. I'm at wits' end
Sorry I mean.
- Hi hello.
Something cropped up suddenly.
Karan is busy.. so I had to come
Suddenly? But you said Karan
informed my Mummy about you..
Really? The car is
parked outside. Shall we..?
Which car do you have?
Just asking because
we've got so much luggage.
Don't mind.
- Come.
No no it is okay. Please..
- Good manners.
Come come let's go.
There's something about India
The country has a smell of its own..
look kids defecating along the kerb
Nice to be here
Son what do you do?
- I run a business in computers
I see. How much turnover?
Mamma! - Rhea is also a
computer buff - Really?
Not much except office computing
Karan says you run a store in Paris.
Not store. Boutique of Indian designs
Boutique is a store no..?
You come into India and you
grab a paper! Always reading
Times of India carries
Karan's Hum-Tum
This Karan is..
Yes Karan..
- Yes this Karan is..
I just joined the chorus
in Bombay you don't
disconnect phones at night?
Yes Karan.
- Hey hi Rhea.
Don't tell me hi. I am okay.
You're angry? Okay I'm going home.
- What?
I'm standing outside your house
I'm famished. Can I
find something to eat?
it is nice to be back in India.
Mamma is right. Your
country is your own
Who told you to live in Paris?
I am sorry I didn't mean..
- No no.
Don't be sorry. Karan
actually the thing is..
if I stayed in India..
..everyone would've begun
to insist that I marry again
After Sameer died
I wasn't interested anymore
You can't stop loving someone because
he's dead. I'll always love Sameer
I will always love him.
Yes I can understand that Rhea but..
..does it mean that you can't
pick up the threads of your life?
You can't stop living.
True. But to start afresh
one needs a good companion
Not someone in an arranged marriage.
What if you might find someone?
What rubbish. Hey tell me.
I think arranged marriages work
I know much about arrange marriage.
What are you talking?
- I am serious dear..
Let's pretend I'm here to
look up an arranged match
Pretences at 2 am!
Hello Rhea I'm Champak Bhumiya
Your aunt's niece's
daughter' friend speaks highly of you
She says we're perfect for
each other. Made for each other
Made for each other Rhea. - Why not.
- Come on Rhea don't be a fool.
Not Champak Bhumiya. if
a genuine smart guy..
asks you whether after
so many years in Paris..
will you be able to adjust
to Bombay life? With me?
Sandwich.
- Thank you.
Hey Rhea come on just sit down.
- Come on Karan. it is not funny.
it is funny. it is really funny.
Remember fun.. come on. - Okay.
Okay what were you asking?
- After Paris..
will you be able to adjust in Bombay?
More important than the city..
..is adjustment between people.
if two people are happy together..
Bombay or Paris what difference?
10/10 it is a perfect answer.
- Thank you.
After the marriage will you work?
You don't want me to work afterwards?
No no I think it is great.
I think every woman should work.
Not as a pass time.
Serious work. Like you Really
Now that is a perfect answer 10/10.
- Thank you.
Now what about kids.
- What about kids..?
Not you. Aren't you supposed
to ask me? whether I love kids?
Yes do you love kids?
- Of course
First I want a daughter.
Beautiful intelligent. Like you
I'll make a fine daddy
if I find someone like me
flirting with her I'll break his legs
You think that will
make you a fine daddy?
Look you'll make a fine mother
What harm if I spoil
the kids a little bit?
So I do all the hard work
and you have all the fun?
Yes look at it from my point of
view and it's a wonderful marriage
A puppy is all it'll take to
complete the family portrait
Let's call him Tommy.
- Awful name
Okay Tommy. On one condition.
You take Tommy out for walks
I can't do all this.
- Done.
I'll only feed him morsels
from my plate. "Tommy take"
That's all I am going to do.
Apart from spoiling the kids
and Tommy what else will you do?
What else is left to be done?
I'll live happily ever after..
with my kids and Tommy ..
and of course you. Sorry
So I come after the kids and Tommy.
And yes.. with you too.
- I come after the kids and Tommy?
No Rhea it is.. I am sorry.
Mention me after the kids and Tommy
and I'll hack you into small bits..
and I'll feed you to Tommy. - Okay
I'm sorry. No more kids-or-Tommy
I'll always love you
more than anyone else
See how easy it is to
discuss an arranged marriage..?
We almost got married
Rhea!
- Hi aunty. - Hi dear. - How are you?
You look gorgeous.
- I ought to be telling you that
You have not changed.
- is it?
Sit. How about coffee tea juice..?
- Just coming from our place
And you know Mamma never
let’s me leave before breakfast
How is she?
- She is okay. - Great.
Aunty this is for you.
- For me?
it is pretty.
But Rhea these formalities..
Actually Karan's dad
has sent it for you
He's fine.
Rhea I'm the one who makes
your Ma laugh all the time
And you make my Mom
upset as soon as you step in
Sorry aunty.
Don't fall for what she says
She is a very bad girl.
- Karan shut up!
I hope they send 150 pieces. I'll pay
after I've checked the consignment
if I find a one-piece short in
the shipment..- God! One piece..
how much poorer will it make you
how much richer will he become?
You women are forever
cribbing over one Rupee..
..one potato one coriander leaf..
why fight over trivia?
- it isn't about money. it's principle
it is about principles.
But why discuss principles with you?
Rhea shut up.
Yes Mihir come over park the car
Mihir is coming?
- Yes.. I forgot to ask you..
How did you find Mihir?
- Okay.
But what is Mihir doing here?
- I thought we'd have lunch together
Hey. - Hi Karan. - How are you?
- Good. - Tell him hi. - Hi.
So how was your shopping?
I wasn't shopping. it was business
I'm hungry. Where
are we going for lunch?
Oh! No.
- What happened? - Lunch reminds me..
I have to meet Diana.
- Who's this lady?
Just a friend. Met her a
week ago. Strictly business
She is damn hot Mihir
you should meet her. Okay.
Not your first lunch date with Diana?
- Lunch yes. For the first time
Couple of days ago
we went out for dinner
You go ahead and have lunch.
I'll see you afterwards
for coffee. Got to run
Karan!
I know a great joint for grilled fish.
Rhea.
- Yes sorry.
I know a great joint for grilled fish.
I don't like grilled fish
Where to? China garden? Delhi Durbar?
I forgot.. Mamma has cooked lunch
Will you drop me home?
Yes sure why not.
Next to your place
there's a Dosa Diner
Today's my birthday.
Strange! Karan never told me.
- Karan must've forgotten
Karan is such a.. he is such a..
Anyway happy birthday.
- Thanks.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday dear Mihir.
Strange you never
reminded me it's your birthday
Sorry I forgot that you forget.
- Never mind. Eat cake
Something tells me I'm
forgetting something
How dare you?
- Daina. - Daina.
You are a very bad boy.
- Listen I am really very sorry.
Enough of your apologies!
You forget that you invited me?
I waited for you for ages
You must be Rhea.
Don't ask me how I know you're Rhea
And you are Mihir.
Happy birthday.
What sort of birthday..?
No champagne?
To new friends.
- I don't drink. - Wow.
A man who doesn't drink and
is man enough to admit to it..
I am impressed. Karan
I really liked your friend.
I think he is cute.
- Cute?
Mihir you didn't tell me what you do.
- I run a computer company.
Micro India
We design computer systems
Really? All the computers in
my office were sourced from you?
Wiz Entertainment.
- You're Diana Fernandez?
Right. - No wonder your
voice sounded familiar.
We've spoken several
times on the phone
You actually spoke to her
or you heard
of her conversations over the phone?
After so many
conversations now we meet.. amazing
How amazing
Karan what a boring song.
- Awful song
No way I love this song.
For the first time I
danced with a girl to that song
So sweet.
- Close dance.
How cute. Me and you Mihir
come let's dance.
Just calm down.
How strange. For the many times that
they talked business they never met
One chance meeting and
they've taken to each other
Somewhat too fast. Who'll
say it's their first meeting?.
Karan shut up.
Sometimes the first look is enough.
Sometimes it takes so many meetings
What..?
- True
Wow
I mean Mihir and Diana..
you know.. Mihir and Diana
they're so unlike
I don't know how they liked each other
They're so different
Karan. Have you heard that phrase
that opposites attract? - Yes.
it's widely accepted that
the more varied the match the
better it is for the relationship
She makes up for her husband's flaws;
he makes up for his
wife's shortcomings
Which makes for a perfect marriage.
Wow Rhea you ought
to be writing a book
Principles of Marriage by Rhea
Seriously.
- Good evening everybody.
Tonight I'm happy.. elated
Guess why?
I just got engaged Mihir and I..
..and the person instrumental
in getting us together..is..
Rhea. Cheers.
if Rhea liked Mihir
if Mihir liked Rhea..
then you and I
wouldn’t have been here today
Karan tried his best to make
Rhea and Mihir fall in love
Then I materialized
I guess I got lucky
So.. cheers to Rhea once
again Oh Mihir I love you
Please give me a chance to explain
Rhea.
- How dare you Karan?
You've no right to scorn me.
Scorn? I was arranging your marriage.
- Marriage?
You know because of all this..
I went away to Paris to avoid this
You know it..
..because out there no one
would be arranging weddings for me
I don't get it!
Why won't people leave a girl
in peace until she's married?
is marriage the sole
purpose of life for us?
Without a man in her life a
woman's life is incomplete?
What tangent are you getting at?
- And you Karan..?
I never expected you
to behave like this
How could you be one of them?
- Come on Rhea..
..over something so little..
- it's nothing so little
it is about my life. My personal life.
Not everything in life is a joke
So what now? Do we
sit down for a quarrel?
Forget it You don't
get what I'm saying
Of course I don't
understand what you say.
I thought you and Mihir..
- What about Mihir and I..?
What is wrong with you?
How can you think like this?
Did you ever ask me what I want?
I only want to see you happy
You think I'll be happy with Mihir?
Will you be happy with a guy like me?
Come on tell me.
Now why are you quite?
Enough is enough..
Listen Rhea.
- Don't follow me Karan!
Love is the problem isn't it?
Karan was right. A boy and
a girl can never be friends
Because love always comes in the way
Come on Rhea.
How long will you hide
your feelings from each other?
if you expect Karan to
make the first move forget it
That fool doesn't even
realize he's in love
No one knows Karan more than I
Every year he forgets
my birthday but
..each little word
about you he remembers
if not love what else is it?
He loves you Rhea. He
loves you very much.
True love is so hard to come by
it happens only once in a lifetime
You are lucky.
To have found this
joy twice you're lucky
Simple. I'm not a nice guy
Not a nice guy and
when it comes to girls..
first class scoundrel.
- He's one of us
You get it?
For the first time in my life
I wanted to do good for a girl
Did I do anything wrong?
- No
I did.
- You did..? - Big mistake I did
Big mistake.. I broke her heart
The tears.. welled up from her heart.
I made her cry.
- Made her cry?
Very bad.
When her tears stream down here..
..why do I ache in here?
Her eyes her tears
And here it aches?
is this any justice?
- No
Oh yes it's justice This is justice
if the burden of both tears and pain
were hers what justice would it be?
Were her tears and her pain to
be mine justice would be done.
Understood?
Understood.
- What can you understand?
She says I don't understand anything.
if I never understood anything..
how come I understand
What am I and what is she?
Understand?
Understood. She's coming for you
She isn't after me.
- Behind you
Hide the glasses.
No drinking in front of a lady.
But I can drink because I'm
not a nice guy. Pass my glass.
Karan come home.
Rhea I'm not a nice guy.
I'll leave brother.
I am not a nice man.
"I and you.."
Let our sighs caress
Let subdued heartbeats race
This moment craves.. a tryst..
"I and you.."
Your eyes let me enchant
in your arms take me as I relent
This moment craves.. a tryst..
"I and you.."
Let our sighs caress
Slumber's caress
smears the kohl in your eyes
Oh was it a fleeting
carnival of dreams..?
Let desire consume us body and soul
Leave yourself to rock
amid abandon and ecstasy
This moment craves.. a tryst..
"I and you.."
Let our sighs caress
Caress me..
like symphony's strings
Darkness hidden in your tresses..
let loose liberate my nights
Wait till night's veil
slips away from her bosom
Wait for dew to moisten her petals
But this moment craves.. a tryst..
"I and you.."
Let our sighs caress
Let subdued heartbeats race
This moment craves.. a tryst..
"I and you.."
Calm down.
Don't take God's name in vain
Where's Rhea?
- She isn't coming
You had a fight with her?
No she is just busy.
My ring. Come on.
I left it in the car
You don't say shit inside a church
We were supposed to come together
no? I waited for you.
I got busy over here.
Just a second.
I can't even face her
idiot even his tie isn't matching
What must she think of me?
Why did we take so long to
know each other's minds?
Whatever happened was wrong
Why does it feel so perfect?
Friends.
We are gathered together..
I've lost her forever
I don't want to lose him ever
On the eve of Mihir
and Diana Fernandez.
is this the end of our relationship..?
The beginning of a new relationship..?
As long as you both shall live.
I do.
How can I start this conversation?
Please say something Karan
I am sorry Rhea.
I am really really sorry.
Whatever happened should
never have come to pass
I mean I should never have done that
I am sorry.
We ought to get married.
Yes we ought to get married.
- Why?
Why do you want to marry me Karan?
Don't get me wrong Rhea
- You're getting me wrong
Do you feel that
whatever happened was wrong?
Yes Rhea. The mistake was mine
Then we ought not to
commit another mistake
We ought not to make another mistake
by marrying for the wrong reasons
Don't get me wrong.
- Enough Karan
You need not say anything more
Need not say anything more
"I and you.."
From the outset
I never liked that Mihir
He was always evading
questions How annoying
What makes you laugh?
- I'm not laughing Bobby
You've been laughing at me
forever on the sly. Sarcastically
Where are you going with those
Huge bags? Our fight is next week
What happened my child?
I'm leaving
I don't know where .. for how long
For four years I kept you away
from your country your relatives
Away from everybody.
This time I want to go away alone
I want to come to terms with
my life with myself on my own
Let me be on my own Mamma please
Rhea my child..
home for me is wherever you are
I'll never even ask you
why we're going or where
But don't tear yourself away from me
I'm coming with you. Period
Wait I'm coming
My darling baby
God can't be everywhere.
That's why He made mothers
Love you dear. I love you.
Karan. Have you
finished your breakfast?
What's the matter? it's been two days
and you're completely uncommunicative
And there's no news of Rhea.
Have the two of you had a fight?
Karan can you pick
up the phone please.
This boy is too much
Hello hi Sheila how are you? Yes.
Just a minute Sheila. Sheila
I'll have to call you back later.
You're not listening
you aren't talking
you aren't answering phones
doorbells
Just like your Daddy
Whose son is he after all?
You..?
Can I come in?
Karan.
- Dad.
What are you doing here?
Coming directly from
the airport to see you.
How have you been?
- I'm fine
it shows. How's Rhea?
What do you want to ask?
I want to know why you're running
away from your life. Like I did
What..?
in my personal life..
I took a lot of wrong decisions
which I have come to regret
I had the loveliest the most
loving wife in the whole word
But I never could understand her
Finally I realised how much I
had been given and what I had lost
Every father wants his son
to follow in his footsteps.
I must be.. the first father in
the whole world who prays everyday..
may my son never become like me
But sometimes when I look at you..
I fear I may have passed on
to you my legacy of failures.
I fear.. you may lose faith
in relationships because of me
But then I look at Rhea
and my fears are allayed
I feel she's the one who
can extricate my son..
..from the orbs of my shadows
Rhea called me in Paris yesterday to
tell me that she's leaving forever
She'd say no more but I realised
you've proven that you're my son
No one else could ever
break a heart so full of love
Dad I'm in love with Rhea. But
how can she love a guy like me
it's what we fail to
grasp about women.
How can they love morons like us?
17 years ago
I broke someone's heart..
..someone I ought to have worshipped
God never gave me a second chance
You're about to make the same mistake.
Know it He won't
give you a next chance
Karan where are you going?
After all I'm your son Dad.
in matters of the heart
I'm slow on the uptake
But now that I know I'm not
wasting 17 years trying to find her
The second chance God never gives.
We ought to seize it ourselves..
like my son is doing
Like our son..?
For 3 hours we've
been only 2 inches apart
and we don't know each other"
You rifled my bag?
Rhea Rhea Prakash.
Why must you spend on my tickets?
- Yes how are we related?
Karan Kapoor.
You're organising the wedding and
you don't know who the bride is?
Sameer is no longer part of my life
But to start afresh one
needs a good companion
in the end Hum-Tum might
end up falling in love
Have you heard of the phrase opposites attract...
I only want to see you happy.
- You think I'll be happy with Mihir?
Will you be happy with a guy like me?
Mention me after the kids and Tommy
and I'll hack you into small bits..
and I'll feed you to Tommy."
Okay I'm sorry. No more kids-or-Tommy
I'll always love you
more than anyone else
more than anyone else.
Tea or coffee sir.
- No thanks.
Okay I'll have a cup
of coffee with.. - Okay.
With very little milk.
- Just about two spoons of milk.
A teaspoon of sugar.
- Brown sugar. - Brown sugar.
You know why?
- Why sir.
Because she loves me.
Sometimes the first look is enough.
Sometimes it takes so many meetings"
I think I'll miss you.
Words..
my eyes spoke..
had you read..
you'd never lose me..
Wait..
if that word.. you ever said..
in loneliness we wouldn't walk
Once a moment craved.. a tryst..
yours and mine
I and you.
Only problem with Hum-Tum..
without you I'm incomplete
Many relationships fall apart because
people can't express themselves..
they can't talk their hearts out.
if you got something to tell someone..
just go ahead and say it.
Don't wait it might be too late
Rhea couldn’t
understand my love because..
I was the one who
couldn't fathom my love.
Now she's gone..
and I never got
a chance to express myself.
Out of this book..
I seek no riches no fame.
I only want to tell her..
how much I love her
That's it.
You believe you'll meet her again?
She will meet me. I'm sure..
because life’s a long while
Rain in January..?
it doesn't rain in January
it was bound to happen yes Karan?
Because whenever we've met..
something always happens
You read the book?
How did you like it?
Reminded me of a friend
Ever told you about
this friend of mine?
Never
I met him many years ago
And you kept seeing him..
till he became my best friend
Then he fell in love with you.
Why did you walk away?
Because he didn't stop me
I don't like your friend one bit
Not a word against my friend
Then what do I say?
What you've never said
That I'll love you more
than the kids and Tommy?
You better! Else I'll
cut you into little bits..
I love you Rhea.
I told you there's one story about
us. - is this the end of our story?
No now's when our story begins
Where are you going? You
didn't hear what he said?
Story isn't over
Who's this guy?
Why is his cot so
close to my daughter's?
He's a new-born!
- You never know these guys
No sooner than they're born they
start flirting with pretty girls
Saw that..?
He's using kids' sign
language to call my daughter
if he's like that I
wonder what his mother's like
When did you see his mother?
- Just a joke
Look your baby is cute.
When did you see his mother?
- I saw his dad. Doesn't resemble him
I thought he must resemble his mother
You and I..
Because I love you
Boys get together and go out
Girls get together and chat
How will we get together?
Deep in my heart you and I