My story travels far and wide across
these beautiful valleys of Ooty
Like roses, and thorns
Here it was that I became
someone's wife... and a woman
Love, devotion, faith
and sacrifice...
it was here that I got to know
what they really meant
Here it was that I practically
touched my life
At this place, I felt the cold
feeling of death, touch my body
There was a group of college students
on a picnic, that particular night
Little did I know that
what was happening then...
would also affect my life
You must do it.
The bottle stopped on you
That's the rule, isn't it guys?
Stop it!
Nisha, stop there!
Where are you going?
You might have to kiss
a lion or a tiger ahead!
Why're you bothering me?
I'm going to find you anyway!
Stop bothering me!
Where are you hiding?
She hasn't gone into that
bungalow, has she?
Nisha! That bungalow
doesn't belong to us!
Come on out
If you get caught, there's no saying
how many guys you'll have to kiss!
Listen to me!
Give me a kiss, please!
Rohit!
Who's there?
Who is it?
Raghu
Yes, sir?
Is someone here to meet me?
There's nobody, sir
Inspector?
Has there been a mishap
in the hills?
It's a strange incident
The police can't understand.
Only you can help us
He's the girl's boyfriend, sir
He has a broken bone
in his shoulder
He can't believe...
how his girlfriend...
attacked him like a wild beast
Where's the girl?
The doctors aren't letting
anyone close to her
If you wish, you can take
a look at her from there
I've awakened! I'm awake!
I'm not going to spare him!
He'll have to come!
I'm awake! And he'll have to come!
They'll all awaken.
Like hell they will
I'm not going to spare him!
No way!
I've awakened...
I'm awake!
What are you staring at,
you swine?
You think you will stop me?
Me?
No!
I've awakened!
I'm awake!
I've already given her two injections.
They have no effect on her, sir
It won't have any effect!
What you think is a disease
of the brain...
is in fact a disease
chasing man for centuries
No matter what you do...
you can't cure this disease
Because you can treat
only human beings
Not erratic souls
And this is an erratic soul
But you are not going
to believe me
Because it does not suit
your profession to believe me
You weren't the one who was attacked.
It was the girl herself
We have very little time
Her body won't be able to tolerate
the spirit for very long. It'll explode
Do you want to save her?
Where did it happen?
Where?
I was standing there
When I heard her cries...
I ran and came here
She was standing right there
Calm and quiet
What did you feel when
you got close to her?
I thought she was upto mischief
to bring me closer
What else?
Was there any other sign?
A gust of wind that could perhaps
have meant to tell you something?
No
Didn't you feel as if you were
being drawn away by the hand...
and you had no control
over yourself?
No
Did you see someone else's face
in hers, when you got closer?
No
Did you see terror in her eyes?
It all happened so quickly
that I felt...
Oh yes! The force with which
she pushed me, it felt as if...
It sure tells us that it wasn't
the doing of a human being
It was an evil spirit at work
Spirits draw strength from places
like this...
where an accident
might have taken place
At places where...
where someone has sinned or where
something foul has taken place
By coming here, you have
awakened a passive spirit
Manoj here.
- Go on
She has left us
This is only the beginning
What does that mean?
Lts goal hasn't yet
been accomplished
If it's really a spirit...
can't we stop it?
What transpired here?
Whose soul is it?
What does it want?
It's all a secret
A secret...
that lies buried somewhere here
Unless we unravel the mystery...
it'll be difficult
to stop the spirit
Looks like lightning
will strike again
On whom? And where?
Nobody knows
This is a city of peace
The air here
is unique
It's peaceful here
Everything is at peace
There's sunshine,
there's shade...
there are moonlit nights
Beautiful girls throng the place
There are dreams,
there are celebrations...
and parties for the young
There's fun and frolic,
and merry-making everywhere
This is a city of peace
The ambience here is unique
Everything is at peace
There's peace and quiet
There are secrets...
and there's love in hearts
There are friendships...
even foes are buddies
There are desires,
there's comfort...
here you can reach
for the Moon
Summer and winter...
you have every season here
This is a city of peace
The atmosphere here is unique
Everything here is at peace
What insolence is this?
You take me for a sidekick?
It's you who's treating me
like a sidekick, Aditya
It doesn't seem as
if you've married me
It appears as if you've bought me!
For three hours, I've been
sitting all by myself...
waiting for you to
cast a glance at me
But you can't find the time
from your merry-making
Don't you know this
is a business party?
They've come in a delegation
from Hong Kong
Let me go in
Apart from listening to your crap,
I've also got to run my business
All right. Run your business,
whether your family lives or not
Everything here is at peace
Everything is peaceful
I can't understand where
the girl went from the party
Why did she have to leave all alone?
Aditya... what is the matter?
Despite such an accident, she hasn't
as much as suffered a scratch
What's this, if not a miracle?
Ask her to be careful
in future
She shouldn't be driving after
having so many sleeping pills
It's like this, Mr Aditya...
she badly needs your care
right now
God has saved her
Or you had surely lost her today
Must you punish me like this?
What if something
had happened to you?
For how long will we keep
deceiving ourselves?
I'm sick of fighting all the time
It's time we separated, Aditya
Don't say that, Sanjana
It's of no use
You're not the same Aditya anymore
You're not the man
I fell in love with
In just a year,
you've changed so much
What's gotten into you?
There's a chasm between us...
- I'll do away with the chasm
I need just one opportunity
Let's go someplace
far away from here
Someplace where only
you and I are there
How about that delegation
from Hong Kong?
They can wait. But I don't
want to lose you again
Where would you like to go?
I want to take you somewhere
far away...
where no voice calls out to us...
except we, to each other
Ooty
I want it to start there
all over again
That's where we first met
That's where we fell in love
I'll do the make up for you!
Lay off!
- Where will you go?
Lay off, I say!
- I'm going to colour you!
No, Sanjana! No!
Hurry up!
How long will you make me wait?
Even if you do come across me...
please do pull
a veil across your face
Our wedding isn't very far away...
I must pine.
You must long for me too
That's the problem
with my heart
You tell me how am
I to remain quiet
Even if I do come across you...
I ought to pull
a veil across my face
Our wedding isn't very far away...
I must pine.
You must pine too
That's the problem
with my heart
You tell me how I am
to remain quiet
These are the times when
I must pester you and flatter you
These are the times
I must try you out
I hope you get the message, my love
This is just what my problem is
I can no longer bear
the distance between us
How will I tell you what
I'm going through, my love
The earth and the skies
will bear witness...
you and I will come together
Even if I look into your eyes...
I wish you would
veil your face
If I were to leave this world,
and never return again...
what would you do, my love?
From God, I would snatch you
I'll make you belong to me
Till as long as we live,
we shall never part
This promise,
we will never break...
even if it angers God
Should I call you to meet me...
I hope you will veil your face
Our wedding isn't very far away
I must pine. So must you
My heart is the problem...
you tell me, how am I
to remain quiet?
What are you thinking about?
- Nothing
I'll go and change
Who's that?
Who is it?
Who?
Who are you?
Who is it?
What's wrong with you?
There was so much of agony
in her cry
She's in deep trouble
We must help her, Aditya
We could help, if there
really was someone there
There's no one
I've heard her screaming.
Not once, but many times over
You can go ahead and think
that I'm mad
For me, however, it's as true
as you standing here before me
If it's true, why didn't
I hear her voice?
Why didn't I realise
her suffering?
You've given up realising anyone's
suffering long ago, Aditya
Sanjana! This is the root of
all your problems
You neither sleep, nor keep awake
after taking these pills
You hear and talk any nonsense.
- I can't go to sleep without it
So don't go to sleep.
I'll stay up with you
We'll chat and I'll hold
your hand all night
When you should have been with me,
you kept running away from me
Times were when I had
so much to talk you about...
and you always chose to keep quiet
I suffered everything in silence
I kept awake, while you slept
Had you steadied me then, I wouldn't
have had the need for these pills today
But I can't do without them anymore
I can't
Aditya? You?
Without even informing us,
the Managing Director...
of the Park chain of hotels
is here in person!
I can't believe it
Do I take it as a stroke of good luck
or is this an inspection, Mr M.D.?
No M.D. A friend is here
to meet a friend
By the way, where is your husband?
Someone has cast an evil eye
on your love
Your love was a shining example
for everybody in Ooty...
and you go through such problems?
She couldn't go to sleep
when you were away
And she now swallows sleeping pills
in your presence
I can't believe it
Sanjana's quite a wise girl.
You haven't?
You could say I'm the one
who's not wise enough
I'm the one to blame
for whatever has happened
But I want to make my love an
example for others all over again
For this, I need help
from the two of you
Just don't worry
The two of us got you married.
We even gave the bride away
It's our problem now. Just see how
we solve it between the two of us
Where is she at the moment?
Madam...
Who are you?
I was told at the hotel that
the two of you have arrived
I was asked to clean the place
Why hasn't Robert come? We've been
waiting for him since last evening
Where has he gone?
- Even his wife doesn't know
He's been missing for eight months.
- Eight months?
Yes, Madam. Even the police
couldn't find him
No one knows what's happened of him
or where he has gone
His wife is in trouble, Madam
Do you know where she lives?
He had started changing
He did very strange things
He used to slog like an animal
in that bungalow
And suddenly, he had started dreading
the very mention of the bungalow
He'd make some excuse or the other
to send me to do the chores
And one day, he just vanished
Why didn't you call and tell Aditya?
- I did, Madam
I called him on his cell-phone
from the post office
I also told the master that
before Robert disappeared...
he had started hearing
strange voices
He used to shut his ears and
rant like a madman all day
He used to wake me up in the
middle of the night and say...
that unless I went out
and stopped the voices...
he'd walk out on me
But I could have stopped the voices
only if I heard any
Only Robert could hear them
What sort of voice was it?
Of someone crying out in pain
The fire rages on both sides
Bodies longing to be
consumed by the fires!
There you are...
The fish escapes,
the shoe gets caught...
this is how, very often,
lovers go awry
Thank you
On an evening...
amidst rainfall...
and a romantic setting...
let the song of love
be heard
There's fire
There's longing
And a sense of failing balance
Let me tell my lover
something today
All those promises we made...
all those oaths we took together...
you are the one who
brought dawn into my life
Do you recollect?
Do you remember?
Beautiful days we spent...
and our nights were lovely too
You are the one who
brought dawn into my life
Do you remember?
We stayed awake all nights
We were lost in each other
We spoke about our love
for each other
Out of loneliness...
we met each other every day
In your arms, I found solace
and spent precious moments of my life
Your beautiful moon-like face...
I etched on my heart
We were so close...
I happened to be your destiny
On my lips was your name
all the time...
do you remember?
Yes, I do remember
I do remember
In daylight, in my dreams...
you were the one
always in my sight
You are my life,
you are what my story is all about...
you are my destiny
I loved you and
took you for my own
You gave me a place
in your heart
With love, you lent colour
to my dreams
Your lips I kissed...
in your arms, I swayed...
in your eyes, I dwelt
Do you remember?
Yes, I do remember
I sure do remember
All those promises we made...
All those oaths
we took together
You were the only who
brought dawn into my life
Do you remember?
Yes, I remember
Did you hear the gunshot?
Sanjana, it wasn't a gunshot.
It was the door
No, Aditya. I heard a gunshot
It wasn't a gunshot, Sanjana.
It was the door
Why didn't you tell me about Robert?
He used to hear
these noises too
His wife telephoned you
to tell you about it
So why did you hide it from me?
I have so many servants, Sanjana
Someone goes crazy,
someone disappears...
and someone hears strange noises.
I can't keep track of everyone, can I?
I'm tired
This woman has been wailing away!
You heard her. Didn't you, Madam?
Only you and I can listen to it
Nobody else can hear it...
not my wife, not my master
I'm fed up, Madam...
I'm fed up!
My brains are going to explode...
these noises will blow my mind
Save me, Madam. Please save me
Or I'll go mad, Madam
I'll go mad!
The noises I hear,
the things I feel...
why doesn't Aditya feel them too?
I want to save my marriage.
At any cost
I brought Aditya here
from Mumbai...
to save our marriage
from falling apart
But having come here, I feel
as if the rift between us...
has widened, instead
of making up
Sanjana, whether someone
believes you or not...
I know you're speaking the truth
Have you heard of Vastu Shastra?
At times, when your house isn't
properly planned...
you begin to get strange ideas
Maybe this is responsible for
whatever you're going through
Whether someone believes
it or not...
I have faith in the
science of Vastu
I think we must consult
Professor Agni Swaroop
Yes. He has great insight
And he can set right what is wrong
Is everything all right?
I'd like to believe
that everything is all right
But my body says there
is something here...
which is not right.
And the body never lies
You might find my question strange
But you must think before
you answer me
Go ahead
Do you believe in ghosts?
In spirits? Good and evil?
Spirits that help and
spirits that torment?
Spirits that long to accomplish
what has remained unfinished
Have you ever heard
of tormented souls?
What?
Has the breeze ever tried to whisper
something into your ears?
You don't find things suddenly
disappearing from your sight...
and coming back again?
Strange voices, I mean
A stunning cry
Feeling of a presence,
despite being all alone
Do you feel as if you're wide awake
and yet, you're seeing a nightmare?
Yes... how did you get to know?
Which means, there is someone
There is someone...
who wants to assert himself,
despite being dead
What's up there?
How many days since you
opened this door?
It's almost two years
But it feels as if someone has
been frequenting this place
If the lemon does not change
its colour till sunset...
you can assume that everything
is all right
Or else...
- Or else?
Or else, you could
face grave problems
Pray that the lemon does not
turn red by this evening
I told you! There is someone!
There is something in our house!
Those gunshots...
There is someone in our house, Aditya!
There's a spirit haunting our house!
Else, Professor Agni Swaroop's lemon
would not have turned red!
It wouldn't have turned red!
I'm not lying, Aditya!
Ask Priya, if you don't believe me
There's a spirit in our house
I have felt its presence
Who do you think you are?
You're a professor? Are you?
You make money out of scaring women!
- Mind your tongue!
There's a ghost in my house?
Is there?
I'll have your blood!
I'll report you to the police if
you even look at my house again!
Call the police! Go ahead!
You don't know who I am!
I'm Aditya Dhanraj!
Call the cops!
- I've dealt with your kind!
But why isn't he taking the phone?
Actually, Adi and
Sanjana have gone out
Let him not take the call,
if he doesn't want to
I'm not fond of lecturing him
like a school kid
lt'll be kind of him if he doesn't
ruin the respect I've built...
over the years, in brawls
and scraps
Yes, Uncle
Yes, my foot! Can't you
make him see reason?
He's no ordinary man
The press always keep nosing around
for such stories
They've splashed the news
on the front-page
Anyway, I haven't called to
talk to him about his exploits
I've something important
to discuss with him
Yes, Uncle. I'll tell him
Adi, you've got to
reach Bombay tomorrow
Uncle says the delegation
from Hong Kong...
can stay for another day
at the most
If you don't have a meeting with them,
not only will you lose millions...
your relations with them
will be over too
I'm glad it happened.
I was fed up of this place anyway
We'll take the afternoon flight back
Priya, will you do
something for me?
Professor, at least hear me out
Sanjana is terribly embarrassed
Or why would she send me here
to ask for your forgiveness?
She herself doesn't know
what got into Aditya
She wanted to come here to
meet you, Professor
But there was this call
from Bombay suddenly...
and she had to leave with Aditya
She hasn't gone at all!
Pardon me?
Till that power accomplishes
what it wants to...
forget Mumbai, it won't let
Sanjana even leave this city
Her husband wants to
take her away, isn't it?
So let him!
Professor, they've already left
They've left
But they haven't reached there
The road is blocked, sir.
It'll take 5 or 6 hours
for the traffic to clear
D'you want some tea or coffee?
- 3 cups of tea
There's a landslide ahead, sir.
The road's blocked for 5 or 6 hours
D'you want me to look
for a lodge for you?
If there are unseasonal rains
or a storm, or a fog...
descending in summer, what can
you or I do against an act of God?
You're being funny!
It's a contract worth millions
If I don't get to Mumbai by tomorrow
morning, I'll have lost everything
You can't get a flight from Ooty.
You'll have to drive to Coimbatore
But there has to be a way.
Some way
No, nothing can be
done about it today
Even if we were to have a chopper
flown in from Bangalore...
it'd take us a day to get
clearance from the army
So call your father.
He'll handle everything
No way. I don't want to
listen to his sermons again
Suppose I take a flight from Bangalore,
instead of Coimbatore?
I must take the flight from
Bangalore tomorrow morning
For that, I'll have to drive
all night through Madhu Malai...
to reach Bangalore at
six tomorrow morning
It isn't a safe road. And you...
- Go ahead, Aditya
I'll wait here for you
As soon as my work is over,
I'll rush here
And don't you dare take those
sleeping pills in my absence
I don't want you to see ghosts
all over again
The ghost's actually in the bottle.
Let it remain there
Stop being stubborn
and pack your bags
I can't leave you alone
in this house
Please, Priya. Go away. I want to
stay here and find out the truth
What truth are you talking about?
Professor Agni has told you
that there's a spirit here
You have yourself seen
the lemon change colors
And even if what
he says is not true...
where's the need for you
to take the risk?
There is a need
I want to find out whether a spirit
is indeed trying to talk to me...
or is it a streak of madness
I want to know whether what I have
felt through the days and nights...
is true, or is it an effect
of the sleeping pills I consume
I want to find out whether what
Professor Agni says is true...
or is Aditya? It's necessary
for me to have the answers
Very necessary
Who are you?
It's my house!
So long as I live, I will not
let you take over my house!
If you think you can drive me
away by scaring me...
it's just not happening!
I'm not going to be scared!
Till such time as I live,
you can't snatch my house from me!
You're going to leave this place.
Not I!
Go away!
Tell your friend that
I don't want any trouble
I'm a simple man.
Let me get on with my life
I don't want to meddle in
anybody's family affairs
But, Professor, you must...
- Not another word from you! Shut up!
You think I will help you again?
So her husband will get
physical with me again?
This time, I will raise my hand too
No
Get out!
I've seen her for myself, Professor
I've seen its face.
It's a woman
What's all this about, Professor?
Earlier, she only
got hear the voices
And now she's seeing things!
What's happening?
You're not connected with
that incident, are you?
Which incident?
This incident took place
in the forests behind your house
Exactly where you
heard the gunshot
It happened on May 16
On the same night, you met
with an accident too
About two hours
after this tragedy
On recovering, you insisted that
you come to Ooty with your husband
Whereas, your husband was willing to
take you to any part of the world
What does that mean?
The spirit in your house and
the spirit which killed Nisha...
are one and the same.
- Which means, she's after me?
I don't know
I don't know whether
she wants to harm you
But one thing is for sure
She wants to say something to you
She wants to tell you something.
- What?
We can decide that only when
we get to the spot
Over there
The boy took me there
You've got to go there.
On your own
If you think I'm scared
to go there myself...
you are not entirely wrong
But believe me...
that isn't the only reason why
I'm sending you there on your own
What else is it?
Whoever it is...
she wants to talk to her
There is something she wants
to tell only Sanjana
If she wants to meet her...
she'll have to go all alone
We'll stay here. In the car
We're not staying here.
We're going with her
Priya, I'll go there.
On my own
Sanjana, you're...
- Please, Priya
What do you want?
What are you getting at?
You wanted me to come here
And here I am
Now tell me
Speak
Professor, I think...
You're right. That gun
was bought from this shop
On the 2nd of September, 1988
After that, till March 2000...
it was brought here for
servicing, every six months
For a year and half now,
this gun wasn't sent here
Whose gun is it?
Who holds the licence?
It's a retired army colonel
He had bought the gun
for his personal use
What's the colonel's name?
- Colonel Arjun Malik
The address?
Yes?
One moment, Madam
Sir, there's a call for you
I've found the gun
you used to kill an innocent
What rubbish are you talking?
Colt 8mm, Serial FB66
That's the number of
your gun, isn't it?
I don't have the time
to listen to your nonsense
Don't hang up on me!
What you have done has made life
miserable for me and my husband
My life is plunged in turmoil for
the disgusting things you've done!
To overcome my problems,
I'll have to meet you
What if I choose not to meet you?
In which case, I'll hand
the gun to the police
The police will find out
whom you killed and why
All right.
Tomorrow at eleven
Where did you find the gun?
And in what circumstances?
Why did you kill the girl?
And under what circumstances?
Don't talk like a moron!
Why would I kill her?
Because this just what
people like you always do
You trap innocent girls, make
them victims of your lust...
and once you've had enough of them,
you silence them with the gun...
so that you can keep your
ugly face hidden behind a mask!
No father on earth can do to his
daughter, what you say I've done!
She was my daughter
But as my daughter,
she gave me no comfort
She was mentally ill
I had her admitted to
the asylum several times
But she would always escape
She once locked me up
in my own room...
and ran away. Forever
After she had left, I discovered
that my revolver was missing
I lodged a complaint with the police,
I had ads published in the papers...
I looked for her everywhere
And my search came to end
when you telephoned me
It was obvious that my daughter
would never come back to me
The Colonel's daughter goes missing,
she then dies...
and her spirit then compels you
to come here from Mumbai
She shows you the gun and
tells you her address
What is more, you even
get to see her
Why's she doing all this?
We have no way of finding out
There is a way
There's no need for you
to go to her anymore
If you wish, she could come to you
With the help of this book
But you will be playing with death
To begin with, you must chant
the mantras in that book...
and summon her when
you're all alone
Another thing: Such spirits
are very stubborn
She will come at your behest
But she will leave
only when she wants to
What if she refuses to leave?
In that case, Sanjana will meet
with the same fate as Nisha
Think it over
I've decided, Professor
Her secret is somehow
connected with my secret
I want to know why she's playing
these games with me
What made her call me here
all the way from Mumbai?
Till such time as I have the answer,
I will have no peace
I want to meet her, look
into her eyes, and ask her
Even if I have to lay down my life
There's a particular way of reading
this book. I'll explain it to you
Feelings help me
to overcome distances
Extend a hand...
so I may touch you
You've even started drinking now?
Intoxication finds new heights
when you drink
Tonight is a night of mischief
Tonight, I won't be able
to sleep without you
You had left me far away
All alone. In despair
You have made me pine so much
But tonight isn't a night of pining.
We ought to shower love
For ages, this dry parched earth
hasn't had a drop of water
Tonight, however,
it will see a storm
Don't say anything...
just listen to me
Let the fires rage
Let me be charred
For very long, this spark
has been buried in the embers
You're acting like a nervous child
It's not the first time
we're doing it
I won't let your wife know anything
even this time
Who's dead?
What have you been hiding from me?
Who was she?
Who was she, I say!
Who?
The last time I came to Ooty,
it was raining very heavily
What I didn't know was that the
storm would walk right up to my door
I've lost my way
Will you please help me?
Come on in
It's cold outside
You're drenched
Sit by the fireplace, I'll
arrange some clothes for you
This is all I could find.
You'll have to manage
On a cold night...
when I'm feeling mischievous and
carry the burden of sleepiness...
I'd have gone away to my house,
if I were in my city
Pardon me?
You're not going to ask me
to leave, are you?
On a night like this,
I just don't feel like...
leaving this fireplace
and going out
There's a guest-room here.
You can rest there, if you wish
Despite putting all the woes
in the world together...
when nature still couldn't
achieve anything...
it gave you those eyes
There's so much of feeling
in your eyes
I made this tune as an acknowledgement
of your loneliness
Distances between hearts are
overcome with feelings
Say nothing tonight
Just savour your loneliness
Heat and desires
burn out in failure
Like the lamp,
I burn every night
The lamp that burns
for everybody to see...
is the flame that
consigns me to anonymity
Whenever your name
appears with mine...
I wonder why people
burn with envy - Malini
If the Board of Directors' meeting
is not held tomorrow...
One moment
I'll call you later
Don't stop
Don't get so close to me.
I could destroy you
And I want to be destroyed
In love with you,
I have begun to blossom
A look at you...
and I have begun to flower
Such is the manner in which
I've fallen in love with you...
I'm going to pieces
In love with you,
I have begun to blossom
Should you make me
suffer like this...
my longing will drive me mad
I've found the one
I've been looking for
I was restless, I was thirsty
through many lifetimes
From our bodies,
we're becoming one in soul
Such is the manner in which
I've fallen in love with you...
I've begun to go to pieces
In love with you,
I have begun to blossom
Our bodies will melt
The fires will rage...
our hearts will go berserk
Should my lips meet yours...
sparks will emanate
even from the dew
We're crossing all limits, my love
Such is my love for you...
I'm going to pieces
In love with you,
I have begun to blossom
What's wrong with you?
It's not loaded
Where did you get the gun from?
I lead the life of a wanderer.
What I might need and when...
and when I might need this...
who knows?
Not every man is as decent...
as good looking and
as honest as you are
It takes time for the romance to go
out of the lives of married couples
And you've stopped telephoning me
in just a year or two
I swear, I was about
to give you a call
I'm glad you called instead
It's difficult to get through
from Ooty
Are you alone, Aditya?
What does that mean?
Is someone else there with you?
Yes, there is
Who? Is it Ajay?
Me. And my loneliness
My cellphone is ringing.
I'll call you in a while
No... I'll call you
Thank you. Thank you for the honour
You're an amazing man
You can share my bed with me
But you just wouldn't want
the world to know about it
And the fool that I am...
I thought you were different
from other men
I was so wrong
Aditya, why haven't you
told your wife about me?
Why didn't you tell her that
you're with me right now?
You're scared of her, aren't you?
Aren't you? Right?
Don't stand there like a dumb animal!
Answer my question, Aditya. Answer me!
Coward! Chicken!
Eunuch!
I'm wiping out every trace
of that bitch...
whom you don't forget
even in your dreams!
You're with me only in body.
You soul's always with that bitch!
Cut the melodrama, Malini!
- I'll drive her out of your life
Out of your house, and your mind!
If I still can't drive her away,
I'll burn that bitch alive!
I beg you. Don't compel me
to do such things
For the decency I had to let you
stay at this house...
please leave in a decent manner
I want to forget whatever
has happened between us
I'm not a line written
in pencil...
that you can erase
any time you wish to
Listen to what I say very
carefully, Aditya Dhanraj
I'm going to snatch you
from the bitch, come what may
This is enough
Leave me alone, Aditya!
Leave me alone!
You can't do this to me, Aditya!
Open the door, Aditya!
You've thrown me out of the house
for the sake of that bitch!
I wouldn't even spit at you!
To hell with you, Aditya Dhanraj!
Get out of my way, please
I shouldn't have done such a thing.
Never
Hit me, if you wish to...
but please don't be angry with me
For all the love you gave me,
what did I do to you?
I'm so ashamed!
But I can't help it, Aditya
Whenever I imagine you with that
woman, it sets my blood boiling
I wish you were not married to her
I wish I could erase memories of
every moment you spent with her
I wish she had never touched you.
I wish you belonged only to me...
Sanjana is my wife. She has a right
to my body and my soul...
notjust in this lifetime
but every time I'm born
Hear me out, Aditya... please!
Please don't leave me...
listen to me!
Don't go away, Aditya
Don't leave me, Aditya... please
- Get lost!
What are you doing?
What do you take me for?
I'll wipe out every memory you have
for that woman in your heart!
I won't let you show your back
to your love and run away!
I won't let anyone
snatch you from me!
You belong only to me...
only to me!
We'll have to provide better
facilities to our customers...
we'll have to renovate the hotel;
we'll have to do the landscaping again
And we'll have to change the
interiors of the entire hotel
It's going to cost us
about 20 million rupees
What do you think, Aditya?
Should we take such a big risk?
Do as you think fit
How dare you come here again?
Just one difference between me
and that bitch, isn't it?
She wears this collar
around her neck, right?
Tie it around my neck.
Tell her everything about me
Tell her that I'm the one
you really love
You're out of your mind.
Go away, else...
I have very little time, Aditya
The police have found my jeep
My Papa will come here,
if he gets to know
I don't want to go back
to the institution
Put that gun away, Malini
Make that telephone call quickly
Tell her that we can't live
without each other
Go on. Call her quickly
Skip this madness. I'm not
doing anything of that sort
Put that gun away.
- You're the one acting mad, Aditya
You know very well that we can't
live without each other. Don't you?
This lifetime and every time
we are born...
you will belong only to me.
So tell her that
You have accepted me
of your own volition
Till she starts believing that
I'm the woman you really love...
she's not going away
from our lives
Go on now. Tell her...
make that call
Make that call!
Malini, I love my wife very much
And I'm not going to tell her
about you and me. Never
You mustn't make the mistake
of doing that either
Because she loves me so much...
she won't ever believe you
Not even if she finds
my corpse in this house?
Put that gun away. Right now!
She's bound to know, Aditya
While I live, or after I die
I had never imagined...
that her madness and obsession
would go to such lengths
That one gunshot blasted my power
of reasoning and my good sense
It was only Robert I could
look to, for some loyalty
With his help, I then did
what I thought was right
We buried her body in the forest
I had no choice
How many people would believe
I was speaking the truth?
The manner in which she was
living with me, a married man...
would only suggest that she had
not committed suicide...
that I had killed her
What would I tell the police?
What would I tell Papa?
And you...
I didn't tell you about it
because I didn't want to lose you
It was as if I wasn't
burying Malini's body...
I was burying the fear of
being separated from you
I can't imagine a life without you
Because...
I love you very dearly, Sanjana
I must compliment you on
your nerve, Aditya Dhanraj
Behind my back, on my own bed,
you had a great time with a whore
And yet, you claim to be
in love with me?
After mercilessly crushing my love
in this very bed...
you want me to forget everything
and accept you?
And take you in my arms?
I won't be able to carry out
the farce, Aditya
I ask for your forgiveness, Sanjana.
Please... forgive me
Forgive your husband, Sanjana.
- I find you repulsive
I cried before you for so many days,
I suffered...
and you kept spurning me,
instead of telling me the truth
To keep our marriage alive,
I begged for your love
And you kept rejecting me
And now, when the shadows of
your past have begun to haunt me...
when I've begun to
hear those screams...
you try to prove that I was a liar.
Whereas you are the liar, Aditya
And I can never forget a liar.
Never!
You have a lovable face...
I could die for it
You do not know how much I love you
You have a loveable face...
I could die for you
This journey of love
is a difficult one
He who steadies himself
after falling...
finds his goal
No matter how difficult
our path is...
we happily walk through it
For your lovable face...
I could even lay down
my life
That's a good thing you did, Sanjana
In your shoes, I'd have
done the same thing
I couldn't imagine that Aditya was
capable of doing something so hideous
You must never return to him
Don't ever make that mistake, Sanjana
That is just what that woman wants.
I can understand it all. Everything!
Why did she draw you here
from Mumbai?
Why did she always try
to talk to you?
Why did she expose your
husband's secret to you?
She wants you and Aditya
to hate each other...
so that you will leave him forever
What would she gain out of that?
- Aditya!
Sanjana is devoted to her husband
And a woman who is devoted to
her husband, acts as his shield
Even God is afraid to meddle
with her husband's life
But this is an evil spirit
She was smart enough to
separate the two of you
As for Aditya...
he's all alone now
Are you telling us that Sanjana
must go back to Aditya?
If not as his wife, as a human being
she must go back to Aditya
Because she's the only one
who can save Aditya's life
That woman will now try to take
Aditya away with her forever
For that...
she'll have to release Aditya
from his body
She'll have to kill him
I haven't come here to
save our relationship
I'm here to save your life
Once I have seen you off
at your door...
I don't want to see your face again
Get the master's luggage.
We're leaving for Mumbai right now
Where's the master?
What are you staring at me for?
I don't understand, Madam
The master left with you
in a car, just moments ago
What nonsense are you talking?
I've walked in here right now
This is how the beginning
of the end always is
That power is now close in
on its victim
She's not going to spare
anyone now... no one!
Listen to me, Sanjana. Please
Look at me, please
Should I leave the world
and never return again?
What would you do, my love?
I'd snatch you from God.
I'd make you belong to me
Till as long as we live,
we shall never part
May this pledge never break
Even if it angers God
The doctors are doing their best
A couple of fractures in
the hip and his legs
They say he'll be all right if he
regains consciousness in two hours
Will he live, or won't he?
Uncle's flying with
experts from Mumbai
These people talk any nonsense
They'll take over everything the
moment they arrive, you will see
Will he live, or won't he?
The car fell from a height of
just 50 feet. Straight down, too
Will he survive, or won't he?
There's just one way
of saving Aditya
He's still breathing.
Before he stops breathing...
let's burn Malini's body.
That could save him
That's the only way that
wandering spirit can be dealt with
After burning in the pyre...
whether she wants it or not,
she has to accept a release
Let's go and find her body
before she takes Aditya and...
She won't be able to do
any harm to my Aditya
Once, she snatched him from me
I won't let her do it again
No matter what she does...
I will snatch my husband
from the jaws of death
Should this lemon turn red
where we place it...
it'll means she's right there.
That's where we must look for her
This is the place
She should be somewhere here
I think we must burn this body
right here
You're the faithful bitch, aren't you?
Despite knowing that Aditya
belongs to me...
you keep following him
with your tongue hanging out...
and even get here?
Shameless creature! Whore!
He has slept in my arms!
Before you can burn my corpse and
try to distance him from me...
I'll turn you into a corpse!
Congratulations, Mr Dhanraj
There's no danger
to your son's life
Sanjana, I was wrong...
absolutely wrong!
My friend has made it
Your Aditya has made it
There's just one reason why
Aditya is alive. It's Sanjana
Sanjana has proved that if a woman
is bent on saving her husband's life...
it can change the minds
of both... God and Satan
Every pain we will bear together
Let's resolve to do that
We shall never break...
let's promise each other
I'm afraid of the very idea
of going to seed
Yours is a lovable face...
I could die for it
You do not know...
how much I love you
To fall in love is easy
To live up to it
is very difficult
Only after I had passed
this test of love...
did my married life really blossom
Only after travelling through
the depths of death...
could I reach the zenith of life
The zenith where I was blessed
with the nectar of love
Forever.