headlines for the front page.
- Oh, drop it!
Here comes Judge Raghunath
Such a gentleman! Why on earth
did that goon want to kill him?
Here comes your friend
ls the jury in place?
Yes, my Lord. Present
ls the accused present?
- Present, my Lord
Who is the counsel for the accused?
Have you no lawyer
to defend your case?
ln that case, the government...
My Lord
l'm the counsel for the accused
l do not wish to defend myself
l promised to defend you, if
you're ever arraigned. Remember?
Does the accused give his consent?
Yes
Raj, you have been accused of
a murderous attack on Judge Raghunath
You may plead your case
l swear to speak the truth
Judge Raghunath, can you tell us
why the accused tried to kill you?
Did he have any enmity with you?
Yes. The grudge that a born felon
bears against the judge...
who sentences him and
grants no reprieve
Could there be no other reason
for such animosity?
None. How else could l
relate to him?
l have no further questions
Defense may proceed with
cross-questioning
Judge, you are senior to me
lf in the course of questioning,
l happen to affront you...
do forgive me. Someone's life is
at stake. And you have taught me...
to ignore all relationships for
the dispensation of justice
This is my first interrogation.
Please give me your blessings
What do you mean when you call
the accused a born felon?
He has been a tramp and a hoodlum...
ever since he was a child.
His record says it
This penchant for crime has surely
been transmitted congenitally
Judge, do you have any children?
No
But how is this question relevant
to this case?
Most relevant. Think again. Are you
certain that you have no children?
No. But l reiterate. This question...
- Can you recount the circumstance...
when you threw your wife
out of your house?
My Lord, am l to be forced to reply
to such meaningless questions?
Ms Rita, you may ask questions
relevant only to the case
We wish to know whether or not,
the accused attempted murder
lf yes, then why?
Enough! Stop it! l'm a murderer!
Hang me if you will!
Proceed with your questioning
The accused does not deny having
assaulted Judge Raghunath
But, as you said just now,
the question is why he did it
This interrogation is meant
to reveal the answer...
if you my Lord, and Judge Raghunath
repose your trust in me for a while
You may proceed
l repeat my question.
Can you recount the circumstance...
when you threw your wife
out of your house?
l beg your pardon, Judge Raghunath,
but this question is very important
And not only for the accused.
For you too
The cause of whatever is happening
today, lies rooted in your past
Remember...?
Can you tell us? Why, when
and under what circumstance...
did you throw your wife
out of your house?
24 years ago...
l was practising law in Lucknow
l was the black sheep of the family,
because l opposed social norm...
and l had married a widow.
My father was a big gun
and was away in Bombay most of the
time. He was unhappy with me
But under no circumstance,
was l willing to leave Leela
She was so good to me.
She was such a good woman
And l was in love with her
But once, on our way from
Kanpur to Allahabad...
little did l realise that
like a boat in midstream...
my life too was to be caught
in cross currents
''Cross currents in the midstream''
'' Beware''
''ln the current you will sink or sail''
''The open skies''
''Careful sailor''
''Your boat is headed into a storm''
''Restless flow the deep waters''
'' Beware''
''Twigs are carried away''
''Steel sinks''
''So what do you think?''
'' Beware''
Aren't you feeling sleepy?
What are you thinking about?
- Why do they sing '' Beware''?
They say, these parts are dangerous.
Jagga the bandit. He's from these parts
Bandits...?
- Yes, but don't worry
As of now, he must be fast asleep
in some prison
Go to bed. l'm feeling sleepy
ln case you're afraid,l can come over
- No
No! The lady is with them!
Leave me!
You heartless bandits!
Where's your chief?
What right have you to terrorise
women from good families?
Aren't you ashamed?
- Ashamed?
Shame is for good folks,
not for bandits and robbers
As for me, my grandfather was a bandit,
my father was a bandit! But l wasn't
And your husband went and made me one!
- My husband...?
Who are you?
- Jagga. And l was innocent
But without a shard of evidence,
your husband framed me...
just because my father, my grandfather
were bandits
He framed me for rape
and he sent me to jail
So l've decided to prove
your husband right
Coward!
See what's wrong with her
Has she come to her senses?
No, she's still in a swoon
Let her go, Chief. She's pregnant.
She's going to become a mother
Touch her, and you go to hell
Pregnant? With a baby?
Her husband said that children born
of good folks turn out good
And children born of bandits...
turn out to be bandits. Always
Now let's see what the lawyer's son
turns out to be
Send her back once she recovers
Good are those born of good folks!
And of bandits are bandits born
You should make me a gift.
- What's the occasion?
Not any occasion.
The lady is back
What did you say? The lady?
Why is it dark in here?
Lights! Tonight we celebrate!
lt is you who lights up my life
Now that you're back,
even the lights seem so bright!
Give me the wick
But Leela, how did you escape?
l hope you weren't in danger?
Your love was with me.
How could anyone even look up at me?
You are tired. Change.
l'll bring you your dressing grown
These last four days
The last four days were
like a lifetime
l took the police and l looked
everywhere for you
All the while, l feared...
l feared you were in grave danger!
But how did you escape?
And who was this bandit?
Some Jagga. He said that you
had convicted him
So he escaped to get even with me!
lf he has done anything to you...
l'll see to it that he hangs!
- At heart, he's a devil
But God saved me at the last moment.
Thank God!
Tell me something
Ask
Does a bandit's son necessarily
become a bandit?
Yes, it's bound to happen
But why do you ask?
Just like that
Let's see what comes first.
Your becoming a magistrate, or...
Why? ls someone expected?
A new guest
Now l don't have any chances
of becoming a magistrate
Why? What happened?
Whatever... let's talk
of something else
How do you like this?
Nice
Listen...
Are you annoyed with me?
Annoyed? No
Why should l be annoyed with you?
Have my lunch sent over
What's the matter?
Where are the servants?
God knows! Maybe they're all dead!
l have to do all the chores
Let me help you.
- You'd rather tell her all this
She's sitting around like a queen!
Not to be cross with Leela.
l told her not to strain herself
You know the condition she is in.
And in a few days from now...
She's going to bear the fruit
of her sins!
What are you saying?!
- What everyone else is saying!
For four days, she lived with a bandit!
And Jagga at that!
Don't you remember what
he was convicted for?
Do you enjoy making someone unhappy?
The jaundiced eye sees all yellow
Do you think you're beyond scrutiny?
Don't you forget...
women have had to stand the test of
chastity. Because society asks for it
Bhabhi!
(Sister-in-law)
Forgive me Bhabhi,
your pot is broken
lt's only an earthen pot. But remember,
a woman's honour is far more fragile
Once disgraced, her honour
can never be redeemed
Just answer my question!
Did you not know that your wife
was seeing her lover on the sly?
The villagers used to say that.
But l didn't heed what they said
You haven't yet told the court
why your wife deserted you
You know it! Women are adulterous!
l know what that means!
Raghu, how can you lose
your cool in court?
l'm afraid your chances of
magistrateship may be clouded
Chances of a magistrateship?
That's out of question now
Can a lawyer whose wife is under
suspicion ever become a magistrate?
The whole town is agog!
- What are you saying?
Aren't you ashamed to talk like this
about your wife?
l'm just saying what
everyone is saying
Let them say what they want
You're right. That's what l decided.
But how do l get rid of the suspicion?
lt's like a leech sucking on...
some dark corner of my mind!
- What now...?
Where's everyone?
Send Bhabhi over to me
Oh, l'm so afraid!
Why isn't someone coming to me?
That's my husband. Please,
send him over to me
Look Raghu...
l'm telling you again! That baby
isn't going to be born in this house
lf she wants to have her bastard,
let her go elsewhere
l'm not going to let the honour
of my family be tainted
l'm going to throw this
wanton woman out!
No! l'm not going anywhere!
No one can take me away from here!
He knows that l'm innocent!
He trusts me, he trusts me!
You're here! Now l'm afraid of no one!
Have you heard? They want
to throw me out!
They say l'm a wanton woman!
They say, l've no right to be here!
But now you're here.
No one will dare anymore
Tell them l'm untainted!
Tell them you trust me
Tell them l'm mothering your child
Why are you so quiet?
Have you fallen for what they say?
You're the one who told me...
''l don't care for the baying dogs''
lf you desert me, who else
in this world can l turn to?
Tell me... tell me that you trust me!
''Do you think you're above scrutiny?
Don't you forget...''
''women have had to stand
the test of chastity''
Why are you quiet?
Speak... speak!
You can see the state l'm in.
l'm afraid... afraid!
l'm going to become a mother
... the mother of your child
Have mercy! This is your baby.
This baby is yours!
Get out!
Get out of here!
''The most chaste of women''
''Were banished''
''Why is not the earth rent asunder
in sorrow?''
''Why are not the skies torn apart?''
''So suffers the girl her father
raised lovingly''
''Her father raised her lovingly;
her husband loved her once''
''Now she goes from door to door''
''Oh such games The Lord above plays''
''ln the oyster
He makes the pearl blossom''
''ln murky waters
He makes the lotus bloom''
''Strange are your ways, Lord''
Congratulations, Lawyer!
A son has born to you.
Son of a decent family!
Born in a filthy gutter!
Do you not know what your wife
and your son went through...
after you shut your doors on them?
- No
Nor did you try to find out
But l can tell you
To get out of your way,
your wife left Lucknow
And your innocent son grew up
in a Bombay slum
One day...
Police! Scram!
Hey Nathu...
Hello, Constable
What are you up there like a monkey?
Why don't you go to school?
At school, the master asks for fees
My father hasn't the money
to send me to school
Look at Leela's son, Raj.
He lives in this slum too
His mother is worse off. Yet she
sends her boy to such a big school
What did you say? He isn't a boy.
He's a sissy!
Ma, why do you put oil in my hair?
- Oil keeps the hair soft
But why do boys in the neighbourhood
call me sissy?
So what? How do they
compare with you?
You're a good boy
who goes to school
You'll grow up to become
an educated man
And those wayward boys
will go to jail
Ma, what's wayward?
The ones who just tramp around
Those who think that whatever
belongs to others, belongs to them
Those who gamble and drink
instead of going to school
And they have fun!
Ma, when l grow up,
l'll become wayward too
Nonsense! You'll become a lawyer
Then a magistrate
And then, a judge
You're sitting here?
Everyone's out there buying chocolates
l don't have money
Why, doesn't your mother
give you money?
Daddy gives me a whole Rupee
every day!
You're rich. And l'm poor.
Eat this
No, Ma says never ask
for anything to eat
lf she told you not to ask,
go ahead and snatch it
No!
You're coming to my place
this evening, aren't you?
Why, what's happening?
- My birthday party!
You must come! lt's going to be fun!
You know, Daddy has ordered
such a huge cake!
Let's go and eat ice cream
Raj, aren't you giving me a gift?
l didn't have money to buy anything.
l'll give you some other time
Must you only buy something
to make a gift?
You can give me a flower
Really?
Here you are
Someday, l'm going to make
lots of money
And l'll buy a gift for you.
Something better than all this
Do that
But can anything be better
than this flower?
Come on Raj, meet my father
Ritu, say hello to the Judge
Hello, Judge
Bless you
You've grown up in these four years
You must've forgotten me.
Happy birthday
l've just arrived from Lucknow.
l owe you a present
As of now, l can give you a flower
Here you are
Let me put it on your hair
Someone has already put a flower
over there
Raj has given me this flower
Daddy, this is Raj.
He's in my class
l see
- Hello
Hello
God bless you, son
Raj says that he will become a judge
when he grows up
Very good!
Your father must be a real gentleman
What does your father do?
l don't have my father.
l have only my mother
Has he passed away?
- No! Don't say that!
My mother says he is alive.
But...
He doesn't live with you
... and you haven't seen him either?
Your father is a strange man.
- Not a word about my father
Else... else...
How can you let your daughter
play with boys like him?
Go to play, Ritu
Why, what's wrong with the boy?
l like him
He doesn't even know his father's
name, and you like him?
l'd say he's just a wastrel
- Forget it.
Must you hang on to
those rotten old ideas?
What was the Bandit's name?
Yes, Jagga
l remember you saying the same
at his trial
That a bandit's son
always becomes a bandit
l still stand by that principle
Principles, principles and principles!
lt's because of these blind dogmas...
that you lost someone
as precious as Leela
And because of your principles,
you never married again
The dry parched desert that
your life is, is your own doing
So much so that you would rather
destroy a friendship...
between two innocent children?
Why, what has the poor child done...
to bring you to harm?
Not this boy. But it was...
someone like him who destroyed my life
... and brought me to disgrace
Maybe today, he too says
what this boy just said...
''l'm only my mother's son
... l have no father''
ln every urchin l see him...
the one whom my wife bore,
the one who isn't mine
My wife's, yet not mine
Rita looks good in that photo,
doesn't she?
But Ma, why do you work so hard?
This is why you fall ill
l'm not going to let you work
anymore, you understand?
You mad boy! lf l don't work,
how are we going to eat?
l'm a man. l'm the one
who is going to work
From tomorrow,
no going to school!
You won't go to school?
Won't you?
How will you become a gentleman,
unless you educate yourself?
Wayward imp!
Without schooling, how can you become
a lawyer, a magistrate, a judge?
lf you say so, l'll go to school
... and l'll work too
But l won't become a judge.
At Rita's l met a judge
l didn't like him
''Are you out for a good time?''
''Hey Mister, Hey Babu,
Hey Mr White, Mr Black''
''Out on the streets
we're waiting for you''
''We, the merry boot-polish boys''
Good morning, teacher.
Sorry, l'm late
l work, you know. l work
What's all this?
Brush, wax... l give you a good polish
Your name has been struck
from the rolls
What?
- You can't study here anymore.
But l've brought the fees too! lf you
say so, l'll stop polishing boots
So l can't study here any longer,
can l?
No
For a minute, can l talk to Rita?
l have a gift for her
Rita's father has transferred her
out of this school. They have moved
Why did you kick my ball?
Forgive me, l stepped on it
by mistake
How dare a boot-polish-boy?
- Hit him!
You're just a boot-polish boy.
You dare take me on?
Hit him!
His coat... strip him!
My Ma is ill.
Let me go to my Ma
You can hit me some other time.
My Ma is ill. Let me go to my Ma
Your Ma is ill?
- Yes
His Ma is ill!
Run! Uncle Jagga is here! Run!
Get up. Come with me
Where to?
Wherever l go. From now on,
you go wherever l go
That's what your father wanted
You know my father?
- Yes
l knew him
Whatever l am today,
is all thanks to him
l owe your Dad an old debt
Then you'll surely help me
find a job somewhere?
Job? What job?
- Whatever! l'll do anything!
My Ma is sick! We haven't anything
to eat! Give me any job!
l'll clean the dishes, sweep floors,
carry luggage... l'll do anything!
Just give me a job! Give me a job!
You fool! Only fools work
You're a smart boy.
And you talk of working?
Unless l work, how will l eat?
How will l feed my mother?
Steal
Steal?
Stealing... no!
Yes, yes, yes!
Steal! Steal! Steal!
Pick pockets, locks,
rob, kill
You took so long, son
You've been hungry all day.
Go on, eat food
Food? Have you cooked?
- Yes, why not?
lt's over there, under the plate
The bread is warm.
l even cooked potatoes
Take some. lt's on the shelf
Have you found it?
Yes Ma, l found it
The bread, and potatoes too
The potatoes are delicious
Eat it then. Give me a bread too.
l'm very hungry
Very hungry
Bread...?
Yes, Ma. l'll get it right now
Right now
''Yes, yes, yes!
Steal! Steal! Steal!''
''Pick pockets, locks,
rob, kill''
You thief!
Stealing bread?
- Excuse me, my Ma is hungry
She hasn't had anything to eat
in three days
Son of a gun! Off you go to the cops!
What's your name?
l asked you what's your name
Father's name?
Ma has never told me
my father's name
Where does your mother live?
l asked you where your mother lives
l won't tell you. l won't
lf you don't, who pays for your bail?
You'll go to jail. You know that?
Where are you running?
- Don't send me to jail!
My Ma is hungry.
Don't send me to jail!
Afraid, son? Don't be.
This is just your first step
The road ahead is very long
Hey, are you mad?
Why are you laughing at your bread?
This bread...
you know this bread?
She makes you dance
What do you mean?
- She made me dance!
Outside the jail twelve years ago,
had l found her...
would l be here time and again,
for her sake?
You've had enough for free.
Come on, the jailer is calling you
Your time's up. Find yourself
some other hotel
Time up?
- Yes
l don't think l like the food here
anyway. From now on...
it's Hotel Taj Mahal for me
lf you want to eat at
the Taj Mahal Hotel, stop thieving
Stop picking pockets
And do some honest work
- Sure. l'm going on a pilgrimage.
''l'm a tramp''
''Whether l'm rising or falling,
l'm always a star''
''l have no family, no home''
''l have no one who loves me''
''l don't have a lover waiting for me
across some river''
''For me the city is empty city
The unknown path is all l love''
''l'm a tramp''
''l'm not rich''
''l'd rather stay a pauper''
'' But the songs l sing
are merry songs''
''My heart is full of wounds''
'' But my eyes are always
full of smiles''
''Oh this world''
''ln this world, maybe l'm doomed''
''l'm a tramp''
'' But whether l'm rising or l'm falling,
l'm always a star''
Raj! You had me scared
Come on, give me a hug
Hey, are you talking English?
- This time in jail...
l came across one of the politicos.
l thought l'd make the most of it
And got to talk some English.
l could use it
Tell me, what news of Ma?
You told her, didn't you?
Yes, a long time ago. She thinks
you're away on a long business trip...
with your boss. When you go home,
you must go home in style
l have it all fixed.
- First, tell me...
have you been sending money to Ma?
- Of course! On the 1st of every month!
Say, you'd need some money,
wouldn't you? Keep this
Looking for this thing?
l guessed it was for me.
So why not take it for myself?
Want a ten or a twenty? No...?
Bravo, my boy! You'll make
your guru proud someday
And someday, l'll ask your father what
the gentleman's son grows up to be
Raj, l've been dying to see you!
This time, it has been a whole year!
Where has this boss of yours
been taking you to?
This time, l've been
to London and more
London?
On my way back, l even stopped
at Arthur Road
My boss is into import and export.
- What's that?
You don't know import-export?
You're so naive
Your son is about to become a big
businessman, and you don't know...
what import-export is?
Listen to this, Ma
lmport-export means moving the money
between here and there
But mostly, it comes in this way
How would l know?
You've even started talking English
Sit, l'll get tea for you
What are you looking at?
l'm a thief
A lying thief
l've sinned
Why did you turn that photo over?
Whenever l look at it,
she seems to be staring at me
She brings back childhood memories.
Why don't you admit that?
Where could she be now?
Why don't you try to locate her?
Childhood days, and childhood friends
... do they ever come back, Ma?
l'm going out
- But your tea?
Forget it. l've got to see a friend
My son he is! Silly boy!
''This is a colourful season''
''Men think it's exciting
to see me tonight on the sly''
''Exciting!''
''This youth is so exciting''
''Your girl is mad about you''
''Why do you refuse me?''
''Why do you look away from me?''
''Look here, the world is yours''
''Why are you afraid of love?''
How much did you make today?
- Ten thousand five hundred
Why only fifty-fifty?
You can have many times more
How?
- Tomorrow morning...
a bank is being inaugurated.
Say, how's the opportunity?
A sleight of hand, and there's
a hundred thousand or so going
All you need is a car.
- Car?
A good car.
- For me, that's a sleight of hand
Eleven tomorrow. l'll tell you where
Good! Someday, you'll surely
make me proud
lt's late
You have to make it by eleven
First class car!
Car? Where?
Out there
Who's driving it?
- No idea
A girl just got down
and walked into that shop
Keys?
- With her, maybe
That one?
Can't you see?
No keys here
Return the bag.
- What for?
lt will make things easier.
We'll make it work.
How will you return it?
What happened?
- l've been robbed!
Who did it?
- l didn't notice
He was with you!
l had it a moment ago
- You didn't notice who robbed you?
Had l noticed, l would've caught him!
You...
Yes you!
- Who me?
Look, there goes the thief!
Stop! Thief!
He jumped over the wall!
Wait here
Come on, help me
There you are! Hiding!
Aren't you ashamed? Give it to me.
Else, l'll beat you to pulp
l'm going to kill you! Give me!
You dare stare at me like that?
Hey... knife!
Are you running away? Coward!
Coward!
He ran away
Anyway, here's your purse
Keep it
You've been through so much
trouble for my sake
No trouble. l've taken more
l should apologise. You risked
your life to get my purse back
And l suspected you
Not your fault
lt's just my looks
Sometimes even the police
are mistaken
Bye
How was the show?
- No use
We'll find a car. Why worry?
Get over to the place
l'll join you after a change
of clothes
Hey Romeo! You tear your clothes
no sooner than you see a girl!
Get lost
Get going
Stop! Thief!
Where are you going?
lnside
lnside? What do you want?
- Strange question
Your boss is the one who called me.
And you ask me what l want?
The boss, or the lady? Who called you?
Yes, the lady
So you're the one
who fixes the piano?
Yes! The piano fixer!
ls the piano in there?
- Are pianos kept outside?
No! lnside. Come on in,
else l'll get into trouble
Looks like a billionaire's palace!
The mantle!
What a lovely mantle!
What a grand mansion!
What kind of a joke is this?
Here's the piano
This piano is in bad shape.
Badly damaged
Rotten! lt'll take me time to fix it.
Go on, get back to work
l'll fix it
Who's playing my piano?
You...?
- You...!
l'm mistaken, once again
l thought it must be a thief
That's what l am.
- What?
l mean, who else but a thief
would come in uninvited?
No, it's good of you
to have come
You did me a favour.
l should've called you over
But l didn't know your address.
How did you find out my address?
No, don't ask me that.
lt's a secret
Let's say, it's luck that has led me
to your doorstep
Please be seated
No, thanks
Matches
Madam, he's the piano-fixer...
- Piano fixer?
Your servant thinks l'm here
to fix the piano
But you said...
Never mind, take the call. Go on
Strange fellow. He took you
for a piano mechanic
Not his fault.
lt's just my looks
lnspector sahib, no thief
came in here
Please wait here
What brings the police here?
Excuse me, l'll be back
A car thief has sneaked into one
of the houses in this neighbourhood
Have you seen anyone?
- No, no one came in here
She's wrong about
no one coming in here
l happen to be a visitor.
Would you be looking for me?
No... how could this be?
Come
Grand house
Yes. lt belongs to the Judge
Judge...?
- Yes, he's my guardian
Like the guard on the train
... signalling red and green?
No. After my father passed away,
l have been his ward
For the sake of my education,
he left Lucknow and he came to Bombay
l am much obliged to him
Do judges sport such grand houses?
He must be making a pile on the side
What a thing to say!
The judge is very principled
He never spares criminals
l hope God spares him!
Not to worry. lf you're ever arraigned
in his court, let me defend your case
You... lawyer?
- Yes
l took you for a schoolgirl
That was a nice one. A couple
of months, and l'll be an advocate
Would you like to see my degree?
A judge lives here. And a lawyer too.
Leaves only one to make a full court!
Yours truly. And here l am.
- And what are you up to?
Thievery
Stealing, picking pockets, locks,
ladies' purses, like yours...
that's what l'm up to.
- You're joking again. Be seated
You don't think l'm a thief?
- No, l think you're a gentleman
This is the new world order!
The thieves, the hoodwinkers...
they all dress in first class suits
like l'm wearing, and we take them...
for gentlemen. But those who work hard
for an honest living and dress shabbily
... are labelled tramps and wastrels.
The capitalists, the blackmarketeers...
the profiteers, the usurers...
who are they? Thieves, like l am!
You sound like a stock broker
or a banker
You might say that give and take
of money is what l'm concerned with
As far as banks are concerned,
l visit banks regularly
Be seated
Tell me your name
Tell me, whose photo is this?
- Mine
You...?
Yes, when l was young
lt's a birthday photo
Your name?
Rita. Why?
Ms Rita, would you like to come
to my house?
l'd like to show you
something unique
My mother would be very pleased
to meet you. Come
You...?
After twelve years
You've changed!
You haven't changed at all
Where have you been, Raj?
Looking for you
And at last, l've found you
- And when l saw you...
l took you for a thief
Not your fault.
lt's in my looks
''Ever since my lover
has come home...''
''my heart leaps with joy''
''His heart said
something to mine''
''And the old days returned''
''Our days have returned again''
''He brings so much of happiness...''
''my heart leaps with joy''
''My heart he could win
through my eyes''
''l could lay the stars
at his feet''
''My hopes soar...
my heart leaps with joy''
''Ever since my beloved
has come home...''
''my heart leaps with joy''
''We are young
and we are in love''
''He is the one who
makes my world''
''My heart leads him to me...
my heart leaps with joy''
''Ever since my hero has returned,
my heart springs to life''
The Judge is here
So here you are. And you're late
The doctor has told you to come home
and rest for at least an hour
But you won't listen.
You look so tired
Just sit here. l'll get you
your dressing gown
Tell me, where have you been
all this time?
l had a lecture in the law college.
l went there directly from the court
All that jabbering
is giving me a headache
That's bound to happen. The doctor
told you to eat before eight
lt's nine thirty now
Listen to that! Even the clock
is angry with you
Come on
Tell me about yourself. What have
you been up to all evening?
You look as if you've found
a treasure
You could say that. A long-lost friend
is no less than a treasure
You'll be glad when you meet Raj.
You're certain to like him!
Who is this Mr Raj? Where does he live?
What does he do? What's his family name?
He's a childhood friend.
We were in school together
l'm seeing him after twelve years!
After twelve years?
After so many years,
most people change
Raj has changed too. At school,
he used to be very quiet
Now he has great sense of humour.
When l asked him what he's up to...
he said he's a thief
Maybe that wasn't a joke?
l don't follow you
Never mind
You know what young men
are like, these days
Who knows, they might steal
something valuable
The water is deep.
You might drown
Not without you
ls that so?
Try that
Hey lady, haven't you finished
dressing yet?
Where are you headed?
Gentlemen don't barge in...
when ladies are changing dresses.
Don't you know that?
How would l know?
l'm no gentleman
Savage
l'm not about to give in
to your type
Where are you running away?
Let go of my hand. What kind
of a stupid joke is this?
You savage!
Am l...?
- Yes!
You're a savage!
- Savage?
l'm a penniless, uneducated tramp!
l don't fit into high society!
How dare l maul your fragile body
with my beastly hands
l told Ma that childhood friends,
like childhood days are gone...
never to return
Good of you to have told me
my class
lt was a joke. Don't get angry
You want to hit me? Go ahead
Whom will l hit?
You...?
Or myself...?
Are you happy?
Where are you lost?
Up there
Come back
Where to?
Beside me
Why?
No reason
Aren't you ashamed?
What are you looking at?
The Moon?
No
Clouds
What's your problem?
You don't see the Moon...
and you see the dark clouds?
Won't you tell me?
Who else can l tell?
We're seeing each other
after twelve years
A lot changes in twelve years.
- The Judge said that too!
But l don't agree. Look at us.
We're still friends
The Judge is right.
You know nothing about me
Who l am...
my circumstances...
my family background...
what l have been doing...
what l am doing
You know nothing about me
Nor do l want to know
All l know is that you are
the one l...
Rita, you are so nice.
But so naive
And you're such a fool
A savage
l'm not talking to you
Look
The clouds?
They are moving away from my Moon
You know, today's my birthday
Which? Tenth? Eleventh?
You don't ask a lady that
All right, l'll whisper it to you
Twenty one
No! lt's looking at us
What?
- That!
''l wish the Moon would
look away for a while...''
''while l make love to him''
''l'd say a thousand sweet nothings''
''l pray with all my heart..''
''l pray for my love''
''The Moon watches me and
my beloved for the first time''
''On our first night together''
''Hide behind those clouds,
O Moon...''
''while l make love to him''
''While l say a thousand
sweet nothings to him''
''l wish the Moon would
look this way for while...''
''l'd make love to her''
''l'd look deep into her eyes''
''l'm a thief;
l steal''
''l have a bad reputation''
''l have always stolen hearts;
that's just what l have done''
''You must bear witness, O Moon''
''While l make love to her''
''When l look into her eyes''
''You have stolen my heart;
do not go away''
''Do not forget the path
that leads to me''
''Do not trample upon the rose
that is my heart''
''Tell him this much, O Moon...''
''l'll make love to him''
''l'll whisper a thousand
sweet nothings to him''
''lf only you look this way,
O Moon...''
''l'd make love to her;
l'd look deep into her eyes''
''lf only you looked away
for a while, O Moon...''
One step more, and the boat
will turn over and sink
Say what...?
Let the boat sink
l don't want it
- But the doctor says...
l should eat by eight
Tonight, it's my turn
to be admonished by the clock
You are angry with me, aren't you?
Today l was...
With Raj?
- Raj is no stranger
He's a childhood friend
l made a promise
to your dying father
To take care of you
as long as l live
You must make a promise
lf someone likes you,
if you like someone...
you will not give your consent
without telling me
l know, l am much obliged to you.
But it doesn't mean that you can,
time and again...
Boss...?
Recognise me?
Thank you very much!
You haven't much time nowadays
Well son, are you falling in love?
Or, have you given up your profession
for fear of going to jail?
You don't know the size of the scam
l've planned for you
She's an heiress.
Just wait for a few days
l'm angling for a diamond necklace.
- Bravo!
l knew it! You aren't the type
to waste your time
But remember!
lf you try to cheat Jagga...
''Nor do l want to know. All l know
is that you are the one l...''
Really...?
''Remember! lf you try
to cheat Jagga...''
''Without you, even Moonlight
is a scorching fire...''
''Come to me''
''Like a flute bereft of melody...''
''without you, my life is a misery''
''Come to me''
''This is no life...
no, this isn't''
''ln the pyre that is my life,
l burn alive''
''Like red-hot arrows
tears of anguish rip me apart''
''l want not this hell...''
''l seek only roses,
l seek only love''
''A season of Spring, l seek''
''My lover has come home''
''My thirsting eyes are sated''
''You are the pearl
deep inside my heart''
''You are the light of my eyes''
''You are all my childhood fantasies
were about''
''And now you are back''
''Don't break my heart now;
don't go away''
''Don't leave me in tears''
''l beseech you''
Ma!
Help me, Ma!
Ma, l want to be good!
l promise, l won't have anything to do
with Jagga and those others!
l'd rather starve than steal.
l will be good
People will say l'm honest!
Let's go back to our slum
l'll work hard for a living.
l won't steal! Ma, l won't steal!
l want nothing but peace of mind,
and my mother's blessings
l won't steal, Ma.
l'll become honest
Yes, sir?
- You're fired. We won't need you
We don't employ thieves
May l ask something, sir? You say
you don't want to employ thieves?
Would you rather that they keep
thieving all their lives?
Fired?
Come on, the boss is calling you
Raj, what reply do l carry back
to the boss?
This
He will either steal
or he will starve
And how long will he not steal?
He has no way out of crime
Let me see how far he goes
Where are you going?
To see Rita.
- You can't go in. The Judge's orders
The Judge's orders?
Then go and tell her that
Raj is waiting out here to see her
l have much to tell her.
- She can't see anyone. Get going
Get going...? Where to?
Come friend
Let me talk to you
Strange coincidence, isn't it?
You're a tramp, l'm a tramp too
You have no name,
l have no name either
You are homeless,
l have no home either
Like me, you too crave for love
Difference being only that
you are an animal, and l'm human
Human
l have nothing to give you
l can only give love
Why don't you watch your step?
Are you blind?
Mind your tongue.
Bloody savage
Savage... am l a savage?
Am l a mongrel on the streets?
To be kicked at will or whim?
''Piano-fixer?''
''Your servant thinks
l'm here to fix the piano''
''Come to me, l pine for you''
''The night is about to pass''
''l pine here;
you long there''
''So come...
the night is about to pass''
''Even the Moon is waning''
''The stars are disappearing''
''A painful, restless hour;
the night passes''
''Carried away with the Moon...''
''l see the bride-like night
disappearing''
''Call out to me...
where are you?''
''The night is passing''
''l fear and l lose hope''
''Even my fate is tiring of me''
''lf you won't come...''
''where do l go?''
''The night is about to pass''
The invitations have been printed
The day after tomorrow
is your birthday, isn't it?
Send them to the friends
you want to invite
All my friends?
Yes, all friends. All, who are
worthy of being your friends
Your birthday
''Raj, aren't you giving me a gift?''
''l didn't have money to buy anything.
l'll give you some other time''
''Must you only buy something
to make a gift?''
''You can give me a flower''
''Someday, l'm going to make
lots of money''
''And l'll buy a gift for you.
Something better than all this''
Back? l knew someday,
you'd surely come back
For you, this is the only door open
l need a thousand. A loan
l'll return it after l've earned it
Loan? What d'you think l am,
a money-lender?
Today is Rita's birthday.
Look, she has invited me
She takes me for a gentleman.
- So you must dress like a gentleman
And to prove yourself, you must
also make a gift to the lady
So gentlemanliness is for sale,
and you intend buying some?
But to become a gentleman, you need
money. One thousand Rupees
For that thousand, you have to steal,
rob, or maybe even kill someone for me
Do you accept?
- No
No! l won't rob!
l won't commit crimes!
What other way out have you?
Once a criminal, you can never
become a gentleman again!
No matter how many times
you change your clothes
Crime is written all over your face!
You even tried working
Not for you, the bread
in the sweat of thy face
For you, the only resort
is thieving, crime
Same as mine!
All thanks to your father
Watch your step, son
l try. But what to do?
Out on the streets...
there are those big guns like you.
- Sharp, are you?
Have you seen Rita?
Tell me something
#NAME?
Who are you looking for?
Want me to tell you?
Look, over there
So you came
Happy twenty-first
Your gift
- Why did you have to do this?
Why did you have to buy
such an expensive necklace?
For you, nothing is too expensive.
Besides, l stole it
You stole it?
- l stole it from the stars
You're such a...
- A savage?
What else? You are a savage
You buy this expensive gift...
but you won't spend
for a velvet case
Case?
Rita, the Judge is calling you.
Hurry up
What's on your mind?
Let me introduce you to the Judge
Come on
Rita, l've been waiting for you
First, my present
See if you like it
Why, don't you like it?
Today's a strange day. Someone
gives me a necklace sans a case
And someone give me a case
sans the necklace
''The man l'm in love with
is full of deceit''
'' But l've fallen in love with him?''
''Oh, what have l done?''
''He looked so innocent''
'' But he turns out to be a crook''
''The innocent-looking crook
that he is...''
''he's a blackheart
with a sunny smile''
''l have given him my heart
l'm driving myself crazy''
''Oh, what am l doing?''
''Those blue eyes have deceived me''
''There's an emptiness inside my heart
and tears come to my eyes''
''l trusted him
l promised him my love''
''Oh, what have l done?''
What have l done?
l've fallen in love with a thief!
And Raju, you...?
ls it some gift you don't like?
l'm going to return his gift
Bring him over.
l'd like to meet him
Raj isn't a bad boy.
He has just gone astray
All he needs is someone to love him,
to support him, to bring him around
He respects you. lf you want it,
Raj can be saved
ls Raj not at home?
- No. He went out early in the morning
He isn't back yet
''Falling in love with you, my love''
''l have cried, and l have laughed''
''Happily l have borne
the pangs of love''
''l have cried, and l have laughed''
''What do you know of
the pangs of love?''
''The pain is so acute''
''l'm transfixed''
''l stood silent''
''l stood in silence, l swear''
''l cried, and l laughed''
''My heart burns, as if on fire''
''My tears flow, as it rains''
''Like the clouds''
''Like a cloud, l was a tramp''
''l have cried, and l have laughed''
''Falling in love with you, my love''
There you are
Haven't you brought the police along?
That bitterness is of no use
Your mother has told me everything
So you know l'm wayward
... l've been to jail...
and my name is on the police rolls.
ls that what you've come to tell me?
Try to understand me, Raj.
l still consider you my friend
Friend?
A lawyer's daughter, a judge's ward
takes a tramp for a friend?
What's your society going to say?
What will your people say?
lf you recant, society
will forgive your past
Raj, you can make a new life
for yourself... you can!
A new life? On what
will l build a new life?
Can you give me back my childhood
... the education l never had?
Everyone says that l have no father
to name... l have no honour!
Can you bring my father back?
Can you give me my name?
Can you give me my honour?
Tell me... tell me Rita!
Rita, l've kept you in the dark.
l've kept myself in the dark
Forget me Rita.
Leave me to myself
l am not worthy of you
You realise fully well,
yet you want to live in this hell
l never imagined you'd be so weak
Rita, don't you think l never tried
to get out of this hell
But tell me, what do l do?
For twelve years, the world
has chased me towards crime
Alone, l cannot face it
Alone, l cannot
You aren't alone, Raj
Your mother is with you
l'm with you
You? With me? With a criminal?
Yes Raj. With you, forever
Good or not, guilty or not,
whatever you are, you're mine
This is a matter of the heart. And
the scales of justice cannot judge it
But this guilt l carry
with me forever...?
For me, as your wife, it will
be the bride's vermillion
Really?
Come with me
- Where?
The Judge wants to meet you
The Judge...?
Sit
Name?
Only Raj?
Yes
Your father's name?
l don't know
l see
What do you do?
As of now, unemployed.
Like millions of others
Any other source of income?
Property?
Nothing
Do you remember polishing boots
when you were a boy?
l still do
And you want to marry Rita?
Yes. lf you allow me
And you've been to jail too?
- Rita must've told you that...
You've recanted...? Have you found
another source of making money?
No
- But there's still hope, isn't it?
lf some silly rich girl marries you...
- Did you call me here to insult me?
We are in love
We want to marry
- All that l've heard
Love!
Sit
And let's talk it over
with a cool head
What do you mean?
- l mean that though l don't know...
how you managed to seduce a naive girl,
it's clear why you played this trick
l want to know what price
you'll take to let her go
Till today, l thought
l was the worst scoundrel on earth
But you turn out to be
one up on me!
You scum! How dare you use
your filthy colloquy?
You think l'm going to let
Rita marry a tramp like you?
She'd rather stay a spinster for life.
Better by far that she dies!
Why not say that you'd rather
she married some rich big-shot?
Or maybe, some judge?
Out of here
Before l leave, l'd like
to ask you a question
What if it was your son in my place?
And because he's poor...
because he was brought up in the slums
and was forced into crime...
what if it was he who was being denied
his love, his life...?
How would you have felt?
Jagga has called you
There's a big heist
A bank is to be looted
Open the door!
Open up
- Who is it?
Open up!
Who are you?
Don't you know me?
l'm Jagga
The bandit?
- You could say so
What do you want here?
Silence!
The police are after me.
Where's Raj?
Get out of my house! l will do nothing
to help someone like you!
l had you once, and l let you go
Remember the day?
For twelve years,l cared for your son.
l made his life! For this day?
Made my son's life?
You forced him into crime
Get out of my house. l don't want
your cursed shadow upon my son!
Get out! Get out of my house!
Go on! Call the police!
Let me see who saves you!
Scream!
Will you challenge your boss?
You're no boss. You're Satan!
Let's hear what you have to say now
No! No! Mercy!
No! Enough!
What have you done Raj?
For my sins, this is atonement!
The accused may be presented
What's the name of the accused?
Sir, his name is Raj
Father's name?
- Not known, sir. Maybe he has none
Raj, you have been accused
of killing Jagga
Do you have anything to say
in your defence?
Have you not appointed a lawyer
to defend yourself?
The case is adjourned. The government
will appoint a counsel for the defence
l know the law. Raj killed
in self-defence. That's no crime
Please save my Raj, somehow
Your deposition is very important.
The whole case hinges on it
Come to the court tomorrow
- All right
ls she dead?
- She has been hurt on the head
And Raj killed Jagga
to save my life
Please sign here. This deposition
will surely save Raj
lf Raj is saved, l will be able
to die in peace
l should be leaving now
My son!
- What happened to you, Ma?
That heartless judge has killed you!
What is his enmity with us?
You mustn't blame him, son.
- Why not?
He has always been trying
to make us miserable
No son! He is your father
My father?
What are you saying, Ma?
What has come over you?
l'm not out of my mind, son.
What l'm saying is the truth
l could not bring myself
to tell you this until now
But if not today, once l'm gone
who else could tell you?
This can't be, Ma!
This can never be!
This is a long story.
But l don't have the time
Keep this. l'm leaving
He will surely recognise you
when you show him this
He has never forgiven me.
But he will surely forgive his son
l won't seek mercy from the one
who tortured my mother all her life...
the one who made her beg from door
to door. Ma, l won't have his mercy!
lf l could see him for once before
l died... But why would he come here
Come
- l'm leaving Ma
l'll avenge you, l will
- No!
l'll surely avenge you, l will
- No, son!
The Judge is here to see you
Which Judge?
- The one whose car ran you over
So he has come... before l'm dead
Alas, l cannot see
Nurse, give him my greetings
l am ashamed about the accident.
Please forgive me
Forgive you...?
You didn't die! You were killed!
That heartless judge has killed you!
To make sure that he isn't exposed!
Have you decided the verdict
about the case?
Case?
Raj's case
You are going mad!
What are you doing to yourself?
You are a mature, educated woman
ln a few days, you'll start
going to court as a lawyer
You might even make a judge.
lf you get emotional over every case...
you will never be able to
dispense justice
This is not a lawsuit.
lt's my life!
Do you not understand as much?
- lrrespective, it won't alter the law
Nor should you let your emotions
come in the way of justice
Justice is all l seek.
Raj is completely innocent
He killed Jagga trying to save
his mother
You can read his mother's
dying declaration
ln this particular case,
Raj might merit pardon
But his whole life is a long story
of involvement with crime and sin
l cannot comprehend how you can
sympathise with such a person
How can you love him?
You have studied the law
But my heart has not read the laws
Heart...
and the laws
The laws...
and the heart
What a strange concoction
But you are right
The heart heeds no laws
No laws at all
Not even mine
No!
- Get out, Rita
l'm in a murderous rage!
- Have you gone mad?
So you have escaped?
- Yes
To settle the score with you
Then you will be happy to know
that your lawyer...
had just convinced me
about your innocence
l was inclined to let you off
tomorrow
l want no mercy from you
l don't want your justice,
your law, nothing!
All l want...
Lost your nerve?
You need guts to kill someone
You should be thanking the one
who has just saved your life
What if l were to use this very knife
to rip your heart out?
Judge Raghunath was compelled to kill
a criminal to save his own life
What else can the verdict
of the courts be?
Have you gone out of your mind too?
- l was. For a second
For the scum that he is,
the hangman's noose will be better
This is the story of
Raj's life and crimes
Now you know why and how
he took to crime
My Lord, the one who is guilty
is his father...
who drove an innocent woman from
his house, and denied his own son
He is the one who forced them
to go begging from door to door
And in the company of criminals,
he went astray
My Lord and members of the Jury...
if Raj is to be punished for his crime,
then his father should be punished too
My Lord, l would like to say something
Emotion has got the better
of the counsel for defence
ln her anxiety to save the accused,
the counsel has presented...
an interesting story,
however incongruous it might be...
to try and prove that
some criminal happens to be my son!
But l ask, what evidence
does the counsel have?
No evidence on earth will convince you
that Raj is your son...
not unless you are willing
to accept him as your son
lf there be proof, it lies deep
in your heart and in Raj's eyes
Look at him. The same eyes,
the same high brow
He even speaks like you speak.
He's just as adamant as you are
Are you still not willing
to accept him as your son?
Ms Rita, the law heeds no emotion
Nor my Lord, does the heart
heed any law
l have no more to say
lf the accused has anything to say
in his defence, he may proceed
Yes. At last, after being branded
a murderer, l hold your attention
Had l been heard earlier, perhaps
l would never have had to stand here
Ms Rita has tried her best
to save me from being hanged
And not only in this particular case;
in my personal life too
ln my defence, l wish to say nothing.
l am evil
l've been a vagabond ever since
l was a child
l'm a murderer, a criminal
You may punish me as you please.
But sin, crime, hatred and violence...
this vicious circle that holds
your society in a vice-grip...
do you think it can be broken
by hanging me?
l don't want to tell you
the story of my life
But all l want to say is, l did not
inherit crime from my parents
From that gutter full of filth
that flows beside my shanty...
l picked up crime. That gutter
is still flowing over
And the virus still breeds
And countless children who live
in those slums...
are falling prey to the virus
every day
Do not think of me. Those children
are the ones you must care for
You must care for your children
Lest come the day when...
yours...
and yours...
and your son too stands
in these docks to reiterate...
that it's an honest father's blood
that flows in my veins
Time was when l was an innocent boy,
just like your sons
Like all mothers, my mother too
wove a golden dream for me
She would say, ''My son will grow up
to become a lawyer''
''Then he will become a magistrate.
And then, a judge... like his father''
l know the verdict that this court
is about to give
And l'm willing to suffer any sentence.
For my sins, this is atonement
But l await the decision
from yet another quarter
l want to know Judge Raghunath,
what says your heart?
What says your heart?
Has the Judge come to see his convict?
A father...
who is guilty
Guilty? You?
Yes.
Tomorrow, the law might
pronounce you guilty
But in the eyes of God,
l am the one who is guilty
Are you weeping?
Yes, for the father who found his son,
and yet he has lost him
For the husband who forced his wife
to become a widow
For society, where poverty
breeds crime
For the son who is orphaned
though his father is alive
For the child who goes through life
looking for someone...
who will call him ''Son''
Son
Raj, son of Judge Raghunath,
you have been proved guilty...
of trying to assassinate
your father, Judge Raghunath
But in the light of the strange and
unfortunate circumstances your life...
which your counsel Ms Rita
has presented...
you are sentenced to only three years
of rigorous imprisonment
Crying?
You silly girl
Silly girls never cry
At this rate, how are you
going to practice?
What use is the practice, Raj?
l wasn't able to save you
No Rita, this penance
is very important for me
Only after l've been through this,
will l be worthy of you
With you beside me,
l can go through anything
l will become an honest man
Everyone will say l'm a good man
l will read, l will write
And just like Ma used to say,
first l'll become a lawyer...
then a magistrate
And then, a judge
Last night l saw a judge.
l'll become a judge
You won't call me a savage anymore,
will you?
l will. You savage!
Time up
Come on
Keep this
lt's your gift
Don't worry. l didn't steal it
l just smuggled it in
Not your fault, Rita.
lt's just the way l look
Three years isn't too long, Raj.
l'll wait for you
l'll wait for you!
- Don't cry
Number 308... move it
l should be leaving