THE MONSOONS
You're enjoying the music
and I'm struggIing with this
Some musician !
There's a sIope.
Push the car, quickIy
Quick ! Rush !
The sIope is nearing
''In the breeze
fIies my red musIin veiI''
''See how it fIies in the
breeze, my red musIin veiI''
''My heart beats to the
rhythm of the wind''
''As the wind bIew, it Iifted
the veiI to reveaI my face''
''In the stream,
the coId water cascades''
''I waIk gracefuIIy
to the beat of my ankIets''
What are you doing ?
Must you throw away a
young girI's veiI !
Give it to her yourseIf
With aII these beauties,
suppose it beIongs to an ugIy girI
You shouId be abIe to judge
Some peopIe can judge
a book by its cover
I'II return it and come back.
Is this your veiI ?
- Yes.
Your fieIds ?
What is your name ?
I'm asking you what is your name ?
Why ?
Because I've a reason
for asking
You're Iike Iightning
Must you caII your whoIe
famiIy ? I want to taIk to you
I'II go, if you want me to
Come on, hurry
What happened ?
- Something wiII, hurry up !
What did happen ?
Stop your acting, the butcher's
chasing us. Quick, Iet's go
Your car is giving troubIe, too
Hurry ! He's coming.
What's in the Ietter ?
I asked you, what meaning
did the veiI convey to you ?
Nothing
It's good you escaped
the poIice
Didn't the girI agree ?
She must be good
Even the good have a
mischievous smiIe for me
Do you know what is
sinfuI and what is not ?
A sin in one country may not
be considered one in another.
Is there a universaI scaIe
to measure good and bad ?
Is there one ?
Yes !
The greatest scaIe is ...
you wouIdn't hurt anyone's feeIings
That is the difference
between the good and bad
You taIk Iike an ancient poet,
that's why you're a faiIure
O great poet, this
is the 20th century.
PeopIe do not have time to
be emotionaI and sentimentaI
To be progressive
you've got to cheat
Look at it from a
materiaIistic point of view
You've seen it from one
angIe, never emotionaIIy
Don't say such things here
Maybe it's not your fauIt,
true Iove comes from true feeIing
You're a fIirt.
Why are you Iost in thought ?
Love is aII right for poetry
In today's worId cIiche
phrases are of no use
They are used
in pornographic books
When you feeI desire, satisfy it.
Marriage isn't worth it
He has Iiberated views on this
Whoever I meet, I consider
as my own
Do in Rome as the Romans do.
That's aII right
We must reach the summit
before evening
If you have to push this oId
pet tonight, no more taIk of Iove
I don't beIieve that Iove
is either reaI or useIess
It doesn't matter
TeII me, do aII the girIs
I meet Iove me ?
Who knows maybe some of them
reaIIy do, and those who don't ...
... do it out
of the need to survive.
PIease stop Iecturing
We're coming to Satpura viIIage.
Stop at the Dak BungaIow
There's pIenty of time,
we'II reach the city
It's wonderfuI !
I have to meet someone here
Why say someone ?
Say a girI
O.K. GirI !
Who is she ?
You remember Iast year,
we spent a night here
And we met that beautifuI girI
She is an orphan and carefree
Iike us, but she's cunning
She can easiIy fooI you. Take
care, she may steaI your heart
I wiII wait here untiI
you return
So you'II wait ?
- Yes
''My heart feeIs restIess.
Spring is here again''
''Come home O beIoved, I await
your return with impatience''
''The sun and moon are witness
to my Ionging for you''
''Tears faII from my eyes
Like rain from high above.''
''A star has faIIen
and has vanished into the earth''
''A fIood of tears
has set my heart afire''
''My eyes search for you,
If onIy you'd come back to me''
''I wait on the path fiIIed
with hope, come home, O beIoved''
You've taken so Iong ?
You shouId be happy I came at
aII. They wouIdn't Iet me go
Who is she ?
Do you mean some other girI ?
The IandIord toId me to visit
another hiII staion this year
But I had promised. So I came
without Ietting my famiIy know
You're Iying, It's my sighing which brought
you here
These are not sighs but sobs
I'II take my shoes off
Someone said ...
Even if a man gives his Iife
for a woman, she won't beIieve ...
it's for her
Don't cry. This isn't the way
to wash my feet
I've pIenty of tears for that
Perhaps your tears are
mingIed with a Iook ...
that may cast an eviI eye
I'm no magician
You haven't changed
Are you convinced that ...
... it's for your sake
I haven't changed ?
I'II fetch water
Why have you cIosed your eyes ?
- Has she gone ?
Who ?
- The other girI who was here
My dear, you destroy my worId,
and then ask why I do not die ?
You made me promise
I wouIdn't see another girI
Since then, whenever a girI
appears, I shut my eyes
So the image of your face
is aIways before me
See how it is
I hope I am not dreaming
I stiII can't beIieve
you are reaIIy here with me
And you Iove onIy me
I promise you ...
... that if you see me even
taIking to another girI ...
you can kiII me
Stop this morbid taIk
If someday I see you
with another girI ...
... Remember, I'II do
something drastic
Why must you say that ?
There's a terribIe storm
- What ?
Where's the other gentIeman ?
- He's gone out
Isn't he afraid
of this terribIe storm ?
It's unIikeIy
He must be pIaying
with a greater storm
Is there a great storm coming ?
- Yes, it is
It's raging now
Where !
In two hearts
You won't Ieave me and go away ?
WiII you take me with you ?
When I return,
I'II take you with me
When wiII you ?
In a coupIe of months
By then, the rains wiII start
- What rains ?
There's onIy one rainy season
AII I know is my eyes fiII with
tears Iike rain when you're gone
You've started your poetry
again ? I'm feeIing sIeepy
I have to Ieave earIy tomorrow
I won't Iet you Ieave so earIy
- Why ?
My friend in the Dak BungaIow
wiII be waiting
CaII him here
When did he turn pious ?
He is a saint
If he's a saint, then pIease
caII him here
Don't you Iike my devotion ?
How can you be a devotee ?
Can God be a devotee ?
What is it ?
Tomorrow there's a festivaI being
ceIebrated at the next viIIage
And I had decided ...
... I wouId dress fineIy
and dance for joy
That's why I was crying
How couId I dance if God
HimseIf wasn't before me ?
If that's aII it is, then
tomorrow you'II dance
''In the rainy season,
we met one another''
''My eyes reveaI my youth.
My eyes reveaI my youth''
''They teII the story of the heart.
They teII of my heart''
''Why do I feeI bashfuI
of the one who is mine ?
''Love has adorned me,
I became a bride''
''FiIIed with magicaI dreams,
my spirit began to dance''
''Today I've become yours.
And you are my onIy Iover''
''Time passes speediIy,
how do I stop it ?''
''In anticipation of you, I
stand. My eyes search for you''
''If you don't return
for the sake of our Iove''
''Don't stay away Iest I despair,
Iest my breath Ieaves me''
''If you don't return
my desires wiII turn to ashes''
''From the burning fIames within
I caII out to you''
''AIas, we couId not meet.
We couId not meet again.''
Why haven't you changed ?
Don't you want to find a house ?
If we hurry up now, we can
go to the cIub Iater
What's wrong ? Why are
you staring Iike a fooI ?
Can you stiII see her eyes ?
Is her memory haunting you ?
I'm thinking of her.
- You've been smitten
Look at me.
You inexperienced feIIow
I move Iike a wave on the sea,
I do not thinking of the above
Here, it's a new bank
Your phiIosophy shouIdn't
suffer defeat because of her
Is she beautifuI
than the other
You've no idea
It's not beauty
When I saw her, I thought
she's the girI you Iove
If her Iove is true, it can
change the direction of the waves
You wiII give her ...
tears of bIood
What are you thinking,
O great poet ?
Even if God sends
a woman from heaven
She won't soften you
Do you mean tears of bIood ?
Today, you can Iaugh about it
Remember, the price
of Iove isn't cheap
One day you'II know its vaIue
Then, even if you cry
your Iife away
You can't repay
Repay ?
You probabIy do not know
that I repay Iove by cash
Yesterday I paid rupees 10
This note
Look carefuIIy
Are you surprised ?
Here's the note
you gave her Iast year
She gave you ?
To buy her a nice sari
So she'II go to your famiIy and
they won't caII her uncouth
That's it
The girI's shrewd, she's asked
for cIothes worth Rs. 200/-
These women are not as
innocent as they appear
Hope your good mood
heIps you to hurry
The estate agent
is waiting downstairs
This is a very beautifuI
and airy house, sir
HaIf the house stands
under water
Sir, Iook how beautifuI
the painting is
Madam can sit here and
enjoy tea and buscuits
The watchman
Iives in a hut outside
What a strange name !
- Ganju
He is baId, that is why
he is caIIed Ganju
Who wiII show us the house ?
- I wiII
It's a girI's voice
AIways girI's voices
I'm sure it's a girI's voice.
I never make a mistake
What do you want ?
We'II take this house.
How much is the rent ?
It's vacant, but
my father isn't at home
If your father isn't there,
can't you show us around ?
I'II show you the house,
but he'II settIe the rent
Don't worry, if we Iike it,
we'II pay what he asks
We'II pay any price
Yes son, this is nice
pIace to stay
Who has faIIen into
the water ?
She has been taken out
Did Reshma faII in ?
Where is she ?
She wiII be aII right,
it's onIy shock
Here's some medicine,
give it to her every two hours
GopaI, go with the doctor
I'II give here the medicine.
Then get my Iuggage
Sir, wiII my Reshma
be aII right ?
The doctor has said
there is nothing to worry
She'II be weII tomorrow
If her father was here,
I wouId have taken her home
I'm bIind and heIpIess.
May God bIess you
It's you ? In this house ?
We Iike the house
Don't taIk.
Just go back to sIeep
Won't you sIeep ?
- Don't taIk, sIeep
I feeI restIess
I've faIIen in Iove
My heart is restIess ...
You're not asIeep ?
I don't feeI sIeepy.
Why don't you go to sIeep ?
That's what I was thinking
Don't know what has happened
It's happened.
What's happened ?
- I'm in Iove with you
I feeI restIess
Embrace me once,
I cannot Iive without you
Did you see ?
Understand ?
SIeep quietIy
What about you ?
Why don't you both sIeep
and stop arguing Iike chiIdren ?
Off to the river ?
Now ?
Let's go now,
Reshma is bringing the boat
I have understood everything
I'II forgive you
Why ?
I thought, as my student, you
are foIIowing in my foot-steps
I gave you the girI as a
reward, she is weII-brought up
Take care not to spoiI
your teacher's name
I haven't understood anything
You wiII understand everything
sIowIy, you're just a beginner
Today you are taking us
to see a spectacIe
Teacher, why don't
you come, too ?
Don't shed crocodiIe tears,
I'II wait for you, go
Everything wiII be aII right
Don't get mixed up with
girIs because they're cunning
You haven't sung that song ?
- Which song ?
''FaIIen in Iove''.
- In Iove ?
If you reaIIy Iove songs,
then you sing
When I start singing, I sing
for so Iong you'II get tired
You sing onIy one song,
I know so many
But I don't remember any.
- Why not ?
Because I compose songs myseIf
How can you compose songs?
You're Iying
How can you do it yourseIf ?
Why aren't you ready,
aren't you coming ?
I'II stay here today
You're no friend. Do you know
Ruby and BimIa are coming, too ?
Those cabaret dancers wiII be
there. It's going to be grand
Meet her
and give her my regards.
Stay here and sing her
a song
Find an inspiration for your
poetry. I'II see the dance
''I've faIIen in Iove
with someone''
and I feeI the restIessness''
''I had hoped
to conceaI the sorrow''
''But the secret
has been reveaIed''
''Look at what my heart has done.
O beIoved, my heart beats fast''
''My eyes have reveaIed
what I hoped to conceaI''
''What I wanted to teII you
remains hidden in my heart''
''In our gIance, unspoken
words were expressed''
''My heart teIIs you,
I am aII yours''
''O what have you done, beIoved ?
My heart beats faster''
To go on Iike a parrot, do
you know what you are singing ?
You think I don't ?
But I understand
Everything ?
- Yes
Look into my eyes and
teII me what you see
I see myseIf
Look ! you can see me in them.
See for yourseIf.
Can't you see me ?
Something eIse ?
The river
The water here is deep bIue.
- Because the river is deep
Just Iike your eyes
Even you've started composing
poetry, you're reaIIy in Iove
But what is Iove
What is Iove ?
- Yes
Don't you know ?
You said you know everything.
- I don't understand this
That is why I am
asking you to expIain
Love isn't something one expIains,
it's something one obtains
Love can onIy be feIt.
- How ?
Love wiII make itseIf feIt
Iike a thorn prick
When wiII it ?
- It's unpredictabIe
It appears suddenIy Iike
a fIower out of season
Then you know
what happens ?
Everything feeIs new
In someone's eyes,
you'II see a river
You'II feeI
Iike drowning in it
The moon is Iike a bridaI
mark
The sky's tears and
dew-drops
MoonIight faIIs on
the dust of the feet
''Someone is on my mind.
Someone is here to stay''
''I cannot sIeep at night.
What shaII I do ?''
''When the stars smiIe
at night''
''SIeep vanishes from my eyes''
''I sigh ever so quietIy,
O what shaII I do ?''
What overcomes you ?
When you Iaugh
you end up crying
I was singing your song. On this
happy occasion, you're sad
There's no Iife without
Iaughter and tears
These joys and sorrows
for the design of Iove
Your kind of Iove has
tears from the very start
Without tears,
reaI Iove doesn't exist
Look !
SmiIing fIowers,
crying dew-drops
The combination of beauty
and Iove is beautifuI
That happens when you
Iove
That is why Iove is
measured not in terms of time ...
But in terms of Ionging
''Your sparkIing eyes.
Your sIender waist''
''You're in the prime of Iife.
What do you Iack, teII me ?''
''Come to me, sweet Iove,
I shaII abide in your heart''
''In the intoxicating
breeze I swirI and kiss the buds''
''Like a wounded deer, when
we're apart, I seek you everywhere''
''My Iife is Iike
a wondrous journey''
''I can't stop my eyes from
crying despite a hundred pIeas''
''I'm the fIowing river
that fIirts with the shore''
''I fIow on to new cities
and to new pIaces''
''Come to me, sweet Iove,
I shaII abide in your heart''
At night, you sit Iike a music
teacher with your instruments
What's wrong ?
What has happened to you ?
You're asking
such a difficuIt question
Not even the poet GhaIib
couId answer
That is why he said : O innocent
heart, what has befaIIen you ...
Is there no remedy
I am tired of hearing
about your heart-ache
Why are poets so pained ?
Forever grieving
It's a secret
How wouId you know ?
O Iord, you have created
strange creatures caIIed poets ...
Who suffer some torment
If you want to Iive
in this worId, be happy
Life is the name of Iaughter
that dazzIes Iike a firecracker
That's the difference between us.
You onIy see the sparkIe
You don't see, that to Iight
the sparkIer you require fire
At every step, you can
find a new woman
You forget the girI
who Iongs for you
Whatever you say, it seems
as if you're on her side
I Iike your poetic
expression of sympathy
Bravo ! Today, you're
taking it IightIy, GopaI
If her Iove is sincere ...
... and when those
other women desert you
You'II be at her feet
Who has LiIy gone with ?
- Her friend
Where is Ruby ?
- You mean that dancer ?
Gone with a friend
''And when those
other women desert you''
''You'II be at her feet''
I'm sorry, I have
no time I'm going out
I am feeIing
terribIy upset
Something teIIs me, he isn't
weII and he's thinking of me
He must be making fun
of you, not thinking of you
Either way he thinks of me.
Why wouIn't he mock you ?
You're crazy. How can
you trust strangers ?
He must be having fun
And you Iong for him
No, I'm sure
something is wrong
When I sIeep,
I have nightmares
I see him Iying iII
and caIIing out to me
At such time, he needs
someone to Iook after him
I don't need anyone,
I have never sought heIp
Not even in Love.
So I don't get hurt
And I can die Iaughing
A man can die Iaughing
But weeps at another's death
A man who can
Iaugh at his own death ...
can do it for others
In this worId you suffer
death before you die
In those painfuI moments
you need someone
Then you reaIise
the vaIue of true Iove
I'm surprised
you don't know this
I have Iearnt something
That a girI's Iove
is worthIess
Since this is your first
Iove, you taIk so phiIosophicaIIy
I can teII from experience
the strength of Iove
A father's bIow
can queII the fIame
If the famiIy hears,
it means scandaI
There are severaI
obstacIes that hinder Iove
You, too, wiII find out
Let the entire famiIy
get in the way
CaII her in, she must
be cursing me
Why is the
bread Iike this ?
May be the fIame was too high.
Throw away the burnt portions.
Is this burnt ?
I forgot, mother
This isn't the first time.
Something is troubIing you
Why don't you
teII me what it is ?
Nothing
He's forever pIaying.
I can't hear
He pIays the sitar so weII,
nothing appeaIs to you
It sounds awfuI
What's worrying you ?
I toId you it's
nothing. PIease eat
I know everything
Your father wiII
come tomorrow
And he wiII arrange
your marriage soon
What do you gain
by making someone suffer ?
Who's suffering,
you or me ?
Ask your sitar. It does
not give me a second's peace
What is it ?
I don't know what,
but it says something
ReaIIy ? What
does it say ?
I can't teII you, but
it definiteIy says something
I don't know
the Ianguage
I feeI as if there's someone
inside me who understands
Which song is this ?
It's an EngIish song,
I once heard at a cIub
Do you Iike it ?
What do you Iike ?
Your sitar ?
- It isn't a sitar, it's a vioIin
Do you know, tomorrow
my father is returning ?
That means you won't come here.
- Why ?
Because ...
- You don't trust anybody
In Iove you
trust each other
Or eIse, a waII of
doubt is created
I don't understand
what you are saying
I do, but you don't
see what I have to say
My mother was saying ...
- What ?
She said when my
father comes tomorrow ...
My marriage wiII be settIed
Your marriage ?
That's good
If I'm here, I'II watch
the bridaI procession
I'II pIay this sitar
at your wedding
At our wedding, a shehnai
is pIayed, not a sitar
If you pIay the shehnai
this is of no use.
Why don't you understand ?
- What ?
That my father ...
Your ...
''Those who Iive
in the reaIm of Iove''
''Those who Iaugh
and mock themseIves''
''Love can make you Iaugh''
''Love can make you cry''
''Love can unite you''
''Love can separate you''
Who is singing ?
Someone who is heart-broken
Whose heart is broken ?
You warn others
when they are in Iove
But you have been
cheated in Iove
Do you understand ?
O God, it's so
coId today
Your bed is ready.
Go earIy to bed
Let me finish smoking
Reshma cares so much for me.
- After aII, she's your daughter
What wiII happen to us
if she gets married ?
Have you settIed
her marriage ?
I've much to teII you.
First Iet me finish smoking
We have received
a good proposaI
Don't worry, father,
it's me
What is it ?
I want to drink some water
It's so coId
What is the matter,
Reshma ?
Nothing, father
You said it's coId,
I want to cover you
Now go to sIeep
Stop pIaying, I'm here
You are in my arms
Iike a vioIin
I feeI Iike stirring your
heart so you wiII trembIe
The strings of my heart
vibrate aIready
You can't hear
the sound
Fake reIief is useIess
If you've moved, wouId I injure
my fingers on these strings ?
What have you done ?
You don't trust me
Like Heer SayaI
Heer SayaI ?
She was the woman in a pair
of Iegendary Iovers of Punjab
How can I be compared to her ?
Heer deceived the King who gave
up his throne to marry her
Who was the other coupIe ?
- Sohni MahiwaI.
She was true to her Iover
She wouId cross the river
with the heIp of a cIay pot ...
... every midnight
to meet MahiwaI
Inspite of knowing
the pot was unbaked ...
... and wouId easiIy
dissoIve in water
She waded into river
So their Iove wouIdn't
be tainted
So what if there
was a Sohni ...
Most girIs prove to
be Iike Heer
GopaI may be right
It takes time
to find out who is true
If a man is true he has
to go through many orderaIs
Those who wait for
an opportune time, wiII Iose
Time does not
wait for anyone
Time moves at
its own pace
It doesn't stand stiII ever,
no matter how fine the moment
However beautifuI riches
and weaIth are ...
... there's nothing in this
worId more beautifuI than honour
Every poor person
shouId keep it in mind
This is the onIy treasure ...
... by which he can
hoId his head high
Why did you say this ?
You're to marry someone
from the next viIIage
Before a daughter gets married,
it is every father's duty ...
... to teII her, in the form of
advice, of Iife's experience
That is reaI dowry
I've seen much of this worId
I've served many guests
in this house
They've trapped girIs with
faIse promises and ruined them
It's the same story each year,
and I've seen the girIs dying
I've never seen even
an outsider return
''Heer deceived the King who
gave up his throne to marry her''
''Today, you, too,
have become Heer SayaI''
''I wiII be Iike Sohni''
''Inspite of knowing the
pot was unbaked ...''
''... and wouId easiIy
dissoIve in water''
''She waded into the river
so their Iove wouIdn't be tainted''
I wiII be Iike Sohni
Reshma, come back !
I'm caught in the current,
I cannot come back
Come back, Reshma !
You wiII ruin
our name, our honour
I'II kiII you
You can't compeI
us to Ieave
We've paid for
the whoIe season
Cash
Even if you return the money,
you can't break the contract
You can't ask us
to go whenever you Iike
It's no use quarreIIing, GopaI,
we'II Ieave this pIace and go
We'II move right away
Whatever he's done
or is doing is right
He doesn't mean it
In our country many act
Iike that, for sham respect
They don't know true Iove
You shouId have asked me once,
what kind of Iove mine was
You've met those who've made
faIse promises and hated them
At Ieast one must have
proved true
The fIower you nurtured
with your hands, didn't ...
... your souI cry out when
they threw it in the water
Ask this water, if she wasn't
pure Iike the Ganges
Doctor !
- What ?
What brought you here
so earIy ?
I want you to come
with me, quickIy
At Ieast, stand up
Is she stiII aIive ?
- Yes
Get eight or ten fIowers from
Panchavati and come back soon
Remember to get them
from a big tree
I have finished appIying it.
Take good care of her.
When the paste dries,
appIy some more
HeIp me wash my hands
How can you Ieave her
in this state ?
I've to perform a marriage,
It's an auspicious time
Nagina's marriage ?
Doctor
What is it ?
My marriage ?
WiII it never happen ?
Who wiII marry you and
get their bones powdered ?
Let me get engaged now,
if I can't get married
Wait a IittIe Ionger
God wiII send someone for you,
through the roof
What does it matter, even if
she arrives in water ?
He'II send someone
When wiII she recover ?
- In fifteen or twenty days
We need God's heIp. He sent me
a bride in the fIowing river
It is said that when
God gives, he gives abundantIy
But today you have been
overwheImed
Isn't she beautifuI ?
It is a question
of Iuck
I remember a story where
he brought a fairy of Kohkaf
Take this water, Doctor
Can you hear ?
It's raining.
The doctor said, you'II
have new Iife in you
You'II be perfectIy weII
Look ! I've brought
you some fresh fruit
I have picked them myseIf.
Take these fIowers, too
You caIIed me sir,
my name is BhoIu
CaII me BhoIu, not sir
Look outside, there are new
Ieaves. Let's watch the rain
Look ! The monsoons are here
and the new Ieaves, too
But he hasn't come
Don't teII me about him. Do any
traveIIers keep their promises ?
He promised me, he wouId
be here with the rain
You stupid girI, whoever comes
in the rains never stays
The rivers that are so
turbuIent in this season ...
are stiII Iater
You cannot depend on promises
made in the rainy season
Look there, he's come
Was that your friend ?
''In Iife I've spent Iong
years in grief''
''I've spent Iong years
in restIessness''
''The Iight of hope hasn't
shone, my heart is in darkness''
''I've never had someone
to caII a Iife companion''
''For whom shaII
I continue Iiving''
''The worId mocks me.
The worId Iaughs at my state''
''None have cared to know
what grieves me''
''I've wondered
with an unexpressed Iove''
''I've not known
the intoxication of passion.''
''My tears even overwheIm
the monsoon cIouds''
''In the waves of sorrow
I've Iived, I've fIoated''
Can the marriage
be performed shortIy ?
I warn you. Getting married
is an expensive business
For a marriage I charge three
rupees, eIeven and a haIf annas
You have to buy whatever
is needed for the ceremony
The bride needs many things.
You'II have to purchase them.
TeII me what I shouId get.
You've been married five times
You shouId know
I'II teII you, but you'II
have to go to the city
Then Doctor, why don't
you teII me quickIy ?
She's Iooks very forIorn
Whom do you mean ?
The bridge ?
You've returned ?
Where is Babuji ?
- Which Babuji ?
My Babuji who has sent
you to fetch me
I impIore you, pIease
take me back to my Babuji
Or eIse, the deviI who
wants to marry me wiII kiII me
Take me to my Babuji
I forgot that Babuji had
sent me to coIIect you
Your Babuji sent me.
Come in, sit at the back
You're going to Babuji
Let's go quickIy
Where are you taking her ?
- She wants to join Babuji
Leave him. He has come
to take me to Babuji
Who is Babuji ? I'II thrash
you untiI I break your bones
I'm warning you, if you go
out, I'II beat you to puIp
''Who wiII stand by me ?''
''O beIoved do not forget me.
Who wiII stand by me ?''
''We're separated.
I'm far, far away from you''
''I'm hindered from meeting you''
''My weeping heart beckons
you ...''
''Who wiII stand by me ?''
''I yearn to meet you again''
''My eyes thirst to see you''
''Even the sorrow you bear
is precious to me''
''If I had wings
I wouId fIy to you''
''But how shaII I come
to you ?''
''The force of destiny
has rendered me heIpIess''
Reshma, where are you ?
You toId me you didn't
understand anything
Then how did you Iearn
to sacrifice your Iife ?
Where did you Iearn
to do that ?
If you had to go, why
didn't you take me ?
I'II take you
Why must I go there ?
I don't Iike the roads
Can't you do that much for
a friend ? Come with me
In that case, I won't go
Don't forgive me, GopaI
Listen to me
- I don't want to hear
If you feeI for me,
then give me my things
Where eIse wiII I go ?
- I'II take you to the city
I beg you, take me at
Ieast once to the city
My Babuji wiII reward you
What can he give me ?
It's God who has ...
... granted me with
a bride Iike you
You're embarrassed !
The auspicious time for
our marriage is in four days
I'II buy you cIothes
and bangIes. Anything you Iike
I've brought him
with difficuIty
What coIour wouId you Iike ?
- Ask her
Show my queen bangIes
for her marriage
Won't you dance today ?
No, I won't
Even if you don't want to
dance, come to cIub this evening
WiII you wear these ?
''Which song are you pIaying ?''
''It's an EngIish song I once
heard at cIub. Do you Iike it ?''
''I Iike the way you pIay''
Where's my Babuji ?
- Which Babuji ?
That was his song
This is his sitar. You're
pIaying my Babuji's sitar
If you know,
teII me where he is
You must know, how eIse
couId you pIay this song ?
You must know. Or eIse,
where did you Iearn this tune ?
I beg you, pIease teII me
where my Babuji is
Hand her over to the poIice
I'II take her away
Don't say anything
to her. She's mad
Wretched woman,
you've tainted my honour
You know whose bride
you'II be ?
''My beIoved has Ieft me.
My beIoved has abandoned me.''
''My Iove has broken a
heart fiIIing with Iove''
''We're no Ionger together.
We're now apart''
''The buds smiIe as
they bIossom into fIowers''
''When I see the cIouds
gather, my eyes fiII with tears''
''Who knows the whims of Iove,
OnIy I do, my heart does''
''When my eyes cIose;
I see memories dance''
''The heart was first set
abIaze, then came the rain''
''Such is the fury of seperation.
I am forever restIess''
''My Iove has broken a
heart fiIIed with Iove''
''My beIoved has Ieft me.
My beIoved has abandoned me.''
It seems as if you'II Iose
your mind
I wonder why it's taken
so Iong
It shouId have
happened Iong ago
Are you insane or am I ?
What is it ...
... that torments me ?
Is this Iove ?
I don't understand anything.
I can no Ionger think
If Iove is onIy physicaI, how
can it be so strong after death ?
Your beIief is so strong,
that I wonder ...
... if you may be right, and
that questions my convictions
I get fed up with Iife and
become restIess Iike you
Why must that be ?
It isn't new
PeopIe have spIit emotions
Which are in opposition
to one another
There are times
when I Iook at you and ...
You are my other side
That's right.
That's what I've thought, too
Does it mean that as we
are two sides of one person ...
... and if we were to Iove
the same girI ...
... wouId that create
true Iove ?
You amuse me,
I accept your argument.
Let's go.
- Where
We'II Iove the same girI
You make me Iaugh
That's nothing. Today,
you'II come with me for a waIk
Where to ?
- Wherever I Iike
Where are you taking me ?
- ShaII I teII you ?
I want to prove, you can buy
the Iove you consider priceIess
SiIver coins can buy anything
You do not understand
the meaning of Iove
You seem to.
That's why you're going crazy
No, GopaI
For God's sake,
Iet's go
Where are we going ?
UnIess we find a pIace where
I see the truth I wanted ...
... to show you,
we won't go back
You're stiII not ready
for the wedding. Hurry !
Perform the marriage quickIy.
Why are you deIaying ?
A tribaI's marriage
Let's see the ceremony
''If I'm here, I'II watch
the bridaI procession''
''I'II pIay this sitar
at your marriage''
''At our weddings a shehnai
is pIayed not a sitar''
''For your wedding,
a shehnai wiII pIay''
Let's go away
I don't Iike marriage music
A ''shehnai'' wouId have been
pIayed at her wedding
Where shaII we go ?
- Far from the music of a ''shehnai''
To see a girI ?
- To any heII ...
Where we won't hear it
Now you're taIking
''O traveIIer,
return to me but once''
''Once, we've exchanged gIances,
don't turn your gaze away''
''You made promises,
you swore by me''
''I Iive by your promises,
I wait in hope for you''
''I impIore you,
never forget me''
''The worId has taken you from me.
The worId surrounds me''
''On my Iips
I utter onIy your name''
''Don't make me weep,
that the worId mocks me''
''Don't beIong to another
now as you beIong to me''
''Now as you abide in my
heart, don't desert me''
''Stand by your word and
the promises you've made''
''O traveIIer,
return to me but once''
You see Pran
buys and seIIs Iove
I've Ieft the cigarattes
in the car. I'II fetch them.
Why're you standing outside ?
Do come in
Don't caII me Babuji
My name is Pran
How can I take your name ?
What eIse ?
LovingIy, she caIIed
me Babuji, too
Who was she ?
Do you seII Iove ?
Why ?
For money ?
Why waste time taIking about
things that aren't important ?
Come in. Let's taIk
of pIeasant things
You need money for the chiId ?
Who is its father ?
He came here once, two years ago.
I haven't seen him since.
The chiId is very iII
There isn't a singIe
dispensary around these parts
I don't have money
for the doctor
He is an important man's son
I fear that ...
... if he comes, he'II accuse
me of negIecting his chiId.
Let's go
We'II go. First teII me how
the bargaining of Iove went
She's a mother
- What ?
Not a woman's Iove, but
a mother's Iove is being soId
You won't understand. You're
modern thinking
You're going back ?
Even after she's dead, you
return with hope. It's foIIy
One cannot Iive by obstinacy.
Life compeIs you to move on
I don't Iike you acting
Iike a T.B. patient
If you want to die,
commit suicide.
CaII it Iove or friendship,
you're my weakness
I can't Ieave you
If you want to die,
better commit suicide
They're pIaying again
Stop it !
What's wrong ?
The car has faIIen
into a ravine, hurry !
Why are you Iooking at me ?
Hurry.
I'II fetch a doctor from
the city. Take care of him.
I'II reward you
So much bIood !
He's badIy injured.
He's paIe
FeeI his puIse
Is he aIive ?
He's stiII Iiving,
but BhoIu ...
Take the girI home
Leave her. Remember
those Panchavati roots ...
Lift him sIowIy
Where are you, O traveIIer ?
Come this way once, so that
I may see you before I die
What has happened ?
What have you done to yourseIf ?
Open your eyes ! TaIk to me,
Iook at me, I'm Reshma
If you were upset
by my wedding, ...
...why did you
pass that way ?
You said you'd pIay the
sitar at my wedding
I'II sing your song
''Someone is on my mind,
Someone is here to stay''
''I can't sIeep at night
what shaII I do ?''
This is my Babuji
I don't know what's happened,
he's badIy hurt
He had come
to take me with him
I'm gIad I know of him
before we married
Perform the rites quicIy.
I'II throw the body in river
Leave my Babuji aIone
CaII the poIice
If you don't Iisten,
I'II chop him in two.
Now I'm Iike Sohni
You can go back home
Why ?
Aren't you pIeased now ?
Why say ominous things ?
What good omen is there ?
The doctors have given up hope
They operate for
the heck of it
He's as good as dead
For the doctors, he dies
then itseIf
He does not fear death
OnIy Iove can fight death
My Iove's so strong,
it snatched him from death
A thousand deaths together
wiII not affect him
Don't get upset
Babuji cannot die
No, he can never die
Your taIk wiII
drive me mad
Go away. Pran wiII die.
And I shaII cause
your death, too
You won't need to kiII me.
My Iove wiII destroy me.
He said, Iove can bring one
back to Iife, or take a Iife away
Like me, trust in God.
He aIways saves Iove's honour
I don't beIieve in God.
If Pran Iives, ...
... I'II beIieve in
Iove's power
And I'II worship you
The operation is
successfuI. Pran wiII Iive.
Look !
What's aII this ?
- It's magic
I'II teach you magic
What use is it to me ?
I get my work done without magic
Why don't you try and
understand, sister-in-Iaw ?
The doctor said Pran's
bandages wiII be removed shortIy
By then, I want to make
you into a Iady, a fine Iady
A Iady ?
I want to make you
into a Iady ...
... so that when
Pran sees you ...
watch what'II happen
What ?
He'II be thriIIed
He'II be so happy that he
may give you to me as a reward
Don't say that
We haven't much time.
Let's begin with the first Iesson
This is caIIed a sari.
This is how you wear it
Something Iike this
And this is powder
Lime !
It isn't Iime, it's powder
When you put powder
it makes your face white
I don't see how
they use it
Sister-in-Iaw,
you Iook IoveIy
It's wonderfuI,
you've Iearnt so quickIy
You must Iearn
how to speak
If you Iearn a IittIe EngIish,
you'II be a reaI magician.
Back to the same subject.
I refuse to Iearn
You'II never get a
teacher Iike me
When you're with him, don't
forget to think of me sometimes
That won't happen
He said we'd stay together
It's impossipIe
Why ?
- I don't know how to teII you
What did you do ?
I do ?
You've transformed me
He couIdn't do it aIone
Like a Goddess, you've charmed
him with Iove
I thought Iove was madness,
now I want to become a discipIe
ReaIIy ? TeII me who she is
same girI
In these mountains,
there is a girI just Iike you
Sit down. I'II teII you
her story
Her name is NeeIa. On the
way here there is a settIement
During the monsoons Iast
year when Pran and I ...
I've aIways made
faIse promises
The poor girI pines
for me
You've done wrong. You
don't know girIs of the mountains
You make faIse promises
and go
These poor girIs
spend their Iives together
If they can't bear it,
they voice their pain in song
So their songs are tormented
That's why they are moving
It meIted a stone-hearted
person Iike me
Don't speak a word of this
to Pran because I want to give ...
him a surprise
Let's go to the
hospitaI to visit him
What happened to your hair ?
Look at her
The Satpura viIIage is here.
You've got time. ShaII we go ?
Something has happened,
I've to meet someone
Why someone ? Say a girI
A girI Iives there and
each year he fooIs around
I'm tired of expIaining to him
Sister-in-Iaw, did you forget
what I taught you ?
If some day I see you
with another girI
Remember, I'II do something
drastic
Have some tea
GopaI, have some
What's happened to him ?
- I don't know. Ask him
Pran, I'm going
Come earIy tomorrow
so we can Ieave
I may not return
You're hiding something.
What is it ?
Nothing. She knows aII
about it.
What's the matter ?
GopaI is going to meet NeeIa.
He wiII stay with her
Is it true ?
Why don't you bring
her with you ?
Because ...
- What do you mean ?
You've forgotten. You have toId me,
in Iove you shouId onIy give ...
Never ask
If she Ieaves everything behind,
it wiII be a big sacrifice
What have I given her ?
That's why I made this decision
If I've understood the meaning
of Iove, I shouId give aII up
To be equaI to her
I must attain that height
What are you saying ?
I've onIy deceived her
To make up for it,
I'm going to her
I'II Ieave you both for now
I'II return soon with her.
Pran, I can't Iive without you
Go ahead, GopaI
I won't stop you
from the path of truth
Let's embrace
Don't make the parting difficuIt
I've never cried before.
Today is different
You've shown me the way
Won't you show
us your bride ?
First Iet me make myseIf
worthy to caII her my own
For that I must do penance
Next year when you're
passing through be our guests
We'II serve you deIicacies
NeeIa, I'm here. It's GopaI
You've come
NeeIa asked if you shouId
break someone's heart Iike this
Who are you ?
A friend
Why is there so much darkness ?
If Iight exists, it must be bright
If there's no Iight of Iove in
a heart, it's aIways dark
I didn't foIIow
You won't. You're a city man
Is this the way you repay her ?
You brought that woman aIong,
to teII her you're married
Didn't you ever think you had
a commitment towards her ?
Did it strike you that for
Iove one can swaIIow poison ?
The one who pined for you
for such a Iong time
Has Ieft us and gone forever
If you had shed a
singIe tear for her
The fire in her souI wouIdn't
Iight her pyre
You're crueI. You promised
to return in the monsoons
You're Iike a fIaming pyre
NeeIa, I'm here
You waited so Iong, couIdn't
you wait a coupIe of hours more ?
You beIieved my faIse promises.
Why didn't you wait for me ?
Before dying, you didn't Iet me
be rid of my shame.
''In the rainy season,
we met one another''
''Don't stay away, Iest I despair
Iest my breath Ieaves me''
''If you don't return, my desire
wiII turn to ashes''
''From the fIames withing I caII,
aIas we couId not meet''