You Tube - Video Running Time 01:33:28
You Tube search name - Jaal (1952) | Dev Anand | Geeta Bali | Guru Dutt (Full Movie)
'If anyone speaks
bad, don't listen.'
'Don't speak if someone does wrong.'
'Stop if someone is doing wrong.'
'Forgive if
someone makes a mistake.'
'All the characters, good or bad..
"Shown in this story are not real.'
'But their deeds are good and bad.'
'And in every country and it's
people, this fault is found.'
'On the eastern border of India,
there are many small"
..foreign
settlements where people from..
...other countries come for trade.'
'From a similar
settlement a ship is".
...going to leave for Bombay.'
For how much more time
do we have to wait, sir?
I had told you to
stand here, so many times.
And you are
strolling about the place.
This is not your house
where I'm your sister-in-law.
And you are my brother-in-law.
Here I'm your captain
and you are my constable.
Sir, I..
What do you mean, sir I.
When your captain tells you
to do something then do it.
Why should I ask, you ask.
I'll ask about my bike.
Are you afraid, do you
fear them? I'll ask.
Mister?
- Mister? Who mister? I'm sir.
Sir, when will this door open?
When will this door open?
When will the luggage go?
It won't go, it won't go.
Didn't I tell you that
they won't tell you?
Lord, Lord. What government?
What police?
Indian police is very good.
Don't worry, he must be coming now.
When will the gate open?
- I don't know.
When will the ship set sail?
- I don't know, I don't know.
One tight slap I'll give you.
You only said that you
wanted to go to Goa, now go.
Let me see, bring it here.
What happened?
I married and then Mummy and daddy.
Drink, drink, have it
for free, have this"
"and you will get 1,000 rupees.
Don't know why my heart
is beating fast today?
Why?
- I don't know.
I hope all the work gets over today.
Don't behave so weak,
all the arrangements"
have been made.
And I'm here only.
- The gate has been opened.
Go, go and get the
formalities done and come to me.
Go, go.
What is this? At least
have a look at our luggage.
Get it fast, come fast, fast.
Get the luggage.
Everything is fine.
Why are you so worried?
Just wipe your face. Take this.
Will you wait till the ship leaves?
Yes, don't worry!
I'll be here only. Go.
Goodbye, Tony.
- Goodbye.
Just hope that this
girl doesn't make a mess.
Wait.
- Sir?
Come over here. Open your purse.
Police.
ls there anyone?
Fifty, fifty rupees and
take the whole basket.
What are you saying, Simon?
All the fish for just fifty?
We have fought and got these fish.
Who said fifty?
- I said it.
That's good, my tiger, in fifty
you won't even get the basket.
Was he counting
the fish or your age?
Move, Simon.
- I moved.
Say, say why do you fear, say?
55.
- 55. - 60. - 60, 60, 60.
65. - Don't shout,
don't shout, otherwise"
"the fishes will feel shy.
Say.
-7o. -75. -so.
..85.. 90.. 95.. 100.
100.. 1, 100.. 2, 100.. 3.
Mister, come and pick up your stuff.
Money.
20, 40, 60,--
80..90..
Give me a smile and
you will get 10 more.
Maria, let's go.
From when did you start
dealing in fishes, sir?
A deal of hearts?
You always feel that
only, heart, love.
Maria, that is because
even I have a heart.
And in that heart
there is love for you.
Love?
Don't make fun of love,
Maria. One day even..
..you might have to
cry for this love.
No, Simon, you will
always see me smiling.
Even I wish for that
you always keep smiling.
Come on, let's go.
- Come on.
Hey old man, have you
seen any girl? - Basket?
You barrack, not basket, girl.
Why? What has happened?
She has run away with the loot.
Keep an eye, she had worn a sari.
- Sari?
Who is it?
- Who is it, Maria?
Who are you? - Save me sister,
the police are behind me.
Why? What happened?
I have run away from home,
my husband is very cruel.
That's why..
Did you see any girl?
She was wearing a sari?
No, no.
"The sun is melting into the sky."
"The shadows of the
evening are spreading."
"The sun is melting into the sky."
"The shadows of the
evening are spreading."
"Something weird
like this is happening."
"Different kind of
divisions are happening."
"Birds are flying with
their wings spread wide."
"The trees are standing
with their heads bent."
"The sun is melting into the sky."
"The shadows of the
evening are spreading."
"If you can find try
to find, oh fisherman."
"The flying clouds
and the turning waves."
"Who knows who has hidden from us"
"and made this colorful sights."
"The sun is melting into the sky."
"The shadows of the
evening are spreading."
"Nobody knows the truth about this."
"One reality and a thousand tales."
"Only one image all day and night."
"Appears while changing many forms."
"The sun is melting into the sky."
"The shadows of the
evening are spreading."
"The sun is melting into the sky."
You devil, you have
troubled me a lot today.
Brother.
- Come on, give me a kiss.
No, brother.
- Give me a kiss.
Come on, come on.
On the other side, come on.
You can go now.
Let it be, brother.
I'm no longer a kid now.
If you're not a kid,
are you an old woman?
Do you know, brother, that
in six months I will be 18?
Yes, I'm worried about that as well.
Lisa, come over here.
Lisa? Who is this Lisa?
She is our guest.
And she" her ship
got wrecked and all..
..her friends have separated.
So I brought her along with me.
This is my brother,
Carlo. You keep talking to..
..him, I'll get some
clothes from the top.
Lisa, come, Lisa, Lisa.
Come, Lisa, change your clothes"
"fast and let's have dinner.
Don't know whether
you will like our food.
We are poor people, we
only have fish and rice.
Made it once and eat it twice.
Just see if this is not too wet.
You put you sari over
here only? This is silk.
There is no place to dry it.
What a small house we have!
We work from
morning to evening and"
"then we have food and go to sleep.
That's what our life is all about.
Brother likes to stay over here,
sometimes he talks to people.
Otherwise what is kept over here?
Two small rooms and a terrace.
Your house must be very nice.
Where is your house?
In Bombay. Bombay? I've heard
it is a very beautiful city.
Don't know whether
I'll ever get to see it.
That's good, your whole
appearance has changed.
Come on, let's have dinner.
Just get this.
Brother?
- Yes.
a is looking so
beautiful in these clothes"
"what should I tell you?
A person is not good or bad
depending upon his clothes.
A good person is one
who has a good heart..
..who does good deeds.
That's good, brother,
you talk like the father.
Have a seat, Lisa sit.
Brother, I have got the plate.
Bless us oh Lord and
give us only that"
"what we deserve, thank
you, Lord. Amen. - Amen.
I'll find her, where will
she escape and run away.
You people are
having dinner, eat, eat!
Gomes, you also come and join us.
No, thanks, I was
just passing from here.
I got some good
smell so I thought that..
...I'll go and have a
few words with Carlo.
If you want to eat, eat
but the food is not fresh.
Maria, what is fresh
and what is stale?
You have made it, if you
insist, I'll taste it.
Don't feel shy, you'll also eat.
Good, good, Maria. You
cook excellent fish.
Eat, brother.
My God, what a huge storm that was.
A storm like this had
come many years before.
You might not remember it,
you were very small then.
In this storm only Carlo"
Maria, who is this?
She is our guest, Miss Lisa.
I see, she is a guest,
then can you pass the sauce.
Thank you.
Yes, so I was saying
that in the chaos"
..of the storm, that girl escaped.
Yes, so what were you saying, Gomes?
Nothing, there was this
girl who managed to escape.
But where will she go?
Wherever she goes I
will get my hands on her.
My name is Gomes.
But who was she? What happened?
She was a scoundrel, but
she was wearing good clothes.
She was running away with gold.
- Gold?
I have told everyone. She
had worn a nice sari, of silk.
Sari?
- You are wanted at home, fast.
Why did you not tell me earlier?
Okay, Maria, I'll take your leave.
Goodnight, Carlo.
- Goodnight, Gomes. - Goodnight.
Maria, Maria.
Wait for a minute, I'm on my way.
What is the reason? Why
don't you come with me?
My head is paining.
You have a headache or a heartache?
You must be thinking
that we are simple people.
We won't know of anything.
But don't try to take
advantage of our simplicity.
We maybe poor but we are honest.
I know. Once upon a
time even I used to..
"stay in a decent house like yours.
Anyway, it is a very long story,
I'll tell you some other time.
Maria, I'm coming, brother.
Maria, I will never forget
this obligation of yours.
Come, let me give you this necklace.
Are you trying to
fulfill the obligation?
You did not understand me, Maria.
Good morning, father.
- Good morning.
What happened?
- Say Geeta, don't feel shy.
Tell me.
- You won't tell anyone, will you?
No.
I was walking by the
edge of the road and then"
And then what happened?
And then he stopped me.
He stopped me and
then he held my hand.
For the past two hours
you are saying that..
..he stopped you and held your hand.
Come on, we're getting late.
You? Have you come
to make a new deal?
Yes, brand new, and priceless.
How much did you earn
in yesterday's deal?
Didn't earn anything
and lost everything.
In such deals a man has to lose"
"something to get something.
This hand is very beautiful
and even you are very beautiful.
I wish I were this chain.
- Leave me now.
Someone might see.
- Where are you going?
Inside, won't you come?
Me? Over there? Only the
weak people go over there.
Weak are those people
who fear to go inside.
'If anyone speaks
bad, don't listen.'
'Don't speak if someone does wrong.'
'Stop if someone is doing wrong'
'Forgive if
someone makes a mistake.'
Man is a statue of mistakes.
We all make mistakes.
That is why we cannot punish
others for their mistakes.
Our mistakes were
washed by the Lord himself.
For our well being he
climbed onto the cross.
And he went and met the creator.
That same creator has the
records to all our sins.
Only he can decide what is
right and what is wrong.
He only is the one who
punished for a mistake.
And he is the one who forgives.
That is why we all lower
our heads in front of him.
And we pray to him that
he forgives all our sins.
So, you have come back? I
knew you were going to come.
Where is the gold?
Forget all this, come
on, let's go somewhere.
Where is the gold?
So you have not come for me.
Come in the evening,
I'll get it to you.
I want it now, go
and get it immediately.
Father.
- Yes, daughter.
I want to ask you something.
- Ask.
You said that we cannot
punish anyone for their crime.
And we can only forgive them.
- Yes, daughter.
If we know that someone
has done wrong and we know..
"about it, then what should we do?
We should leave everything upon Him.
'Stop if someone
walks on the wrong path.'
"Stealthily to come
to my area is bad."
"Leaving without
talking to me is bad."
"Stealthily to come
to my area is bad."
"Leaving without
talking to me is bad."
"These signals are not good."
"There is something
going on in my mind."
"Don't come over
here to have a chat."
"Or to flirt around with me."
"The heart is for
loving and having fun."
"Listen, it is bad to
trouble an innocent soul."
"Stealthily to come
to my area is bad."
"Leaving without
talking to me is bad."
"My heart has come
on you, handsome."
"What is the fear of
getting embarrassed?"
"What place does
fear and hatred have"
..in the world of love and trust."
"The heart is for
loving and having fun."
"Listen, it is bad to
trouble an innocent soul."
"Stealthily to come
to my area is bad."
"Leaving without
talking to me is bad."
"The heart is for
loving and having fun."
"Listen, it is bad to
trouble an innocent soul."
"Stealthily to come
to my area is bad."
"Leaving without
talking to me is bad."
"Stealthily to come
to my area is bad."
"Leaving without
talking to me is bad."
Tony, a weird thing happened.
Where is the gold?
The gold is not there,
someone has taken it.
Where had you kept it?
Outside the house,
someone must have..
"seen me keeping it over there.
If the police come to know,
will you save me, Tony?
What do I know? That
is you and your work.
I'm all alone over here, Tony,
don't leave me alone and go.
Tony, TO"!!-
Yes, brother, this is the same gold.
I had seen her
hiding it in the night.
And as soon as I could, I
removed it and got it here.
If someone would
have seen it, then God..
"knows what would have happened?
My heart had told me
before that this girl..
..will come as a
trouble and not as a guest.
And when Gomes had
said that she was"
"wearing a sari, then
something struck me.
That she might be the thief.
She doesn't look like a thief.
Whatever she has done
who knows under what".
"circumstances she
must have done it.
Whoever commits a
crime should be punished.
And this will be
decided by the police only.
Who are we to decide what
is good and what is bad?
Our duty is only to stop a person"
..from going on the wrong path.
Maria, you don't understand.
Th is that spark that will
create an explosion one day.
And in that
explosion she will burn..
..our house and it's happiness.
No, brother, don't say such a thing.
Why shouldn't I? She
is a thief, a scoundrel.
There is no place
for her in this house.
Brother.
Fine, I am a thief and there is no
place for me in this house.
I am that spark that can
cause an entire explosion.
But don't worry, brother,
nothing will happen to the..
"house that has given me shelter.
I will go away from here.
- Wait.
You can't go from here,
the police are coming.
Police?
Yes, I have sent Simon
to inform the police.
You did a good thing.
Whatever a person does
he has to pay for it.
Even I did wrong.
But once upon a time"
..even I was a good and decent girl.
Even I had a house,
parents, a life of happiness.
Then all of a sudden he
came in my life like a storm.
And he trapped me in his golden net.
Then I left my household
and I came into his world.
I did everything
for his love, even..
"the things I shouldn't have.
To the limit that I started
to rob and cheat. All for him.
And that man?
What's the use of
saying anything now?
If I ever meet him,
I'll break his neck.
On which lucky person are you
going to do this favor, Maria?
With your permission, my
neck is at your service.
If you do so, I'll get an
entry straight to heaven.
Why are all of you'll so quiet?
Did you called me over, Carlo?
All the villages and
district are in your favor.
Maria?
Come and have lunch?
Wait let me change first.
After falling for you all my
life I'll cry on my destiny.
Why, is it okay?
Maria, why are you so quiet?
What did you say? I didn't hear you?
I was saying that if I go
what is going to happen of you.
If such a thing happens,
then what will you do?
There is no shortage of water,
I'll go there and jump inside.
Tell me beforehand,
I'll properly find you.
You also, Maria, here, have food.
Simon, you did not get water?
I forgot, I'll get it right away.
What is this shamelessness?
Am I a cattle that
you put a rope around..
me and pulled me?
What do you want?
So, you don't know what I want?
- No.
Whenever say yes.
- Oh yes!
And when they say no then it
means yes. - Anything more?
She says tail.
I like you a lot.
- So soon? - Yes, only a..
"first sight was required.
Do you only keep following
girls or do you also do some work?
Nothing, right now. But
lam searching for a job.
But you used to sell fishes.
- Yes, but it was not profitable.
So I am thinking of
casting fishes instead.
What do you say?
Will it be profitable?
Yes, it would be profitable.
- Certainly, right?
Then inform Simon he
is in need of keys.
Should I inform Simon?
"I have already given my heart."
"Forget it. Forget it.
Avoid your romantic poetry."
"Forget it. Avoid
your romantic poetry."
"I lost my heart at first sight."
"I am floored by your graces."
"Now it's hard to find interest
in something else besides you."
"Forget it. Forget it.
Avoid your romantic poetry."
"Go wash your face and
don't try to entrap me."
"lam not going to
be conned by you."
"This is an old trick.
This is an old trick."
"I have already given my heart."
"You have stolen my
heart and now you deny it."
"People who die on
you will really die."
"Stop throwing
tantrums on my heart."
"Forget it. Forget it.
Avoid your romantic poetry."
"You find Romeo at every step.
You find Romeo at every step."
"How can you believe them?"
"Everyone give the
same excuse of love."
"l have already"
"I have already given my heart."
"Everyone give the
same excuse of love."
What‘ s the matter?
What are they asking?
- He is asking for gold.
And he is asking for his share.
- Ok, tell them they'll get it.
Tell them that if they
don't trust me then.
They can find
another man for this job.
They are saying that
they do trust you.
And they want to only work with you.
But they also say that you
do nothing but sit idle.
lam not sitting idle.
But I am doing some work.
lam thinking of a
new trick tell them.
And I'll let them know
when I feel the time is right.
Go, now you too get lost.
- Sir, give me 5 rupees.
My family is starving.
- I said I don't have. Now get lost.
Go take it from there.
Uncle, this sudden change in whethe
r can cause problems.
Yes, brother lots of problems.
We won't be able
to get into the sea.
And here on the shore the Material.
And I have not saved a penny.
Now God only knows how
I'll survive these days.
Don't worry, uncle.
Everything will be fine.
Antonio! Paul!
Where had you gone, Maria?
- I was lost.
The same thing happened
that you told. I was lost.
Don't joke Maria.
Who told you? - My friend.
- Ask the one who told you.
But I don't have any
work for a man like you.
What do you mean?
- You sometime buy fishes.
You sometime ask for labor charges.
I want an honest man at work.
- What are you saying?
Am I not honest?
"With your full strength.
With your feet on the ground."
"Take the risk on your life."
"With your full strength.
With your feet on the ground."
"With a lot of hope
and faith in her eyes."
"The fisher women is
waiting for you in pleasure."
"With a lot of hope
and faith in her eyes."
"With innocence of a
child and love of a mother."
"Row with you full endurance,
fishermen."
"And let not the water creep in."
"With your full strength.
With your feet on the ground."
"Take the risk on your life."
"With your full strength.
With your feet on the ground."
"Take the risk on your life."
"For generations the
storm has been overhead."
"Storm has been overhead."
"Waves and clouds have
been like our companions."
"Clouds have been
like our companions."
"For generations the
storm has been overhead."
"Waves and clouds have
been like our companions."
"To carry on is the
motto of our life."
"Don't worry about
the summer and winter."
"We shall carry on the work
irrespective of the seasons."
"With your full strength.
With your feet on the ground."
"Take the risk on your life."
"With your full strength.
With your feet on the ground."
"Take the risk on your life."
"Who knows when there
is a whirlpool or rain?"
"When there is a rain?"
"Who knows when there
is a whirlpool or rain?"
"When there is a rain?"
"Think about today's victory
and forget about yesterday."
"Tell your arms always
to be enthusiastic
"With your full strength.
With your feet on the ground."
"Take the risk on your life."
"With your full strength.
With your feet on the ground."
"Take the risk on your life."
We have never got so much wealth.
Wealth is so nice.
Siamon brother prices very high.
God has heard our pleading.
Now this season
will pass peacefully.
A fortunate man receives wealth.
Yes, indeed a fortunate man.
- Then will I get the job? - Yes.
Hey Maria! You seem to be happy.
Have you guys caught something?
Brother, don't ask anything.
The fishing net was too heavy.
Even applying the strength to
the fullest, couldn't pull the net.
Simon, George, Charlie
everyone were there.
But none could succeed. So I
thought I would help them out.
And as soon as I touched
the net, it was pulled out.
Brother, the net was full of fishes.
And the fishes were shining,
as they were to be of silver.
Now we are rich. Let the
rainy season begin today.
We have no fear.
- Maria, thank God.
Besides God there is one
person to be thanked. - Who?
Come in Tony.
- Tony? Who is Tony?
Hi! I am Tony Fernandez. May
God grant you a peaceful life!
From today onwards he too
will be working with us.
We had to plead to
Simon to give him the job.
Very well, Maria. Tell him
to have his meals with us.
Tell Lisa to cook for him.
- Food is ready.
Come on, brother.
- Come on, Maria. - Come on, Tony.
Tony, come here.
Haven't I given you the job?
Now you don't come
in that girl's route.
You and that girl have different
routes. - And what about you?
My route is same as hers.
- But be careful.
There might be thorns on the way.
You don't worry about the thorns.
I'll take care of them.
Tony, your talks are comical. To w
hich village, you belong?
Baghdev, it's just
behind the mountains.
We used to do farming there.
But we lost everything.
And then when I was mature enough,
I migrated to Mumbai city.
There is everything in
Mumbai city. But not what is here.
And that is peace.
- Tony! It might be alive?
- Tony, I.. I..
Great! You got a chance
to entertain everyone.
But you had left this place,
then why did you return?
You want to understand
this matter. Understood.
You are here to find peace of mind.
"Maria!
- Maria! - Maria! - Maria!"
"Laugh, sing and enjoy yourselves."
"Word is water"..
"Ma" Ma.. Maria! Ma..
Ma.. Maria! Ma.. Ma.. Maria!"
"Maria!
- Maria! - Maria! - Maria!"
"Far away a star is indicating.
Far away a star is indicating
"That the one who has lost
everything is the winner at last."
"There is storm in my heart.
And I feel like dying."
"I don't know what
kind of wish is this?"
"Laugh, sing and enjoy yourselves."
"Say whatever in your
heart to your beloved..
..as the night is romantic.
- What kind of crave is this?"
"Ma" Ma.. Maria! Ma..
Ma.. Maria! Ma.. Ma.. Maria!"
"Maria!
- Maria! - Maria! - Maria!"
"Your city is too far
and the road is lonely."
"My companion, don't ever ditch me."
"There is storm in my heart.
And I feel like dying."
"I don't know what
kind of wish is this?"
"Laugh, sing and enjoy yourselves."
"Say whatever in your
heart to your beloved..
..as the night is romantic.
- What kind of crave is this?"
"Ma" Ma.. Maria! Ma..
Ma.. Maria! Ma.. Ma.. Maria!"
"I have broken all the
relationships and come to your home."
"Just tell my beloved to accept me."
Listen there is a dark shadow
that is going to over cast you.
And you'll be able to see nothing.
What kind of shadow?
Say something more.
That shadow will have spots on it.
Spots of someone's blood on it.
Hey! What will you get by shooting"
"someone who is already dead?
Aim there and you
might get some prize?
Hold it here. Now aim.
And focus with ..
"this pointer. Shoot!
1 ,2. You shoot very well.
- Oh! You were shooting, Maria?
Aim, aim, you should
join the Police with us.
We need good shooters like you.
- I too think the same.
You seem to be very learned.
If I am not wrong then we
are meeting for the first time?
Yes, unfortunately never got a ch
ance too meet.. - He is..
our inspector Mr..
And he is.. - Constable. -
And brother-in-law also. Come on.
Will you have cigarette?
- No. - He is Tony.
He works with us and
he is from Mumbai.
Yes, ask.
- No, need not bother right now.
Any ways I'll find that girl.
- Which girl?
The one who ran away
with all the gold?
Yes, the same girl. But now we ha
ve come to know about Whaa.
Who is Whaa? - Whaa is the
one who helped the girl.
To steal those gold.
- Jerk! - Come on, Tony.
Let's go for a ride.
- Yes.
Stay away from Tony.
- Why? -
What do you mean?.
It's easy to recognize a snake.
But it's difficult to
understand Tony. - What do you mean?
How well do you know Tony?
- I know him very well.
You remember once I told you that"
..a cheater spoiled my life?
Tony is that cheater, Maria.
Tony is that man?
- Yes, Maria.
Maria! Where had you been? ..
- Simon! Hello, Simon.
What's wrong with you Maria?
- Why? Nothing.
One never knows whether you
are awake or you are sleeping?
Should I ask you something, Simon?
- Yes, Maria.
Have you ever loved someone?
You don't love someone,
Maria. But you fall in love.
How? - All I know is
that love is such a fire.
That you can't light
nor can you extinguish.
And the same fire is
burning in my heart.
And you have lighted it.
- What are you saying, Simon?
This can't be possible. This
can't be possible. - Maria!
Who is it?! You.
- You got scared? ..
- I knew you would come.
Oh yes!
- Just like the impatient"
waves rush towards the shore.
Just as a moth is
attracted to the light.
The same way you'll come to me.
I am not here to given
my life like a moth.
I am here to ask you to leave.
As one dirty fish
spoils the whole pond.
Till yesterday I was like
an angel of mercy to you.
And today I have
become a dirty fish?
ls this what you have come to say?
- Yes. - Lies.
You are here because you love me.
And you can't be far
from me for a long time.
This all is false.
- You are cheating yourself, Maria.
I don't know how to cheat like you.
- Oh! Understood.
Maria, good or bad at
last we all are humans.
The one who is good
today can be bad tomorrow.
And the one who is bad
today can be good tomorrow.
And Maria I may be good or bad.
But whatever I am. I am
yours and you are mine.
You know to con very well.
- Maria!
And you know too entrap people also.
But I am not going to be conned.
You can't deny that
you too love me. Maria!
People get hurt in love.
- But that's the fun, Maria.
What a romantic night i is Mari .
And you'll come to me tonight.
No I won't. - Yes, you will,
Maria. - No, I won't. I won't.
You will come I know. - I won't. -
Your intelligence will stop you.
But your emotions will bring you
here. You'll come to this door.
And then the moonlight
will play with your tresses.
And the wind will kiss your cheeks.
And you'll be lost in my thoughts.
Then with a soft voice
you'll call out Tony.
No, I won't come.
- I know you'll come.
"Where will you find such a
beautiful night and moonlight?"
"Come, listen to the
tale of my heart."
"Where will you find such a
beautiful night and moonlight?"
"Come, listen to the
tale of my heart."
"On these bark of trees"
on these bark of trees."
"Are resting the moon light.
Are resting the moon light."
"And they are lost
in your thoughts."
"And after some time
they'll go away, disappointed."
"And this romantic night
won't come back again."
"This atmosphere is going to
last for only few moments."
"Come, listen to the
tale of my heart."
"Even the waves" even the
waves are singing a love song."
moist winds have fire in it."
"You also get burnt
in this fire of love."
"And change the tune of your life."
"You'll have to hear
to my hearts language."
"Come, listen to the
tale of my heart."
"These passing winds.. these
passing winds are very exciting."
"Let's share a story
in this moon light."
"If they go away
after calling you then..
"This romantic
atmosphere won't ever return."
"If they go away
after calling you then..
"This romantic
atmosphere won't ever return."
"Come to me as still we are young."
"Come, listen to the
tale of my heart."
"Where will you find such a
beautiful night and moonlight?"
"Come, listen to the tale of my hea
rt. Tale. Tale. Tale."
Did something fall in your eyes?
- Yes, maybe.
Tony, I love you. And you can't ..
"hate the person you love.
You'll call me and I won't
come. Can this be possible?
Maria!
- What's the matter? - Nothing.
Something fell in her eyes.
I am just removing it.
Ok, remove, remove. Remove it, sir.
Sir, how are you?
What about your Whaa?
Sir. - Sir. - Sir. - Sir.
- Sir. - Sir. - Sir. - Sir.
What were you saying, sir? - I
was asking, sir, what about Whaa?
Sir, if I find that girl then
I'll automatically find the boy.
I'll automatically find the Whaa.
So sir, are you running after
that guy? - Sir, what to run?
lam planning to trap
him by staying calm.
Sir, you are remark less.
- Listen!
I have asked for the
photo of some jerks from..
"Head quarters. Once
if I get those photos.
Then I'll see how far that
pair can run away from my claws?
Sir, they can escape
from the claws of others.
But how can they
escape the claws of John.
Fernando.
Sir.
- Sir..
Sir, do you know them?
- No, sir.
These Arabs are pestering
me in Hindi and English.
May God's peace be upon you!
May God's peace be upon you too!
Let them ask what they want to.
They are asking
what about your plan?
How long do we have to stay here?
Until when are we going
to waste our time here?
Tell them that all the
arrangements are done.
Now we will take the
gold via the open sea.
They are asking, from
where will the boat come?
Tell them that they are donkeys.
You are donkeys!
Tell them in Arabic.
Let it be or else they
will get unnecessarily angry.
Tony's arrangements never
fail and Maria is also stuck.
I have thought of a
plan that there will..
not be any quarrels for Tasneem"
Nor there will be
the fear of the police.
We did not understand.
Make them understand.
Arab sir, the matter is
that you will come with us.
You did not understand.
I will have to make
you understand in Arabic.
Maria! Where are you going, Maria?
- Nowhere.
Are you going to meet Tony?
How many times have I
made you understand"
..that don't play with fire
or else you will get burnt.
There's real
enjoyment in getting burnt.
Maria! Whichever flower
he saw and liked, he..
..broke it, smelt it and
crushed it under his feet.
Just look at me, that scoundrel"
"used me and ditched me.
You are saying this because
you have been ditched in love.
He does not love you. He loves me.
He has told me himself.
It is very easy to
show love for someone.
But is difficult to fulfil it.
He does not love anyone.
He just loves money.
And for money he will
sell his self esteem"
"and he will sell you too.
No, you will not do this!
You will not ditch me!
- Hello!
Tony! Tony! Do you love me?
Yes. You will not ditch me. ls it?
No. - You will not crush me
under your feet. Will you?
Maria, do you love me?
- Yes.
No. If you do love me then ..
..why do you doubt me?
No, no, Tony I have no
doubts on you. I love you.
I love you more than myself.
I can do anything for you.
Anything? Yes, Tony.
Look what I have got for you.
All these are for me!
- Yes.
How gorgeous is this necklace!
Tony, you are very nice.
You quickly change your clothes.
Till then I will tell you a story.
There was once a boy and a girl.
It was just recently
that they got married.
Both were poor.
But both were willing to
give their lives for each other.
She was proud of her
long and beautiful tresses.
If the world wanted"
The boy had a gold watch,
who was also very proud of it.
But, because it did not have a st
rap he could not wear it.
And the poor fellow did not
have money to buy the strap.
Christmas was just
round the corner"
"and the girl wanted to buy
a gold strap for her husband.
Even after saving
each and every penny..
"she could not
collect that much money.
The girl was worried.
She was mad in love..
"and the girl went and
cut her hair and sold it.
And she bought a gold
strap for her husband.
Then what happened?
It was the night of Christmas.
The husband came home and saw his"
..wife and was astonished.
And asked what
happened to your tresses?
The wife smiled and said look, I
have got a good strap for you.
Now you can wear your watch.
But, what happened to your tresses?
I sold it.
- Why?
Because I wanted to
buy a strap for you.
The boy's face frowned and said"
..what will I do with this
strap. I also had to buy..
..a gift for you. I
sold my watch and"
"bought you a silver comb.
How much they loved
each other, isn't it?
How I wish I could have
done something for you!
Maria! - Tony! Tony, no power in th
is world can separate us.
Yes, it will happen.
And this is the power.
Look at it carefully.
This is the thing, which you
love above all in this world.
How lovely is the shine that
you cannot keep your eyes off it.
You cannot see anything before this.
This is your life
and your self-esteem.
You have ditched
me because of this"
"and who knows how
many girl's like..
"Maria you have spoilt.
Why are you talking so negatively?
You want to take revenge from me.
Whatever you
wanted I could not give.
That is why, what I like you
want to steal away from me.
This is all false.
Don't fall for his words.
Come, Tony. - Maria I
want to save you from Tony.
You have done a favour on me by..
"saving my life and
giving me shelter in your house.
That is why I want
to repay your favour.
If you want to repay her favour,
don't waste our time.
Go, run away. Come, Maria.
Maria! Oh! It's you!
Where did you go Lisa?
Just for a walk.
- Where is Maria?
She must be sleeping upstairs.
- False.
I have been wamng here since
evening. Maria is not at home.
Why are you quiet? Tell me, Lisa.
What is the matter? Where is Maria?
Simon, you love Maria, isn't it?
Lisa, you do not
understand how much I love her.
Then why are you standing over here?
Maria is treading a wrong path.
Go stop her and
make her understand"
..that Tony is not worth her love.
Tony! Maria loves Tony!
Yes Simon, she has
forgotten herself"
..her family
members and even Carlho.
I tried very hard to
make her understand"
..but she did not listen to me.
Where has she gone?
Both have gone for a dance.
Simon, Tony is the same
person who spoilt my life.
Lisa, what if Carlho listens to it.
Carlho! Carlho! Carlho!
- Maria! Maria!
"Be very careful
when you love someone."
"Look, the times are bad."
"Don't be deceived
by the innocent face."
"Look, the times are bad."
"Be very careful
when you love someone."
"Look, the times are bad."
"Don't be deceived. Don't be
deceived. Don't be deceived."
"No, no, no, no."
"Tread very carefully you lovers"
..when you are passing
through the lane of love."
"There are robbers and
looters moving around in disguise."
"Don't be deceived.
Don't be deceived."
"Look, the times are bad."
"Be very careful
when you love someone."
"Look, the times are bad."
"Don't be deceived. Don't be
deceived. Don't be deceived."
"No, no, no, no."
"In this world, a market place."
"It is the thirst of
the body not the soul."
"In this garden of beauty,
there are many colours of lust."
"Don't be deceived. Don't be
deceived. Don't be deceived."
"Look, the times are bad."
"Be very careful
when you love someone."
"Look, the times are bad."
"Don't be deceived. Don't be
deceived. Don't be deceived."
"No, no, no, no."
"Love is like a glass bangle.
Just a jerk and its shattered."
"In this world of
conditions and loyalty."
"Don't be deceived. Don't be
deceived. Don't be deceived."
"Look, the times are bad."
"Be very careful
when you love someone."
"Don't be deceived. Don't be
deceived. Don't be deceived."
"No, no, no, no."
"Don't be deceived. Don't be
deceived. Don't be deceived."
"No, no, no, no."
Beware! If you try to meet Maria.
"I think of you so much like the
broken strings of the violin."
"My body is wrapped with the
flames of the fire of love."
"The smoke from the
fire sways in my heart."
"Just listen to the
call of my heart."
"Where will be this
night and the moonlight?"
"Just listen to the
call of my heart."
"Where have the star studded
night and the moments of love gone."
"The waves sing the
lost moments of love."
"All the gardens of
hope have been deserted."
"Where should I search for you?
I do not know where you are."
"I do not know where are you lost.
Only the next world knows."
We will come here by the shore"
"and we will reach
straight to the border.
Tell them to wait for
me in the boat here.
That is why I have come
here to take you with me.
No, Tony how can this happen?
If you love me, anything can happen.
You will come. I have
made all the arrangements.
Tonight you will come to
the beach near the rocks.
I will wait for you.
And across the border there will
be a motorboat waiting for us.
How can I leave, brother?
Do you love your brother or me?
I love you Tony, but I am
the light of his vision.
If I go away then his
world will be shattered.
And anyhow you
will have to one day"
..leave this home and
settle down somewhere else.
Come, Mama!
'He does not love anyone.
He just loves wealth.'
'And he can sell himself and
his self esteem for wealth.'
'And you too.'
'Do you remember, I had told you".
..that a scoundrel
had spoilt my life?‘
'He crushed me under his feet.'
'Yes. Yes. I do remember
- He is that scoundrel, Maria!'
'Tony!
— Yes. Tony!-
'His shadow has stains.
Blood stains!'
'Blood!'
Maria! Come, Maria.
But, how can I come?
I am weak and alone.
And a woman.
Do you remember that you said"
..that you can do everything for me?
Yes, I do remember.
Then why this doubt. Have
trust in me and come along.
If you deceive me. If
you do not support me then?
How can I dispel your doubts?
Maria, how do I make you
believe that I love you?
I promise that I
will never deceive you.
Do you promise?
- Yes.
Oh God! I vow that the way in..
"which I am accepting her
as mine in front of you.
The same way I will
accept her in front..
..of the world and be
her partner for life.
Till death do us apart.
- Till death do us apart.
Amen.
- Amen.
Let's go.
Tony! Tony!
Sit down, Maria!
Maria, come back!
- Tony, stop firing!
Move away, Maria. Go back.
I will not go.
- I am telling you do step forward.
I will come and surely come.
I will shoot you, Maria.
You cannot shoot me, Tony. My
love is rooted in your soul.
You love me and care for me.
And you don't kill
them whom you care for.
Stop talking and go back, Maria.
If you take a step
forward I will shoot you.
You cannot shoot me.
You love me, Tony.
You will feel restless without me.
You cannot live after killing me.
If you can live then shoot me.
Maria, what do you want?
Throw your gun away and face
the punishment for your crime.
You want me to spend my youth,
crying in the jail?
And finally die like a dog.
Before that I will kill all of them.
Tony! Tony! I will
not let this happen.
I love you. I will not
allow you to get ruined.
Are you telling me, Maria? I have"
..spoilt Lisa's life.
I deceived you.
And above all I
left you for wealth"
..alone in the middle of the sea.
Maria, I am so bad that you too can
not save me. I am very bad.
Tony, do you
remember you said that"
"whatever is bad today,
will be good tomorrow.
But Maria, on whose
hope and by whose support.
He is the only one to give support.
Have faith in God and with His
support these sad days will end.
Take this. My prayers and the
idol of divinity are with you.
You were searching
for the serenity"
..of the heart and
peace of mind in the..
"pieces of gold and silver.
If they are there, they are in
the shadow of the idol of divinity.
Go, Tony. You have blessed me with"
"happiness by
accepting the path of truth.
I will be waiting for
you here until you return.
'Don't listen to
anyone who speaks evil.'
'Don't act evil if
anyone does evil.'
'Stop the person
treading the wrong path.'
'Forgive the person
who makes a mistake.'