Near the city.
This magnificent house
is in Mufassil.
Choudhari house.
In which stays a happy family.
This is their story.
What is his name?
Son, this time you have
made a tricky move.
Ok, now take care of your knight.
Then you'll know.
Oh no no!
Not the pawn, not the pawn
Just move this horse to the front.
Section 29..
.if clause 2. Just let me check.
So why you said while
going to court..
..that after coming back | will
take you to Kalyani's home.
Yes,
yes definetly | will take you..
When did | said no?
Just bring that book,
let me have a glance at it.
Meanwhile you get ready.
I will not take time for me..
..I will change in a snap
of your fingers.
Women take time to get ready.
But before | get ready..
.finish your Hindu
succession act.
65,66..
..67 68 69 70.
7, 72..
73,74..
75..
-Enough, now | can not do his.
What can't you do?
You can do it.
Kamal, what was the count? -75
times. -That's it? -How many more?
You don't understand..
..in a day, at least 200 counts..
..of skipping should be done
by you. -200 times? -Yes.
If it's your rule..
.then | will die.
-No nothing will happen..
..just excess fat of the
body will be lost.
Come on start it again.
Come on, come on, come on.
Kamal my son you start counting..
..this way you will learn
counting well.
| know counting uncle.
Son you will learn better.
Ok start counting.
Jayashree,
| am going to Kalyani's home.
Please take me along
Manjali sister..
.| will get rid of this problem.
No,no!
Then brother-in-law
will order me..
..to start skipping with you.
Oh!! You are still standing like
that didn't you start..
..Come on, come on ,come on.
Sister-in-law you start too..
It is good for you too.
| am going for the feast
brother-in-law.
But don't be greedy to eat a lot.
Even if | over-eat
whats the matter..
.there is a doctor in the house.
No no no no no.
Overeating is very dangerous.
Look.
Ok Kamal have your food and sleep.
I might come late.
Ok son? -OK aunty.
See..
..dual show of younger
sister-in-law & brother-in-law started.
So, even | should start now.
Ok, Kamal start counting.
76 77
Oh oh.. you have messed up after
reaching the third section.
You are making such an outcry..
..give me freedom from
this third section.
It is just a small error
in counting..
Just count the fractions
properly..
..just stamp your
feet like a bomb.
But | am tired.
Just forget this tune this tune
is becoming a trouble for me.
Trouble?
Have you gone mad?
This entire world is a tune.
A rhythm, a tune..
..and nothing else.
Problem comes when
there is no tune..
..and you are running away from
this tune? -Come on. Start now.
No no. Now | can not do it..
..| have to change various
different attires because of you.
What will family members say?
That this new daughter-in-law
wears weird clothes..
..and dances all day.
And nothing more.
When you say family members..
..you mean brothers and
sisters-in-law right?
They were impressed after watching
your dance at conference..
..and that's why they brought
you home as daughter-in-law.
Why would they think something
else? -Come on, start.
The conference is on the day
after tomorrow. Come on.
Ready? -1, 2..
| won't speak to you Krishna.
You hold my hand walking
on the street.
| won't speak to you Krishna.
Go away, | won't speak..
..I won't speak to you Krishna.
Radha you're the soulmate
of Krishna.
| swear by the flute | have..
..oh my upset beloved Radha.
Radha is upset and Krishna
is wooing her.
| swear by the flute | have..
But Radha doesn't agree.
Go away, go!
| won't speak to you Krishna.
You hold my hand walking
on the street.
| won't speak to you Krishna.
Go away, | won't speak..
..I won't speak to you Krishna.
When the bangles clink together.
The drape rustles in the wind.
The joyful beating of the drum.
| won't speak to you Krishna.
You hold my hand walking
on the street.
Go away, | won't speak..
..I won't speak to you Krishna.
Very good, very good,very good..
..| bet this time you will get
an award in conference.
Sister save me..
..he will kill me by making
me dance like this.
| was under the impression
that only..
..females can make males dance..
..so why is it opposite
in your case?
No sister-in-law no..
Till now Ganga has never
flown backwords..
..and will never flow.
Actually its her only who makes
me dance day and night..
..but the irony is that no
one can see my dance.
Its your good luck
brother-in-law..
.that no one can
see you dancing..
..otherwise the the god who does
Taandav The lord Shiva..
..would have been forced
to become your student.
Ok Manju now | am going.
And you.
| guess some screws..
..are loose. -Whos?
You are joking again.
-Come on, start come on.
Again?
Oh ho Hindu succession ad
is still not finished.
If you do not wish to go there
why did you promise me?..
..and ordered me to get ready.
We must go there..
But, the thing is that..
..without drafting this new
petition | will not be at ease.
Ok Listen..
..I was telling Madhav
the same thing..
.that Mr. Z is the most devilish
and wierd person.
Just to trouble Mr. X..
..this guy have raised objection
for no reason.
But this objection..
..understand that.
Madhav.
-What does the common sense says..
Please pass the Tobacco. -OK..
..What would you have done
if you were in his place?
I would never have filed
the complaint.
Get up lets go.
Where?
Oh my luck.
You are my moon..
..take only very little
is remaining..
..drink fast fast.
Very good.
Satya..
Sire! -How much milk did
you gave to Amar?
Come here!
| have given him 3 litres.
1 told you to give
him a bit more..
..just now he have recovered
from the illness.
Daughter Champa you also please
keep a watch everywhere.
What can | do madam?
Thakur sir eats opium..
Beware Champa..
..it's me who looks at this
family as big as Ravan's.
Ram ram ram.
Sir, you say whetever that
comes to your mind..
..my family..
..| can't praise them enough..
..and you defame it.
Champa. -Daughter take him..
..take him to his mom.
Go.
Today you have to decide
about this thing.
About which thing? -Just send
me today to my parents home..
..today! -l just heard that you
are going for the feast..
..now you are eager to go
to your parents place..
What's the matter?
Doesn't brother-in-law want to
take you to feast? -Don't know.
Grant me permission from
elder brother..
..I will go to my parents
place today itself.
And Kamal?
His parents have left
him with you..
..will he stay without you here?
If he can't stay then send him
to his mother at Benaras.
1 don't have a child..
.| will leave peacefully.
-Sister? -Send me to my parents place.
Now what happened to you?
I know the reason for
her being upset.
Sometimes she developes hobby
for getting upset.
Manjali sister develops a hobby
to get upset and to you.
I my life is in danger..
..my back is broken dancing.
Sister? -Yes..
..you also want to go to
your parents home? -Yes.
Please get me brother's
permission.
Why? -Have you fought with
me doctor brother-in-law?
|1 don't get time to fight only..
..I get lifeless doing
just skipping.
No no sister..l will definetly go
to my parents place. -l will go.
| said first.
-No no sister | am the youngest.
You must listen to youngest one.
Oh god..all of you want to
go to your parents home..
..so with whom should | live here?
Thet Engieneer brother-in-law
first was staying..
..in Banaras with his
daughter-in-law and now.
We don't know all those things..
..you just give permission.
So you will go for sure?
Yes.
What about you the youngest one?
Me..
..even | will go.
After going there..
..will watch movies comfortably.
And what about you Jayashree?
| Said.
OK..
..when you all have
decided alredy..
.1 will ask them..
..maybe they must be upstairs.
You all came?
Good.
| have convinced them with
a great difficulty..
..now you all can go to your
respective parents home.
But..
..but if | stop dancing..
..won't | get problems of cramps?
You granted us the orders..
..but have you ever thought..
..that without seeing
elder brother..
..what if my Raju falls
sick by getting upset.
They said yes..
..and you agreed tell me..
..to whom Kamal will go and sleep?
She will rule the house..
..after sending all of us
to our parents house.
What will you do if we
decide not to go?
Why don't you answer?
I know..I know everything..
..without my brother-in-laws..
..you all can't stay
even for 1 day.
You just say big things.
Even if you search the entire
world with a lamp in your hand..
..you will never find guys
like my brother-in-laws.
This the only bad thing you
have in you sister..
..that you notice good behaviour
of them only..
..and we are like no one to you.
Oh silly..
..what do | have apart from you..
..you all make this small
world of mine.
You all are my home's
Lakshmi..Lakshmi.
Madhav.
Yes coming.
Coming..coming.
Madhav. -Oh coming.
Madhav.
Oh Madhav.
-l guess everyone is calling you.
Everyone calls..
..but there is only one Madhav.
Just check why are
they calling you.
| know why are they calling me..
..its morning and everyone wants
tea. -Elder Malkin is making tea.
Calling me.
Hey listen..
..bring Raju here..
..if he has finished his milk.
-To play for?
Madhav -Madhav Madhav Madhav
Madhav is dead.
Oh Madhav..Coming doctor.
Take it upstairs.
Carefull. -Oh this is a clock.
No its not a clock.
Its a weighing maching.
Ok Ok so it's a weighing maching..
..so i'll take to store house..
..where we will weigh rice,
wheat and everything.
Idiot
This is used to weigh people.
Oh..
People are weighed?
This is a very different time.
Even people are weighed.
Doctor sir?
-Why people are weighed?
This is matter of health..
..human's body who should
get how much calories..
..who should get how
much proteins..
..but you will not understand
anything. -Go call.
Ok calling.
Suresh.
What brother?
Come on come come on..fast..come
upstairs..come upstairs.
Whats the matter?
-As of now there no matter..
..but how long does it take?
Go upstairs in front of doctor
sir's room and see it.
In front of my room?
-Yes..och my god.
No no there is nothing
to be afraid of.
You will be weighed. -Go upstairs.
Elder sir, Dinesh sir is calling
Raju. -Go go do not disturb us..
..while playing.
All problems come at
this time only.
What is it's name?
- am taking him. -But why?
Why should | not take him?
-You are also called..
..weighing will be done.
-Weighing? Who's? How?
Oh at least listen.
See
Munni..80 pounds.
80 pounds.
Kamal 105 pounds.
Correct.
105. -105
Madhav
Good you brought Raju..
..make him stand on the machine.
You all please wait for a while..
..let me finish with the kids..
..then it will be your turn.
Raju is 182 pounds younger uncle.
Including me.
Madhav. -1 will cut your throat..
..joking at the time of work.
-Get down.
Give him to me..
..and you get out from here.
Ok son..
..come on stand up.
Write -28 pounds
Raju 28 pounds.
28 pouds?
Weight is very less
compared to age.
Jayashree.
See with your own eyes..
..only 28 pounds.
I have told you many
times that Raju..
..must get 10 X 50 means
50 ounce of milk.
If Raju drings milk
4 times a day..
..so everytime he should get
bit more than 12 ounces.
See | am very poor in keeping
the accounts..
..I did not inderstand anything.
You make sister understand.
“Understood..| understood everything.
Raju will get more milk.
-Ok? He will get it.
Its your turn now..what?
-Let it be.
His childish behaviour will never
change. -Childish behaviour?
Without knowing how much everyone
weighs individually..
..food value means how
many individually..
..calories. So now we also
have to eat as per..
The ounce?
Absolutely
Come on..do it fast..l have to
weigh everyone..getting late.
Listen first check weigh
of elder sister..Hey
How can younger ones
can be first..
..in the presence of elder people?
Oh correct correct..come on elder
sister-in-law. -You come.
What are you saying
brother-in-law..
..with my weight machine
will break down.
Let it break down sister..
..vitamine..calories..
..you will not understand
all these things come on.
Come on sister-in-law, come on.
-Leave me. -Come on.
Come sister-in-law come.
Just stand up.
Jayesh..
..Whats the matter?
-Where are you running?..
..weighing is not yet done.
-Let it be..they came.
Oh this a difficult problem..
..without checking your weight
how can be it found out that..
..how many grans of sugar how
many grans of protein.
Elder brother you only tell me..
..without knowing all these things
how can health be fine?
Right right. Whats the name.
-OK So elder brother..
..you only stand on the machine.
Me?
Yes yes.
OK.
Did you weigh Raju?
How much should | praise
about his memory?
If he gets good meals..
..s0 understand that.
Why Ramesh is not called?
All day he is busy in work..
..its necessory to check his
weight also. -Madhav. Madhav.
Go and call second number sir.
No no | will no call
second number sir..
..if 1 go to call him he will
start making law on me only.
1 will not.
-Don't irritate go and call him.
Ok. -Remove your shoes.
OK
Suresh write..
..256 pounds.
Brother what problem is this?..
..reduce this belly of yours.
This is a Banaras Belly.
I know you will not reduse it..
..even this work | have to do.
The proble is that in your house..
..no one gets balanced diet.
Its not only our house only
even in our country..
..anywhere no one gets
balanced diet.
Suresh.
-You do all day this sa re ga ma..
1234,
Why don't you write a
nice song on health?
Both husband-wife combinely sing..
..and I'll make everyone do the
exercise. -Ok thats good.
Doctor sir.
Second sir cannot come..
..he is fighting with
his opposition.
What kind of fighting?
Tricks of the law.
Doctor sir..
..meanwhile check my weight..
..my health is not
well now a days.
Even my.
Health is not fine?
Yes yes.
Come on.
Weight? Yes.
Oh my god.
What have you done? -Nothing.
How many rotis you eat? -Only 25.
257 -Yes 5 20.
Maharaj from tomorrow
give him half food..
.maximum to maximum..
..13 roties he should get.
-And Madhav..
..from tomorrow you have to
exercise along with the kids.
And. -Maharaj where are you going?
Someone called me..
..have to go and pick
up the rice pot.
Oh no no no. No one called you.
As you have come till here so..
..why don't you check
your weight aleo.
Don't go now.
Don't be afraid.
123 123 456 78
Health is first..
..smallest is the thing..
..front back up down..
..left right all together..
123 123 456 78..
..health is first smallest
is the thing..
..front back up down..
..left right all together..
123 123 456 78..
..health is first smallest
is the thing..
..front back up down..
..left right all together..
..123 123 456 78..
..human outlook is
a machine only..
..with grat difficulty
we have received it..
..you keep all its part clean..
..do exercise and remenber this..
..remember well being well body..
..remeber..
-1 1121 ..
.1112345678..
..123 123 456 78..
..health is first smallest
is the thing..
..front back up down..
..left right all together..
..123 123 456 78..
..health is first smallest
is the thing..
..front back up down..
..left right all together..
.12345678..
..who eats one tomato
every morning..
..doctor never comes
to his house..
..who eats one tomato
every morning..
..doctor never comes
to his house..
.. half a litre milk
in the morning..
in the evening..
.. half a litre milk
in the morning..
in the evening..
..doing bit of exercise daily
makes you strong..
..remember..
2111210,
.1112345678..
..123 123 456 78..
..health is first smallest
is the thing..
..front back up down..
..left right all together..
..123 123 456 78..
..health is first smallest
is the thing..
..front back up down..
..left right all together..
.12345678..
What happened? -He fainted.
Faint? Yes why?
You only ordered yested..
..that he should get half
stomachfull of food..
..while having dinner poor guy..
..cried so much..
..that even rock would
have melted..
..but | did not shake..
..kept him starving.
Oh | see.
Maharaj
-No need to reduce his food..
..let him eat how much he
used to eat earlier ok.
Maharaj
My eating started.
Salute me and say thank you.
Salute.
Thank you.
-Mention not mention not.
Called me for tea..
..so feeling relaxed.
So daughter-in-law,
exercise is a very good thing..
..Dinesh want to keep everyone's
health fine..
..Oh whats the name?..
..where is the younger
daughter-in-law?
She is making a pan for you.
Must be coming. -Ok ok.
One more cup of tea sister-in-law.
-Ramesh
Are you going to have tea only?..
..don't you want to
have breakfast?
Elder daughter-in-law
give give him sweets.
Let it be sister-in-law | have
to have lunch and go to court.
Sister-in-law Sister-in-law..
..give me tea fast Sister-in-law.
-Why suresh..
..why are you in such a hurry?
-You don't have to go to th court.
Come on have breakfast.
No elder brother | have
to start practise.
Hurry up sister-in-law.
What happened?
Starring at the plate..
..don't you want to eat?
-1 am thinking.
There are less calories,vitamins
in kachori and samosa.
Yes right?
-Why not indeed it is less..
..why all of you give
all these things..
..to him.
Elder daughter-in-law give
him some sweets..
..rather give him 2 boiled eggs..
Yes yes who knows when he will
get time from the clinic.
Eat till your stomach is full.
Yes. Patients don't even
peep into the clinic..
..and no one calls for visit also.
-And wanted to run a clinic.
Whats her name?
Noble profession..
..service of people.
Yes yes
Sister..
..ask that thing also
to elder brother.
What the matter?..
..now only ask second
daughter-in-law.
Say it.
-You feel shy in speaking also.
Thing is that..
..she wants to put
janawa on Kamal.
Find a holy day in this month..
..and Kamal's yagyawar ceremony
should be done.
This is a very good idea.
As he is 12 years old..
..and year 13 is running thats
why | am thinkinh that..
.that. What is there to
think sister-in-law?..
..if your wish and brother's
approval is there..
..then this should be done
as soon as possible.
But brother Ganesh and
sister-in-law are not here.
Letter should be sent to
them right now only.
Whats its name?
You only write.
-But, it's a quastion of a job..
..what if leave is not approved?
If leave is not given
then should..
..resign from the job and come.
No no..Why to resign
over this matter?
Salary is Rs.1100 every month.
He is district engieneer of Kashi.
-Who ever he is.
If required then will come
here and open a firm.
Suresh write a letter to Kashi.
Will write for sure but
on one condition..
..there should be a grand
party on this occasion..
..special feast should be there..
..big and famous artists
should be called..
..hows the idea elder brother?
-Yes yes. Definitely definitely.
On this event of happyness
celebration should be done.
Whats its name?
And jewellery?
Jewellery? Yes.
Fingering, button etc. For Kamal.
Sister its difficult
to deal with you.
Kamal will get the jewellery
what about us?
We will just be engaged
in work nothing else.
No no no. You also get them tell
me second daughter-in-law?
Whats its name?
Necklace,
bangles what you want let me know.
Just now we will check the catalog
and choose the designs.
OK -And sister one nice
necklace for you also.
What will | wear in
such an old age?
You select for yourself.
Come on Jayashree we will see the
catalog for ourself. -Come on.
What catalog sister? -Of jewellery
Just come with me.
-Elder brother work.
Just listen.
Don't ferget Kamal's mother..
..select jewellery for her also.
Yes. OK
Seen their madness?
So whats the problem?
This their age to eat and to wear.
Whats its name?
If Raju have finished his
milk then send him..
..one chess game should be played.
-Take.
Raju.
Raju. Maghav.
What a voice younger
madam has got..
..when she sings it feels like..
..that someone is putting drop
of elixir into the ears.
Oh don't praise so much..
..what kind of throat is this..
..this throat can only be used
to eat and not to sing.
Maharaj what expertise do
you have abou the throat?
What?
1 don't have knowledge of sound?..
..how many throats are there
on anyone's shoulder..
..tell me such a person who will
fight his head with my voice.
Have you ever heard name
of ustad Kila khan?
Who is he Maharaj?
Have you heard the name or not?
Just answer in yes or no.
Fateh khan is his student.
And pandit Dutkarnath is..
His teacher-brother.
And | am.
So it's you.
Why you disturb me in between?
| have spent 10 years
at his home..
..and you say that | can
not identify throat?
How can you have expertise
of voice Maharaj?
Can not be there?
He gave me a job only after..
..hearing my voice.
On one dark moon day..
..| was sitting near
the river bed..
..I sang a few lines..
.listening to which Panditji
fell on my feet.
And started saying..
..would you work at our place?
That's it.
-Because of his insistence..
.| said yes to them.
So you must have got a
cook’s job over there.
Yes yes.
That too of a special cook.
They said..
..feed us the same thing which..
..made your sound like this.
Thats it.
Then what..
..started feeding them
both the time..
..omlet made out of Cuckoo's eggs.
And then what a great improvement
in voice..
..what a improvement in voice..
..what to say? -Thats it.
Could not sleep entire night..
..was restless was restless..
-Why?
Ants used to surrount the throat..
..because his voice
became so sweet..
..that entire night he used
to remove the ants..
..stuck to his throat.
So why do you cook..
..instead of singing?
Its the case of luck.
Will tell you some other time.
No no Maharaj. Tell now only.
That pundit Duthkarnath
begged in front of me..
..saying that if you sing then
1 will be out of job.
Oh so thats why you quit singing?
Oh no. Why would | quit
singing on this thing?
| said if you are getting out of
job then what should | do?..
..Why should | quit singing..
..| started singing..
..Maal kans khamal tanana.
Hey friend.
In this house no one
has talent to..
..recognizes knowledge of music.
Yes Madhav.
-Room is locked from many days..
..get it cleaned properly.
Elder madam you don't worry..
.. will make this room
spick and span.
You don't now..
..that | have not fergotten
Ganesh sir.
If Ganesh sir finds bit of..
..dirt or problem also
in his room..
..then he will break my head.
OK
Why are you standing idle?
March
Come on
Come on move your hands and feet
fast and clean the room.
Shamu..yes brother.
Go to the attached room..
..remove all the cobwebs and make
windows clean and shining.
Where is Bhiku? Bhiku.
-See You just clean out this bed..
..and clean the cupboard also.
Have you brought the duster?
-Here it is. Good job..
..dity person..
..brought the dirty duster..
..hey only dirt will spread
with dirty duster..
..go get the other duster
from elder madam.
Bringing it right now. -Kamala
You get some water and just wash..
..the room OK.
Good job.
Brother Madhav.
Brother Madhav her health
is very bad..
..if you want I'll do
her part of work.
See. You dead person..
..why are you so concerned
about her?..
..you look after your work.
Come on. Clean the fan.
What does brother Madhav
have to loose?..
..he don't have to do any work..
..just gave an order
and then thats it.
You started cribbing again.
Go get the water.
What she thinks of herself?
Ok Madhav brother..
..is Ganesh is a big sir?
Exactly.
He is engieneer..
..do you know the meaning
of engineer?
Yes -Person who rides engine
is an engineer.
Donkey. You are a donkey.
-Oh idiot engineer is a person..
..who doesn't work himself..
..and gets the work
done by others.
Like..like..like you.
Oh Champa
She is very smart.
-She is very smart.
Why are you smiling?
Clean the fan.
I am checking on Bhiku and
will be right back.
Champa come on.
Wash the floor fast.
Please hold the ladder..
..otherwise | will fall down.
If you are so scared
then you should..
..have brought someone else.
| am so tired today.
Let me eat a pan.
Whay are you starring?
| don't stare..
.. look at you.
What?
You.
Idiot!
What if someone comes?
Do your work.
I m doing it..
..but if four comes it will become
one. -Whats going on?
Get down, I'll beat you up.
He does not work.
Doing it or not? -Please save me.
-You are coming down or not?
Please save me from this devil.
-No -You are coming down or not?
Leave your hand. -First become
more that the Maharaj.
See he brok the fan.
You arrogant person.
Who are planning to beat?
Ok Manju please tell me
which ma was that?
Whos mother?
Yersterday | was making
a tune in that..
Was it first ma or the second ma?
As per my knowledge it was..
..a step mother.
-Oh ho again jokes.
Should not joke with the work.
Come on sit. Start your practise.
No no.
| cannot sing in the morning.
Oh ho what are you doing?
-Leave me. What if some one see?
What if some one see also?
-They will say..
..that younger sir was holding
younger daughter-in-law’s..
..have and teasing her.
This world will not fall in the
ocean of confusion. -Come on.
Should | do any work or not?
Work? Is this not work?
You are again joking with art.
We are artist..
..worshiping art is
our ultimate work.
Come on.
Come on come on come on.
Your love has..
..made me crazy..
..your love has..
..believe it or not
| am your admirer..
..had made me crazy..
..came in my dream and expressed
it many a times..
..came in the dreams..
..came in my dream and expressed
it many a times..
..became a begger during the day..
..and queen of the night..
..believe it or not
| am your admirer..
..your love has..
..made me crazy..
..people who can see
are watching..
..people who can understand
are aware..
May my youth burn in this lamp..
..my youth..
..believe it or not
| am your admirer..
..your love has..
..made me crazy..
..my and yours love is old..
..mine and yours..
..every moment has its own story..
..believe it or not
| am your admirer..
..your love has..
..made me crazy..
..believe it or not 1 am..
..your admirer..
..made me crazy..
It will be a great fun. -Ganesh
uncle and aunty are coming.
Yes. See. They will bring
many things for us.
Gauri. Going for the second time.
-Call him. Lets make him fool.
Maharaj. Maharaj.
Just listen to his english..
-Will be a great fun. -Maharaj
Can you talk in english? -Why not?
Whos english you want to ask?
Go get some milk.
That is very easy.
Go milk the give come.
| know everything Kamal sir,
| know everything..
.-1 have a bad luck thats
why doing a cook's job.
OK Maharaj,
from where you learned english?
Thats a long story will tell
you sometime later.
Cannot create a lie thats why.
-What?
Who have the guts to
tell me that I lie.
You know that a consert was there
at english sir's home.
10 years was working there.
If | don't know english
then who know?
You don't know english.
-Don't know? No
Don't know?
Ask whaterver you want.
1 will answer fast.
OK say my head is spinning.
Spinning.
My head is eating circle.
Is it correct? -Yes very correct.
It will be.
Quite quite.
You would have messed it up
now where are you going?
Stand in the line. -Get away.
-Always behaving like kids.
Its not childish behaviour..
.children's father will
do what children do..
..and same children's mother
will do. -Stand up quitely.
Kids are you ready?..
--1 2.0
Guptaji came. Lets go.
Oh they have arrived.
Sister they all have arrived.
Come on. Lets go
What Kamal?
Ok Now lets go.
Sister-in-law
-You came brother-in-law.
Why you are so late? -My throat is
paining due to al the shouting.
So what was the need to shout?
Oh see. -After 1 year home
coming ceremony is done.
Why are you shouting? -Ganesh.
You came?
Long live. Long live.
Be married always.
Anjali.
You came?
Oh Badho you are looking very
happy. -Whats the matter?
You came from Banaras must have
brought sweets from there..
..will get to eat them.
-Will get. Will get.
Come on.
Unload the luggage from the car.
Ganesh -You came?
Brother.
Any problems during the journey?
Why not problems?
Suffered a lot. -What problem?
Eating and drinking.
Brother-in-law kachories
are ready..
..if they turn cold then don't
blame me. -Lets go fast.
You have food and drink,
meanwhile ..
.| just.
1 will just fix up a case..
..thats what you are
going to say right?
Oh second brother this case only
will take you down one day.
Ok come on. -And that doctor.
Doctor must be coming. You com.
Sorry disturbing you
after many days.
This is a Lucknow's mediocre kada.
Lets See.
-And this is Kashi's ordinary.
And sister this one from Agra..
.this is the best. -OK
Agra's best tobacco will
be best for sister.
Yes yes.
Will be best with the pan.
Sister-in-law.
-l am dying because of hunger.
Getting it brother-in-law.
Bringing it.
Listen.
Food and hunger,
and hunger and food.
Whay are you blaming..
These are the days of youth
this is the age to eat.
Take it. -Go fast.
Invitation sending work is done.
Ramesh personally went to give
invitation to your in laws.
Ramesh's father-in-law also
came from Lucknow..
..Now Whats its name?..
..You think and let your friend..
No need for anything..
..Just show me samosa
and kachori..
..so | can go and
sleep peacefully.
Ganesh brother.
Oh doctor..
..where have you been?
-Today suddenly one patient came..
..but now why you were talking
about sleeping?
This wish of sleeping at odd
time is not a good habbit..
..maybe your blood pressure.
-Beware Dinesh..
..no doctor treats his family
members understood?
Sister-in-law.
Oh sister-in-law.
Unnecessarily you are
getting impatient.
I am blessed that |
got view of you.
Oh
This is snaks of a mountain.
Brother Ganesh..
..first you were talking about
sleeping on odd time..
..and on top of that all this..
..no brother Ganesh your
blood pressure..
..is definitely not normal.
-You keep quit Dinesh..
..this is not your stethoscope..
..that you can pick it up slowly..
..and keep it on patients chest..
Keep this also sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law.
Tomorrow check the weight
of brother..
..Ganesh also brother-in-law. -OK
Weight? Mine?
Oh this means that..
..if it is iNn excess
he will reduce it..
..never this will nover
happen in any case.
Brother Ganesh there is a
yagnya ceremony at home..
..many guest have arrived..
..what if amongst the crowd,work..
..god forbid you fell sick.
If | felt sick then whats
the problem? Nothing..
..You will work..
..and he will work..
..I am here to enjoy..
..| will eat and sleep..
..and sleep and eat.
Yes yes you eat.
Dinesh do not disturb him now.
Come, please come.
You came? What a problem!
Problem? What kind of a problem?
No problem.
You came..
..in this.
What its called.. our good luck.
Ramesh.
Ramesh.coming elder brother.
Your father-in-law came.
You took a long time. -Late?
No not late. Whats its name.
-Long live long live.
Take him. Take him inside
and make him comfortable.
| have decided that
our Lucknow house..
..should be named after you two.
-But any other claimant?
Rightfull person.
-Claimant, rightfull person..
.| will make a will
and give my house..
..to my daughter and
my son-in-law..
..so who can stop me?
Who have the guts to
raise objection?
What kind of lawyer are you?
-Yes? Who gave you the degree?
Who threw the dirty
plate over here?..
..put bleaching powder
on this also..
..put put.
Open it.
How the colour of
water turned red?
Special drink is made
for the guests.
Its not a drink your head..
..this is potassium permangenet.
What you said sir?
All those are english. English.
You will not understand.
-You do your work.
Come in come in. Mr. Kunjbihari.
Did Ganesh came from Kashi or not?
Yesterday only he came. Good good.
There is no other example
of the love..
..that exixts amoung
your brothers.
Eyes are sitisfied
after looking you.
Like Pandavas in the Kaliyug.
Oh you also. Talk anything..
..Come on come on.
Oh yes..
..I have seen a big stage out..
..have you called any drama
party from the city?
No. Our younger brother Suresh.
Yes yes.
Just its his some friends only.
So its a young guys program?
Oh yes. Whats its name.Correct.
Come on come on.
Friends.
You will be happy to hear this..
..that to welcome you..
..arrangement is made
for a grand party..
..in this party world
famous sarod player..
.. Khan sir Ali Akbar khan..
..Swar samrat Mr. Pankaj Malik..
..person who can make elixir
drom from sitar's tune..
..Khan sir Wilayat Khan..
..sweeter that honey singer..
Sir Hemant Kumar..
..Master of tune sir.
Sachindev Burman..
..all of them we could not invite
even after wishing so.
Listen. Listen. Listen. Listen.
You don't need to be upset..
.. am going to present in
front of you the one..
..after seeing her you
will be delighted.
Whats that person's name?
-No need to tell name..
..you will identify him
in first glance only..
..he will present his life
experience in front of you..
..he is todays famous artist..
..is he on time?
Where is he?
Here here.
Hey you cheater.
Kishore Kumar!
In the well..
..after taking bath with
cold water my throat..
.. is a bit sore..
..in the well..
..jump and die..
..but my friend don't
get married..
..jump in well and die..
..but friend do not get married..
..don't do. Don't do..
..don't do..
..jump in well and die..
..but friend do not get married..
| saw a girl from Delhi...
..looking at her my heart
started fluttering..
..a cold sign came
through my mouth..
..a fire raged inside me..
..| asked her name and family..
..1 asked her address..
..with all me heart's desires..
..I reached at her bunglow..
..as | reached | did a salute..
..and told my heart's story..
..innocent dady said..
.ok ok ..
..yes yes your thoughts are nice..
..1 know that..
..I will inform your dad
by writting a letter..
..you have nice thought..
..you want tea or cold drink?..
..or should | make
scrambled eggs?..
..you want tea or cold drink?..
..or should | make scrambled
eggs or feed you eggs?..
..when that girl smiled and said..
..that my heart is wounded..
..| became very happy..
..as unhappy gods were convinced..
..kartar you should win always..
..you should win always..
Oh my god..
..meanwhile his brother came..
..said..
..sell this moong and
masoor pulse..
..and get lost. Get lost..
..get lost from here,
you son of devil..
..his brother was
very good boxer..
..his brother was very
good boxer...
..he took attacking position..
..I just ran from there..
..on the way my heart said..
..what what?..
..in the well..
..jump and die..
..but my friend don't
get married..
..jump in the well and die..
..but my friend don't
get married..
..| was a dairyman
reached honolulu..
.there he is called Mr. And
here Bhola singh bholu..
..git pit git pit dinner lunch..
..claim that you should
get it fast..
..reached in a new world..
..where everyone is brother
and sister..
..ball dance samba samba..
..guitar bonga tongs..
..was she a girl or was
she a lightning..
..her name was miss pole..
..something happened
something failed..
..oh my god..
..thet nite was scary and dark..
..and dogw were barking..
..| was awake on my bed..
..and slept in the morning..
..did not see front and back..
..never thought about tomorrow..
..got married..
..got married to miss pole..
..then every nite..
..then every nite shut up..
You shut up then every
morning..get out get out get out..
..get out get out go go go..
..you you me me yes no no..
.then at one nite..
.-1 ran for my life..
..on the way hear said..
..what what?..
..in the well..
..jump and die..
..but friend don't get married..
..jump in the well and die..
..but my friend don't
get married..
..whereever | went
| was stumbling..
..no one knows the
pain of others..
..ram merged all 5 ghosts..
One day | didn't see her....
..look at my condition..
..friend don't get married..
..jump in the well and die..
..but my friend..
..don't do don't do..
..don't do..
..jump in the well and die..
..but my friend don't
you get married..
-no no ..
Madhav take these bulbs..
..and give it to the person
standing near the gate.
Now? Yes yes make it fast.
Madhav where have you bee?
Take this thali.
Put paan, clove, cardamom in it..
..give it to the bearded
person out.
| have to give these
bulbs at the gate.
Oh do that later. This is urgent.
Take this. Go fast.
Madhav go to the kitchen
and bring some sweets..
..kids are eating,
just bring it fast.
| have to get Paan, cardamom
for younger sir's friends.
You can do that later go first
get the sweets. Fast.
Madhav Madhav..
.listen just go upstairs
and get the perfume.
And what about all this?
This you keep on doing
you just go upstairs.
Elder daughter-in-law,
second and youngest..
..whoever is ther just
get the perfume.
If perfume is not available then
middle sir's father-in-law..
..will be upset and leave..
..Have to arrange for the
perfume anyhow go fast.
1 am all alone where
to see and what..
..to do | don't understand
anything.
Raju. -Give the Raju to me.
What is this?
Guest have not eaten and you
are secretly for urself.
Keep quit Doctor sir keep quit.
Whay should | keep quit?
Do | fear you? -Don't make noise..
..whatever you want to see
just peep from the window.
From the window?
Yes yes you brought it Maharaj..
..These are so nicely fried
that what to say..
..Just bring some more.
-Now what others will eat?
What you said? -l asked what
you would you like to eat?..
Kachori or cutles?
Bring little of whatever is there.
Whatever you have kept
in front of me..
..will get stuck in my teeth only.
-Oh my god.
Thats why you were not
to be seen anywhere.
Secretly you are eating
all these things right?
I am just testing..
..thet what is going
to the guests.
This is testing?
Your blood pressure is
definitely wrong..
..I will check just now.
-Kill the blood pressure..
..sit come. You also eat.
No | am checking blood pressure.
Take.
-You check the blood pressure.
Oh Madhav
The lights have gone off.
Shut up. How much work should
| alone do? -Go make it fast.
Oh going
| mean to say..
..issue a factorial mortgage..
..the property which
is kept closed..
..legally on that property.
Second sir food is served..
..send guests upstairs fast..
..OK lets go. -l am making you
understand the mortgage laws..
..understand will understand
later we are getting late..
..will they go to their
home or not?
There are 3 cars at home.
They will be dropped..
..sit sit you also
sit for a while.
Younger sir younger sir quit.
-What quit?..
..food is served send them
upstairs to have food..
It will take some more
time you go. -What go?
Its midnite when will
these people eat?
Its just 11 o'clock..
..music concert actually starts
after the midnite only..
..and what to be afraid of?..
..there are 3 cars at home.
Will drop everyone by car..
..go go you do your work.
Lord Krishna..
Take again trouble..
..See you are sitting here
and playing chess..
..and there guest are getting
angry because of hunger.
So go and throw some
water on that.
Its very late already..
..come on get up. Stop the play..
..are the guests going to eat
and goto their home or not?
We will send them in the car.
Everyone is saying same thing.
Will send in the car..
..why should | be bothered?
OK
Oh ho its 11 O'clock..
..Lect go now. -..Where to go?
Have not had food yet.
Thats what | am saying thats
its 11 O'clock and nowone..
..is talking about the dinner..
..If we leave now only
it will be better..
..maybe we can find some
restaurant open..
..or after this that too will be
closed. -You are really leaving.
Then what should | do?
-This is a strange joke..
..we are just sitting here..
..and no one is asking
us about the dinner.
Why are you getting angry?
Just have a sit.
This is a metter of
getting angry..
..we are guests. Guests..
..understood?
And host is nowhere to be seen.
Just sit for 10 more minutes..
..if no one comes then we
will also leave with you.
Elder madam younger madam..
..come fast come fast come fast.
What happened?
You are shouting like that there
are thiefs in the home.
If thieves come then I'll
hide under any bed..
..and would not breath also..
..this is bigger problem than
that come on come on.
But what happened?
What happened?
all guests are angry and want..
..to leave without having dinner.
-And where are the othere sirs?
Sir? -Elder sir is playing chess..
..second sir is teaching
father-in-law the law..
..and younger sir is..
..ducting medicine all
over the house..
..and engineer sir is
nowhere to be found.
Heard sister? -Come with me.
Where? Where else?..
..now we only go and ask
the males to eat..
..whaterver work males do they
always mess it up come on.
Saw Maharaj?..
..did you understand abything?
-Yes..
..from now onwards
daughter-in-laws..
..will start going to court..
..and all the sirs.
Sir.
You are right.
You must have..
Sister-in-law
What happened?..
..not a single cup of
tea since morning.
Why are you throwing tantrums?..
..whats its name?..
..yesterday nite till 2 O'clock..
..they were busy in work..
..so thats why must have got up
late in the morning today.
Late? Whay is that?..
..we were also working hard.
-Sure..
..you worked a lot..
..giving big big orders
with your friends..
..that is also a big work.
Oh to my father-in-law
means you father..
..teaching mortgage law
means..yes yes..
..the most important work
yesterday was that only.
Ganesh listen..
..what sister-in-law is blaming..
..that we have not done
any work only..
..get this get that
go here go there..
..go up go down pick
this keep that..
..we were drained by the work..
..and you say that we did nothing.
If we did not work then..
..who did everything?..
..how many people came for
the feast last nite?..
..how many dishes were made?
but did anyone fell itt?..
..I myself went to kitchen and..
..disinfested even the water
for washing utensils..
..thats why not only
no one fell ill..
..but also no one complained
about the indigestion.
That is correct today we came
at breakfast table on time..
..not even a single minute late..
..this is called unity
of 5 brothers.
What have you done?..
.lif | eat so much then
I cannot have my lunch.
No no can definitely have lunch..
..stale puri and juice
of gulab jamun..
..is a first class combination..
..sister-in-law if lawyer
brother is not eating..
..then give it to me.
-Brother Ganesh.
You keep quit doctor.
-Whay should | keep quit?..
..You must take 1 dose of mcself.
Yes.what? -Mcself? -Means
dysentry? Yes dysentry. -l refuse..
.-1 totally refuse.
Sister-in-law.
Listen..
..when | went to kitchen today..
.. saw loads of curd..
..| was saying that
today make rayata..
..and dahi wada..
..they are tasty and good
for digestion as well..
..but tell the cook
to make them fast..
..lawyer brother have
to go to the court.
Let it be brother-in-law..
.. guess no one ever
went to the court.
OK listen when there is
a function at home..
..then 1 day's leave
can be taken..
..but no he wants only court..
..no contact with other world.
Why you interfear in thing that
you are not aware of?..
..whover can do whatever
work he is doing..
..thats why such a big family's
unlimited expenses are met..
..otherwise 10 male servants..
-10 female servants 3 cars..
..baggi have you ever thought
about the expenses?..
..you can give..
..example of our family.
| second you. -Yes.
One for all..
..and all for one.
Brother-in-law please
talk in hindi..
.50 even | can understand.
Ganesh was saying..
..we all brother live
for each other..
..have anyone seen love..
..among brothers like this?
Never..
..now a days in vevery home there
is fight and partition..
..everyone is talking
about the pertition..
..and we 5 brothers..
..through the sea of
fight and hatread..
..navigating our boat beautifully.
Said a thing of a 1 lack..
..| will said responsibility
of running the hoem..
..is on us only.
Yes yes | know..
..proof of this thing was
received yesterday only..
..if we were not there then more
that half of guests would..
..have returbed without
eating only.
Feeding and making dring
work is of you females..
..why should we males interfere?..
..our work is to gather the food..
..do we say anything
to you for that?
So what you want?..
..we females also start
wearing coat..
..pant and start going to court?
Oh you keep quit middle
daughter-in-law.
But sister-in-law you will look
good on coat and pants.
Let it be till looking only..
..brain is.
Why are you all troubling
middle daighter-in-law?
Middle sister-in-law is
not less that anyone.
Oh its 8 O'clock.
Brother | am going.
OK OK.
Where is my pen?
My dear lawyer sir please open
your eyes and check..
..sir do you know its 9 O'clock.
Oh its 9 O'clock.
Did driver took out car from the
garrage or | need to do that?
Car is ready since a long time
waiting for the sir..
..you get upset unnecessorily.
What will you understand pain
travelling so long everyday..
..its me only who
is understanding.
So ask elder brother and..
..buy a house near the court only.
Yes.
If we start hearing to females..
..then will have to live
this ancestral house..
..leave the brothers..
..I should make a new house
near the court..
..and Ganesh should
make one at Kashi..
..we would have done this if
we were wife's servants.
Maharaj please go out.
Then who will bring down
such a big pot?
1 will do it. You please go.
Thats fine.
Champa you also go.
Whats the matter?
-Will tell you now.
Chhoti please close the door..
..Jayashree you close that door.
You have trouble me.
Whats the matter?
Have to do a very important
meeting. -Meeting? Yes yes.
Whan? Here right now.
Come here. Come near fast.
Whats the matter Maharaj?
You say something, why are you
sitting here? -1 got an off..
..got an off? -Give me the bidi..
..I cannot recognize the
breed of this home..
..second madam came in kitchen
and said go out..
..and closed the door immediately.
And also sent Champa out.
Sent out Champa also?
Who does this poor guy have..
..You idiot. Why are you afraid?..
..Madam after closing the door..
..must be eating stale puri
and mango chutney.
Stale puri and mango chutney?
Yes.
Madam from big home..
..she doesn't like Halwa pulaw..
..give them stale puri..
..and mango chutney.
Will eat till they are satisfied.
Will keep on eating only.
What all of you are
planning to do?
You get scared of everything
sister.
She is saying right..
..everytime all brothers
unite and bully us..
..they should be taught a lesson.
But.
They should made understood that..
..this love between the brothers..
..exists because..
..we all daughter-in-laws are
good. And we also have a unity.
But how can | do all this?
We all combinely correct it..
..you don't worry about it sister.
Worry can be caused by
this younger one..
..day nite either cham chama cham
or ha ha he he hoo hoo..
..don't know when and
what she can do?
If | am smiling then what
should | do? -2-4 days..
..maximum 1 week stay serious..
..if you smile like this in front
of youbger brother-in-law..
..then will pack you
in a trunk and..
..will sent it to your parents
home. -Sister..
..Malti you also act smart.
Don't worry form my side..
..1 used to do dramas in school..
..1 act first class..
..yes but beaware of
this Jayashree.
Beware Jayashree..
..if you roam like a young girl
in front of brother-in-law..
.then | will.. -OK no never..
.. am from Banaras..
..now one can read my mind..
..you all keep faith in me.
But what is the need
to do all this?..
..1 don't like this.
Maharaj
Where you went leaving
the kitchen?..
..are you not going to
take the pot down?
Don't know what will happen?
Do not have fear sister..
..have a glass of tea..
..put 4 paans in your mouth..
..eat Agra's kada zarda..
..and sit comfortably.
Whay Maharaj?
What are you looking at?
Mango chutney.
What? -Madhav said.
Why?
-Haven't he reduced his afeem?..
..Go take the pot down smartly.
OK listen..
..I am sending elder sister's
kids to sleep in your room..
..and she has closed the door..
..now you go and send Kamal
out of your room..
..then it will be interesting..
Listen. Are you sleeping?
Trying now.
Should | massage your feet?
Why suddnely today you
are showing the love?
No..
-Last nite there was lot of work..
..thought maybe you are tired. -No
Nothing like that. But if you
want to massage my feet..
..then you can do that.
-But apply some pressure.
Oh Kamal..
..whay are you here?
Where to sleep?
Go and sleep in middle
sister's room.
Arun and Usha are..
..sleeping there..
..they said go and sleep
in elder sister's room..
..but her door is closed.
Oh OK OK..
..go and sleep next to munna..
..go.
Please listen to me.
Oh you trouble me a lot..
..if you want to sleep
then sleep..
..no need to nitify me about this.
I am not giving notice middle
daughter-in-law..
..has given the notice..
..since a long time Kamal
is sleeping with them..
..and today there is no
place for him there.
Why there is no place?
How would | know that?..
.. have heard that..
..today we are sleeping with
elder sister's kids.
Kids must have trouble the Kamal.
But this is not right..
..we always stay out..
..and leave Kamal with..
..second daughter-in-law
and elder madam..
..if they only become
irresponsible then.
See you started snoring..
.. am a mother how can | sleep?..
..Left our son here
for his study..
..and now he is habitual
to sleep near her..
..how can he now in this room?..
..OK ferget about the second one..
..even elder madam cannot
think or what?..
..Kamal can sleep near her only..
..but no..
..they closed their
door first only..
..what kind of person are you?
sleep after 2 minutes..
.first please listen to me.
I am listening you tell.
What should | say my head?..
..if you keep your right intact..
.then its fine..
..oh god what my kid faced today..
..even my enemy should
not see such a day..
..tonite my kid is sleeping
without the pillow..
..useless.
You engineer brothers wife..
..is always in the air only..
..thats good then..
.lier at heart..
..When last nite elder
sister's kids..
..came to sleep in our room..
..she was..
..and became angry..
..started shouting..
..stated saying whatever
came in her mouth.
.Really.
Was saying..
..You cannot see our son Kamal..
..sister also feel
jelous with him.
Champa
Leave Raju here.
1 did not say even a single word..
..but he was getting more angry..
..hung up the phone with a thud..
..essence of all the things was..
..that now they will not allow
Kamal to stay with us..
..abd devide the property.
What you said..
..partition?..
..partition cannot be
done so easily..
..hindu joint family..
..means joint family..
..while doing the partition
biggest..
..baristers also get confused..
..this is the matter of rights
means Successor..
..which part? -..mitakshari..
..and if devetter is there..
.then thats it there
is no other way out.
My client Mr. X..
..got into this partitioning
matter and lost..
..now he can see stars in the day.
You started showing stars
in the day to me also..
..are you going to court or
giving me lecture on law?
Yes yes.| am getting late.
So sister How was it?
Very bad..
..I was shouting for 1 hour..
..and in return he started
teaching me law..
..whats you news?
My news?..
..even | fell on my face..
..| was continously speaking..
..and he slept like Kumbkaran
and started snoring..
Now what?
Enough.
There is only one way.
What?
If elder sister helps us.
Elder sister cannot do anything.
We should at least try
|1 got a new idea.
Maharaj where are you going?
She came now she will
ask me to go out..
..so | am first only. Go go.
Sister whats this?..
..day nite you keep on
doing something..
..or other in the kitchen..
.- am asking in Kamal’'s yagna
we got new jewellery..
..but you did not get anything
is this good thing?
Now why | need new jewellery?
Even if you don't need..
..but we need them Today at
nite you must demand for..
..new jewellery from
elder brother.
No no | cannot do all this.
-Will happen. Definitely happen..
..as soon as brother
comes in the room..
..you change your side thats it.
| am telling you don't bother me..
..now in this old age. -What old
age are you talking about sister?
Just put on a bit of make-up
and that enough..
..we will groom you perfectly.
1 will die in water.
Then we will drag
you out of water.
| am saying this will
not be good..
111 will go to
my parents home.
We will also come with you..
..but only after demanding
for jewellery.
Have you brought the lipstick?
Yes yes sister, | have brought it.
OK. -What are you making?
Can't you see sister?
Come on make it fast.
Perfect. Perfect.
Come on sister.
Now go and sleep on your bed.
How can | sleep they
have not yet come?
If one day you sleep before them
then will you be sinned?
Go praise a lot..
..then only say do you remember
what you have to say?
| am fergetting everything..
..I cannot rememer all these
things. -1 knew you will ferget..
..thats why | have
written it down..
..see this just look at this
even if you ferget..
..understood..
..Come on go.
Come on and elder brother.
-Madhav bring tobacco upstairs..
.-Madhav look at. Whats its name..
.| think I left my
room open only..
..just lock it.
Where are the kids?
All the kabab's are dried today.
Oh elder daighter-in-law you
so early are you fine?
Where am | counted?..
..what me and what my health..
..why are you worring?
Whats its name.If health
not proper..
..then won't there be worry?..
..doctor is at home only.
I am far more lower than
servents that..
..no one cares about me.
What are you saying..
..you are this home's..
..you are everythig
of this house..
..just look at me..
..let me see what has happened?..
..see if you don't tell me then
how will | come to knw?..
.. am begging you..
..Just roll around..
..at least listen to me.
Shouldn't | have liking
for anything?
Why not..
.tell me what is
it that you want?
Just. Whats its name?..
..I will do all the arrangement
in the morning.
Sure? -Yes. Definitely sure..
..tell me till now have | ever..
..lied to you?
For me | mean me..
Yes yes tell me.
.Don't you trust me?
For me one. | mean one..
..means..
..means, means one cycle.
Cycle?
Yes yes the one with
three wheels..
..that cycle..
..for our Raju.
Oh such a small thing?
Whats its name? | will order
it tomorrow morning only.
Sister you are strange ..
..what you had to do,
and what did you do..
..you have spoiled the made game.
All of you have irritated me now.
Even if | die | can't
do this thing.
It's my request to you.
Please don't drag me into
this matter. -No..
..you can't do anything.
Now let me and younger
sister try to do it.
Can you both do it ?
-Of course, | can.
You just give us a chance.
And for your brothers-in-law..
.its not that old
also its new one.
Yes, but the bet is that..
..sister won't be saying anything.
Just sit silent.
1 will take that responsibility..
Maharaj go outside a
meeting is going on.
You'll have a meeting everytime
so when will you be eating.
When food will be cooked.
-Malati just close the door.
See this.
It's 10 o'clock already..
..after all what happened
to this younger sister.
Has she forgotten?
Just be patient.
Black drops of rain
fall steadily.
Many dreams arise.
Many storms arises.
Many dreams arises.
My heart can't stay still
without my beloved.
Black drops of rain
fall steadily.
Come, my love calls you.
Why don't come that's why
my song calls you.
Come my love calls you.
Why don't come that's why
my song calls you.
Old memories comes to my mind..
..nights that | met you.
..nights that my meeting
with you..
..then why have you
made me your's..
Black drops of rain
fall steadily.
Lost dreams arises.
Lost storms arises..
Lost dreams arises..
..many storms arises..
..thunders are not liking
without you..
Black drops of rain
fall steadily.
fall steadily...
..your black curly
hairs like black..
..in this black night,have
taken away my sleep..
..your black curly
hairs like black..
..in this black night,have
taken away my sleep.
1 will love you only.
Will wait for you only.
Without you my dreams
are false one..
Black drops of rain
fall steadily.
You are also not predictable
brother..
.. in this midnight time..
..lights are on..
.. you are shouting open throat.
This sister its a matter of art..
..art for this..
.. you have to do
Yes, If you are getting each thing
freely then who will work..
..rest of the brothers
are there to work..
..and make blood and sweat one..
..you just sit eat,
drink and enjoy..
..give lectures of art..
..if your devotion gets
completes then..
.. then we can go to sleep.
Middle sister..
Middle sister.
Yes what | said is right..
.. for fighting with me..
.. just make your husband
understand search some job..
..and start working..
..useless.
Whats the matter?..
..today middle sisters mood.
Daughter of big house..
..how will not show the mood..
..you have got to see the
opporunity today only..
.. and because of her angry..
.. my life is miserable..
Why? What did he say? -You should
have at least punched him.
Now lets see what happens..
..lets go.
Aree Ramesh..
..now some sort problem has come.
What is it ? Sit brother..
No no | won't sit..
.. the thing is at rajganj
settlement work has started..
..and here..
..Tajigamiya is on leave..
..among us anyone has to go..
..I was thinking | will go..
..but since few days my health..
..feeling to be low.
From few days ?..
..your health ..
..that dinesh what he is doing
can't even medicine ?..
..dinesh O dinesh.
No, not that bad also..
..you are also always
in work burden..
..so was thinking..
..atlast whom to sent.
| feel..
..younger brother whole
day stays at home..
.. if he is sent then how it is.
No, no daughter in law poor thing
he is still a kid now..
..his song practise..
..in that rural village area..
Rural Village ..
.. Why in rural villages areas
humans don't stay ?..
.. He will always remain
a kid only..
.. you are also getting old..
.. you don't need rest..
..Suresh..
..0 suresh..
Listen to me why are
you calling him..
.. these are land and
estate matters..
..what he will understand in this.
But slowly has to
learn everything.
Yes yes you have said right
daughter in law..
..what you say is right..
..send him only.
You called me brother ?
-Yes called..
.. what you all have thought..
..that Dinesh doesn't
give medicine..
..you don't have time to
see land and estates..
..the only bull who.
-What happened ?..
.. what | will understand
about land and estates..
..big brother only.
Yes, Yes whole life big brother
will only do everything..
..his health should
also need rest..
..go,
get ready to go in the morning.
Ok..
..but where? -How will | Know..
..ask big brother.
Thing is like that..
..last few days my health
is little bit low..
..for the middle daughter
in law and Ramesh..
..wants to send you to rajgan;..
..SO you go tomorrow.
-1 will go whats problem in that.
Hahaha
What is the problem in it?..
.tell 1 am jealous of you alot..
..your singing and all..
..I can't see through my eyes..
.. for harrassing you only..
.. | am sending younger brother
in law to that village..
..go go to your room..
..go na she is coming.
You don't like me any more..
.little bit also not.
Yes my honour..
.. whats the new blame
you are blaming on me.
Then what..
..| am seeing clearly..
.. towards my dance and singing..
..you are darn careless..
..not teaching a new one..
..but now | will not leave..
.tomorrow onwards without
fail start teaching me.
Not from tomorrow | have to
go to rajganj for few days.
Rajganj ! ..
.. all of sudden whats
the work at Rajganj.
Regarding this property and land.
Ok can | ask you something..
..sending you to Rajganj plans..
..middle sister and
brother has made..
Might be..
..but how come you came to know.
-Whats the benefit in asking..
.. sitting at home without work..
.. so you have to listen to
elder brothers orders.
Workless..
.. so do | have a hobby of sitting
workless or what?..
.. | got call from Allahabad for..
..the job of proffessor or not..
.. that middle brother & sister
stop me from going.
That time your elder brothers
had some love for you..
..ok for this property work
you will nearly take..
..some 10 to 15 days.
Yes it will take.
So how will | live without you.
So what to do?
Ok, sent me to my parents house.
Ok, can | ask elder sister.
Why. Why to ask elder sister?..
..for each thing elder
sister elder sister.
Listen.
I don't want to listen anything.
-Strange problem..
..thought can sing freely..
..curtain..
.. you that time. -No, No you
don't have to think about me..
..you go where ever you want..
.. what you feel you do that |
will not say to you anything.
Will not say means!
will say and tell thousand times..
.. | will not go there..
.. whoever looks after
lands and property..
..they only will look after..
..it will not possible for
me to do all these things.
Mallu..
..tell driver not to keep
vechile in the garage..
..have to go out again..
..0 Good how come this raju
with you today ! -Why ?..
.. | don't love the child or what.
No, No this is not the reason..
.| said because..
.. this the elder sisters
perfect department..
.. hello.
-Ok come now drink the milk.
Only this much milk.
You only make rules..
..50 ounce 50 only..
..here 5 ounce is also not
possible to go into childs stomach.
Why ? -Why What ?..
..Champa Take raju downstairs.
Come beta.
Your son is not the only at home..
.. many others are there.
This goodness..
Milk is only a staple
food for him.
Shouldn't say..
..but god has also given
more children to sister.
As milk boils before it drinks
it goes to there room..
And the rest remains..
.. in that water added.
What are you saying?..
.. water added in the milk..
..NO no.
Milk is his main food.
This happens in all
the big houses..
..child was crying of hunger..
..do | say to you such
small small things..
.. as such things comes
to mens ears ..
.. then starts interfereing.
So my only son will also
not get full milk also.
So why don't you make other
source for milk.
As you say other source of milk
happens or what? for that.
OK Your share from this ancestoral
property is there..
..earning is there or not..
..ok let it go..
.. what | have do with
these things..
.all are your brothers only..
..what they think right
they will do. -No..
.. first of all child health
responsiblity is on us..
..milk is the main food for him..
.. and in that also water added
and in share only 5 ounce..
.. | can't bear this..
.. | will go just now
and make decision.
What decision you will
make that | know.
What do you mean? -Means what..
..you can only come to your room
and scold your wife only..
.. your mind has become
so hot wait wait..
.. | will breeze you
it will become cold.
Leave it.
-..I don't want to be cool..
.. | will make decisions
of all the things..
.. | don't have fear of anyone.
Sister. -Sister. Your are wearing
shoes in the kitchen.
These are useless things Sister..
..Raju is becomimg so weak
have you seen it..
..he is also not milk properly.
I, in front of me.
You are there in the fornt but..
..back of you water is mixed
in milk have you seen that.
Mixing water.
Yes.
Who said ?
Aah in this big pot if little
water is mixed also..
..so what happened being
a man you just.
Why mens don't have
life in them ?..
.. | say who wants more milk they
can make separate source.
What is the meaning ?
you wait sister..
..as womens you came to fight..
.. then has to say there
is nothing to say..
.. like elder sister god gives me
also five seven childrens ..
..then your child must have
feeded on water only..
..will not its going on ..
.. child was badly dying
1 will not bear this..
.. | say now onwards child
will stay upstairs..
..and milk will be given by his
mother. -Brother in law..
Brother in law.
Elder sister..
..| was just saying..
..raju should get milk properly..
.. this matter you all
should keep attention.
Ahh any intolerance has
not said not all..
..you all looking after
four children firstly..
..after that only you will
look after my raju..
.. so its better to do separate
source for milk..
..or this matter elder sister
has felt bad then..
.. today only send me
to my parents house..
.. how onwards..
..Ahh. -Then why to send
to parents house..
..why this house is not mine ?
you will be at parents house.
Dinesh ..
..whats happening ?..
..Why are you shouting. -Nothing..
You look out your work, go.
Nothing why..
.. his face has turned red..
..feels like he will kill someone
now what happened to you..
..you don't have blood pressure.
No No thats not the reason..
..raju doesnt get proper milk..
..50 he said to sister in law
in future dont feed him milk.
What ? elder sister don't feed
milk to your children..
.. have you said it..
.. | say have you said it.
Yes | have said..
.. milk is the only staple
food for raju..
..and that he gets
regularly less..
.. raju is my son and even | cant
say this much also for him.
1 will Kill I will kill you..
..one day | will kill you dinesh..
..| will scrumble your bones..
..stupid..
..who has feed you and made big..
..havn't elder sister
kept you on..
..lap and gave you food and all.
Yes that time elder sister
didn't have to..
..keep big pot of milk aside for
children. -What you said..
..elder sister keeps your
child hungry or what..
..and gives her children. -Yes,
yes | am saying the right thing..
..at home everyone is excepting..
.. | should send raju’s mother
to her parents house..
..so that expenses should be low.
O god..
.. what you said.
This way no one has said
brother in law..
..these are you husband and
wife assumed things.
| understand everything
| understand..
..you all are doing something
against me..
..but | am also having proper
share in this house. -Share ok..
.. how adays shares are
coming in your mind..
.. just come to the elder brother
let me see your courage..
Girish.
Elder sister today decision
should be made..
..come Girish stop !
Elder brother..
..have you seen dinesh's
childishness..
..whatever has come
in his mouth he..
..has said to elder sister today
today he insulted her.
Elder sisters ? not at all..
..I said only.. Yes.
You were only saying
that elder sister..
..in sake of her childrens milk..
..mixed water in his child milk..
..foolish one for insulting
anything is left.
Ok he said in anger. -O in anger
he says whatever comes..
..in his mouth to elder sister
this is your insult also..
2.
..when he insulted me..
..normal one. -Normal..
..today childs milk..
tomorrow wifes saree..
..then clothes,
jewellery, property..
..have you imagine from where to
where saying can take place.
Aare Aare.
What matter you have taken..
Why are you standing
silent there ?2..
..why are you not saying
something. -Me..
..what should | say now.
You cant say anything now
| will teach a lesson..
..middle brother
o middle brother.
Let it why are you calling him.
You don't understand big brother..
.. today mother like
big sisters insult.
What happened ?..
.. whats the problem what
are you doing here ?..
.till now not gone to rajganj.
-No, | mean.
Means, means what..
..why didn't you go,
just give answer to that.
Just leave him..
..this poor thing was..
..what name is his .
-You wait big brother..
..in your support only
they are all on head..
..middle brother you know today
even he said to elder sister.
Today milk is the only main menu.
-You be silent ..
..you know what this donkey said..
..that | am not anyone
in this house..
..in the ancestral property
I don't have any share..
..his foolishness has some limit.
By blaming one man what the use..
..malati sister when she
talks whom she cares..
..that night also regarding kamal
sleep she made a fight.
If you are the thing..
.. then why are not saying
whole real thing..
..nobody cares about kamal
and for that small child..
..my whole share would had
gone but | have never.
Share.
Heard brother share..
..is anything left to hear..
..his share, his share..
.. his insult,
with him forcefully..
..his right, his right..
What is right ?..
..everyone has equal right.
This suresh..
..was he less selfish..
..yesterday | told him
to go rajgan;..
That | will not go that
messy village..
..whatever happens. -Whatever
happens means ? partition..
..heard brother this share
and partition talks.
Now what is there to
be said and heard..
..now onwards we all will see
the accounts together.
| am saying brother..
..if dinesh has said
about partition..
..give his share and
separate him..
..if he is not ready to
go to rajganj then..
..give his share also and separate
him also. -Separate.
? whats going on..
..why to do. -l saying brother..
..suresh and Dinesh both
should be separated.
This is not aeasy job..
..hindu joint family..
..means joint family..
..in this anyone person
wishes to separate..
..then everyones shares penny
penny account should be taken.
Whats limit is there..
..do | want a partition..
..milk is a staple food for raju
that is also not satisfied.
Will be satisfied..
..separate requirements are
fulfilled then satisfaction..
..and essential things will get..
.but..
..hindu joint family..
.file a case of partition..
..is not a laugh and play..
..and make the papers
will take long time..
..and in the mean time,
some new problem get started..
..for that we should make full
arrangement. -Then its ok..
..if fight has been started
because of milk..
..let each ones kitchen
be separate..
..then there will be no problem.
-Are you all listening ?..
..I am saying listen even now..
..have patience sister..
..after these effort
we have got it.
In this way separation is
becoming seriously..
..this is like playing with fire..
..if really fire spreads then.
-Then we put water and off it..
..you don't worry..
Come, come..
Come na.
But maharaj..
..what is the real problem..
..brothers were having unity..
..living happily.
Madhav use to say five pandavs..
..now this is a kalyug..
..so five pandav formed
kurushetra.
I am thinking maharaj..
.. that engineer sir..
..and his madam had
done some trick.
Stop your stupidity..
..the thing you don't understand..
..don't give opinion about that..
..this is not a simple
or normal thing..
..some reason will be there.
-Then..
..what reason madhu brother
only god knows it..
..from childhood | am here..
..but have not understood
the real thing..
..but | will also be alert now..
..and will find out..
..yes.
Malati..
..today what have you prepared.
What is prepared,
why should | shout that..
..what vegetable we get,
that we will boil and eat it.
O god ?. -Yes..
..why to keep others on that.
g
1 will cut vegetables..
..madam you just grind
masalas na..
..otherwise it will get late.
-What you said ?..
..for you | should grind
the masalas..
..where is madhav..
..madhav..
Champa please grind masala
for middle sister.
She is calling madhav..
..why should | go.
-What is this ?..
..middle sister anytime has
done any problem or what..
..and madhav had grinded
masala so far..
..or do one thing give
some from this one.
Why ? they all are separated..
..now you see your work.
Today how many peoples cooking
will be done here ?2..
.. vegetables you all
are going on cutting.
You stop your nonsense..
..since thirty years | am cutting
vegetables over here..
..and you are teaching
lesson to me now.
? kheer half cent..
..basmati rice two cent
ginger one tola..
..cardamon one tola coriander
two tola. -O wait wait ..
.. you have ordered
for full party.
Party what in this cooking book
its written like that only.
Looking in the book,
you can't cook good food..
..for you,
only two persons food you want na.
Yes then | will listen
in the radio and do.
So till then cooking
food is stopped.
What ever you know to cook,
cook na..
Yes as you say.
Look it ok,
to cut potatoes this way.
This way we cut potatoes..
..you keep it aside, | will cut
cut it. -How will you cut?..
..Have you ever cutted potatoes
if fingers get cutted then.
O mabharaj what are
you doing still?..
..do it fast na..
..ok let it be..
.| will grind it.
You will grind masala! Yes
Why where is madhav gone?..
..madhav madhav.
Cutted your fingers you left
Tanpura, and taken knife..
..left harmonium and took
grinding stone..
..don't know what all
should be seen..
..now go upstairs and
apply iodine fast.
Malati Ramesh brother.
O jayashree..
..don't put salt later.
To make pulav you have
put salt sister.
O making pulav now adays.
If we are eating pulav..
..then whats the reason to poke.
Yes brother in law you are right..
..but the expensive of this pulav.
Don't worry about expenses..
.| will sell my share
of property..
..will go and stay in the big city
and practise over there..
..when the kitchen is
separated everyones..
..then why is this headache
in someones head..
..what food is ready..
..I have go outside fast.
Maharaja has not bought the
grocery what should | cook.
Why? what does madhav do..
..madhav..
..listen you should
also look after..
..if everything is separated.
Why should | go to buy
things at market ?
I didn't mean that..
..Madhav. -Yes.
Why grocery has not come?..
..what you do whole
day do gossips..
.. don't you take salary?
Salary | use to take..
..but thinking this months salary
from whom should | take.
See without money how
will you bargain..
.. have you given money.
Money is not there..
.why..
..okK. -..come with me.
| asked whether the food is ready.
Food. -Yes.
| am alone,
what all | should do?..
..Roti and vegetable
has not yet made..
..only dal is done.
Only dal?..
..today dal is ok..
..give in the vessel..
.. eyes is not seen
becuse of hunger.
O, now just..
..what should | give you..
..over taking kids..
..go don't disturb me.
Ok.
Daddy, we are feeling hungry.
Feeling hungry na..
..only two biscuits remaining
you take this..
..and you take this one..
..eat slowly..
..eat..
..you are kids..
..here this old man is
also dying of hunger..
..since morning what
we have eaten..
..one dried roti..
..with that do health remain fine.
Stomach is not full.
How can it full also..
..madhav..
.0 ..madhav.
Coming sir.
See madhav..
..kids are feeling hungry bring
five rupees jalebi sweets.
Five rupees Jalebi.
What happened in five
rupees jalebi?..
..how many are kids they all
will have and do onething..
..and for me one rupee pakodas..
.thats all.
One rupee pakodas.
Ok then bring of two
ifitis less..
..OK Kids madhav will be
bringing sweets now..
..come.
Madhav brother why you sat here..
..what happened.
Just shut up..
..don't eat my brain,
let me breathe..
..strange problem is there..
..for doctor sir from
market grocery..
..for engineer sir oily pakodas..
..one this,
other that come here, go there..
..this madam, that madam..
.its better that |
stay here only..
..I don't want to die so early.
Is food ready?
No,
its time vegetable has not made.
Why it is not made?..
..everyone has separate things
arranged na then why late.
Kitchen is new thats why |
can't make food on time..
..today go and eat at some hotel.
Eat at hotel.
Heard bharati she is sending
him hungry frome home.
Make two persons food
ready sister..
..help the middle sister.
-Ok,ok leave it..
..in the matter of food,
what joke..
..brother in law, brother in law.
Sister
Brother in law.
Sister. -Can you listen to me.
What happened sister?
| said if you want eat,
then food is ready..
..today eat with me.
Sister why are you coming
in this issue.
Issue what, middle sister..
..think | have given you a treat.
If it is treat then no matter..
..I am ready for the treat.
Treat whose, when where.
Nothing like brother in laws
food was not ready..
..he was going somewhere
so | gave him treat.
Our also food is not
ready sister..
..and because of hunger,
dying quickly make my treat also.
Ok yours also..
Champa go and bring younger
sir and doctor sir..
..today everyones treat is
here kitchens are new..
..daughter in laws are?..
..if not made do breakfast
with me.
Ok | don't have any objection..
..if the matter of food,|
don't have any objection.
Then come.
See..
..how elder sister spoiled
the made game.
Elder sister can't do anything.
Have patience | will make
the spoiled game.
What you will do tell na.
Tell fast someomne will
come otherwise.
Come here..
..today is sunday..
..all are at home..
..on kamals ..?
Childrens played a drama..
..that drama we will again.
By drama what will happen?
What will happen that will be in
fornt of you only. -O God..
..kitchen and vessels
are separate..
..disscussions between you all..
..whispering there
is no difference.
Go, Go you do your work..
..what you have to do with it.
From childhood | have eaten
salt of this house..
..nobody has kept sceret with me..
.. but this confusion,
doesn't understood in my mind..
..no matter | will find out
this secert. -Secert ?..
.. what secert?..
..if we are seperate then also
we can't talk to each other.
You say whatever you
want my rajus toys..
..your anand steals what obident
is it. -What you said ?.
OOHH..
..again it started..
.. | name is madhav madhav..
..not made of mud madhav..
.. | will find out the secert..
..ok
1 will without war..
..five states or what..
..needle point space also will
not be given to the padhavs.
Ok..dhuroyodhan -..o dhuroyodhan..
..tomorrow has not come today..
..this is always problem
of destroying only.
Brother leave the hands.
-Leave the hands.
Pandhav this message.
-Give Pandhav this message.
My moustache can't come down.
O your has fallen down.
These kids are also
doing good acting.
After all whos kids are
they ours are they..
..are we doing less acting.
Ok get up now lets
start our drama..
..ya come on.
One two.
Drama studies are going hell..
..here drama is going on drama..
.thousands of times
said to kamal..
..not to spread on other kids..
..go to his room and do the
studies everytime all the kids..
Sit along among others
and do there studies..
..why you are make issue of it.
Its mine kid for his wellbeing
1 will do anything..
..what you have to do with it.
-Why today kids love grew up..
..earlier where it was..
..we also have kids..
..but we have not fought with you,
never.
Yes Yes know each and everything..
..for your kid milk
somewhat little..
..both husband and wife went
and insulted elder sister..
..what came in mouth said it..
..that time why didn't kept mum..
..giving others advice
yourself not proper.
This is not proper malati..
..she has only one kid if he
also gets milk less then..
..so she will keep quiet..
.. | am not in anyones matter..
..speak out clearly..
..if you like it or not.
Its ok middle sister..
..we have seen your colour also.
What you want say ?.
Sending him to rajgaj whos
hands were there..
.this | don't know..
..seeing us your heart burns..
..this | know properly.
Shame
In this house what culture
kids can learn..
..kids don't stay with parents
becomes careless.
Listen Ganesh.
Whats it ? -Heard what your wife
said about kamals studies.
|1 don't want to hear anything..
.. only know that..
.. took leave and came home..
..to eat, drink and have fun..
..but here everything
is on gods grace..
..having food half stomach and
become weak but not now..
.. tonight | will go to banaras.
-What you said..
I will put IP 144..
..come ready,
without sign you can't go.
Big sir.
Madhav.
-Do something about me also.
What to do?
Sir due to work,
my back is breaking..
..kisan,biko..
..champa,
myself, all should be divided.
All should be divided !
Yes.
Madhav..
..you are here from
the childhood..
..proper man for the house..
..now you only tell..
..this dividing bridge
from where it came..
..between all brothers..
..how much love was there..
..areas people..
..use to call us five padhavs..
..with small milk problem..
..we are separated..
..kitchen and vessels
are made separated..
.oK..
..people will hear then
what they will say..
..being one mothers
children also..
..can't leave united..
..then lane society people ..
..what love we will
have for them..
..madhav..
..when our father expired..
.that time this ramesh..
..ganesh, dinesh, suresh..
..all were small ones..
.. like my children | have..
..love,crudle, had bought up..
..has bought up so big..
.. and today..
..0 god..
..are these days to be seen..
..you have kept me alive.
Ok sir..
..don't say anything more..
..ok you don't do our
partition uncle..
Raju keep quite.
No | will go.
-Sit here. -Send him here..
..this is rajus voice na..
.see..
..just look..
..they dont let him
to come to me..
..with whom should | play..
..how will my time pass..
..he is crying willing
to come to me..
..you go and bring him..
..see anyone stops..
..bring him forcefully to me..
..yes forcefully.
O sir..
..sitting in the dark
are you doing..
..tea also has become cold..
..should | bring another one.
- don't want.
Ok sir.
Nadu listen.
Yes say.
Nothing. -Go do your work.
Listen.
Say.
This letter.
Post it or what ?
No.
Big sir,small sir..
..give everyone one.
Sir..
..your letter.
What letter is this?
Middle one sir has given.
Letter for what..
..today night at 8:30 ..
..at drawing room..
.. for partition meeting
will be there.
Brother..
..Ganesh..
..Dinesh..
..suresh..
..you all are here..
..take brother read it..
..if you felt ok ..
..then sign everywhere.
Ramesh..
..what is his name.
No brother you have do fully..
..how much sad you feel..
..you don't want read..
..these read and sign it..
..but.
How will | know these
legal things..
..for you all this is right,
then it is right for me also.
We the undersigned persons..
..willing and voluntarly
agree to..
..for above this is abig problem..
.this | will not do.
| am saying that.
You all agree it.
Me, what will | say..
.. ask big brother.
| mean.
| wanted to say..
..that.
What you want to say, say clearly.
| mean to say..
.. | want to say..
.. that these papers..
..if shown to all daughter in laws
once. -Daughter in laws..
..ramesh in this matter daughter
in laws. -Its ok..
..if for him daughter in
laws thinking matters..
..then call everyone..
..madhav..
.madhav.
- am coming middle brother.
Where you were.
Was filling tobacco..
-Go call all daughter in laws..
.. tell I have called. -O ramesh..
.. you are not understanding.
-No brother..
..its getting night,
why to make late.
What happened ganesh brother..
..ganesh what happened.
Giddyness.
Blood pressure has not
increased your bag.
Ganesh. -Kisan kisan. -Birju. -?..
Girish.
For today you keep
your anger ready..
..have to change one thing.
| can't see this strange
drama now.
You are this way your dying..
.. this is not happening truly.
I am not understanding
truth and lie..
--1 will go and tell the whole
thing leave me. -Maju catch.
Just give sister betel leaf fast.
Sister will have tea.
-What are you saying.
Why are you dying of thinking..
..we will handle everything..
..as time comes we will
tell them everything..
..because of your uneasiness..
..we all womens..
..to make you fool we all played
drama yes malati..
..open sisters hand.
Ramesh brother before your eyes
there is no blankness na..
-.No..
..yes comes. -Fool.
Today you bought two
rupees pakodos.
Middle brother everything sinked..
?.. -Don't shout. -Its secert
middle brother. -Shut up
Big brother please tell
them hear me. -Ramesh..
..just see what he wants to tell..
..go,go.
Now tell fast,
why didn't they come, all of them.
How they will come..
..they are sitting upstairs..
..and making you all fool.
Who, where? whom.
You all who else..
.. you all are in the
matter of partition..
..and upstairs all the
daughter in laws are..
..hugging and laughing
at your foolishness..
..root of the cause is..
..middle daughter in law. -What
you said middle daughter in law.
Yes.
This is the thing.
-Ok | am happy..
..now with raju..
Just like blood pressure
I am alright..
.. for this good news..
.. 100 rupees for you.
What did you say? thank you.
We are giving 100 rupees..
Doctor sir.
Now go from here..
Ganesh brother..
.. we all brothers..
..were made fool.
What is his name..
.. you don't understand anything..
..they are making fool everytime..
..will make fool ever.
Don't move..
..SO.
-Again we have to sign. -Wait..
..appeal has given in high court..
..we can't leave this matter
undone. -So what that.
Madhav. -Yes.
Get out..
..we will have meeting.
Again your meeting?.
Yes, get out kisan you also go.
Come kisan.
Ramesh. -..what is his name.
Want to decide.
Decide.. -What decision?.
| am not understanding any thing.
1 will make you understand
everything.
Everything is destroyed..
.. thought everything
will go fine..
.. here again all
went wrong come..
..meeting,
we will also do meeting come.
They are coming.
Sister they all are coming..
..for sometime shut up.
Now | will not keep mum.
Now how much time is left just
sign on papers thats all.
If it is signed also then what?
Signed papers can be teared,
how much time it take.
We want to make them
understand that..
..men and women are..
..the two tyres of family life..
..if both are fine then
only vechile can move.
Mens don't have any right
to say false things..
..what are mens..
..candle wick or wet mud..
..we can make them how we will.
Understood middle brother.
-You keep quiet..
.fight with me is not a play..
..now they will be ok..
..come..
..SO you are here..
.oK..
..our parition has got ready..
.tomorrow at court
it will be filed..
..we five brothers have signed..
..now you all sign in the
place of witness..
..judge sir's order is..
..in this no changes will be.
O god what is this happening.
No, No what was to happen
has happened..
.-tomorow onwards lands, property
doors, clothes, shoes hat..
..all are separate
fully seperate..
..what middle brother.
-Fine,fully fine..
..taken sister sign it..
..but to do partition who
told you brother in law.
Who will say..
..we are mens, mens.
Right.
-Not,candle wick or wet mud..
..on someone's order we work..
..our decision is this
house's order.
We five brothers decided
and made this decision.
To do partition is
the better one..
Yes na big brother.
You are not saying anything you
are also thinking this way.
| said to him.
-No, No big brother..
..now what the use sister come
sign. -Brother in law!
No sister today | won't hear you..
..we five brothers have promised..
..will be separated.
Brother in law!
I am not only your sister..
..in your all mother's
place also..
.-all of you were sitting
on my lap..
..feeded you all and
made you all big..
..today if your mother was alive..
..will this partition
will be done.
Sister.
-Judge sir has given the order..
..now it can't be changed.
See now suffer..
.. | was telling you all..
..don't play with fire..
..nobody hear's me..
..my golden family..
..has broken into pieces.
Big daughter in law where
are you going?..
.listen..
..big daughter in law ! listen.
Now middle brother..
..we get sign from big
sister later on.
Ok..
.firstly you sign.
Listen..
..if partition is not done then.
Means. -Means..
..Means that..
..what has to be happen
that has happened..
..now whats more. -Kids play..
..according to sir's order
draft has been made..
..no way is there. -O mother..
..everything is spoiled..
..so really partition will happen.
-Yes, and will happen..
..don't you remember
that midnight..
..kamal was thrown
out of the room..
..we should get our share.
| say..
..you only make understand
middle brother..
Make understand middle brother
what is left understand..
..raju is my only son..
..for him also milk
mixed with water..
..no milk is his staple food..
..this partition will happen.
| am begging before you..
..why are you quite
you do something.
1 will do have to do something..
..don't remember said jobless
and insulted you also..
..ok, now partition..
..my share | will sell..
..in big city | will start
a dancing school.
Listen | am saying.
You sign..
..don't have to say anything..
..after partition we can breathe
easily. -Partition!..
.. am begging before you.
What is there to laugh here?..
..if you can't control partition
happiness then..
..go to your room and laugh alot..
..middle brother will
sent the papers..
..and you all sign
and send it back..
..here our ancestoral property
is getting distrubed..
..and his happiness is getting
broken come now..
..come, go to your rooms.
Whatever happened is good..
..can escape from everyday's
fight's.
It was not fights..
it was all lie.
Lie !.. -Lie ! Means.
Means, means that..
.. you all brother's..
..use to say about your
love for each other..
.so we all..
..malati,
jayashree,manju, myself..
we all..
..planned that you
all get a lesson.
O so you all were teaching
us lesson..
..planning but before law
no planning can be done..
..before sir no reason
can be said..
..now no way is there..
..it will be contempt of court.
Listen..
.. | am begging before you..
..however you just tell sir once..
..whatever you say | will do..
..kamal at night didn't
sleep with me..
..whole night | was
not able to sleep..
..without talking to sister..
..malati, manju,jayashree..
without doing jokes..
.how will I live..
So this the thing..
..you are also not less.
We all are wrong..
..then why is middle sister
harrassed.. Yes. -What big brother..
Yes, whats his name..
..Ramesh is doing over.
Please save me.
Tear into pieces thats paper..
..just now,Tear into
pieces thats paper..
..want to play with fire..
..daughter in law,
you don't worry..
..we both the parties have failed.
Now, sister its fifty fifty.
For that only women..
..is called in hindi better half.
In english better half..than
hindi one foot ahead.
Come, come downstairs..
..what is his name..
..call panditji..
..peace harmony and holy
book should be read..
..lets go go,go..
..come.
Will you do it again?..
.what !
What..
..whats the new problem.
You all felt good that
you have done..
..middle brother now you
all do the partition.
What partition?.. -Yes..
..among us who is with whom..
..just look into it.
Go, go away.
Go away from here..
..Go away. Yes
Not understood go.
O madhav.
Whats it where..
..take your gift and go.
-Gift ! -Yes..
..said us at the right time.
But what is his name..
2.
Big brother | have
given that means..
.its from the state.
Right..
One for all..
..All for one
Jai ho..
One for all..
All for one ..
..One for all..
.All for one.