You Tube - Video Running Time 02:13:46
You Tube search name - Bluff Master
- Shammi Kapoor I Saira Banu I Lalita Pawar
- Old Hindi Film -(With Eng Subtitles)
Passengers at the back
can get down.
Why have you stopped the coach
here? I have to go ahead.
A coachman's spirit roams here,
which stops the coach.
Hence I was shouting
to you to get down.
Go coachman go,
the spirit has left you, go.
Come Sultan.
- Well, Mr Gupta, how are you?
- All fine, with your blessings.
Here are your Rs.2. Pardon me,
I had gone to Calcutta.
Hence the delay.
But there is nothing outstanding
against you.
The lender may forget,
but not the borrower.
I will see.
There is some mistake.
You don't owe me anything.
It is a small amount.
You may have forgotten
Please keep it. Good day.
Great, there are such honest men
around, who never forget.
- Mr Gupta, you must be having Brylcream.
- Yes.
And one pack of biscuits.
Get one pack of biscuits and
a bottle of Brylcream.
And please write down the
amount in your note book.
Your word is enough.
- Thank you.
- Hello!
This business of words,
has never been dull.
Sister Lajvanti.
Who? OK. I am just coming.
- Uncle! Uncle!
- What have you brought for us?
Keep quiet boys, everything is
for you. What did you get?
I have brought English biscuits
for my nephews.
Are your nephews any less
then Englishmen!
Here.
Sister, you also eat!
Where is brother?
He has gone on shift.
When he returns I will go.
Our life is going on very well.
Husband and wife earn together..
And all share and eat. Look,
the commander has also come.
Ashok,
were you left early from office?
Yes, we are always free.
Here, take this.
99,
100. What a beautiful body you've
made, our gaze slips off
Ashok, this time I want
to become Hindu Kesari.
Consider you are one already.
I have brought such a oil,
if you apply an ounce everyday,
You will gain 4 kilos a week.
- Honestly?
- Yes, have I ever told you a lie. Look at this.
The Englishmen have made a
concentrate of strength and..
Put it in this bottle.
What is the name of it?
The name is Mr India Oil,
or Creme la bluf.
How much price?
I have bought it for 16 but in
the market it is for Rs.25.
It can't get common man.
Ashok,
please give me this bottle.
No, if I give the bottle to you..
I'll become weak myself. No way
You don't have to wrestle,
so you give it to me!
Ok, I will give it to you.
Take out Rs.16,
-I will just bring it.
Use it every day,
see the difference in a week.
- Bye!
- Good day, Munim.
- You have decorated the room very well.
The room, the breeze and the
air, have I decorated..
I don't understand this poetry.
Spin your top and let us listen
to some nice beat.
Straight away..
- Listen! -That is a fake!
- Ask what is real here!
Agreed I am not rich,
but the atmosphere is of wealth.
See this tub, it has a hole,
so it cannot hold water.
This shower works when it rains
& water comes from the terrace
And see my beauty queen,
whose dance I see without ticket.
I know, you are making me dance
also. Do you have my rent.
Of course, here are Rs.10 in
cash. Remaining Rs.50 in credit.
Rs.10 after 10 visits. Come on
what will I tell the owner.
A poor man must help another poor
It is just a matter of a ..
Few days,
& I will complete the amount.
Promise? It is a friends promise.
- Good bye.
- Bye.
For one 75 year old girl,
wanted e suitable groom.
A room on rent. Give it.
Wanted a photo journalist,
Bhukump Weekly Press.
If I can get hold on one camera
from these, my job is certain.
Come, sir. Come.
Has my camera come?
I will just pack it.
No, my train is about to come.
Give it to my man, Mr Sengupta.
Do a job. I forgot to give
him his ticket to Pune.
Give it to him
I am Sengupta, I'm late. Did my
boss leave a camera for me?
But I don't recognise you.
You certainly recognise me well.
From a name how can you
recognise a face?
What should I do, call the
police, or the military..
To confirm I am Sengupta!
Did my boss leave me
a ticket for Poona?
Yes He did.
You are the right person.
- Where are you put up?
- Hotel Tajmahal, Room 213.
- Don't you see and walk?
- I will pick up for you.
Are you Mr Sengupta?
Take your wallet.
Your boss has just left..
Left a railway ticket.
He has taken the camera. Go now.
- Who are you?
- I am Ashok Azad.
Your name sounds familiar.
That means you've also
visited London.
I was the Chief Reporter of
Sensational Newspaper there.
Glad to meet you.
Please sit down.
You have come at the right time.
Bhukamp needs a reporter
like you.
I too am on the lookout
for such..
A paper as Bhukamp which
can utilize my skills.
I like your paper name,
Bukamp (earth quake)
It looks, it will shake the
world like its name.
I like your personality
and views.
If you get some good news, you..
Will find a permanent
place in our newspaper.
Keep your ink wet on your
machine, I will just get the news.
Lady, have your breakfast.
I told you so many times..
When I'm going out,
don't mention food!
Driver, take out the scooter.
I feel like becoming a martyr
under her scooter.
- Come I will show you.
- Sister, I never said a thing.
Nothing said?
- Mister, what is this?
- Nothing, I just took a photo.
What was the need?
Do you know it is a crime to take
photo of a unknown girl?
Lady, it is a public road..
You took law into your own hands
by slapping a pedestrian.
If you want to live,
give me the negative.
Give me your address.
I'll come tomorrow morning
and give you the positive.
Will you listen and give
me the negative.
Watch your scooter or some
one will take it away.
- Has this man molested you?
- No, he has taken my photo.
Is this the way you disrespect
other ladies?
I will tell you the whole thing.
A goon teased.
- This lady got down from the scooter and slapped him.
- Then?
I saw this scene and
took a photo.
What theft or dacoity
have I committed?
In fact I have captured the
scene of an Indian..
Brave lady in action
for posterity!
But where is the goon?
The lady started fighting with
me & the goon ran away!
- But how?
- He ran away. It is not difficult to run in Bombay.
I will tell you how.
The bus was coming from
this side, it halted..
The goon got into the bus
like this and went away!
I will definitely send you
the positive tomorrow.
Yes, the paper sold like hot
cakes. Its all due to Asok Azad.
He is a very useful man.
- Yes.
- Mr. Verma..
Send Ashok to me.
I want to met him
Okay.
What? A lady's hand and a manly
work. A shameless fraud!
- May I come in?
- Who is it?
I am Ashok Azad.
The editor has sent me.
Ashok. Please come in without
permission. Well done!
- You have held a falling wall.
- What is your salary fixed?
- It is 300.
- Only? It should be Rs. 500.
Thank you.
Whether it is 300 or 500..
Makes no difference to me.
It just covers cigerette money.
I have to get a 2000
more from home.
- Uncle what is this?
- What happened dear?
Just look at this.
You are hitting your own head!
- Today I have my program.
- When they see this, what will they say?
At 3 O'clock Munnibai is coming?
What will she think?
What will she think? Only good!
- You?
- I have only praised you.
Now you don't even need Munnibai.
Go on the stage yourself.
You will receive only claps!
Shut up!
- Uncle why are you quiet?
- Yes, uncle why?
- Do you know whose photo is this?
- Yes, hers!
I was correct, you are fearless
as well as shameless.
Mr Ashok, do you know who is she?
Wait Uncle. I will tell him.
I am the owner of this paper
& you are my servant.
This house too is mine,
Now get out of here.
And remember, don't show your
face at this door here, again.
- Atleast I can show my back?
- You shameless chap!
- Kumar!
- What a welcome!
When did you return from London?
Jwala Prasad,
no news of my going or coming.
And you are?
She is my niece, Seema.
Seema, this is Mr Ram Kumar.
He has a big export
business abroad
- How do you do?
- Namaste!
You appear to be made
up of old traditions.
When the man is new, it pays to
have your traditions with you.
Good.
A good answer.
Come Mr Kumar. Come..
A modern fool.
Mr Kumar, how did you come
suddenly from London?
You suddenly stopped sending me
money. You know expenses there
How will I manage then?
At present I have only
one source of income.
But you never told me,
you've such a beautiful niece.
I never got the opportunity.
Well, It is never too late.
If I had known earlier..
Your balance installments would
have reduced by half.
Do you like Seema so much?
Her beauty is apparent.
But she also appears intelligent.
Yes,
after my elder brother's death..
I too have looked after
her with a lot of love.
Then do one more job.
Where will you find a better
son in law than me.
And then you don't have
to worry about..
- Sending your installments at all -Sister! Hello!
- Coming.
Sister,
I have brought Derby tickets.
Buy one, you will get Rs10000001.
A million!
Has any body got it before?
Yes. That man in the lane behind,
his mother got it.
- And before that barber, his third wife too got it!
- Really!
Do you think my luck is any worse
than theirs. Here's Rs10.
Take Gods name and issue
me a ticket also.
- Hail, King Raianal!
- Who is this god, Rajanal?
Why to God while gambling?
He is the greatest gambler.
Rajanal,
make my sister a millionaire.
I'll change her name from
Lajwanti to Damyanti.
- Be Happy. God keep you happy.
- Bye.
What has happened Seema?
Read this, Munnibai is finished.
- What?
- Show doomed.
What will happen now?
Should I tell?
But first give me my chair.
- You? You have come again to trouble us?
- No.
You threw me out of a iob.
I have a job here.
I raise curtains here.
This chair is for this iob.
I relax as well as work here.
But today is a holiday for you.
Munnibai is ill.
How terrible!
What will happen to the show now?
Now the chairs will dance.
But I have an idea.
I also know one Munnibai.
She is a very good singer.
Shall I get her.
Your show will be a hit.
If the show is a hit,
your job will be confirmed.
But Munnibai will dance and sing
on one condition, that ..
- You too will perform with her.
- Me, never!
Please Seema, agree or we will
have to face humiliation.
Please come, please.
How is this wind blowing..
That the flower is dying
for the drone now.
What'll be fate of the flowers,
if the drone appeals to them.
Though they refuse on the face,
it is evident they die for us.
Fact cannot be hidden by hiding..
The heart will become more
restless by suppressing love.
If the heart gets restless,
we know how to pacify it.
If it gets distracted,
we know how to get it back.
How the wind is blowing..
You say that giving the
heart is a game.
In which world are you living?
Love is something else. The heart
burns and there is fire.
We are not those who
will cry in love.
By falling in love we
spread happiness.
The fate of the flowers is bad..
That the drones appeals to them
We have made you the target &
have shown the path of love.
You are teaching us love
and you show us eyes?
If love is true,
then the tongue is silent.
It is that flame,
which survives in stability.
Auntie Jamuna,
there is a letter for you.
A letter for me?
It must be Dabbu.
- Hello, aunty.
- God bless you.
- Here is your letter.
- It must be my son's letter.
Wait. I can't read,
please read it for me.
My dear mother, you will be happy
to know your Dabbu has..
- Become a reporter.
- What is a reporter?
Repoter?
I think it is the younger
brother of Governor.
A governor's younger brother!
Read further, Murari.
From my first month's salary
I am sending Rs. 10 for sweets.
There is nothing inside this!
Sending money in an envelope
is a crime..
So he will send it
by a money order.
Who is bothered about money,
my son's letter has come. Read!
Next written is..
From this spend Rs.2 in the
temple and 8 is for you.
I am so happy, I will distribute
sweets to the entire village.
Yes, show to the entire village..
They thought Dabbu was useless..
And now he is a big man.
Has he given his address?
Yes, he stays in Taimahal hotel.
He stays in Taj Mahal! Wow.
Ok, auntie, I will go now.
Good day.
- Kumar, impossible!
- You will have to make impossible possible.
- But I don't want to go with this man to Theatre.
- I don't like it.
- Don't say that, Mr Kumar is your fiancee.
- Fiancee?
Yes, your father had chosen
Mr Kumar for you.
And he had said on his
death bed that..
Your marriage be with Mr Kumar
But Uncle, If he was alive today
he wouldn't have said it now.
It is quite possible.
But I am bound.
I'll have to abide by the word
I have given to my brother.
Can't say anything more
Editor, Mr Ashok has been
taken back on the job.
And I have a ticket of Widow
Ashram Charity show.
Row A. Seat 14.
I have a spare one,
which I will send for Mr Ashok.
Very good, when Mr Ashok
comes, I will tell him.
You have called me sir?
Mr Ashok you can resume work.
Thank you. Can you tell
me who recommended me?
Are you interested in the work
or who recommended you?
Certainly its work.
Then go to this Widows Charity
show and attend the program.
Other details you will get there
Here are your tickets 12 and 14.
Nonsense, they are 12 and 13.
Have a look at your tickets!
Ashok,
when did you return from America.
Only the day before, please sit.
You should have informed me!
Anyway meet Mr Kumar,
a very big man of the city.
And this is Mr Ashok -Who has
just returned from America
After getting a diploma is
Journalism and Photography.
It is good, we have our
own man in Seat no 13.
Yes.
If you don't mind will you
shift to seat no 14?
Yes, I do.
13 is a very lucky no. For me.
I was born on 13th.
Left for America on 13th.
And today is 13th.
Perhaps the month is also 13th.
Must be!
Ashok,
what do you think of ice cream.
It is a very good thing.
- It keeps the mind cool.
- What do you think? -As you like it.
Then can you get three
ice creams for us.
- What is this on my seat?
- It is my camera.
- Keep in your side.
- Thank you.
- What does this Kumar sell?
- At this time ice cream.
You made a waiter out
of a good man.
But after all he is waiter
for whom? It is Seema!
I was telling him about you.
He is a very rich man, Mr Rich
You can make out from his face,
See!
Jwala Prasad when are you
going to clear your dues.
After Seema's marriage,
each penny will be cleared.
After marriage..
All property will go into
the name of son in law.
But he is my own man.
Today you saved me
from that bore.
For that you must make
me your body guard.
Don't forget the picnic
invitation.
Seema, I was waiting upstairs.
- I thought you had come before me.
- Come!
Miss Seema, you are coming
with me on the picnic?
Nothing doing, we are going to
watch the Derby on Race Course.
Derby? I too will come.
I will give you good tips.
What very good,
what tips can he give me.
I haven't wasted my time abroad.
Mr Ashok, I was a trainer there!
My father is an owner and
trainer in Calcutta.
- That's great!
- Let us see whose tips are more correct tomorrow.
Come.
There is a party at Mr
Kapoors residence.
Take some nice snaps of the
party. Here is the address.
Good.
Welcome,
are you from Bhukamp Papers?
Go ahead and take some photos.
At last I got you. I had to come.
I went to return the the
camera in the shop,
But I came to know of your
son's birthday party.
Not birthday party but a
marriage anniversary.
Please sit down. It is possible
I might have heard wrong.
I thought I will join
your party..
When I am in the city and do..
Some thing good for you.
But where were you
all these days.
I rang up Mr Sengupta
in Taimahal hotel.
But they said,
nobody by that name is there.
You are right.
Since I had come to rest here..
I had given my name as Johnny
Breganza -Doesn't matter.
Kamla, get some tea and snacks
for Mr. Sengupta.
I have to go the airport to see
off my friend to Japan..
I have taken a few snaps.
Should I take some more?
Don't worry. I have asked for a
photographer from Bhuamp Press
I know him, he is a good worker.
I will take leave.
Atleast return the camera!
I will develop the prints
and return the camera.
Developing is done
at our shop also.
I don't want to trouble you.
Good.
Namaste!
Aunty!
Is that you Ramdas? Yes, Auntie.
Come.
How are you? Fine,
I was returning from the city, ..
I thought I will meet you.
I am here, due to your love.
How was the crop?
Very good,
I have paid off my loans..
Bought clothes for next year,
and have Rs 100 left. Take it
I will take return,
when will I need it.
No, thank you. You are being
extremely kind and trusting.
I have someone's jewels,
some money, somebody's clothes..
Aunty, you are our bank,
and post office.
After 6 months is
my sons marriage.
If I keep the money
it will get spent.
A son has to give his
salary to his mother.
Ok,
I will keep,
these 5 knots are your mark.
Mine will be 1 .2,3
- Lajvanti, sister.
- Yes.
- Hello!
- Hello, be happy.
What is this big mark
on your forehead?
Today is my birthday,
and so I had gone to the temple.
And you didn't get sweets
for your sister.
Today I am taking the kids for
getting ice cream for them
Ice cream!
Come kids, Your uncle is taking
you out for ice cream.
Is the Editor there? I am Mr
Kapoor. I had such a big party.
You didn't send a photographer.
What? ..Wrong.
There was no Mr Ashok.
Impossible..
I am telling you facts!
- He is right.
- Mr Sengupta, please come.
Don't call me Sengupta,
I am Ashok.
I am the photographer of Bhukamp.
You mean you have been cheating
me from that day?
A man who has been struggling
all his life, at times cheats
Before you get angry
or call the police..
I want you to spare some
valuable time for me.
I have no time for cheats.
I am ringing up the police.
If you have no heart,
please call.
These children's mother has left
for her heavenly abode.
I will leave them & go to jail.
Listen, at least listen to
him, he looks so unhappy.
- Ok, say what you want to say.
- Children sit down.
It was 1947.
I had a shop in Lahore.
Business was so good
I used to bring..
Money home in a cushion cover.
That year I got married too.
But it was God's wish..
Due to partition riots
my shop was burnt.
I came to Amritsar.
There I came to know my
father-in-law died.
My wife became mad. For 3 yrs I
ran around for her treatment..
At times in asylums in Bareli
and at times in Agra.
I got her cured. 2 years later
our first child was born.
God is witness, I had no food
the day he was born.
So we named him Shivvrath
(fasting).
Then we came to Mathura.
I borrowed a camera and started
business on footpath.
We had several children.
It's rightly said..
Poor people have more children.
Bachchu was born next..
Then Sutuwa..
Then Kunnu..
Munnu, Chunnu..
During her last delivery my poor
wife met with an accident.
She was going to buy
milk one day..
But she met with an
accident on the way.
She fainted there.
She was taken to the hospital.
Chunnu was born but she died.
I don't want to say
anything more.
When I remember that day my
hair on my body rises.
Don't cry son, happiness and
sorrow are two sides of life.
Guru,
get some sweets for the children.
Tell me, what can I do for you.
Now you know why I took the
camera? Just for these children.
Really. To raise these orphans..
Eat sweets.
In Bhukamp there was a place
vacant for a photographer.
Without a camera how
could I get a job.
I surely cheated you..
But god knows I had
no bad intentions.
I had thought I would repay
you for your camera.
He is a man with responsibility.
Help him.
Mr. Ashok how can I help you?
If you return the camera to me..
I will worship your
photo everyday
I will lose my job
without camera..
And my children
will be homeless.
If you can help me, I promise..
I will repay you every
month for your camera..
And feed these kids
If man doesn't help, during
hardships, who will? Take it
Mr Kapoor, you have saved a
sinking boat. I am grateful.
- Here, take some money.
- Mother, I am already indebted.
But I am not a beggar.
Thank you. Come children.
Poor chap, though fate has been
unkind to him, he is so nice.
You have done wonders!
Were you a jockey earlier?
- He was a trainer in England. Training donkeys.
- What?
- I mean horses.
- Ok, but see me in Derby.
But Mr Kumar,
I hate horses and donkeys.
You are referring to Ashok.
I too hate such kind of people.
- Horses would hate humans, Mr. Kumar.
- What?
Who will win the Derby?
100 that one.
Mention and here comes No. 13.
- How is it going?
- Ask her.
- He has already won thrice!
- Great, your luck is great here.
You should remain here only till
the derby race is finished
Good, till then we will make
arrangements for the picnic.
Yes, you stay here.
Don't move. We will just come.
Mr Ashok, you were going to
give me the Derby winner.
Give the book, put on No 11.
He is a good horse.
No11? He will not be able to
catch even the tail of Bone.
Yes, for he will be ahead.
Now leave this fight.
If Kabab Me Haddiwins..
Then Kumar and me will
go for the picnic.
If No.11,
Bluff master wins then..
Mr Ashok and myself will go and
you can come with the girls.
Ok, let us shake on that..
It is not Bluff Master, but it
is the beauty which has won.
Beauty has made such a move,
that lover is in a bad shape.
By love, a miracle has happened
The heart says no,
but the eyes say yes.
By love, a miracle has happened
Some times she comes near,
sometimes she is far away.
Is this the style to steal
people's hearts.
The arrow has yet to
leave the bow..
Somebody tell him to
safeguard his heart.
Beauty has made such a move,
the lover is perplexed..
By love, a miracle has happened
How long will you
save your self..
It is now difficult to save..
Yourself,
now that the aim has been taken.
What about me! I will die if you
just look at me and smile.
This heart is yours,
the world is yours..
You look there but
your mind is here.
My hair sends out a message &
one who is love struck comes
You are asking me how
was the picnic.
It was such, that taste hasn't
still gone from the mouth.
- So you had a ball!
- No, we had gone but somebody else enjoyed.
- Who was that?
- My permanent enemy Ashok.
So he had reached there too.
Yes, and he duped us.
Look,
I don't like what Seema is doing.
She goes with me and
enjoys with him.
My sandwiches and
she feeds Ashok.
In front of me,
she went off with that Ashok.
Kumar, that was very bad.
Look Mr Dwarka, don't rub salt
into my wounds with sympathy.
In this what can I do?
She was with you.
Whose job is it to keep her
in check, mine or yours?
Should I take her in chains.
Look, please talk to her today..
Else I'll put you in such a fix
where last wishes are asked.
You haven't behaved correctly
with Mr. Kumar.
But neither have I wronged him.
In the picnic you fooled him and
went away with that reporter.
It won't be tolerated.
Uncle, explain to him, not to
take lime in a curd pan..
Else he will cut his mouth.
Seema, he is your fiancee.
Roaming with Ashok is incorrect.
Else our family name
will be soiled.
Why do you think Ashok is just
an ordinary reporter?
He is from a good family.
I have called him for my birthday
party. You talk to him.
I don't think it necessary to
talk to one who works for us.
Love made such a move..
The lover is perplexed!
Turn back.
You were alright yesterday.
What has happened today?
By love, a miracle has happened
She has accepted my love.
Now I am hers, & she is mine.
Damn this love.
Listen, spread your legs looking
at your sheet, and ..
Stand upright looking
at your ceiling height!
And give your heart,
looking at your pocket.
Where are you, a pauper,
and she, who is so rich.
You put a horse in a tonga,
not a deer.
It is a matter of love.
In love all these are immaterial.
Love sees only the heart.
Seema has called me for
her birthday party.
But what gift are you taking
for her, a rattler?
That is too cheap, I must give
her an expensive one. Listen
Leave me,
I don't have even a penny today.
Ok, I am leaving everything for
tomorrow, but think over it.
Look what has happened?
I am finished.
Jumna Auntie, what has happened?
Come inside and see!
See,
in the darkness of the night..
They have taken everything.
It belonged to all!
Oh God, some poor farmer might
have to buy seeds..
Someone would have marry
to his sister or daughter.
God, he should be burn in hell.
Such a big wall was broken,
and you didn't hear anything?
Do you sleep so soundly
in old age?
All those who trusted
her are finished..
Trusting this old woman.
You are saying this?
Don't you know Aunt Jamuna?
I don't want to die by swindling
other's money.
Perhaps you have sent the
money to your son!
Sahivda, I'm a landlady.
I shall kill a son like this..
Who would be raised
on stolen money.
Today I'll go to my son..
Get the money & throw
it into your face!
So now you want to disappear?
Do you think I am going
like a thief..
I am leaving my house
& land behind.
If I do not return,
you may confiscate them.
Seema, please come here.
This is Lala Harbans Lal.
Congraculations, Seema.
Seema,
whom are your eyes searching for?
- It must be that picnic guy.
- Neera, don't cross your limits.
What did I say, if lightening
falls, don't blame me.
Understand my compulsions. I
touch your feet. Return my Rs.50.
You don't know how I
have saved this..
Money for my friend's birthday.
But didn't you give your
word for today? Yes.
What will I tell the proprietor?
Tell him in Rs.50 one can't
marry a second time..
But only once.
Just remember your young days.
You too must have loved a girl.
No, in our family we don't
love and get married.
You may not, but think of me.
I am in love.
Give me the money.
Mr Ashok. You may rant & rave.
But now my heart is now stone.
If I had known I wouldn't have
set my house on fire.
I have seen a beautiful present
for your beloved.
It is Tajmahal.
Then why are you telling me.
Inform Shah Jahan.
- Munim has taken the Rs.50 I had with me.
- Oh hell.
Excuse me I got a bit delayed.
A cow came in the way.
May you live a 1000 years,
and It each year have 50000 days.
Why are you cursing me,
Mr. Kumar?
- I want to die in young age!
- I am here to die, why you?
- Have you thought of anything?
- No Idea!
May be we have thought the same.
Govinda.
Today is festival
of Lord Krishna.
And Satoriya babu organises
"Dahi handi"..
Festival in Mangalwadi
every year.
Yes, in its pot he keeps
a Rs 100 note.
It is a dangerous job,
but what to do.
On one side is love & on..
The other broken bones.
Let us see what happens.
Govinda has come,
keep the pot safe, Brijbala.
1,2... 7 cowherds are with with
Here comes the butter thieves.
Be careful of them.
They are very naughty.
If they decide,
then there is no chance!
See how happily have they come.
They will play a festival
of milk.
No matter how much water you
throw, their enthusiasm is great
Govinda has come..
Watch out for the pot..
Govinda has come.
- What have you come to take?
- Nothing, but to give a present.
This you should have brought
365 days later.
You are not ashamed.
I told everybody that
you are coming.
Why am I jinxed?
And you are coming now?
Just listen to me
I don't want to listen
to anything.
- Seema, open the door, may be it is our last meeting.
- Why?
That's what I want
to explain you.
My father has come from Calcutta.
My marriage is fixed.
- It is good then.
- Is it? Ok, then.
- Your marriage is fixed.
- Yes, that is how I got late.
But reach for your marriage
in time. Ok then.
Listen can't you say no?
He will be a fool who will
say no to a marriage.
Did you see the girl?
No, but her photograph.
Big eyes, long hair, pink cheeks.
She is good. Then why were you
doing this drama with me.
If you were to marry some other
why were you romancing me?
I didn't know you were serious.
You never said a thing!
What is there to say?
All these days we
were dancing &..
Singing it had no effect on you?
My god, does singing and dancing
mean this? I am a simple man.
If you tell me frankly I will
straight away cancel ..
My ticket to Calcutta.
What do they say?
Same thing what a lover say in..
English to her beloved,
I ..love..try and understand.
You have slapped me.
You are saying it as if you
are reading from a book.
You have said it as a mother
will speak to her child.
Please tell me how to say it,
I have never said it before.
- Seema do you see English films?
- Yes.
There how is love expressed?
Yes, that is it. I will tell
Dad to cancel the marriage.
But tell dad,
he must have a meal with us.
- He only eats food made by mother.
- But why?
He is traditional,
and vegetarian.
He is very careful of purity.
- Ok then tea?
- My grandfather hasn't taken tea.
He is very short tempered.
Don't ask as he may
give you a slap.
Ok, at least let me meet him.
If not, then I will not become
his daughter in law.
- You are marrying me, isn't my meeting enough?
- No.
Ok, I will bring him.
Happy birthday.
Lady, I had said..
I'll light a candle when
I am successful in love.
I have come.
I had thought I'll not love.
And I will not die for a face
But the heart fell on one.
I sifted through the sands
of this world..
I didn't listen to
anybody till now.
But then how did I slip?
If I had not given my heart,
I may have a become big man
But what better work would
I have done than love.
I thought I will not fall in
love. I will not slip on a face.
- Son, is there a Tajmahal Hotel?
- Yes, there is.
- Then take me there.
- I will take Rs 1 for it.
But I have only 8 annas.
What!
You won't get change for it there
But are you going to beg in
front of Tajmahal Hotel?
What, do I look like a beggar?
I am a land owner in a village
Pardon me, I will just drop you.
Mother, this is Tai Hotel.
Is it I will just get down.
Here is your 8 annas.
If you want more, just wait..
My son is the owner here.
I will get it for you.
No mother, I am happy.
Look I want to meet Dabbu.
- Dabbu?
- Yes, he is my son.
He stays in this hotel.
Looking at you, your son must be
staying in some charity home.
Your son must be staying there.
My son stays here only
He is governor's younger brother.
What! It looks you have
lost your brain.
Careful, if my Dabbu hears you,
he will break your head.
- Brother, you know my Dabbu?
- Dabbu, what is dabbu?
He stays here, Here is his photo.
You know him, where is he?
Is anybody there,
I want to meet Mr Jwala Prasad.
Who are you?
You do not know me. I am Seth
Suraj Mal, only father of that..
Ashok who has been entrapped
by your niece.
Have patience.
- Why don't you sit down?
- Sit down
My name has been rubbed
into dust.
He has fallen in love with
a girl from a family..
With whom we have enmity
for the last 300 years!
I do not know anything.
It is only yesterday that Seema
told me about your coming.
What else could I have done!
Now tell me frankly
what is the matter.
It is clear Ashok and Seema
love each other.
My God, couldn't he find any
other family to fall in love.
Forget all these old quarrels.
Why should the kids suffer?
It is no ordinary fight.
Don't try and give advice.
Fool! Trying to be smart.
Can your words cool
down this rage?
If I has known this Ashok on
growing up would fall for a ..
Girl from this family
I would have...
OK, call the girl.
I have spent Rs.300, traveled
1200 miles by air, and come here
Go and call the girl.
Here she comes.
Touch his feet,
he is Ashok's father. God bless.
This girl cannot be
from this house.
Amongst these scoundrels.
A girl like her, impossible.
- You must forget old enmity.
- I will have to.
Sit down there!
- Girl, how old are you?
- She is just.. -You keep quiet!
- Let the girl talk.
- I am 18 years old.
And Ashok said you are 17.
Doesn't matter.
- Girl, what is your education?
- I have done matriculation..
- I applied for college..
- When you fell in love with Ashok.
This love is such,
it makes you forget all.
Anyway, walk & show
I am an old player.
I know you walked till this place
-But sir..
But one can know of a girls
character from her walk.
Just show your walk. Please walk.
Beautiful.
Very nice. I am satisfied.
I had decided to take Ashok back
with me to Calcutta, but..
This girl has doused all
my anger against Ashok.
Such a girl, so remarkable,
so sweet, so beautiful.
So what if the family is useless.
Girl, do you have any
liking for any art.
I play sitar,
and I know classical music.
Get a sitar.
Let us see this quality also.
Chandan, get the sitar.
Heartless lover,
go away My lover is bad.
Go away!
Go away Don't go on talking
Playing the flute, you overwhelm
me with its melodious tone.
You have many forms, and in each
you attract me.. Go, go.
Wonderful, Ashok's mother too is
fond of such devotion to god.
In youth, she too sang.
What fusion of beauty and talent.
She will sing and mother
in law will nod.
Mr Kapoor this is Ashok's father.
Glad to meet you.
Your face is very familiar.
Have we met before?
I accept this marriage
whole heartedly.
You may celebrate this marriage
with great gusto. And you?
Oh, I am a busy man.
Consider him your son
& get him married.
- Your introductions please.
- Mr Kumar, he is Ashok's father.
- Oh I see, meet her.
- She is Ashok's mother.
Now, should I use my hands or
you'll show what you really are
Mr Kumar,
what nonsense are you talking.
Seema, it is good that this
good lady has come in time.
Else your life would
have been ruined.
Mr Kumar,
I don't need your sympathy.
I will get a taxi.
Ashok, were you playing with
me as if I were a toy?
Dabbu, I cannot understand
what is this drama.
The drama is over. God knows how
many people he has duped.
Don't know how much people
have been trapped.
I'm also one of them.
He took my camera, and also Rs.
100 from my wife.
Look, we are respectable people
but this shameless chap..
But this useless..
Ashok you have disgraced me.
You have made a joke of my life
Why did you have to
do such a thing.
Daughter, he is a fake coin.
Is it for today's disgrace that..
How can he love..
- I gave you birth?
- Mother!
Your mother is dead.
If I had known you will
become like this..
I would have killed
you at birth.
Our house got burgled.
People lost their belongings.
I thought I will return people's
belongings which were stolen.
I did not know my son is
now cheating the world.
You will not have to be
disappointed about money, mother
You will steal,
you will commit dacoity..
Your father never even took
a Loan, and you? His blood!
You have defamed me.
Remember if I can give you birth,
I can take your life also.
I will kill you.
Mother! Why do you need a mother?
You have shocked her by
telling so many lies.
She has received a big shock.
BP is also high.
- Doctor, is there any danger?
- Let her regain her senses.
Then only my medicine
will work properly.
- All this has happened due to me.
- You are realising this now?
I didn't know the effect of my
lies will endanger my mother.
Mother, open eyes.
Mother, it is my fault,
and you are suffering.
Mother I accepted I have
done all those things.
I told lies, I impersonated,
but I am not a thief.
I thought one day I will
become a big man..
I could help you..
But I was misled.
Please forgive me, mother.
I swear by you today..
I will never do such
things again.
I will be honest.
Forgive me, mother.
Mother perhaps has heard me,
and has perhaps forgiven me.
Even God forgives those who
seek true repentance.
God, you are very kind. I'm
leaving this Lottery ticket here.
If not 7 give me at least 2,
3 lakhs.
God, when will you fulfill my
wishes of becoming Mr India.
I asked Ashok to get imported
oil for massage.
When will you fulfil my wish,
God!
God, please fulfill my wishes.
I will be happy even with little.
Yes.
Hello Ashok come and take
God's blessings.
The prayer session
has gone well..
I will surely get the lottery
Oh God!
What happened to this climate?
When a person cheats..
And tells lies,
there are storms & tempest.
But brother, there is no such
sinner in our building.
God please forgive me.
Give me strength..
So that I can control myself.
I have been a cheat at all steps.
Sister you'll never
get this lottery
Brother, don't fool around
with your sister.
Ashok, are you kidding?
Rambharose,
I am telling the truth.
You can never become
Mr India in life.
I gave you fake oil
it was hair oil.
Here is your money Take it back.
I had told you lies your
voice is fit for films.
Forget becoming a famous singer.
Otherwise you sing well.
What are you standing here for.
I think he has gone mad.
When are we getting our money?
Mummy has said she will make
good clothes for us.
Please explain to all, that this
is not a lottery ticket..
It is a laundry receipt.
Yes, sister.
This is a laundry receipt!
My god, he has been cheating
us all this while.
He has fooled us all along.
He has deceived us by
staying with us.
Mother, where are you going?
Where are you going?
I came to the city with
great expectations..
But everything is lost.
He,
who I gave birth to has put the..
Black spot on our character.
No, mother, Ashok is
not the same Ashok.
He has realised his folly and
washed his sins with remorse.
He has sworn he will walk on the
road of truth and honesty.
- You have faith?
- Without faith there is no life.
With this small happiness,
I will return to my village.
No, who is letting you go.
Doctor has said you need rest.
You have now your daughter's
request.
Come with me.
Mr Kapoor, here is your property
and your Rs.100.
Where did you get this money
from. Did you again cheat?
I am your defaulter.
You can say whatever you want.
But I have decided to walk
in the straight path.
How did you correct
yourself so soon?
Time teaches a lot very soon.
Ashok, come over. You seem to
have come down to mother earth.
Oh, you are in one piece.
I was about to be doomed!
Whatever happened
was for the good.
But what will happen
to mother's debt.
If I cannot arrange it..
Our respect will be soon
dragged in dirt.
Great! Suddenly you care
for family respect?
Friend, my life is at your
disposal. Take this coach.
I cannot snatch your daily bread
and earn my lively hood.
Now I will work myself and earn
my living. Understood, friend.
It is only a question of time.
Pipe down, why are you
unnecessarily making noise.
I know him. Wait.
Why are you going in a coach,
when you have this car.
I understand your problem.
Who doesn't require
money in Bombay.
Here, take this Rs 10000..
Go and start some thing
in another city.
Rs 10000? I do need the money.
I don't want to pawn my love.
If not pawn, sell your love.
You want some more money?
Here is another Rs 5000.
Rs.15000?
It is big money Kumar.
Whatever it is,
you look a very interesting man.
And big hearted also.
You want to trade in love?
Go, keep your money under the
pillow and dream of girls.
Love can never be traded,
Go from here.
Whatever it is, we should not
back out of our decision.
- Uncle has come.
- Get in all of you.
- I have come to meet you.
- Why?
I have paid my rent.
All the people of the building
have sent me a complaint.
You have been cheating them.
They don't want you to stay here
When I used to lie, they used
to love me, what do you want?
You will have to vacate
this room. When?
Today, if possible now!
It means there is no place for
a person who says the truth!
Tell this to others,
first vacate this room.
Why do u act pompous?
Why room, I will leave this life,
but all these people I love.
I love them more than my life.
I gave them nothing when
they gave me love.
I am grateful to all of them.
You know..
Somehow I am indebted
to them all.
Today why do you want to
humiliate me in front of them?
Wait downstairs.
I will pack and come down.
Ashok, had you not told lies,
this day would not have come.
- Please forgive me, I am going.
- Go, get away from here.
Eat! Has your mother died
that you are not eating?
- Sister!
- You have no sister here. Eat you brats.
Go and take over the room.
It is empty.
Now you can make an extra
amount on deposit.
- Uncle why are you leaving?
- Speak uncle
Why are you leaving the colony?
Tell me.
Why are you quiet? Tell us.
I am not leaving.
In fact everybody has left me.
Uncle,
why do people call you a liar.
Because I have stopped
telling lies.
Uncle, I have brought you a
sweet, I stole from my house.
For me?
You have not stolen a sweet,
you have stolen my heart.
- All of you come up.
- Don't talk to that liar!
Go. Your mother is calling you.
I will return one day. Go.
Go, mother is calling you.
Always listen to your mother.
Go. Go.
Hey heart, today nobody is
mine and I am nobody's.
When I walked a crooked path,
the world loved me.
When I found the path of truth,
the world forgets me.
Nobody knows what I want,
and nobody waits for me.
That is why one tends to look
back time and again.
- What is the purpose of this?
- Your blood.
Why are you wasting time.
I have a thick skin.
And you won't find a
penny in my pocket.
You want money, look elsewhere.
You want to get away talking.
- Who sent you? Speak up!
- Ok, I will talk.
Jwala Prasad, two for one who
is dying. What is happening?
You have not even one and
your hands are shaking.
I am feeling nervous. Kumar,
Your telephone hasn't come.
Why are you standing
like a thief?
What are you doing?
You are staying in a place where
Dacoits and murderers stay.
- Which Dacoits?
- Just listen.
The telephone is as dead as
Ashok whose body must be..
Lying some where.
It is a matter of murder,
Mr. Kumar.
So what, you are not new in
this school of murder.
A person who can kill
his brother..
Why should he worry about a small
murder such as this one.
- Don't keep referring to it time and again.
- Why not?
- Memories are refreshed.
- Enough.
A small mistake,
and now I am branded for life.
You are getting annoyed
unnecessarily.
We are partners now. After
Seema's marriage it will be 50-50.
Now you have heard it yourself!
Have believed me.
I cannot understand what is
happening. After all why?
They want to cheat you.
Look, I am very grateful to you.
You have helped my mother..
I have this opportunity to
repay my debt to you..
If you agree I can help.
I have an idea.
What have I to do in it?
We stage a small drama by..
Which they are convinced
we hate each other.
And the effect will be..
Jwala Prasad,
you take the last drink
- Uncle, are you all right?
- Why dear, I am all right.
Thank god.
I just has a bad dream.
I dreamt somebody was chasing
you with a knife.
Beautiful people should not
have such horrible dreams.
Take this hanky and wipe
away your tears.
- Such dreams have no meaning.
- But my dreams always come true.
- But this time I am right.
- Uncle, I am scared.
- In the dream I saw your dead body.
- My corpse!
Yes. And you were shouting
'Please save me, save me.'
And the murderer was saying
'Now God can't save you'
Jwala Prasad,
you are trembling like a child.
Look Seema,
if you feel scared, get married.
And even if you still
feel scared..
There'd be some one
to reassure you.
Ashok! Save me, save me.
Ashok, you want to kill my Uncle?
Not me, your uncle wants to.
I could never imagine..
For the small quarrel we had..
You asked your uncle
to murder me?
Here is the knife your
uncle sent to kill me.
Shut up,
do you think we are so fallen..
That we will stoop to murder!
What do you think of my uncle?
In fact you are a goon
& lust for money.
Fault is mine that
I befriended you!
Not yours,
fault is mine that I had..
Relations with such a family..
Who value everything with money.
Now I know the real you.
From today I'll never
enter this house.
Seema, do you now realise
how bad this man is.
I had told you not to let
this man come near you.
You were right.
The fault was mine.
Forgive me.
Now on I will listen to you.
You decide now where & to
whom should I get married
Congrats. Lala, the girl has
come on line on her own.
Then should I start the
marriage preparations?
But at least now you can
return the photographs.
Lala, here are the positives
and negatives of the photos.
I consider a word given
as above everything.
I hope you don't have
any more copies.
Lala, there is honesty amongst
thieves. Please trust me.
Well done, today you are not
burning & I too am relaxed.
May I come in please?
- Am I dreaming?
- First permit me to enter.
I cannot imagine! Please come in.
No, first say you forgive me.
First say what fault
have you committed.
My fault is I did
not trust a man..
Like you and involved myself ..
With a cheat and bluffmaster.
Forget all this.
As long as you have returned
all is forgotten.
And returned in such
a way there will..
Be never a thought of leaving
-Great thoughts.
Now please.. First tell
me you accept me or not
What are you saying?
If darkness gets light,
will it ever reject it?
Then should I give the
good news to Uncle..
That you will permit
me to serve you.
Don't say that.
I will place you in my heart.
Yes, & tell him to fix
the marriage date.
I too am interested in
a quick marriage.
I want to teach that
Ashok a lesson..
Which he will never forget.
Leave it Seema,
he will suffer on his own.
Just forgive & forget.
Uncle has agreed on one
small condition.
Every wish will be fulfilled.
Tell me.
He wants all my property
transferred..
In his name before the marriage.
So that is his small condition!
Yes, but how are you worried
about my property!
- Write it down.
- No need for money.
Ur uncle doesn't have a wife or
kids, then why is this greed?
But I too am not a kid.
I have a copy still with me.
- Copy?
- Yes, a copy of the photo.
Don't worry on this. I will just
now sort out that old man.
Not now.
In the morning we talk
of love not war.
Talk in the evening.
But don't take my name.
And today we have started
a new life.
Teach me a new Spanish dance.
- Not now. It is time for romance.
- No, take me now.
Come on.
No, that statement is all wrong.
See this side.
This is Seema my friend and
a first class dancer.
What are you saying!
- Well a small dance for my sake.
- No, I won't dance.
Well if Ashok asked
you would dance.
Today when I ask, your refuse.
Now I am your fiancee!
- Mr Kumar, what are you doing? Quiet.
- Don't utter a word.
If you interfere then what will
we do? I'll break your bones.
I will pay for your loss. Ok?
Fine.
Ok, Mr Kumar. If you are
insisting I will dance.
Ok, go to the dressing
room and get ready.
See the result of insulting me.
You had declined to come
with me on that day.
Since I have known you,
my life has gone.
My heart fell in love.
My lover is very aggressive.
How should I come out of this?
Seeing his style,
my heart was hurt
Hundred appeals lie
In just one glance.
I am a boat and you are my shore!
Since I have known you,
since then my life has gone.
My heart has fallen in love.
Seema, come!
Uncle I am very happy today.
You know despite all this
Mr. Kumar wants to marry me.
That's good.
But he was saying a very
strange thing today.
Before marriage everything should
be transferred to his name.
What? In name of Mr Kumar.
And that too before marriage?
Yes. In a way he is right.
After marriage too,
all will be his.
You are still a child. Your good
or bad, I would know better
Yes, who will know better. After
father, you looked after me.
Uncle he was saying
another thing.
- What was he saying?
- Something about papers.
- Papers?
- Yes.
He has a paper which can put
you into a lot of trouble.
I didn't understand.
Well, I just worry..
What will happen to you
after my marriage.
Well here are 5 lakh rupees.
They are yours.
But tell anything to Mr Kumar.
Now I am going out. Take it.
- Have you come to meet uncle?
- See how the meeting takes place
Leave it Kumar. For my love,
give me one more assurance.
With your love,
don't try to cool me down!
Here you are angry,
and there uncle is angry.
You will fight and what
will happen to me.
Look, I beg of you..
- If uncle has taken 24 lakhs just ignore it.
- What!
Are you airing the notes,
or counting them.
Perhaps I have come before time.
How are you keeping the notes?
This is not my money.
I am just paying Income Tax.
I have bought the Income Tax
office. Give the money.
- No!
- Give.
Living in water, you want to
challenge the crocodile.
Playing a double game with me!
Not me,
you are playing a double game.
Did you not promise that you
will return all the proof.
I returned all but one!
But kept only one important
evidence.
If I hadn't you would
have vanished today!!
Kumar, now it's time for
you to disappear.
It would have been better if
I had finished you earlier.
Don't threaten.
Kumar has a chest of steel!
Then we will know only
after firing a round.
- What are you doing here?
- I was involved with Kumar's goons
Your friend hasn't come.
You go to the police station,
I will fetch mother.
Is your mother's life more
precious or the tape?
You forgot whom are
you fighting with!
- What do you want?
- At this time you are a beggar, not me.
Are you not ashamed,
putting a mothers life at stake?
Everything is fair
in love and war.
But I admit you are cunning
as well as beautiful.
With your cunningness
you caused..
Split between your uncle & me.
You lost nothing but your
uncle lost his life.
Now to save your own life, one
more will have to be finished.
If your thirst is quenched
with blood, take my life.
Don't say that mother.
You want to put a price on my
mother's life? Spell it out!
It is a small amount.
You will accept responsibility
of Uncle's murder.
I will accept this for
my mothers life.
No, you have sworn to walk the
path of truth. Don't ever lie.
There is one more way.
Seema, what sacrifice can
you give for your love..
Jewels or your family line.
I am ready to give
whatever I have.
Then take out whatever you have.
I have nothing here.
Everything is in the bank.
I don't deal in cheques.
Give the tape.
A million for this life.
Bring the money to the caves,
& you will get your mother back.
I accept.
Seema, why are you losing
everything for me.
- Can't I do this much for mother.
- What happened?
I will tell you later,
there is little time now.
Mr Kumar has kidnapped
Ashok's mother..
& is asking for a million!
Your name? I am Mohan Choti
I am Ashok's friend.
Come. Come out!
No, son, no.
Fake notes, you are trying to
make a monkey out of me.
I tell you, leave me.
Mr Kumar,
will you take a cheque or cash?
Mother!
My Dabbu!
Dabbu's mother's would be
daughter in law, come here.
Come her..
Touch mothers feet.
Govinda has come, take care of
the butter pot, Brijbala.