After all, Dharamdas has proved
his innocence.
Looks like a strong pair of
hands choked him to death.
The murderer is one of us.
But who is he and what
is his motive?
And why isn't he facing us?
You look upset.
- Not really.
So what are you thinking about?
- Nothing.
Who could be
singing that song?
Who knows?
- Is it a stranger?
Do you believe in spirits?
What do you do in Bombay?
- Nothing.
What is your opinion
about the murderer?
What do you do in Bombay?
- You've evaded my question.
You haven't answered me either.
Do you always smoke cigars?
- Yes, why?
I found a piece of cigar
near Kishan's corpse.
Haramdas smoked cigars too.
- That's true.
But he was killed. There's someone...
- What are you insinuating?
That I am the murderer?
- Don't feel offended.
It's for me to dark
a shot in the darkness.
Who know? One might
hit the target.
Sometimes man himself
gets targeted.
I still maintain that I like
alcoholics, not alcohol.
Till we met, how did you
know about my qualities?
And this is still alien to you.
Try it and you will befriend it.
Isn't it enough that we're friends?
- There's safety in numbers.
Drink it. This will fulfil
all the voids in your life.
Why don't you say that I must
get drunk so that you will...
I know my way around, Rake.
I know all these tricks.
And suppose I don't drink it?
- Then I'll force it.
Sometimes you forget that
you are up against Kitty.
I've handled people like you
all my life.
Then let's see how you handle me.
C'mon, drink it.
It is not necessary to expose
your character to everyone.
There are decent
people living here.
Of course, and I've read
their names in the diary.
You had better leave.
- This is Ms. Kitty's room.
You'd better behave yourself.
- Darling, then you ask him to leave.
And close the door behind you.
Look, I can't tolerate
a woman being insulted.
Get out, you have no chance here.
Slowly does it... care
for your health, doctor.
Good! That's a match!
What are you both upto?
Aren't you ashamed of yourselves?
If we fight amongst ourselves,
how will we trace the murderer?
Go on...
Go to your respective rooms.
Kitty, beware of them.
Where are you going?
Please sit for a while.
Poking fun at my old age?
I am only complimenting you.
The way you separated them
was really commendable.
I mean, for a person of your age.
I've always had this bad habit...
- Pardon me?
I've always been fond
of exercising.
Perhaps that's why age has
not reduced your vigour.
Seeing your strength,
I'm tempted to befriend you.
So that even if I'm attacked,
I can be saved.
It is our duty to help each other.
You?
Why have you come here?
- To know about Dharamdas' death.
I've already told you.
A strong pair of hands
choked him to death.
Strangulation wouldn't have
turned the body blue, doctor.
Dharamdas did not die
of strangulation...
someone has poisoned him.
- I myself examined the body.
I'm a doctor,
I can't be mistaken.
If you are a doctor,
I too am a criminal lawyer.
I've been practicing
law for 15 years.
I've sent many guilty men
to the gallows.
What do you mean?
- My doubts are now confirmed...
that the murderer is one of us.
You may take another look
at Dharamdas' dead body.
The crime will itself reveal
who the perpetrator is!
What is the matter?
- Who killed Dharamdas?
What's the point in worrying
about those who are dead?
Let's worry about those
who are alive.
The old man is right. Instead of
others, worry about yourselves.
Worry about yourselves...
worry about me!
Go and attend to your work.
- I'm doing my work, all right.
What is your opinion
about the butler?
He's a harmless fellow.
But there is surely
someone behind all this.
That's true.
- How do we get to the murderer?
Right. How do we get
to the murderer?
Madame, what are you doing
in the kitchen?
I wanted to know the menu.
The menu is prawn
curry with rice.
My black colour on a fair skin
is considered a beauty spot.
But any white on my dark skin
is considered a disease.
Oh my sweet heart!
There is no dearth of beauties.
I'll managee with my dreams.
My dreams...
Oh God, I've made a mess
of my kitchen.
How will I feed
the free-loaders now?
May I ask you something, Anand?
- Go ahead.
I have a feeling you are
not what you appear to be.
But you should know that I'm
not what you suspect either.
That's just what I want to know...
who are you?
Who are you?
Why must you need an introduction?
I'm the one you had scolded!
Stop joking.
What else can I do?
Every moment spent in fun
is well spent.
Life is quite meaningless now.
There's the fear of death
at every step.
I wasn't afraid
when I came here.
I wasn't much scared even after
knowing the contents of the diary.
I didn't attach much
importance to death.
But now...
- My company makes you a coward?
No.
I don't want to die now.
I am not alone.
- I'll protect you from all harm.
But there is no way of escape.
I think we'll finally
suffocate to death.
Death will have to deal with me
before reaching you.
No one had any inkling of
this whilst leaving Bombay.
All this is a coincidence.
And incidentally,
we may even survive this.
I hope so!
- But we'll always be together.
What happened?
- Nothing.
Go on home.
- Are you going somewhere?
I'll just check everything.
You?
- No Kitty, sir... his is male!
You're mistaken.
It was me washing the clothes.
Ain't I a clever guy?
- Oh God!
Sir, can I tell you something?
- Speak up.
Give up drinking.
It's an awful thing!
Have you ever tasted it
or are you just abusing it?
My father was an ace drunkard.
My veins have more
alcohol than blood.
No wonder your face
is like this.
Come here!
Why is the doctor so frantic?
- Someone has murdered Mr. Sharma.
The contents of the diary
were true afterall.
The letter says, don't grieve
Mr. Sharma's death.
Because he had planned
Mr. Sohanlal's death.
I don't get this...
There's no one here besides us.
I think one amongst you men
is the murderer.
You left yourself out.
Perhaps you too...
How can you say such things?
Had I wanted to kill you all...
couldn't I have
poisoned your food?
Maybe you don't possess
the poison.
Well said! When I could arrange
for the food...
when I could bring
buffalos for milk...
couldn't I've arranged
for the poison?
Don't you doubt me. The earlier
ones died after a hearty meal.
But the rest of you
will die of starvation.
I won't cook for you!
She was only joking.
You could never kill alone.
Lay the food.
- That's a nice joke!
The food isn't ready yet.
I'll bring it, when it's ready.
You were right, Anand.
One of us is surely the murderer.
You, Anand or the doctor?
- Perhaps!
We must search each other's room.
And discard any weapon found.
I've no objection
to my room being searched.
You can gladly search
my room too.
What will we find in your room?
- Where else?
How was Mr. Sharma killed?
You have not answered me.
- What do you mean?
The pick-ax used to kill Mr.
Sharma was in your possession.
I've no pick-ax
in my possession.
I myself saw you hiding it.
Even when caught red handed, a
thief doesn't accept his crimes.
Why are you silent?
Answer him, Mr. Rakesh.
Even if that were true...
but then how was
Dharamdas killed?
By a pick-ax? No!
He was poisoned.
And only the doctor
had that poison.
The empty bottle of which be
hid in the vase that night.
This is a lie.
I have not poisoned anyone!
I admit, I did
have the poison.
So too, I am innocent...
though I did have a pick ax.
No reason for that.
Why should I feel offended?
So you are mourning
Mr. Sharma's death?
What nonsense! With you around,
I won't grieve even my own death.
But are you alive?
- Only outwardly.
Actually, I died the day
you called me Rake.
But you haven't get
accepted my love.
You too haven't seen
through someone.
So have a drink today...
for my sake.
For your sake?
Okay, I'll have it.
Do you really love me?
I've never spoken the truth.
But when I do, I mean it.
I don't understand this.
What did that letter mean...
that we shouldn't grieve
Mr. Sharma's death...
because he had master minded
Mr. Sohanlal's death?
That's a lie! I feel the
conspirator was someone else.
You are right.
- But who is he?
Some one.
- How can you be so sure?
Because I was Mr. Sohanlal's
private secretary.
Isee. So that's
how it is!
I think a drink more will
loosen your tongue further.
It was I who sent that will to you
for alternations. Understood?
No.
- You too need a peg to comprehend.
So darling, it means...
- Everything happens for the best.
Life is a gift and to find
a confidante is a real boon!
We are sailing
in the same boat.
Think it over!
You too may not drown.
I don't care.
- Then let's leave it to fate.
Hey butler, come here.
- I'm coming.
Where were you going?
- Where can I go, sir?
But what are you doing here?
- I was taking some photographs.
What?
- Photographs.
Take some of mine too.
- Why?
It will please my sister.
- How?
My sister has seen a girl for me.
- What?
If I send her my picture,
she'll perform the marriage.
Even if I click your picture,
it will remain in the camera.
Why?
- No developing facilities.
What is that?
- Washing the film.
Oh God, does one wash
the photographs?
But how will you send your
photograph to your sister?
There are no postal
services here.
Weren't the pigeons better couriers?
- That's true!
But cameras didn't exist earlier.
Can I smoke?
- Sure.
What did you do in Bombay?
- I was a butler there, not Hitler.
How did you come here?
- In a boat.
Alone?
- Two buffaloes accompanied me.
That boatman saw us off
with our luggage and left.
Who, in your opinion,
is the murderer?
Well, sir...? Trying to trap me
with this cigarette?
I just asked.
- I don't know anything.
Sir, now that your girlfriend
is coming, I'll go my way.
Seeing your wet clothes...
I think you've taken great
pains to find me.
True. Anand, I came to
give you some news.
What?
- Rakesh and Kitty are marrying.
Had a marriage been possible here,
we too won't remain bachelors.
There is no means of
getting married here.
Though one can romance and
make a commitment.
They've decided to get married
on reaching Bombay.
Only if they survive
this ordeal!
Who knows who's turn it is
to die today?
Isn't it possible that Rakesh
is the murderer?
Perhaps that is what makes
Kitty so care free today.
He will die.
He too will be murdered.
How can you be so sure?
Who will kill him?
Are you hinting at the doctor?
I think all of us will
be murdered.
Don't say such things, Anand.
I feel scared.
No need to worry. No one will
harm Mr. Sohanlal's niece.
Because what will happen to
the property after her death?
You won't die, Asha!
What are you saying?
You speak as if...
Yes, I'm saying it!
Go away! And wait for me,
should have faith in me.
My identity and my deeds
actions are a mystery.
And the day the mystery
is solved, you...
Are you trying to suppress
death with music?
Death is a reality
which we all have to face.
Where is everyone?
I've warned them to keep us
informed of their whereabouts.
But everyone ignores that.
- No one is loyal to anyone.
So the doctor has
also been killed!
He had Anand's name on his lips
before he died.
I've always suspected it. And the
doctor has solved this mystery.
Now don't ask me
who killed the doctor.
He took your name while dying.
- That's is a lie.
If you don't believe us,
ask Asha!
The doctor uttered
my name before dying.
Maybe he wanted to absolve me
and hold Rakesh guilty.
You can't mislead us with that
glib talk and hide the truth.
It is clear.
You are the murderer!
You are the killer!
You accuse me of being the killer.
And I say, you are the murderer.
The truth will be known
only after another death.
It's your turn now.
It's your turn next.
Your turn to die!
You die now!
You've come to the wrong place.
This is my room.
Let me stay here.
I'm getting scared.
Is Anand not in his room?
- No.
I went to look for him,
but in the living room...
I can't describe what I saw!
There, the doctor, Dharamdas,
Mr. Sharma's dead bodies...
were staring at me and warning me
that it's my turn now.
Scared of dying, are you?
Life is, in fact,
worse than death.
Drink some...
You will overcome your fear.
I don't drink, Kitty.
- Go on!
You can't live in fear.
Besides, the ones we suspect
end up dead.
But this... it gives you life
even after death.
Drink it.
- No!
You?
- Yes.
How about you?
- Yes, it's me.
There is still
some liquor remaining...
drink that too!
Why don't you drink?
There is very little difference
between you and Kitty now.
You appear to be angry...
Here, take a sip.
Then you won't differentiate
between me and Asha.
You ought to be ashamed to
introduce her to this poison.
And you don't give a damn
even if I die.
I mean nothing to you!
Kitty, this chap, Anand...
he loves me immensely.
But no one knows who he is...
not even me!
You didn't like the
bitter pill, did you?
How can a liar fancy the truth?
Go away, Anand!
I don't need any support!
You will not drink that, I say.
- Why not?
It isn't any more bitter than you are!
I will drink it.
I said you won't!
- I will!
You look upset. You don't appear
to have slept last night?
Kitty has told me about everything
that happened last night.
I think Anand...
- Have you seen Anand?
That's the only thing
left to do.
The rest...
- What are you talking about?
Just that he will
never face us again.
Anand has been proved
to be the murderer.
It can't be anyone else.
I've already warned Kitty
and am warning you too...
not to venture out alone.
- I am already scared.
Kitty is not in her room and
Anand too is missing.
What?
Who's that?
Someone has killed Kitty too!
Not someone... it's Anand.
Look there.
I've been waiting for
that murderer all this while.
But he didn't turn up.
He has killed my Kitty.
Shut up!
And forget Anand.
No one can reach here.
Mr Sharma... you were
supposed to be dead!
No.
My death was a ploy to
mislead others.
When I realised my game as up...
and that Kitty and Anand
suspected me...
I confided in the doctor.
I told him there was only
one way to nail the murderer.
We'll play a ploy to
find the murderer.
I'll injure myself
and you declare me dead.
Since you are a doctor,
everyone will believe you.
Then?
- After I'm declared dead...
I'll try to find
the real culprit.
And thus he proved me dead.
After that,
he was my first victim.
Because I feared he may expose me.
But you are exposed now.
Now that you know the truth,
you won't live for long.
You would have been
dead long ago.
But I had a desire.
I too have a desire, Mr. Sharma.
Inspector Anand. We've been
looking for you for many days.
And we meet today.
Won't you shake hands?
Had I known you were a
C.I. D inspector then...
Perhaps you would've
killed me too?
Had I known you are the
fugitive Madanlal...
had I known you are
a devil in human guise...
I am the Lord of death.
They were destined
to die at my hands.
I know everything. It was Khanna
who got Mr Sohanlal killed...
but you killed not only Khanna,
but his friends too.
You would've been exposed the
day you killed Kitty.
I gave you a chase
and Rakesh chased me.
You played a trick
and escaped.
You caused a smokescreen.
Do you recognise me, inspector?
This is Madanlal.
And she is Asha.
There is only one bullet left.
I don't know where it is lodged.
One bullet for two people!
Let's see who deserves it.
Before challenging me,
you should've thought twice.
I've already committed 6 murders.
This is the seventh.
This gun has only one bullet.
Let's see who between you,
does death favour?
This word doesn't
befit a criminal.
Yes, I am a murderer!
And who compelled me to kill?
Who?
- Mr. Sohanlal...
Khanna and his friends.
We were partners in smuggling.
How is it related to your
being a murderer?
I was arrested once.
In prison, Sohanlal and
Khanna assured me...
that if I admitted
to my crime...
then on release,
I'll get my due share.
But they not only deprived me
of my share...
but raped my
innocent sister too.
She committed suicide.
Now I won't spare you either.
Who informed you of your
sister's suicide in the jail?
My brother did, but before he
could harm Khanna...
Khanna got him also killed.
Khanna was a bastard.
His greed made him kill
Sohanlal too.
You were released from the
jail on the 13th of this month...
when you went to Khanna's
house and killed him.
You are omniscient, inspector.
On the 24th, on the occasion of the
silver jubilee of Princess Club...
you gave the lucky ticketsto five people...
so that as per your plan they'd
board the chartered plane...
to reach the place of their death.
Though they were all
Khanna's people...
but they were strangers
to each other.
But you killed them brutally.
Yes, I tortured them to death.
Society and law could
let them go scot free...
but not me. - No!
You've escaped again.
- But you won't escape, Madanlal.
You may kill both of us,
but there's a third person too.
The butler and his sister?
So you know about it?
- Yes, I do...
about the spirit,
and the mad girl who sings.
She's the butler's siste.
My condition to employ him
was that he came alone.
But he secretly brought his
sister too.
This time too you were saved.
Perhaps the bullet is in
this slot, inspector.
Behold your beloved
one last time.
Maybe you won't get
a second chance.
You are very lucky!
The decision is made now.
You are fated to die firt.
But I'm not heartless.
I'll give you a chance too.
To behold your beloved.
Don't you ever dare
sing that song again!