Satyakam's story is all about truth,
love, conscience and fearlessness
Satyakam, the character in our
ancient texts, The Upanishads...
Approaches Goutam the Guru,
seeking to be his disciple
The Guru asks him,
to which family do you belong?
Satyakam says,
I asked my Mother
My Mother has told me that she has
served many before she begot me
She says, I do not know your
father's name. But I am Jabala
So your name is Satyakam,
the son of Jabala
The sage embraced Satyakam,
and he said...
"You are the true Brahmin,
enlightened because..."
"you have the courage
to speak the truth"
That story was told ages ago.
Now, listen to our story
Many years ago, a young man
set out in quest of God
When he reached the foothills of the
sacred Himalayas, he heard a command
"Upon the path for the quest of truth
you shall find God"
Young Satyanarayan Acharya
settled down in...
A village named Saptaparni, to spread
this word. Here, he set up school
Our story is about this family
of Acharyas
Every heir of the family carried
the name Satya (Truth)
Theirs was a creed founded in principle
and practice on the quest for truth
Not even in their dreams would
they stray from the truth
And no insult for them could be worse,
than being blamed of having lied
One of them Satyapriya,
used to be my class-mate
His mother died in childbirth
His father renounced the worldly life
and went away to become a monk
Grandfather Satyasaran brought up
the orphan lovingly, caringly
I met Satyapriya in
Engineering College
Gradually, I developed
a liking for him
At the hostel, we shared the same room
...and the same dreams
Satyapriya goes back to those days...
In 1946... our country
was still enslaved
Our exams over, we were waiting for
our results. On our last day...
Prof Sen was making
the valedictory speech in the college
You are going to become engineers
Your education, your skills,
aren't merely for making a living
I hope you will use it
as a way of life
In college, you have seen
the Bucker machine
You have seen how the machine
how the machine splices steel
Many a times you will feel
that life is a BUCKER machine...
And you are the steel being spliced.
- Excuse me silt..
Man is not steel. Man is many more
times stronger than steel
I pray to God that you will be able
to prove that
This courage, this confidence is
the greatest wealth of a free nation
And I am certain that our country
will soon be liberated
Will we really get our independence?
- Who can stop us now?
Look around you. The fires of
the revolution are spreading
The Netaji's Indian National Army,
and now the mutiny in the Royal Navy
Didn't you read the newspapers?
The Air Force has come out in support
What are you thinking?
- Naren, we are truly fortunate...
To have been born in such times.
Hunger, unemployment, the black market
It is all coming to an end. The future
belongs to hard work and honesty
I'm moved to tears at the joy of it
I'm going to take up education.
I'll become a professor
You fellows will pass.
I'm on the endless vigil
Naren, whom are you writing to?
- My mother
Send her my greetings.
- Sure. Yes, there's a letter for you
Grandpa?
- Yes. I had written to him asking...
What I should do after graduation.
This must be his reply
So what does he say?
"My blessings be with you.
You want to know what you should do?"
"I reply, I will tell you this canto
from The Gita"
"Only to work, yours is the right
Not the fruit"
"Be free, stay pure, and dedicate
yourself to your work"
"This is my blessing for you"
I'd really like to meet your grandpa.
- Come along
Living in a gurukul (school)
Is an experience in itself
Over there, it's as if,
time has come to a stop
And the last four years
seem to have passed in no time
Now you'll go your way,
and I'll go mine
Sometimes, I wish we both would fail.
- Don't you say that!
God has a fine sense of humor
He has only to say "Let it be done"!
Miracle! I've passed!
Congratulate me too! I passed!
Did you see me on the lists?
- Number 332. Second Class
Damn it! And he?
- First Class Second
Who ranked first?
- Must be Harbhajan
I must tell my mother
Naren, go and get some rest.
I'll take over for some time
I sent Peter to inform my mother
He hasn't returned yet
That heart ailment of hers...
what if she reads the papers?
Excuse me, my name is Pramod Das.
How is my son Sunil?
Yes. Sunil Das
Yes, he's fine.
- Are you lying? I hear he's dead
The name of the person who has died
is Harbhajan Singh
But where's my son, Sunil?
- Take him to Sunil
I've told your mother
- You did?
Yes. But it was such a snafu!
- Why?
I told her that you've just
scratched your head
And she drags me right into
her prayer room...
And she wants me to swear it
by the Gods!
I couldn't even tell her that
I'm Christian
Had I said that, she would've thought
I'm trying to fool her
And you warned me that
she has a heart ailment
So I just shut my eyes tight, and
I touched the feet of your God
That's when she embraced me, and she
started crying. And I was praying...
Holy Mary, Mother of God, forgive me,
but I made a mother happy, didn't I?
Son, I just read about the accident
in the newspapers
Are you hurt too?
- Nothing serious
One of your relatives too?
- Yes. We read someone's dead!
May I look around?
Yes, why not?
- Please be seated
Hurt in the legs?
- Yes, it's very painful
I know, but you must be brave
You have to become an engineer
You must serve the nation
I shall pray to God
for you swift recovery
Hurts?
- Not really. A minor wound
Have you sent word home?
- Yes
It's just a passing phase, son.
Keep this
Cracked that skull?
- Yes
You know, that's a crack hard to fill.
- Yes, but it isn't split wide open
And with your blessings, it will heal.
- Of course it will, son
A leg and an arm too?
But don't you worry.
Everything will be all right
What?
- Do you know who he is?
No.
- Not even from his hair?
Grandpa...?
- Yes
I should've guessed. Family or not,
it makes no difference for him
Naren... hurry up! Come on.
- Why?
I think Harbhajan Singh's parents are
here. I haven't the guts to face them
Come along
Excuse me, I'm Gurnam Singh
...Harbhajan's father
Where's Harbhajan?
What is the matter?
Where is Harbhajan?
Why do you not speak?
Why don't you speak?
Where is my son?
Look at me
Swear this by me,
if God asks you...
Which one of these boys will you
give away to keep your Harbhajan?
Would you have Him take away
another mother's son?
Harbhajan was a good son.
Everyone loved him
My son...!
- That's why God has taken him
Come
What are you doing here all alone?
I've been looking all over for you
You always tell me...
Look up at the sky once a day
and you will know yourself
Not I. Swami Dhruvanand said that
But it makes me afraid.
- Why Naren?
Look, those stars are
full of questions
Still thinking about Harbhajan?
Does life hold a meaning?
- Yes
What?
- Second-hand impressions won't do
Every man must try to find
the meaning for himself
No, I don't think there's
any purpose, any meaning
Harbhajan is gone. Of the rest of us,
who's headed where no one knows
Tomorrow, I'm headed home...
and you, back to your village
And afterwards, what remains
of this friendship, this love?
Why must you think like that?
Wherever we are...
Under these very skies
we shall live...
And we will be as far from
those stars, as we are now
Naren, see those stars over there?
The brightest of them is the "Swati"
Shall I tell you a secret?
- What?
I'm in love with Swati!
I've even told her that...
When I marry, I'll call
my bride Swati. By her
That star beside Swati is "Chitra".
You can have her
All you need to do is look up at them.
And you'll know, we're still friends
Well, what reads the New India?
- The Gita
What a revolution!
These days, they use the book
to swear by
And those who read it are either
recluses or lovelorn souls
Nothing of the sort. I'm neither
a recluse nor am I lovelorn
Then you should settle down.
I have a girl in mind
The kind that poets like Kalidas
would write about
"Lean, like a whip"
"Lips, like ripen pods"
"Eyes, darting like the doe"
"Darting downwards, the navel
and downwards"
"Swaying gently, upwards
from the hips to the breasts"
Need I explain more?
- Oh no
But the verve with which
you describe her beauty...
Gives the impression that the girl
you have in mind isn't for me
Not so much of a century or so ago,
one as high-born as I am...
Could've had one,
even at my age!
Letter for you
Have you told him?
- I was just telling him
What does he have to say?
- He is yet to say
But I have described her,
to profound effect
Certainly profound. But a wedding
will have to be kept in abeyance
Why?
- I've been called for a job interview
Job... what?
- Interview. In Bombay
You have been asked in
Be seated
Mr Shyamsunder, our managing director
First class second?
Why not First class First?
The one who stood first
was a better student
Well said. That's a healthy outlook
Only one thing goes against him.
Lack of experience
Experience will come after he joins
Besides, if not people like us,
who will patronize...
Such capable young men?
- You are right
If you can please us,
we will keep you happy
We wish to send you to America
for further studies
Any reservations about going abroad?
- None at all
Send Chatterjee in
You may join right away
But there's a condition.
- Yes, sir?
You may have to travel.
At 24 hours notice
I have no problems
Mr Chatterjee, this is
Mr Satyapriya Acharya
Project Engineer.
Mr Chatterjee is our overseer
Chatterjee, take him around,
introduce him
The wisdom of appointing someone
without a proper investigation...?
What's there to investigate?
- I have a feeling he's too smart
He'll weather with time
And, we have to finalize everything
at the meeting this evening
How do you expect to find a qualified
engineer at such short notice?
Please don't call me MiSt€ll
My name is Ononto Chatterjee
Anant Chatterjee?
- Only O's. Ononto
Call me Ononto, or just Chatterjee.
- All right, I'll call you Chatterjee
Let's have the papers, Chatterjee.
How about getting to work?
Work? Forgive me, what work?
I've been here all of two months,
and there's no work to do!
How do you spend the time?
- I'm not spending time
It's time that's spending me!
Sir, as a kid...
I used to love writing poems.
I've taken it up again
But I have a feeling that work
is about to start soon enough
But Chatterjee, I can't sit idle
for a whole day
I'm talking months, sir
This evening, we have a meeting
of the Board of Directors
I'd like to introduce you to the
Board members. Please stay back
It's been going on all evening.
Now it's past ten!
They might've forgotten all about you
Where are you going?
- Inside
Don't! In there, they are drinking.
- So what?
This is Prince Vikram Singh
of Bhawanigarh
Mr Acharya is a gold-medallist
On the project, being smart will be
more useful than gold medals
I don't yet know what
I am supposed to do
All you have to do is to conduct
a survey of the Prince's estates
How much land is it?
- Say, a thousand acres
I'll need to take Chatterjee along.
I'll require tools for the survey too
Skip the minor details. Be at the
Victoria Terminus tomorrow evening
We are taking the Calcutta Mail.
- May I know where we are going?
Mr Acharya, you're coming with us.
If we go to hell, you're coming too
Say, any reservations?
- This is not about reservations
But I didn't know of any train
to Hell from the Victoria Terminus
Anyway, Heaven or Hell, please let me
know, so that I can make arrangements
I'm Sujan Mehra. Geologist.
We're headed for Central India
To the State of Bhawanigarh.
We have a paper mill coming up there
Geologist?
- Yes
A geologist is concerned with
what's in the soil, not a paper mill
Anything else for me?
Your Highness! You...?
May I not have a cup of coffee here?
- Why not? Welcome
How is Ranju?
- Fine, thank you
Take care of my guests, will you?
- As you wish, sir
Some celebration...?
- Where?
Those guns...?
- Gun salute. For the Prince
I thought it's for our arrival
How about starting the survey directly?
- No. First, you are to be taken to...
Guest house. The Prince's orders.
- Who's the caretaker there?
Old Rustomjee.
- I had asked for theodolites
Without it, the survey can't be done.
- Don't worry
This is Gurbachan Mehta, the overseen
He will organize everything
All India Radio. Today is
Monday, 30th June, 1947
Last night, Lord Mountbatten
while speaking to...
Pandit Jawaharlal Nehru and
Mohammad Ali Jinnah said that...
India's independence from Britain
will also bring to an end...
The British protectorates in India,
namely the Princely States
During the devolution, the rulers
of the Princely States...
Will have to choose one of the two
incumbent governments
Stop this nonsense!
We have been betrayed!
The British cabinet is meeting
in London today. Till it decides...
To hell with the cabinet meeting.
We have been betrayed!
The other day, Sir Conrad assured me...
- Sir Conrad has no such powers
The Nizam of Hyderabad has
issued a statement...
Dissenting against this decision.
And not only the Nizam
Sarwarpur, Jodhpur, Jaisalmer, Junagadh
and even Kashmir have dissented
Where's the Dewan? Has my emissary
to Sardar Patel returned?
He is still holding talks.
- Talks? Talks, talks and talks!
Over 500 Princely States in India,
comprising a third of the territory!
If we want, we can do more than
just talk, can't we?
Welcome
Be seated, Your Majesty
Go to the site, and start
working immediately
The survey is entirely
your responsibility
Gurbachan Mehta will assist you.
Ask him for whatever you need
I'm returning to Bombay
the day after tomorrow
Hello, Ranju! How have you been?
It's so heartless of Rustomjee
to keep you caged like a bird
The next time I go to Bombay,
I'll take you along
There are so many amusing things
over there... cinema, zoo, museum
Say what Rustomjee?
- Thank you for your kindness
My girl is indeed fortunate
No thank you, I don't want coffee
Mr Shyamsunder, we're going
to the palace
No thank you.
I don't drink coffee
Aren't those rocks strange?
Have you noticed something else?
- What?
We've been surveying for so many days.
But there's no sign of the theodolite
But Rustomjee said that Gurbachan Mehta
is arranging a theodolite
And in the meantime, we're spooning
water out of a sea
All right, if the theodolite doesn't
arrive by tomorrow, we'll stop working
Why tomorrow, sir?
Let's do it today
All right
Pack up and bring the stuff
back to the camp
Whose jeep is that?
Mine
Have you brought the theodolite?
- What this thing is...
Gurbachan doesn't seem to understand.
- Then how are we going to work?
That's why I came to fetch you.
The Prince wants to see you
Good. Now you can clear the matter
Let's go.
- Let me wet my throat, first
I had sent you two bottles.
They are still lying as it is
And I come to know that you haven't
invited the beauties to the camp
How have you been spending your time?
- I'm here to do my work
Work, work and work?
Mr Chatterjee, don't you like...?
You're going nowhere in life!
- One monkey is bad enough
What did you say?
- I said, I don't drink
I see
Why so sad a song, Ranju?
But it was a nice song.
- Your Majesty is kind
But a song like that doesn't
suit your lips
For you, this is the age of hope.
- What have the poor to hope for?
Then find something to hope foll
Look, do you like this?
No, my Lord. For so grand a prize,
does not befit me
Ask me what befits you.
A connoisseur knows a gem
Please forgive me. I am no gem.
A gem is nothing but a stone
My name is Acharya. I have
an appointment with the Prince
Please wait a while
I'll take a tour while
you're waiting
What do you want?
From you, nothing.
- He is our engineer
See me Iateli
- My name is Satyapriya Acharya
May I know who I am talking to?
- Certainly
I am Bansidhar TalWall
I am the Dewan of this State
Glad to have met you
Excuse me sir, no one
is allowed inside
Sir, I have my orders
Where is she?
I'm going to shoot her!
This is my kingdom. I am the King!
And this tart...!
Gentlemen I told you, later
No, I have called them.
Come inside
Have you completed the survey?
- No, I need some equipment
What equipment?
- A theodolite, and...
To hell with "lites"!
First finish the survey
You'll get all that Iateli
- But without it...
I don't want to hear any excuses.
I want the work done
The plans must be ready by Friday
You may leave
Stop all this, and get ready
Let's take the train tonight,
and let's get out of here
Why?
- The situation is delicate
Everything hinges on the conference
on 25th July
Mountbatten has called these regents.
He is deciding about their fate
Why should we run?
- Because, either way, we're dead
Whether they retain their kingdoms
or not. We shouldn't be staying here
Look Chatterjee, I'm not leaving
without completing my assignment
Go back to the camp.
I'll write to Shyamsunder tonight
I'll come tomorrow morning,
after I've met Gurbachan Mehta
Who do you think you are, a fairy?
You see, she won't listen to me.
I'd rather you made her see reason
What's going on?
What reasons do I make her see?
No need for a detailed explanation.
It's just that some people...
Spoil their chances. And there are
those who walk straight into trouble
Tell me, who is the Prince?
A layman?
He wants to make her his Queen!
And not just any Queen.
The Queen of his heart!
She was to be laden with jewels, her
trousseau would be piled with silks
And she is such a fool, that she walks
out on him in a rage!
Have you ever asked her
what she wants?
That's the funniest part!
The princess refuses the prince...
Because she wants to get married!
Like a cat dreaming of prize catch!
Sir, you are a gentleman, and you
surely belong to a reputable family
Did you ever hear of
a whore's daughter getting married?
Silt..
This girl is just too headstrong
Maybe you can break her in?
Rustomjee! Open the door
What kind of a joke is this?
Listen Rustomjee!
Open the door!
What a madcap!
Where's the servant?
He'll open the door, won't he?
But we must do something...
Rustomjee did this on purpose
Tomorrow morning, he will come armed
with his witnesses to open the door
I don't care for myself.
I'm worried about you
After this, you will be considered
unworthy of serving the Prince
Don't cry. I'll climb out
and I'll open the door
No! You might fall down...
If I don't, you will
Come in! I trust you. I won't let you
do something so dangerous!
But...
- About people? I don't care!
Come inside!
Come back in! I implore you
Oh God!
There being no way out,
you should sleep inside
I'll sleep out here.
Go on. It's very late
Why are you sitting on the floor?
- This is where I belong
Lie down on the bed.
- Please don't ask me to do that
Well, who do you have at home?
I have no one
If you don't mind,
may I ask you something?
How is Rustomjee related to you?
My enemy.
- Not even an enemy would do...
What he just did to you
Not his fault.
It's my birth
Forget it. Go to sleep.
It's quite late
She has left
But I'll tell you something.
You are an useless fellow
This morning when I opened the door,
I saw you out here...
And the girl in there.
You aren't man enough
Rustomjee, I did not react last night
because you were drunk
But what you speak now can be called
nothing but sexism
You are right. In your place,
I'd say the same
And if you were in my shoes...
forget it, and don't be angry
Up in the morning, let's be civil
I'm going to Bhopal for a few days,
as the Prince's emissary
I have to be back with the reply
before he returns
In the meantime, I shall leave Ranju
in your care
In my care...?
- Yes. Now I know that...
You are a gentleman.
And taking care of Ranjana...
Is also a part of your duty
to the Prince
Ranjana is his ward
Remember, that for the next
two or maybe three months...
The Prince can still make decrees.
And an order for execution...
Could be made in a trice! Goodbye.
- Excuse me...
May I ask you a question?
- You may ask anything you want
But God knows how much I can answer.
- Why are you ruining her life?
This ruination she is fated for
- What do you mean?
That's a long story
All you need know is,
I knew her mother
She came from a good family.
But as luck would have it...
She eloped with her father's
chauffeur when she was fourteen
Now the daughter is paying
for her mother's deeds
I met her mother suddenly,
a few days before she died
I gave her my word that her daughter
would never have to beg for a living
Tell me, what could be more than
a Prince taking a liking to her?
Why not? Find a suitable boy.
Get her married
You want me to conceal the truth?
- Nowadays, men are educated
There are those of us who care
a damn for castes and classes
Touch your heart and say
you're telling the truth
Yes, why not?
Would you marry her?
Actually, I...
Easier said than done
I should be leaving
Could be, that by the time I return,
Bhawanigarh would not be...
On the map of India, like
so many other principalities
Could also be, that you will
have become so great a man...
That ones like me will have to
take care ere the hat falls down...
When I strain to look up at you!
Farewell!
What's this? Where is the servant?
Why, am I an untouchable?
Untouchable, you are
I cooked your dinner last night.
The servant just served you
I didn't say I won't eat
what you cook
But last night I came to know that
you are an untouchable
Listen... do you know the meaning
of an untouchable?
Someone who is not to be touched.
Last night you stayed in my room...
Untouched, aren't you?
You haven't given me a reply
to my question last night
Question...?
- How is Rustomjee related to you?
Apart from being your enemy...?
- Foster father
Foster father..?
- Why can't he be?
He's forty years older than I am!
- 40 years? How old would he be?
You aren't as simple
as you make out to be
What do you mean?
- I've told you he's 40 years my elder
If I told you his age, you'd know
mine, isn't that so?
I'll tell you. I'm nineteen.
Now you can add up to Rustomjee's
And I know too. You aren't as simple
as you make out to be
Now foster father he is, but why
isn't he getting you married off?
Who would marry a girl like me?
What do I take this for? Boyishness?
Maybe you want me to say
that you are pretty?
No! I'm tired of hearing this.
It's cloying my ears!
I hear every man say this.
Not you...
Why do you count me among them?
- Then why do your people want...
To push me into a hell?
- I never knew all this
Now that you know,
let me see what you do
Silt..
The jeep is here.
- I'm coming
What do you mean? First,
you will eat your breakfast
Sit. I'll drive
Do you eat or do you hog?
Sit in the back.
I'll sit up front
Where are you going?
- Wherever you are going
Meaning?
- You go out every day. Can't I?
I'm not out on a jamboree.
I'm going to work
I know! You are so busy!
But remember what Rustomjee said?
You're supposed
to take care of me
Put the basket in the jeep. Hurry!
He's busy, and he's getting late
What's all this meant for?
- Am I supposed to stay the whole day...
Without a change of clothes?
- In that jungle...
Who will look at your beauty.
- Never mind
I'm taking along the one
who will appreciate
Move it! You are delaying this
We have a working picnic here!
Hey, have you started eating too?
Am I? No. I'm just tasting, Sir
- Sit down and do it, will you?
No Sir Not once. I'm going to eat
for two today
Sit down. Let me brush my teeth
Chatterjee and I will eat together.
You go on
Aren't you eating? I thought we were
sitting down to lunch together
My mother used to say, first feed
someone who isn't greedy...
And you will get to know whether
you have cooked well
Who tells you I'm not greedy?
- One look at you, and I know
I won't mind it if you tell
a small lie
Small lie...?
- Yes. For my sake
Even if you dislike the food, don't you
get up till you've cleaned your plate
Really, it's great! I'm not telling
a lie to please you. It's great!
As for me, without this falsehood
I cannot even touch someone's heart
I see no falsehood in you
You wouldn't know it
I'm putting on. Like my mother
What I saw just now, is that
real self of yours
Solemn, a picture of peace
This is the first time someone
is telling me all this
This is the first time
I've cooked for someone
I cannot explain to you what
this means for a woman
Such joy! But no, I wasn't destined
to be so happy
You're crying... how am I to eat
if you cry?
Writing a letter?
You... welcome
You write a lot of letters?
- Who told you that?
Chatterjee.
- So you've made out as much?
Won't you sit down?
- Who are you writing to?
Home? To your parents?
- I haven't parents
My mother died at childbirth.
My father went away to become a monk
Then you must be lonely?
Lonely? Why? My grandfather
has brought me up
And...
- And there's Dasrath
He took care of me when I was a kid.
- Who else?
Friends. From college
And...
I'm not married.
- Did I ask you that?
Were you writing to your grandfather?
- No. A friend from college. Naren
I haven't had the time to write
to him ever since I came here
Is that why it's such a long letter?
- Yes. We always write to each other...
Whenever we come across
something beautiful in life
And what are you writing to him about?
- So many things
Like...?
- Like the Tungri river...
Its blue waters.
- And...?
And the tall trees, and the air
whistling through it
And...?
- I've written about you too
About me?
- Yes, about your eyes
Ranjana, you wouldn't know
what your eyes remind me of
Of what?
The eyes painted on
the idol of a Goddess
"From his letters I got to know that
Ranjana stayed over for a few days"
"And she carved a placed for herself
in his heart"
"But he was steeling himself"
"Because for him, the dignity of his
family, his grandfather came first"
"But does the heart listen to reason?
And a heart this age..."
"a heart that longs for someone,
a heart that longs to hear..?"
"He got to know that the paper mill
was just a fraud"
"All they wanted were the minerals
buried under the land"
"After the independence, the minerals
were to be nationalized"
Welcome Mr Acharya, we've been
expecting you
We are happy with your performance.
- Yes, you're due for a promotion
Really? I haven't been able to do much
in the absence of the theodolite
I haven't been able to draw up plans.
- We have the plans. Just sign it
Who drew up those plans?
- No one did
We did scale the relevant parts
from the Survey of India
Mr Mehta has done the scaling.
- Why not have Mr Mehta to sign it?
Because the registrar wants
a graduate engineer to sign it
Poor Mehta is just an overseer
You also have to attest
this field work
Looks new, does it?
No need to worry
We'll make it look aged and genuine
I will not take the responsibility
of what I have not done
Don't be childish!
This is a matter of millions!
Find someone else to do the job
What are you saying? How are we to
find someone at such short notice?
There can't be anything wrong with
the Survey of India
What's your reservation?
- You will not understand
Stop being childish, Mr Acharya.
Just a small initial over here
You will leave this room a rich man.
And you will have your promotion
Are you trying to bribe me?
Bribe?
There are a number of other ways
in which that term is expressed
In Delhi, it's called the "dastoori".
In Punjab, it's the "inaam"
In Bihar, the "ijji". The Bengalis
call it "something for a snack"
I don't know what it's called in
Tamil and Telugu
Considering your penchant for honesty,
shall we call it an honorarium?
Keep this
I haven't filled in the amount.
Write what you want
So you refuse to sign?
- Tamil or Telugu, I don't know either
But I guess, in every language,
this is what the answer ought to be
You're an interesting person,
and I think I like you
Not to be abrupt.
Think it over, once again
Mr Talwar, what use wasting time?
Goodbye
You... haven't you gone to bed?
Do you want to say something?
What's going to happen to me?
Am I to die gagged in Bhawanigarh?
You are nineteen.
You are a minor
Why don't you leave this place?
- Where will I go?
Who have I, in this whole wide world?
- You have a grandfather
Rustomjee has told me all about you.
Surely he knows your grandfatheliu?
Surely he does. But he won't tell.
- Why? Why won't he?
The chauffeur my mother
eloped with...
Who... who is he...?
Ruston”ljee. . . ?
Take me away with you.
As your servant!
After you marry, I'll serve
your wife
But I'm not married yet.
Where will I keep you?
With you... wherever you are!
No, this cannot be!
- Why not?
I live with Rustomjee, don't I?
You are a gentleman
But society won't accept this
What has society given me, for me
to live in fear of society?
Besides, I'm an outcast
But I'm not
You are right.
I have made a mistake
I don't even trust myself now
I don't understand.
- Do you trust yourself?
What if I take you in my arms?
- Please, don't psyche me!
Don't!
Not that you trust yourself, either
What if I were to become an animal?
Will you be able to save yourself?
- What if I say that...
I do not wish to be saved?
What if I want to die?
Why will you not be the one?
- Go... go to bed
I will. But don't ever tell me again
that I'm a minor
Come on! Will you come, or won't you?
- I won't!
Come with me!
- No!
Rustomjee, what are you doing?
- Why are you holding Ranju here?
She has come here of her own volition
I'm talking to your boss!
- Enough! I'm his boss. Not you
Sit in the car.
- I won't!
Will you, or won't you?
- Rustomjee!
I'm her boss. Not you.
Come on
She is a minor. You cannot force her
- Don't try your luck
The Prince doesn't know
that Ranjana is here
Else, you would've been dead
in small pieces down the river
Now, are you coming, or aren't you?
You too, mister. The Prince
wants to see you too
I'm not his dog to answer his call
in the middle of the night
Very well
You should've stopped Ms Ranjana.
- On what grounds?
It'd have been better had you gone.
- How come?
Are you forgetting what day it is?
August 1. Whatever Delhi's decision...
Whether it favours him or not...
he's going to take it out on her!
That's why she was hiding here.
Too bad, sir
The innocent girl is going to be
the Prince's prey tonight
Stop talking nonsense!
Chatterjee, forgive me.
- No problem, sir
I know you're angry with yourself
Chatterjee, come on, we're going
to Bhawanigarh
Sill..? You can't do anything now
Leave me!
Where's Ranjana?
She's not feeling well.
She doesn't want to meet anyone
Tell her that I want to see heh
- Forgive me, sir
Rustomjee has told me not to let in
any visitors
Is she in her room?
- Yes
Sir, please don't go in.
- Why?
What is the matter?
All last night she was locked up.
- Where?
Where?
In the Prince's Bahaddur
Ranjana, wait.
- What do you want?
Step out for a moment.
We have a score to settle
What score? Go away.
- Will you come out, or won't you?
What will you do if I don't?
- Don't think I can't do anything
The report that Ranjana's grandfather
lodged with the police...
Is still in their records. And I know
who the chauffeur was...
And where he is right now.
- So you have come to blackmail me?
For someone who has always done
the wrong things all his life...
What else can you think?
I'm giving you this chance to atone
I'm taking Ranjana into my custody.
Let me take her away with me
Do you propose to marry her?
I cannot
But I will have her married to
someone who is broad-minded
And till that happens, Ranjana stays
with me. Yes? Give me a reply
Take it from me. No use talking
to him about it
As for me, I'm unwilling.
- Ranju is right
If you won't marry her, why talk of
getting her married to someone else?
An woman whom a man keeps in his
custody without marrying heh..
Is called a mistress.
Yes, a slave
If I have to be someone's mistress,
why yours? Why not the Prince's?
I'm telling you the truth.
You come from a good family
Why get involved with this filth?
For the sake of a whore's daughter?
Let her go to the dogs
Ranjana, I will marry you
Ye s
Rustomjee, I will marry Ranjana
Are you in your senses?
- Very much
Despite whatever happened last night?
- Yes
If this is what you had in mind,
why did you not tell me last night?
Why did you not stop her?
- Call it my foolishness
And she has suffered for it
Not I, only you can give him a reply
Lord be my witness, I have loved you
like my own daughter
But I am so helpless!
If you marry her, I don't care
what the Prince does to me
But you must swear to perform
the marriage according to the rites
I swear
No, this cannot be.
No, not this marriage!
Did you not hear? I am sworn.
- Forgive. Now, this can never be
Look at me... look up
In my family, do you know
when a man touches a woman?
Only when she is his wife
Yes, from this day,
you are my wife
Finally, comes the day
the whole country has waited for
1947. August 15
The country cast aside the shackles
that held her slave for centuries
In free air, we breathed
And the promise was to put an end
to hunger, unemployment...
Profiteering and the black markets
Now began a new era
of industrialization
Those of us who were educated,
spread out all over to achieve it
My uncle recommended me to a job
with the government
Peter left for Agartala.
Kohli went to Mysore
I always kept abreast of everyone.
The only one of whom I had no news...
Was Satyapriya. All I got to know
is that he was always between jobs
After about three years,
I suddenly met him
Or rather, it was he who spotted me
What are you doing here?
- I spotted you first
What are you doing in my territory?
- Your kingdom, is it?!
I was here in the matter
of a development program
What are you doing here?
- Building a bridge
I'm a working partner
in Shah & Mehta
But you're strange! Not a letter
in three years!
Where you are, what you are doing...
the last was that letter from...
What's-it-called Bhawani...
- Troubled years
Why don't you take the train
this evening? Come home
Your sister-in-law will be pleased
to meet you
Sure
Sister-in-law? Whose?
You rs
Whose wife?
- Mine
You got married and you didn't
inform me?
I did it in a hurry. Come home,
I'll tell you everything
Hey listen! This is my friend Naren
Coming
How many years has it been?
- Three years
Incredible! Even after three years
of marriage...
The wife rushes out at the sound
of her husband driving his jeep?!
Smart alec,
come, let me show you my bridge
There. Bridge over River Chanda.
- What's the type?
Cantileveli
- What's the length?
Won't you give me a cup of tea?
- She's coming with the tea
How does she know I want tea?
- It's meant for me
For you?
- Yes
Since when did you start drinking tea?
- I even smoke cigarettes
Improving!
Hello
This is Naren.
My dearest friend
My wife, Ranjana
No, her name isn't Ranjana
We decided about your name long ago.
Your name is Swati
You still remember it?
- Tell me, what news of Chitra?
Yes, Chitra.
- Has she dawned in your skies?
Luckily not
Bring him here
The baby...?
- Mine
One minute...
Tea, cigarettes, wife, and kid!
Any more surprises?
How many surprises can a man take
in a day?
Boy or girl?
- Take a closer look
Boy!
Hi kid! Do you know who I am?
I'm your uncle
And I know your Dad far better
than you know him
I'm your father's best friend!
Were he able to speak,
he'd ask you...
What kind of friend doesn't show up
in three years?
Don't you teach him how to pick
a fight. Let him learn in his time
Someday, he's going to become
a very renowned man
Are you an astrologer too?
- No need to be one
He looks just like his father
The same face
I'm glad I met you
It was just like the good old days
Oh yes, how's Grandpa?
- Fine. He keeps to his school
He has cut off all relationships
with me
Cut off...?
- He couldn't accept Ranjana
Why did you have to tell Grandpa
everything about Ranjana?
Ranjana said that too
But you missed something
Had I concealed the facts,
not only would I have lied...
I'd also deceive my grandfather.
- But something so harsh...?
Something that hurts someone?
Do you still call it a truth?
Cowards would say that, Naren
If one has the courage to bear
with the truth...
One must also have the guts to
speak it, unhappy as it may be
Truth is like the burning coal
You cannot expect it not to hurt you
when you hold it in your hands
Had Grandpa seen your son,
I don't think he'd be so harsh
You want to hear the whole story?
After marrying Ranjana, I decided to
meet Grandpa, and tell him everything
When we reached, Grandpa was sitting
outside the temple, reading a book
Grandpa
Who?
Satyapriya
You...?
What happened?
Why are you standing outside?
Why don't you come in?
Wait...
- Who are you, my child?
Who is this girl?
- My wife
Your wife? You're married?
- It's been eight months
Why didn't you let her touch my feet?
- I'm aware of my family's honor
I do not know whether you will
accept her
Why, what is the matter?
She doesn't know who her father was
And you...
You married a woman like this?
A baby?
- My son
But you just said that you married her
eight months ago!
So you were forced to marry
to cover up for your sins?
This sin I have never committed
It is my son.
But not born of me
You...? One who was born into
a family of preceptors...!
Good of you not to have entered
For not desecrating this house of
fourteen generations, I thank you!
After that, Grandpa refused to accept
the money I used to send him
I didn't understand something.
You said...
"It is my son.
But not born of me"
Simple. On the night of August 1...
The Prince raped Ranjana
Ranju? Come
What is the matter?
Do you want to say something?
Say it
You must be very unhappy.
- About what?
Naren's remark... about how
Kabul resembles you
Looks like you are unhappy.
- Yes! The sorrow is mine!
All my life I have burdened
people with my sins
How are you to blame?
- Yet, I'm suffering for it!
Ranjana, have I ever said anything
to hurt you?
Is that all? Is there no more
to be desired
No more to be desired of life?
Every time you try to come near me...
Every time you want to take me
in your arms, do I not know...
Who stands between us?
Can't I understand what it is?
I want to forget the past. But...
Forget it. You know I love you
Oh, that's just why!
Sometimes I wish I'd kill myself!
And be born again, anew. For you
Have the coolies been paid?
- No sir
Why?
- Our bills are pending
How are the coolies to blame for it?
You've rubbed the government officials
the wrong way
You didn't go to the project engineer's
house on his daughter's birthday
Nor did you let us send any gifts.
- What has that to do with our bills?
Cause and effect sir,
beg your pardon
It's still not beyond repair.
If the graft is settled...
It'll be smooth sailing.
- Come with me
I'm lucky indeed! Mr Acharya himself!
In my office!
Why aren't our bills being cleared?
- First, be seated. Please
Why haven't our bills been cleared?
- The Assistant Engineer wants...
To discuss something personal.
- What do you mean personal?
We have sent the bills.
And we insist upon a reply
Ask why the bills haven't been passed.
- Very well
Please type out a letter
According to terms of the contract,
we can stop work immediately
If need be, I'll meet
the district engineer too
The bill is ready for payment.
If you wish...
The decision can be taken
today itself! But...
What is it?
- A matter of transaction
Please meet the engineer.
Everything will be settled
I have drawn up the bills myself.
And they have been audited
There can be nothing wrong
with the bill
Not that there is, sir
Just a matter of transaction
Some adjustments, maybe. It could
also be a matter of interpretation
That means, you will not pay?
- You are wise. You can understand
Tell the Assistant Engineer that unless
the bills are paid in two days...
I will approach the highest authorities
Only God is the highest authority!
Mr Acharya, only God can save you!
Mr Acharya...
What is the matter, Mr Mehta?
- Apocalypse!
The minister has come here.
We have been summoned!
No need to get alarmed. I know.
- You do?
I wrote to him asking him to come oven
- Goodness!
You wrote to him? But why?
The contractor building the bridge
and his engineer are here
Send them in. Please wait outside
Please be seated
I have received your letter
You seem to have a complaint
But there is no mention of
the nature of the complaint
Some things can't be put in writing.
That is why I wanted to see you
Very well. Go on
No need to be apprehensive.
Tell me the truth
Why are you laughing?
Nowadays, one is apprehensive
about telling the truth
But I've never hesitated to tell
the truth. Nor will I ever
The fact is that I can complete
the works ahead of the schedule
But the officials here,
are causing hurdles
What do you mean?
- They aren't paying my bills
Why?
- The assistant engineer wants a bribe
Why have you not spoken about this
to the district engineer?
He wants expects a bribe too.
- There are those superior to him too
You happen to be the supreme authority.
That's why I am telling you
Let us see what you can do
Very well, put down the names
of the persons against whom...
You have this complaint.
- They don't take bribes in writing
How am I to give you their names
in writing?
Are you aware of the implications
of bringing so a serious complaint...
Against senior government officials
without any evidence?
Even I might be forced
to take action against you
Then do it!
Then you will have to answer
my lawyer in court
Sir, you see the matter is...
- You may leave too
Mr Acharya, do you realise
whom you have spoken to?
Ye s
Please come to my office
Is this any way to behave
with such a senior person?
How else is the truth to be spoken?
- Independence doesn't mean...
That you may talk to a minister
like this
A minister is a public representative.
He ought to take care...
Of public interests.
- My interests come before that!
I've invested 300,000! Am I to be
black-listed for your sake?
You will have to apologise
to him right now
What did you say? Apologise?
- Yes, apologise!
Or would you rather have me ruined?
- Not at all
Please decide your course of action
after we have parted ways
What do you mean?
- While joining, I had told you...
That there are several things
I won't do
Apologizing is one thing I won't do.
- He's mad! Completely mad!
You...?
Yes son, I have something to tell you.
- Yes, go on
First, please do not mind me
if I am being informal
You are old enough to be my son.
- Why should I mind that?
Son, in life you will suffer much,
and you will have to tolerate much
But for us, this suffering that you
will go through, is our last hope
On this hope, much of our future
is tied
I don't know whether I'm worthy enough
to give you my blessings
But being your elder,
I shall pray that...
God gives you this courage. Always
"The stubborn streak continued"
"He got several jobs"
"But everywhere, it was his obsession
with the truth that was the hurdle"
"He could never stick to a job.
He never planted his feet"
"In his letters, it was as if
he was taking on the whole world"
"Sometimes I felt he was also
fighting against himself"
"Once, he caught someone
accepting a bribe"
Forgive me, sir! I have committed
a grave crime! I won't do it again
I beg of you, sir!
- Aren't you ashamed to say this?
As of now, I am suspending him.
Please investigate the case
I swear by God! I'm in trouble!
Just come home, and see for yourself
If you sack me, I will
have to kill myself!
What could be worse than a citizen of
an independent country taking bribes?
Should be ashamed!
Forget it, Mr Binay.
You know what he's like
He has come
Listen... she has come to see you.
She's Mr Binay's wife
You seem to have suspended...
- She should not have come here
Forgive me, I can do nothing
in this case
My son has been sick for ten days!
There's no medicine for him. We don't
even have money to pay for food
The doctor has prescribed
so many medicines
And we don't have a penny!
- That gives no one the right...
To take bribes. The wages of sin
one has to pay. I can do nothing
May I ask you something?
I accept that...
He has committed a crime. But we are
neighbours in this community
We are supposed to share
Yet, you don't even know that my son
is dying for lack of medicines!
Can you escape that?
I cannot
A child dies a slow death
for lack of medicines
Have our social peers
no responsibility?
So how do you punish yourself
for this? Is the peer penalized?
You cannot do anything to him,
because he is your peer
But you can punish my husband.
Because before you, he is powerless
And you have the power. But is this
what power ought to be used for?
This is all I ask you
Mr Supervisor. . .
Who is it?
- I'm Acharya
Silt.. you?
- Yes, please come to the office
At this hour?
- Have you sent Mr Binay's file...
To the head office?
- I'll post it tomorrow morning
Please give me the letter
- All right
Instead, please send this letter
What's this? Are you resigning?
Yes.
- But why?
I cannot explain this to you
The duty to foster precedes
the right to punish
But my position compels me to punish
But who am I punishing?
An innocent child, who is dying for
lack of medicines? Or that woman...
But how are they to blame?
I don't understand...
I'd rather punish myself
Goodbye
"He writes fewer letters now"
"Once, maybe twice in a yeah
From what little I make out...
From his letters, and from what
I got to know from the others..."
"he's going through hard times"
"The very reason why
I'm going places..."
"is the same reason why Satyapriya
is going nowhere"
"The unwillinness to com romise
1 to ignore small irritants"
"One day, my wife and I had
just returned after shopping..."
Wait! Is this a dream?
This is a nightmare
Where have you been so long?
He's the one who made a star out of you
...the fellow who named you "Chitra"
This is Satyapriya
Hello
How long have you been here?
- About an hour and a half
Had I known you were coming,
I would've stayed at home
I'll make you a cup of tea.
- No thanks. I've had a cold drink
Keep these upstairs
Let's go and sit over there
First of all, where have you been
all these years?
Where are you working?
How is your wife? How is Kabul?
They are in Janakpuli
And I...
Nowadays, I'm unemployed.
- Why did you quit this job?
It's just as easy to explain it,
as it's difficult
Why don't you say, you're footloose?
You don't want to stick to a place
You think I don't want to?
- What else?
Am I the one who's going out
of my mind...
Or has the world changed so much?
I can't quite make out
Remember those dreams we dreamt
before independence?
We were proud to be fighting
against the British
But today, we're fighting
with each other
Good and bad have always been.
But now it looks like...
The competition is all about
how evil who can become
In the last job, when I stood up
for the truth...
They implicated me for theft.
For a year and a half...
I fought the casein courts.
In the end, I did win
But it cost me even
my wife's jewellery
All around us, everything
is rotting away
There's no morality, no honesty
I feel like whipping everyone
in sight!
Don't let that temper consume you
The problem is with our social system,
the entire machinery
Just the system and the machinery?
Are we not guilty too?
As citizens, haven't we any duty
towards the country?
Blaming others for our woes
is becoming our racial trait
The truth of it is that 200 years
of slavery has changed us completely
I agree you're right.
But what can you alone do?
No! I'm not alone. Had I been,
I still would've done the same
But you're the one who stands to lose,
isn't that so?
Would it not be a greater loss, were I
to have lost myself in the quagmire?
But in life, one makes compromises.
- No! I won't!
Never! I am human! Created by God
in his own image
I represent Him. I shall never accept
what is wrong. Never!
What happened?
Not to be alarmed. I was just giving
him a lecture after all these years
Now, shall we stop it?
Oh, but I must be leaving?
- Won't you stay back for dinner?
Excuse me, I must take the train
to Janakpur tonight
Very soon, I'm going to give you
a very big surprise
What surprise?
- You ass...
Forgive me
What surprise would it be,
if I told you?
Nothing about you
can surprise me anymore
Wait and watch. Bye
Goodbye lady.
- I'll see him off
When did you start getting formal?
Relax, I can make it on my own
"Not in my dreams could I have
imagined the surprise he'd spring"
"I was transferred to a new division.
As a Divisional Engineer"
Welcome, sir! I am your clerk.
We are very happy to have you here
I'm delighted to see someone as young
as you are in this position
How long have you been working here?
- Nearly 20 years now
20 years! Then I will have to take
a lot of help from you
There aren't too many problems
in this Division
Only the new road to Radharangpur
...there's a bit of litigation
Yes, I'm aware. It's nothing serious.
- A new hassle has just cropped up...
At Nupurpur.. some 40 miles from here.
There's a new Assistant Engineer there
Problems have been cropping up
ever since he took charge
Problems?
- At every step, he cites rules
He has picked fights with everyone.
One day he came here...
And he gave us a big lecture.
- New recruit?
New, yes. But he's an old warhorse.
- What's his name?
Some "Acharya"
What name did you say?
- Satyapriya Acharya
No Mr Ladia, I cannot approve
this building
But Mr Acharya, the work
is nearing completion
And your predecessor gave his approval.
- He made a mistake. I will not
Well, every man has his own style
of working
And my duty is to keep you happy
What are you doing?
I ordered the tea for you!
Why are you paying?
For a government servant on duty
to have tea at your expense...
Goodbye, Mr Ladia
Smart alec, isn't he?
A thousand or two won't do for him
Every man has his price. And this one
has to be taken care of
He's the one who's sitting on
my supplementary bill for 52,000
It's going to be very tough. I hear
he's a scoundrel of the first order
Doesn't take bribes
Where's Mr Acharya?
- Out on inspection, sir
He should be back anytime now.
- Does he live here alone?
No. His family is here too.
They have put up on the first floor
Please tell Mrs Acharya that
I'm here to see her Naren Sharma
Very well, sir
Please also tell her that
I'm in dire need of a cup of tea
Very well, sir
Sir, the Divisional Engineer is here
You...!
Cut the crap, and have a cigarette
I jumped when I heard about you
But why have you taken up this job?
What's this?
Stop chewing my ears!
- You are my boss
Friends, first.
- Sure. Outside office. Over here...
How long ago did this hack begin?
Have you consulted a doctor?
I did. He says, consult a specialist.
- Why haven't you seen a specialist?
I haven't found the time.
I will, as soon as I get time
The lady has invited you upstairs
for tea
Thank you, I'm going
Come, let's have tea together
- I have work to do
Clear up fast, and come up
Sister-in-law...
Hello!
- Hello, brother
He has become a big boy!
Lady, you don't look like his motheli
You look like his sister!
Kabul, this is your uncle.
- God bless you, son
Kabul? Is that a nice name for
a boy as smart as he is?
Son, you go and play. And you head
straight for the playgrounds
Don't go to the office
and disturb your father
All right. You call him
a brother, don't you?
Yes, son.
- Then he's my mother's brother!
To your father, I'm more of a brother
than I am to your mother
Go on, son
Please come in
What's this? Are you coming,
or are you going?
I haven't had the time to unpack.
Now where are you going to sit?
We don't even have a chair.
- I'll have one brought upstairs
No! Don't do that!
Please... sit here
What is the matter?
Yesterday, folks from the neighbourhood
dropped in to pay a visit
The orderly brought up some chairs
from the office
He screamed at him. Poor fellow,
he broke out into a cold sweat
He says it's government property,
not meant to be used at home
Good old Satya. Pure gold.
- Pure, yes
But you can't craft jewellery
out of pure gold
You have to add alloys...
some impurities
No one can tolerate an official
who is as honest
At every step, he picks fights.
He has earned everyone's displeasure
That's why he can't stick
to any job
Worse, he has been picking fights
even with the radio
With the radio?
- Yes
It makes me feel like crying.
But you might laugh at it
Whenever there's an announcement
of so much of money allocated...
To such-and-such a plan,
he starts cribbing about...
Who's going to pocket how much.
As if the radio is listening
He goes on talking to the radio
How long will this go on?
These days, I'm scared
We've no one else in this
whole wide world
Don't say that. I'm not dead, am I?
I came over as soon as I was told...
That Satya is here.
- There's no end to this conversation
Tell me, how's my sister Chitra?
Chitra...? Well, she's fine
But nowadays, I don't get one bit
of her attention
Why?
- Ever since she had our daughter...
She thinks she has achieved
the greatest thing in life!
All day, she's in a trance!
- Are you jealous of your daughter?
Yes, a little jealous. But I've found
a way to get even with heh..
Provided you help me.
- How can I...?
It just occurred to me
You know, I can't bring myself
to say this... oh, but I must
Then just say it.
- You can take my daughter
I...?
- No, not so soon
Maybe after 17 years or so,
if you don't mind it...
Maybe Kabul could marry her?
Now, not to be so apprehensive.
She isn't ugly, you know
And I'm not saying this just because
I'm the father Others say that too
She's a beauty.
And ours is a reputed family
That's just why.
- What do you mean?
Reputation
Let's not discuss all this
I understand
What?
What do you understand?
Satya is the dearest of my friends.
The bond we share...
Is stronger than ties of blood.
He has told me everything
About you
About Kabul too
Don't look at me like that!
Don't belittle me
I love Satya and I love his family too
Now that I know all this,
I respect him all the more
To seal this friendship,
for the sake of my own honour..
I am begging you
I was expecting a hot cup of tea
And you've started crying
This is ridiculous!
- I'll make tea for you
Be seated.
- All right
While you make tea, I'll go down
and fetch him
No! He will not come upstairs now.
- Why not? I'm seeing him after ages!
I'm telling you. He won't leave
his office before five-thirty
Even his boss will!
I'll drag him up here
For all that posturing in front of you,
he can't act tough with me
I'll get him
Come up. Tea is ready.
We're going to have a long chat
Sorry, I have work to do.
- I know how much work there is
Putting a few things off isn't
going to rock the world. Come
Excuse me.
- Look, I'm the boss, you agree?
Now I'm ordering you. Come on.
- I don't take wrong orders
I live by my principles
I know, honesty is the best policy.
- Then what you know is wrong, sir
As far a policy goes, not honesty,
but dishonesty is the best policy
Honesty is no policy.
Honesty is a religion
So you won't come up?
Not until the office has closed
for the day
Brother. . .
Excuse me, sister-in-law.
Let's have tea some other day
He's expecting you
Come in
I apologise for disturbing you
again and again
We cannot do anything about your
supplementary bill for 52,000...
Until Mr Acharya has validated it.
- I'm not here for the bill, Mr Sharma
All I want to say is that
Mr Acharya's attitude...
Is making it very difficult
for us to work here
Why, what happened?
- The culvert at Sharanpuli..
Has been completed
as per specifications
He is stopping the payment
on a strange pretext
Strange pretext?
- Yes
He says we haven't paid
the laborers
I ask you, how is your department
concerned with that?
Mr Acharya is coming here.
Let me ask him
By all means. But Mr Sharma, unless
my bills are paid in 3 or 4 days...
I will be forced to move
the higher authorities
If need be, I will even
go to court
I told you, he's coming.
Let me ask him
If you still insist on taking action,
suit yourself
Sit down
Please excuse us
I'm going on a month's leave
I was told on the telephone that you
want to discuss something important
You see, I'm not going to be here.
Someone else will officiate
And you might find
the going tough...
Because lots of people here
have a lot to complain against you
May I know the reason?
- Not one. Several
For one, you wouldn't even let
your own staffers use...
Tarpaulins and tins for a festival.
- I cannot permit the use of...
Government property
for private purposes
But this is an age-old practice.
- Something that is wrong...
Cannot be allowed to go on forever
- But one has to make compromises
Do you know the meaning of compromise?
Compromise is a synonym for corruption
A word meant for cowards. Sir please,
not to give me this kind of advice
I was just talking as a friend
Now I know. And I won't regret this
As your superior, may I know why
Ladia's bills haven't been paid yet?
I have sent a detailed note.
You will receive it by tomorrow
I hear the bills
haven't been paid because...
Mr Ladia hasn't paid his laborers.
- What you have heard is correct
How are we concerned with his affairs?
- We are. Very deeply concerned
Wrong! All that concerns us
is whether or not...
The contractor has met
our specifications
For us, nothing else matters.
- Maybe not for you
But to me, it matters
A government official doesn't have
anything to do with that
Official or otherwise, one is first
a human being. I am human too
I will voice concern, whenever I see
any wrong done
If the laborers have grievances
against him, they can go to court
That creed of the nation,
"Let Truth Prevail"
that you use to adorn the wall,
is also the creed...
You exhort your children to follow.
Cross your heart and tell me truly...
Those laborers who toil every day
for nothing more than a mouthful...
Can they ever go to court?
Can they pay lawyers?
Can they fight court cases for years
against these millionaires?
Cross your heart and tell me!
- What do you mean to say?
Despite the fairness
and the impartiality...
Our courts are beyond the reach
of the poor
Try to understand. Please!
Mr Ladia is no small fry
If you try to use every opportunity
to pick fights with him...
Sir, I have a lot of work to do
Listen. . .
As the Divisional Engineer,
I will have to pay the bills
Yes sir, as you please.
Mr Ladia is no small fry
You have to take tough decisions.
- How can I?
What Acharya says is a fact too.
Had he been an official with...
The Central Public Works Department,
he could've stopped payment...
For defaulting on wage payments.
But the state laws are different
And it leaves much to be desired.
- Law as it stands, we must abide by
What's right and What's wrong
isn't for us to question
That's exactly what I told him
Sir, Acharya is an old friend of mine.
And I respect him a lot
It's his honesty and his integrity
that pits him against everyone
But what can I do?
I have to run my show
Sir, please transfer me elsewhere.
Tackling him is tough for me
Aren't you going on leave tomorrow?
Go on. Leave it to me,
I'll talk to Acharya
"In Kashmir, that pristine beauty,
made me forget all else"
"That one month, I lived
in a state of bliss"
"I forgot all about my office
and Satya"
"And in no time,
a month was over"
Hello!
- Hello! Did you enjoy your holiday?
Very much. What's new here?
- Only one news
That Mr Acharya... he fought with you
before you went on leave
He had a big fight with
the Chief Engineer
He might have to resign
He has been asked to go on leave
for three months
Where is Mr Acharya?
- They left yesterday
Where to?
- I asked him repeatedly
But he refused to tell me.
As of now, I'm officiating
Sir, you have come a long way.
Do have a cup of tea before you leave
I'll ask someone upstairs
to make a cup of tea for you
Thank you, some other time
Someone wants to meet you.
- What for?
He didn't say that.
But he says it's important
He says he has news
of a friend of yours
Friend...? What name did he say?
- He didn't say his name
Send him in
Hello, Sir
- Please be seated
I'm Ononto Chatterjee. Your friend
Mr Acharya has sent me
Who... Satya? Where is he?
He is in hospital
What happened? Some accident?
He's suffering from cancer
I won't hide it from you.
He has no chances of surviving
I had gone to the hospital
visiting someone else I know
I saw Mr Acharya lying there.
He has sent me to you
He says, you're his best friend
Are you crying, sir?
The best of people in our times
have died of cancer too
Mr Acharya is also a great man
Where are Mrs Acharya and their son?
They are putting up with
a surgeon... one Mr Ladia
Who...?
A contractor Mr Ladia.
He's taking care of them
Please come with me
Excuse me... where's number nine?
- Over there
You...?
Come, sit down. Look at me, I've got
one of those glamorous diseases
Don't you talk to me! You didn't
inform me where you are. On purpose!
You did all this to punish me!
- Rascal, is this any time to fight?
Let's talk all we have to.
You won't get another chance
What nonsense!
- That's right
Don't you see what state I'm in?
- I know. But you're talking nonsense!
In today's world, what disease
can't be cured?
Just a few days ago, I was reading
about these new cures for cancer
After all these years with me, are you
still afraid to face the truth?
Was this disease ever cured?
Where's your wife?
- She should be here in sometime
I sent her away to eat lunch.
All day, she sits here
At nights, Chatterjee has to
practically push her out
He spends the nights with me
Naren, what is to happen
to these people...?
Who is to take care of
Kabul and Ranjana?
I'm here! Don't you worry
a bit about them
I don't even have the strength left
to think
Daddy!
Hello Uncle!
- Hello
Hello...
- How are you?
Fine.
- How is Chitra?
Fine. Please let me have a word
with Mr Ladia
I'll be back soon
So how is school going on?
- Daddy, when are you coming home?
I don't like studying without you.
Why?
- No one teaches me
But Mummy teach to you, doesn't she?
- All day, Mummy only cries
I am very apprehensive when
I think about their future
Mr Acharya has no insurance,
nor does he have any money
They are in dire straits.
I had to use the excuse that...
The hospital is close to my residence,
to make Mrs Acharya put up with me
I had such a tough time getting
Mr Acharya to agree...
To come to the hospital
Mr Ladia, I had a very wrong perception
of you. Please forgive me
Not to be apologetic.
We all make these mistakes
Judging a man by outward appearances
is a difficult proposition
Mrs Acharya, I have something
important to discuss with you
Surely, you are wise enough
to understand everything
Considering his condition... what
have you thought of yourself?
What am I to think?
- There's much to think over
You have to bring up Kabul.
You have a whole life ahead of you
I wouldn't have raised this topic had
I not admired you for your courage
I know, this is no time
to discuss all this
But no use giving up a chance
that comes your way
What...?
You may have noticed
the laundry downstairs
The owner died some two years ago.
An old servant looks after the laundry
The owner's widow want to sell
the laundry and move out
I thought about you
when I heard of it
Why don't you buy it?
- I...?
Yes, you needn't do much.
The old man is quite honest
He could run the show, and you'd
make maybe 300 or 400 every month
Besides, the laundry is going
quite cheap. 25,000 maybe
Where would I find so much money?
I have it worked out.
I'll let you have the money
Are you wondering why I'd give you
so much money?
This is a bit delicate.
Please give me a patient hearing
Mr Acharya knows what this is about.
It's a supplementary bill
A bill he had blocked. If he signs this
paper without mentioning the date...
I stand to make a sizable amount.
Sparing 25,000 won't be a problem
How could you dare to mention this?
Is this why you made the gesture...
Of taking us in?
- Not to be annoyed, Mrs Acharya
If you mind it so much...
- What do you mean?
Is this not a wrong thing to do?
Let me answer your questions
one by one
Yes, in that gesture of taking you in,
there was also a certain selfishness
But let me assure you that despite
I would've helped you...
In such a time of crisis.
- It's best not to discuss this
Best? In whose interests?
Kabul's...? Yours...?
Mrs Acharya, I have seen life.
I've been through it all
I'll tell you, from my experience...
- Thank you for your sympathies
But there are still those who would
help me without any selfish interest
Mr Sharma, maybe? No doubt, he will
help you a lot. But for how long?
Do you expect this sympathy
to last forever?
Or, would it befit you to be
supported by him all your life?
This is a considered opinion.
I'm as much on your side as mine
Keep it with you. Show it to him.
If he dislikes it, tear it up
I will not raise this topic with you
ever again
Your wife isn't here as yet...?
- By now, she's normally here
Please be seated.
- Not today
We were on our way here when her sister
turned up. She's sitting in the car
How have you been?
- I'm all right
I'm just worried about
Ranjana and Kabul
Not again! How many times have I to
tell you? We'll share what little...
We have. I'll talk to Ranjana
right away about coming in with us
I'll be back after I see them off.
I'll also call up Mr Ladia
Let's find out why
they aren't here yet
Were you talking about bringing
them over to live with us?
Yes, why?
- You should ask your mother at least
Why? Satya is my best friend,
and he is in trouble
What's wrong if his wife
comes to live with us?
Why don't you understand? You know
how religious your mother is
If she comes to know about Ranjana,
she's going to boycott us
That's true... but...
- We must think it oven..
Before we bring them home.
Let them stay where they are
Of course, you can send them money
every month
In the situation that they are in,
the money would be useful
Let's talk about it later
What happened, Ranjana?
You're late today
Has Kabul not come?
- I didn't bring him along today
Naren and his wife just left.
- I know
Why did you have to tell them
all that? Naren! Naren!
How is Naren related to us?
- What is the matter with you?
After being through so much in life,
you still don't understand?
You think it's all so easy?
Irrespective of what Naren thinks...
His wife and his mother are there too.
Why should they bear our burdens?
You wouldn't like to hear what
I just heard them say
Do you want to know what the truth is?
- What have you heard?
Forget it. Are false hopes all we have
to fall upon to live life?
I carried this paper just to
tear it up in front of you
But now I think, we have
no other option
Where did you get this?
Who gave you this?
Mr Ladia
He has promised to give me 25,000
if you sign this
But wouldn't that be doing a sin?
I ask you, for all your virtuosity...
What have you got out of it? Have you
ever been happy, even for a day?
Forget being happy, tell me,
how am I to bring up Kabul?
On the very streets where you walked
with your head held high...
Would you have me beg? Do you want me
to live off your friends' charities...
To live off scraps thrown at if they
like it, and none if they won't?
Better than this,
was my mother's calling
Do you want me to take that up
for a living, for Kabul's sake?
What if Kabul were your own son?
Hurry up!
- What is the matter?
Chatterjee had called me.
I'm coming directly from the hospital
What's the matter? Tell me the truth.
- What we feared worst
He has vomited blood.
He can't speak now
I'm coming too
Hurry up, will you?
There's very little time
Please inform his grandfather.
- Why him? He has disowned Satya
And why make him grieve at this age?
- He must
Who else will perform the last rites?
Who else can light his pyre?
Kabul isn't his!
Mr Ladia, I'm taking her
to the hospital
Kindly send cable Satya's grandfather
Ask him to come immediately
Also state the reason. His address is
Satyasharan Acharya, Saptaparni, UP
Do you want to say something?
You did it! For my sake!
No! I won't let this happen!
I won't let this happen! Ever!
You knew I'd tear it up
Didn't you?
His grandfather hasn't arrived yet.
I don't know what's taking time
Chatterjee is at the railway station.
Maybe... he doesn't recognise him?
God! One last meeting...!
He vomited blood again
There he is!
Who are you, son?
- Satya's friend. Naren
Tell me the truth, son.
Is Satyapriya...?
I cannot lie to you.
It's just a matter of hours
He stopped talking yesterday
You mustn't lose courage. Maybe he
has lived so long just to meet you
I have not lost courage.
I just remember the day he was born
Come
Grandpa is here
Do you hear me?
Satya, look Grandpa is here
Yes Satya, Grandpa is here
So you fought with me that day and
you walked out on me, didn't you?
I couldn't even scold you
to my heart's content that day
Now that you can't talk back to me,
I think I'm going to give it to you
Are you crying?
Why are you crying?
I know. Because we're meeting for
the first time after that fight?
What else could we do? This is the way
God wrote our destinies
You were to have lived your life by
your convictions and your principles
And I was to bound
to the honor of my family
The clash was inevitable
Are you afraid, son?
Of course, you have nothing to fear
For you know that you are entering
a life of eternal bliss
Know that as men discard worn clothes
to wear the new...
So also the soul discards the body
that is tired and worn...
To enter a new abode
For the soul is unassailable,
nonperishable, eternal
No sword can sever
No fire can consume
The soul, untouched by the impure,
unscarred by sorrow
Eternal. The soul transcends
time and space
No! Don't take my Daddy away!
Come, son
You mustn't do this. Come
It's time for the last rite
I will perform the last rite.
- But his son should be doing it
Please take care of this boy
After friends and family
have turned away...
All you have left
is your Religion
Only this far can your friends
and relatives give you company
The rest of the journey
you will travel alone
For company, all you have
is your Religion
Son, I left everything behind
to come here
Will you please arrange for
my transport up to the railway station?
I will accompany you
to the railway station
Satya's wife is coming to meet you.
She wants to pay her respects
You know, Satya was like
a brother to me
I'll take care of his wife
and his son. Don't worry about them
I never did. Now isn't the time either
Please be seated
Where are the rest of the rituals
to be performed?
At the village.
- Then his family should go there too
Not necessary. I will do the needful.
- I don't understand...
Will you perform the invocations
to rest the soul of the departed?
Yes, I will do it all.
- But his son should be doing it
He is too young. That's why
I lit the funeral pyre too
Lie! He's telling a lie!
You are lying!
Kabul! You mustn't talk like that.
- But why is he telling a lie?
Daddy used to say that lying
is the worst sin
What lies?
- It isn't because I'm too small
It's because I'm not Daddy's son.
It's because I'm someone else's son
That's why I cannot perform
the rites. Mummy told me so
Who told you...?
Mummy. And Mummy never lies!
This stark, bitter truth! I couldn't
bring myself to speak of it
For fear of shame, for the first time
in my life, I've strayed from truth!
And a mother says it! To her son!
Without as much as hesitation...
Just like Satyakam's motheli Jabala
Naren, I have been defeated
This is my greatest defeat!
The one I turned away
from my door because...
She was born a half-caste,
an untouchable...
Has taught me that to speak the truth
is not a merely a matter of pride
It takes courage to admit it...
No matter how bitter,
how harsh the truth may be
She has proved how great...
How magnanimous she is!
Call Ranjana
Drink this
Yes son, I have thirsted all my life
Let this child give me the water
Give it, son
I am at peace!
Are you bidding me farewell, my child?
Come on, it's time for the train
He is the only heir I have left
I have to give him an education.
I have to bring him up
The school that my family has nurtured
for fourteen generations...
Has to be passed on
I have very little time left, my child.
You will have to do it all yourself
Enough now, my child
Satyakam
My Satyakam
Come, my child
Go on
"I was about to give the old man
his walking stick"
"But I saw that he needed none.
He had found the support he needed"
"Family lines, the old man realised
are drawn not only in blood"
"A true heir is one
who inherits the legacy"
"There was no beginning to this story,
and there is no end"
"Till the day man lives,
till the day he considers...
"himself to God's representative
on earth..."
"till such time, Satyapriya's story
will be told over and over again"
"Satyasharan, Satyapriya, and Satyakam
...they will come again and again"