This Air India flight is headed
from Delhi to London
Among the passengers
Indian and foreign
Newly weds and those married
for many years
Ministers and sentries
And a very strange girl. Deepa
Young, beautiful and rich.
She's fed up of life
At 23, she has three unsuccessful
love affairs behind her...
and she's going to Paris
to seek solace
She bears the impression that there
are no real lovers in India
"An opportunity like this,
you will never have again"
"A man with a heart like mine,
you will never find again"
"Come, let me take you around Paris
on a colorful evening..."
"An Evening in Paris"
"An opportunity like this,
you will never have again"
"A man with a heart like mine,
you will never find again"
"Come, let me take you around Paris
on a colorful evening..."
"An Evening in Paris"
"Look at this bevy of beauties"
"They say such sweet things"
"They do color your heart..."
"when they choose to play
hide-n-seek with you"
"Look at this bevy of beauties"
"They say such sweet things"
"They do color your heart..."
"when they choose to play
hide-n-seek with you"
"Where will you find an
opportunity like this again?"
"Where will you find
someone like me again?"
"Come, let me show you a
colorful evening of Paris..."
"An Evening in Paris"
"Arm in arm..."
"they're very much in love"
"Seek your companion here..."
"and you will have
a beauty too"
"Arm in arm..."
"they're very much in love"
"Seek your companion here..."
"and you will have
a beauty too"
"Where will you find an
opportunity like this again?"
"Where will you find
someone like me again?"
"Come, let me show you a
colorful evening of Paris..."
"An Evening in Paris"
"Have a heart..."
"fall in love,
before you die"
"Who has seen tomorrow?"
"Take a walk down these lanes
right today"
"Have a heart..."
"fall in love,
before you die"
"Who has seen tomorrow?"
"Take a walk down these lanes
right today"
"Where will you find an
opportunity like this again?"
"Where will you find
someone like me again?"
"Come, let me show you a
colorful evening of Paris..."
"An Evening in Paris"
God! It's so late, and the
mistress's vehicle hasn't landed
She's arriving in a plane,
not in a bus, sardarji
I know, I'm at an airport,
not at a bus-stop
There she is!
What do you mean?
- I'm your slave, your chauffeur...
Sardar Makhan Singh.
- You're making a mistake
What mistake? Here's the
telegram you sent
That isn't my telegram.
- This garland isn't yours either
I'm sorry
Namaste, Deepaji.
- You?
Damodar Dayal, your manager.
- My uncle in Paris!
I'm your mistress, right?
- That's right
I'll fire you if you are formal
with me again. I'm just Deepa for you
And you're my mistress...
- Who?
Your driver.
- Sardar Makhan Singh
Please wait in the car.
I'll go and fetch your luggage
This is the best locality of Paris
And I've engaged this flat
specially for you
How about you?
- I have an apartment near the office
This is Honey.
She's studying in Paris
I thought you'd need a companion
I have an important meeting,
if I'm not needed here, dear
Go ahead.
- Deepa mustn't have any trouble...
You needn't say that, uncle.
- See you tomorrow morning
I'm terribly tired.
I'd like to take a bath first
Where's the bathroom?
- Right ahead
Hot water, towels...
everything's ready
The driver's bringing my luggage.
Please fetch my dressing gown
It's right at the top.
- Okay
Would you like something to drink?
- Coffee
Mistress, I've brought your luggage.
- Keep it there
And what do I see? A dream!
Beautiful! Very beautiful!
You're too good to be true!
What did you say?
- Solid! You're for real!
Honey...
- Coming!
Honey! What a sweet name...
like the petha from Agra!
Did I hear you say something?
- I want to
I know today what
hate at first sight means!
Nut!
- I think you like me
What happened?
- Come here. Quick
I open this door and
guess what I see
A peeping tom?
- No
Look down there
That's perfectly normal.
- Out in the open?
Out here, they romance every where
and every time
It's something Paris is famous for.
If you don't fall in love in Paris...
you won't fall in love
anywhere else in the world
But love, you've got to find.
- In Paris?
In Paris, love finds you
- Really?
Honey, I always have a dream...
an unfinished dream
Of love?
- Yes
It isn't about lust or fancies.
It's a dream of true love
You mean you don't have a boyfriend?
- Why not?
I have many.
- So what's wrong?
But they love my wealth...
not me
I've lost faith in lovers
But nobody knows you here
You can pretend to be
a simple, poor girl
And if someone falls for a poor girl,
he'll be a true lover. Right?
Please put this away safely.
I'll ask you for it, when I need it
I'll keep it in the safe
at the office
Another thing...
I'm a very poor girl
This flat belongs to Honey,
and I'm her maid-servant
Pardon me?
That's what you will tell anyone
who asks you about me
But...
That's a secret we can't
tell you about, uncle
You may leave now.
- Very well. Here I go
Makhan's late, Honey.
- Here I am
I had to look in every nook
and corner of Paris...
to find this dress of
an Indian maid-servant
I'll try it on
Try something, beautiful one.
- What?
My love, I mean. I'm willing
to do anything for you
Shut up, or you'll lose your job!
- For you, I'd even give up life!
Look what I've got for you.
- Lipstick?
Yes. Apply it on your lips
That's something!
Had I known you'd cling to me
after one little burst...
I'd have bought
a dozen fire-crackers
Cheat, rascal!
You dare do this!
I'll fix you yet!
Shekhar?
- What's this?
Daddy, since when you have
started dealing in jewelry?
Put that back in there.
- Is that fake or real?
It belongs to my mistress.
- Mistress?
Yes. Deepa, she's here
on a tour of Paris
I'll take her around Paris, daddy.
Just introduce me to her
Never. You're not worthy of it
Didn't I ask you not to come here?
- I'm in need, daddy
What is it?
- I need 200,000 rupees
200,000?
- I've got to repay some debts
Debts of liquor and gambling?
- It's a question of my life, daddy
I have nothing to do with it.
- I'm your only son, daddy!
Our relationship ended when I got to
know of your misdeeds
Please, daddy! You must help me!
You have millions!
The money belongs to Deepa's father.
I'm only their manager
Daddy, I might lose my life!
Shekhar, I have no sympathies
for a gambler. You may go now
Where will I look for her?
My word!
Who's that?
- Why are you there, Your Majesty?
I'm right here!
- What are you doing here?
I asked you to look for Deepa.
- You're right
From the Eiffel Tower, I was
looking for her.
I saw you and I came
down immediately
Where could she have gone?
- I'll tell you
She has gone looking
for her true love
I can speak a bit of Hindustani
An Indian guy is my friend.
- Wonderful. What is your name?
My name is Deepa
Deepa! Wonderful!
A beautiful girl like you isn't
in love, nor married. Why?
Boys in India look for money
in marriage
No. They're all very greedy
Cheats! Frauds!
What?
- You're beautiful and I'm in love
I'm very poor?
- Eh?
Good! I'm poor too.
No Mama, no Papa
Aren't you married?
- Not married
You and I will marry.
- I must leave now
Leave? Will you come tomorrow?
Sure, I will
I will too!
Photographer! Where have you
been all these days?
I want an Indian dress. Quick!
What do you want?
A dress! I want to be
an Indian Maharaja
An Indian Maharaja?
Are you in your senses?
I'm not! I learnt Hindustani from you
and met a beautiful Indian girl
I've fallen in love with her!
What's her name?
- Deepa
A look at her, and my heart skipped
a beat. I'm going to marry her
Marry her? Couldn't she
find an Indian boy?
Indian boys lust for money.
- Says who?
Deepa. They're frauds and cheats!
- Who's this insolent girl?
Where are you meeting her again?
Really? I've got to fix her...
I sure must!
I want to be an Indian Maharaja!
Deepa! Are you happy?
And who are you?
- An Indian Maharaja!
We're going to marry, okay?
I'm not their father!
Lady...
Because of one man, you have a
wrong impression of all Frenchmen
You said you're French.
- Sure. I live in France
But you speak Hindustani?
- As well as you do
Spent twenty years in your country.
Are you from Lucknow?
No. From Delhi.
- I see
My father was a professor
of French in Lucknow
I see
Your name?
- Deepa
Lovely name... you are, too!
On a pleasure trip in Paris?
- Yes, no...
I'm here with my mistress.
I'm a poor maidservant
Strange. When I was in India,
maid-servants didn't speak English
Anyway, we're all equal in Paris.
There is no discrimination
To prove that we must have
some coffee together
No, I've got to go.
- But I must do something for you
Why?
- To dispel doubts...
that Frenchmen aren't good human beings
- That's what my first experience was
So you must have another experience
What did she say?
She says, only fortunate men
have beautiful wives
What?
- Do not take offense
She thought I'm married, too,
although I'm not
I haven't come across a girl who
isn't hankering for money
What do you mean?
- No offense meant...
but girls are generally very selfish.
- Boys are the ones who are selfish
I know them all very well.
- Maybe you do
But you don't know French boys.
- Something special about them?
Yes. They could die
for the girls they love
When they fall in love, they
follow the girl for an eternity
Don't you follow me, mister.
It won't be good for you
Why must I? Strange girl!
You haven't even asked me my name...
I'm not at all interested!
"Ask me..."
"what my name is"
"Give me a loving look..."
"and ask me what I seek"
"Don't meet me after that,
if you don't want to..."
"Ask me..."
"what my name is"
"Give me a loving look..."
"and ask me what I seek"
"Don't meet me after that,
if you don't want to"
"Do not be angry"
"Listen to me"
"Take me for your own"
"From a distance..."
"you could yet have
been deceived"
"From a distance..."
"you could yet have
been deceived"
"Get to know me, now that
I'm so close to you"
"Ask this crazy man..."
"what his name is"
"Give me a loving look..."
"and ask me what I seek"
"Don't meet me after that,
if you don't want to"
"IIlusions have faded away"
"I understand it now.
I remember it well"
"In my dreams..."
"I often met you"
"In flesh and blood,
I have you here today"
"Ask me..."
"what my name is"
"Give me a loving look..."
"and ask me what I seek"
"Don't meet me after that,
if you don't want to"
"It's a colorful evening
in Paris"
"Here's where love happens.
Beauty blossoms"
"A love story we
will surely make..."
"a legend we will
surely leave behind"
"Ask me..."
"what my name is"
"Give me a loving look..."
"and ask me what I seek"
"Don't meet me after that,
if you don't want to"
"Ask me..."
"what my name is"
"Give me a loving look..."
"and ask me what I seek"
"Don't meet me after that,
if you don't want to"
Who are you?
- Mr. Shekhar. The manager's son
This is our first meeting, but please
don't treat me like an outsider
I have a role to play with Dad
in handling your business
That it's my business and I'm Deepa...
who told you?
Not I
Two things in the world
no one can ever hide
Beauty. And wealth
You are a living example of one
who possesses both in abundance
You are an interesting man.
Please sit down
Thank you, but I'm in a hurry.
Are you free tomorrow?
What for?
Maybe I'm the lucky man
who will take you around Paris
We're going on a picnic tomorrow.
I've fixed it up with my friends!
I'm no enemy, am I?
- What?
I mean, I could join you and
your friends on the picnic
Ask her.
- May I?
Suit yourself
I'll be here tomorrow
Quite a smart alec!
What do you think?
I think they are like that.
One and all
Are there going to be only girls
on the picnic tomorrow, or?
There will be boys too. But we
can get rid of them
So do that
What are you guys doing?
Shameless guys!
You knock down a small boy?
Leave me alone! For God's sake!
I don't know where
the girls have gone!
Aren't you ashamed to be
following those girls?
I'll hand you over to the cops
Get lost, for God's sake!
- Sardarji...
Here comes another
Is there where Miss Deepa lives?
- Who are you?
I'm Sam. Tell her, she'll know.
With a bouquet as big as that,
anybody would know
But my mistress is away
on a picnic
Your mistress?
- You want to meet Deepa, right?
I'm her driver. Sardar Makhan Singh
Mistress, eh? And where has
she gone for a picnic?
All these guys here
want me to tell
I'm not supposed to squeal
What does that mean?
- There are 12 girls in the party
The guys here are the boyfriends
who've been ditched by the girls
Morons! Girls who have ditched them
can be straightened out too
How?
By going on the picnic.
Will you join me?
My heart-throb's out there!
- Where?
Honey! The mention of her name
sends my heart aflutter!
You love her?
- I'm scared, as much as I love her
I'm trying to make it work.
- But it won't!
I can make it work for you
Come with me.
- You're god-send for me!
My word! You've broken the record!
How did this break?
God broke it because
this man is a liar!
I didn't tell him...
he came here on his own
Who is he?
- The greatest magician in the world!
Hukum Pasha!
The sparkle in your eyes tells me
your name... it's Deepa!
He's lying! He's a fraud!
- By God! Who are you?
A cheat! A vagabond!
Shekhar, don't mess with the magician.
He'll turn you into a dog
I don't believe in any magic!
- But I do!
You seem to be a very learned man.
Can you tell me a secret of mine?
Pick a card, son.
- Here goes
A slave!
- Whose?
Fall at the feet
where this card lands
What are you doing?
- I'm your slave!
Hats off to Hukum Pasha!
- Makhan Singh!
Forgive me
They've ruined the picnic. Let's go
elsewhere. I'll go and get the bus
He'll return in a moment.
His tires are deflated!
Look...
Twelve boyfriends!
Twelve girls have ditched
twelve boys to come here
Can you tell us where they are?
- I can present them here right now!
This girl doesn't believe me!
Those girls have left with their
lovers. Where's yours?
I have none.
- Lies! He's here, right before you
What?
- That's the truth!
I should've known that
such a cheap thing only...
a true lover could follow his beloved
anywhere, everywhere, in every guise
Is he the one?
- Can't you tell from his face?
Hats off to your magic!
- So you knew who he is!
I swear! I still don't know
who he is!
You don't need to know.
She knows and this is between us
What a nuisance!
Makhan Singh, could there be
a pump around?
A petrol pump?
- No, an air pump
Some scoundrel has deflated
all four tires
How will we return?
The city's far away
Arrange for transport, Makhan Singh.
- Transport?
There aren't even horses here!
But wait...
Let me play up to the magician!
Sir... can you help us, please?
- I'll arrange for your transport
It has been arranged.
Follow me
There you are!
- Magic! This is a miracle!
Are you God himself?
Sit down.
- I'm not riding with him
So sit with me. Car or scooter,
what difference does it make?
I'm your driver anyway.
Sit down
Where will I sit?
- Hop aboard. He's like your brother
What happens of me?
That which God wishes!
"We'll come face to face again...
and you will realize"
"I am unique,
you will concede"
"We'll come face to face again...
and you will realize"
"I am unique,
you will concede"
"We'll come face to face again...
and you will realize"
"I am unique,
you will concede"
"These beautiful climes for love,
the breeze and this moment..."
"they're all with me"
"My goal is here before me..."
"it's all a matter of moments now"
"These beautiful climes for love,
the breeze and this moment..."
"they're all with me"
"My goal is here before me..."
"it's all a matter of moments now"
"We'll come face to face again...
and you will realize"
"I am unique,
you will acknowledge"
"We'll come face to face again...
and you will realize"
"I am unique,
you will acknowledge"
"Every path I walk,
leads to you"
"So call me over to your place..."
"when may I come?"
"Every path I walk,
leads to you"
"So call me over to your place..."
"when may I come?"
"We'll come face to face again...
and you will realize"
"I am unique,
you will acknowledge"
"We'll come face to face again...
and you will realize"
"I am unique,
you will acknowledge"
I was dying for a cup of tea.
- Was it tea, or was it someone else?
What does that mean?
- What do you think of Sam?
He's an insolent beast!
- All said and done...
he's madly in love with you
Or he wouldn't have been
following you around like this
Do we fall in love
because he follows me?
That's what usually happens.
- Nonsense!
You think he'll follow me
every place I go?
I'm sure about that.
- Let me see then!
Is that Uncle?
This is Deepa here
Please come over immediately.
This is very important
Uncle, have you thought of something?
- I'm trying to
You don't like it here in Paris...
- In Paris?
I don't want to stay here another day!
- There's Venice, Rome, Cairo...
Uncle, I'm sick of touring places
just for the heck of it
I want to do something now.
- So attend office from tomorrow
You have a business of millions
I don't want to get into business
to make money
I want to do something for
the welfare of the people
Something that will benefit mankind.
Or else, what life am I leading?
Just a minute, dear.
Let me think
Air hostess? No
Modeling...? No
Next month, there's an international
youth festival slated to be held there
The Red Cross society from every
country sends its volunteers there
I know the Director
of the Festival
Here's your chance. You can be part
of the Indian group, if you want to
Mankind will benefit
Please arrange for
my departure immediately
By tomorrow morning,
it'll all be arranged
Wow!
Amazing! All youngsters here...
not an old fossil in sight!
It's a youth festival, idiot!
So let's you and I
have a festival too
You're young. So am I!
I'll shut up, but tell me,
what good is youth...
if it's spent in pining?
Why be young at all?
There he is!
- Forget Sam!
Thanks for the telegram
But where is she?
- In the Indian Red Cross section
We're put up at the Meridian.
- I see
See you soon
So this guy has his fingers
in two pies! The flirt!
What do you mean?
- He's in love with my mistress
To you, he says "See you soon"!
- Idiot! I'm only helping him
I sent him a telegram and
told him that Deepa's here
Is anybody here?
- What happened?
Please sit down
Take off that handkerchief
You?
- Yes
Ever since I've seen you,
I can see no one else
I wonder what disease this is.
- I know what it is
Shamelessness!
- Really? Do you have a cure for it?
Sure. A patented cure.
Coming up in a moment
Matron, this is Deepa. Please come
here with the police immediately
Get on with your work.
I don't think he'll come again
I'm sure he'll come, sister
I'm really hurt! I swear!
I'm really hurt!
Stand up, mister!
- I can't, sister! I'm badly hurt!
Where? In your heart?
- No... here on the leg
Is it this man?
Yes, but...
Can't you see the injury?
Attend to it immediately
Take a good look. Go ahead
You should know it's your
sacred duty to look after me
It's something I've brought
myself to this state for...
You've shattered my dreams!
Killed me!
It burns, really!
- It'll be okay
When?
I'm talking about your injury.
- And I'm talking about my heart
But how would you know what
happens to someone's heart?
Did you have to show up now?
This is fun! I've found her!
I've found you at last!
- Is this any way to come?
Had I taken the proper route,
you'd have vanished. What then?
What then?
It would be twilight,
whilst I looked for you
It would soon be night
and what's in my heart...
would have remained in my heart.
- What is it?
Here's where my truck
always grinds to a halt!
I want to say it,
but I can't
I find myself tongue-tied
Honey, see that?
- What?
That little English boy?
- Yes
Guess what he'll do when he grows up?
- What?
He'll be a youngster someday.
Like me
Really?
- Yes. And he'll meet a girl
Like you.
- Really?
Their acquaintance will grow...
and grow...
and grow some more...
like that balloon?
- I know what happens next
Do you? Tell me then
It'll all be over.
Like that balloon
English boy!
Little devil! I wasn't
doing a dance, was I?
You had to burst it?
Couldn't you blow it some more?
Get lost! Go on!
Shameless boys!
They've ruined it for me
You? What brings you here?
You're here to treat people.
And I come ailing
What disease do you have?
- Some diseases show. Some don't
And that which don't show,
are really very dangerous
What are your plans?
- I've just returned from duty
I think I'll rest for a while.
- As if people come here to rest
Have you seen the range?
- Yes.
What does that mean?
- It's a beautiful mountain...
with snow everywhere. Go and
change quickly. I'll take you there
All right, I'll be back
in a moment
Mind the rope
Skiing? I can't do it.
- I'll teach you
No thank you, not I
Planes out here?
- Why not?
I want a joy-ride!
- It's a private plane
I don't know that!
Please arrange something!
Please arrange it...
- Okay. Stay here, I'll be back
Is there no place in the world
where I don't have to see your face?
There is a place certainly.
- Which one?
Your heart.
- You know that, don't you?
Yes, that there's no place for me.
But I'm not willing to believe it
Because I was taught in school,
try and try and...
Let me see
"All by yourself..."
"where are you going?"
"Wherever you're going,
take me along too"
"All by yourself..."
"where are you going?"
"Wherever you're going...
take me along too"
"All by yourself..."
"where are you going?"
"I lie destroyed"
"Are you even aware?"
"I already belong to you..."
"do you know that?"
"What's all this about?"
"Have you any inkling?"
"All by yourself..."
"where do you think you're going?"
"Take me along,
wherever you're going"
"All by yourself..."
"where do you think you're going?"
"Take me along,
wherever you're going"
"All by yourself..."
"where do you think you're going?"
"Do not leave me in turmoil...
you're the life in me"
"Do not turn your face away,
"Do not break my heart...
you're my very life"
"All by yourself..."
"where do you think you're going?"
"Take me along
wherever you're going"
"All by yourself..."
"where do you think you're going?"
"Take me along
wherever you're going"
"All by yourself..."
"where do you think you're going?"
"Somebody might stop you...
what will you do then?"
"What will you do if
you're forced to halt?"
"What will you do...
if I pander to your whims?"
"All on your own..."
"where do you think you're going?"
"Take me along,
wherever you're headed"
"All alone..."
"where are you going?"
"Take me along,
wherever you're headed"
"You're all alone..."
"and where are you going?"
Come, Deepa
Where were you held up?
- I had lost my way
You could've taken help
- I did
But very few people here
understand English. So...
Which is why I ask you
to always be at my side
Well never mind.
Hey, you're shivering!
Yes. It was terribly cold up there.
And there was a chilly breeze
Your hands are cold
Do you want to fall sick?
Go and change... Go on
We have met.
- Maybe we have
Your name?
- Sam
I'm Shekhar
Lost something?
- Well?
Looks like you're desperately
looking for something
Looks like you're in the habit of
interfering in people's affairs
Only when Deepa is concerned.
- What does that mean?
Stay away from her.
- Why?
Because she and I are close
You're in love with her?
- Very much so
So let's shake hands.
I'm madly in love with her too
More than my life, actually
No one wants anything more than life.
Because life is most precious for every
human.
What do you think?
I think that in mine and Deepa's
affairs...
...her father's servant's son should
not interfere.
Still feeling the chill?
- Yes
Have some brandy. It'll disappear.
Decent Indian girls never drink
You understand English, don't you?
Here, gulp it down.
- But...
Don't drink it, Deepa!
A dance will warm you up
I want to say something to you!
I say, are you watching
what I'm watching?
How did that leech
stick to my mistress?
God! What's he making her drink?
Whose room is this?
- Mine... yours actually
May I lie down.
- Sure. Do lie down
Will you please call Honey
from my room, Shekhar?
Honey? Sure, why not?
Hurry up, Shekhar.
I'm feeling very sleepy
He raises the bottle to his lips and
gulps it all down. Without any soda!
He's now unbuttoning his jacket.
- And Deepa?
Deepa's knocked out.
She's lying on the bed
I'll keep you posted
Come with me... come on!
- Where to? Tell me!
How I have waited for this day
After tonight, you will
forever belong to me
It's your death
What?
- If you want to live anymore...
get out of that room and come
downstairs to the reception
Jaggu? How did you land here?
As if you didn't know!
I promised to pay the rest of
the money after a month
Where's Jack?
- Right here
Here? Now look, Jaggu...
take him away somehow
I'll pay you 5000 for it.
- 10,000
All right, 10,000! But Jack mustn't
come anywhere near me
You're so scared?
As if you don't know! Your boss will
shoot me at the slightest provocation
Wait
Something is fishy.
He's talking about murder
God! What's he saying?
Shekhar, come downstairs
Downstairs?
The boss's orders. We'll wait
for you for 3 minutes
Suppose I don't come?
In that case, we'll have
to come upstairs. Get it?
No, stay there. I'm coming
Hurry up!
What's the scoundrel done to her?
Let me sleep
Get up, Deepa! Come to your senses!
Sam, you love me?
Let's get out of here
before he returns
Go ahead. I have other plans
He's a dangerous man, you don't know.
- Never mind
If he's a snake, I'm a mongoose!
Just take her away and I'll come
after I've broken him up!
Come to your senses, Deepa
I think we must take her to her room
And I think she ought to
remain in this room...
because when she comes to, she must
know what could have happened to her
Go to sleep. I'll keep watch
Jaggu? You?
Where's the money?
- I told you I'd pay up in a month
Where will you bring it from?
- I'll get married
It's a millionaire's daughter.
It'll take just a few days
You're kidding!
- It's the truth. Believe me
Where is she?
- Right here, in this hotel
I want to see her.
- Okay, but it'll be from a distance
"I'm terribly embarrassed about
what happened last night"
"I'll forever be grateful to you
for the things you did for me"
"I can't dare face you.
So I'm going away. Far away..."
"after getting close to you"
"You'll receive this letter
after I have left"
There she is
Hurry up!
Suzy? How come Suzy's here, Jaggu?
I don't get it either
Come on, Deepa
Jaggu, isn't that Suzy?
Suzy? Who's Suzy?
- The dancer at our casino
"Take it away,
take away my heart"
"It's your world,
your merry gatherings..."
"I've always waited for you
with a heart full of love"
"Take it away,
take away my heart"
"It's your world,
your merry gatherings..."
"I've always waited for you
with a heart full of love"
"Why're you sitting away from me?
"Come closer, and tell me the truth"
"Tell me that you belong to me and
that we shall walk together. Forever"
"Let me give him my heart...
Let me"
"Take it away,
take away my heart"
"It's your world,
your merry gatherings..."
"and I always waited for you with
a heart that was beating only for you"
"What are you scared of?"
"Let the world know"
"Cupid struck, our hearts met,
and we fell in love"
"Take it away,
take away my heart"
"It's your world,
your merry gatherings..."
"and I waited for you with
love in my bosom, my love"
"Take it away,
take away my heart"
"It's your world,
your merry gatherings..."
"and I waited for you with
love in my bosom, my love"
"Come sunset, and lamps were lit"
"Your desires, your thirst,
was awoken"
"Take it away,
take away my heart"
"It's your world,
your merry gatherings..."
"and I waited for you with
love in my bosom, my love"
"Take it away,
take away my heart"
"It's your world,
your merry gatherings..."
"and I waited for you with
love in my bosom, my love"
What brings you here, Jack?
- I came along to see you
Had I not seen it for myself,
I'd never have believed it
Now that I have met Suzy, I can say
for sure that that girl wasn't her
Which girl?
- We saw a girl exactly like you
An absolute look-alike
There's just one Suzy in the world.
And she belongs to you
Suzy can't belong to anyone else
Who's the other girl?
- Deepa. Daughter of my dad's boss
Mr. Malik's daughter?
- You know him?
No. All I know is that he has
more money than he'll ever need
Deepa's his only daughter?
- Yes
You want to marry her so you
can swallow the entire wealth?
Where's Deepa right now?
- Beirut
What do you get for returning
a millionaire's daughter?
A million dollars.
- Good
Go to Beirut immediately. You know
what you've got to do
Wait. What are you guys
getting at?
We will only kidnap Deepa.
After that...
we'll strike a deal
with her father. Get it?
Makhan hasn't returned, Honey?
Yes, he's not around
Here I am!
Have you arranged for a speed-boat?
- Strict laws here, madam
Those who can't water-ski,
can't hire speed-boats
Buy one, if you can't hire it.
- You don't understand
You need the club's permission
to go into the waters
And that you can get
on only one condition
You need an instructor with you.
- So go and find an instructor
Right away!
Why're you being stubborn, Deepa?
A speed-boat's very fast
I need the pace. Fast. Very fast.
So I can leave everyone else behind...
and go far away
Only to forget Sam?
You're a strange girl. You looked
for true love all your life...
and when you found him,
you want to go away from him
I need an instructor
Not a police inspector, an
instructor to teach water-skiing
Make it quick. In five minutes.
Okay?
Water! Get me some buttermilk!
Such a fast speed-boat?
No, I can't do it
Coward!
Deepaji! Good luck! We've found an
instructor from our own country!
Are you a Bengali?
- No. And you?
I'm Deepak Sen.
A swimming champion
Absolutely! Thank you!
Mr. Sen, how much time does it
take to learn water-skiing?
With an expert like me teaching you,
it'll take just an hour
An hour? I'll go and
get a boat in a minute!
Take it off
Beautiful. Very beautiful!
Very fine figure!
You have a slender waist!
Won't help you to feel shy
with your instructor
I can see it all. Your face,
your figure, your heart...
you're in love?
- What do you mean?
I mean, those in love cannot swim
The beloved's face swims before
their eyes... all day and night
Shut up and go away!
- You're angry?
Which means there's something
wrong with your love!
I'm not going to teach you
any swimming
What I'll give you
is a lesson in love
Come on!
"My love..."
"Cast a look at me"
"From the skies I descend..."
"to give you lessons in love"
"In my heart is my beloved's picture.
I come to show it to you"
"From the skies I descend..."
"to give you lessons in love"
"In my heart is my beloved's picture,
I come to show it to you"
"Say you love me"
"Go away"
"Say you love me, my love"
"Learn from me,
ways of falling in love"
"Tell me that you're
in love with me"
"Learn from me,
ways of falling in love"
"Tell me that you're
in love with me"
"From the skies I descend..."
"to give you lessons in love"
"In my heart is my beloved's picture,
I come to show it to you"
"Say you love me"
"Go away"
"Say you love me, my love"
"My love, for you..."
"I have left the Moon behind"
"To give you..."
"I have brought my love
as a present"
"My love, for you..."
"I have left the Moon behind"
"To give you..."
"I have brought my love
as a present"
"From the skies I descend..."
"to give you lessons in love"
"In my heart is my beloved's picture,
I come to show it to you"
"Say you love me"
"Silly"
"Say you love me, my love"
"Don't be silly"
"Like a shadow..."
"I will always remain with you"
"I'm your lover"
"I'll carry you away in my arms"
"Like a shadow..."
"I will always remain with you"
"I'm your lover"
"I'll carry you away in my arms"
"From the skies I descend..."
"to give you lessons in love"
"In my heart is my beloved's picture,
I come to show it to you"
"Say you love me"
"Yes"
"Say you love me, my love"
"Oh yes"
"I said so"
"Say you love me"
"Oh yes, I am"
What are you staring at?
They've gone
And they've taught us a lesson too
A girl who doesn't agree,
ought to be carried away
Makhan Singh! Let's return
Makhan Singh isn't going
to be cowed down today
You are with me, I have the boat
I have desires, and there's
a storm in my heart!
Let's go! Hurry!
Makhan Singh's in a great mood today
It was great fun!
Come on, Honey!
The weather's so funny!
Why have you brought me
to this scary place?
Scary? Even as a kid, I dreamed of
bringing you to this romantic spot
There's silence everywhere...
no one around to slap me either!
You and I...
Iost in our love
Listen, moron!
- Who the hell is that?
Where has the other girl gone?
What's that to you?
Are you her uncle?
Makhan Singh, he has a pistol!
- It's a toy gun
It'll only make a noise.
I'll get rid of him
Get lost! Go away!
Now where's a smaller stone?
Makhan Singh!
What happened to you?
So you have a real pistol?
Go ahead and fire.
Provided it's not at us
What are you doing, Makhan Singh!
What are you up to?
Have you gone mad?
One shot is fired,
and you cling to me
If there 10 or 15 shots,
I'll have it worked out!
What's this?
Quietly tell me where
I will find the girl
Hurry up! Else, I'll shoot!
Paris
Put that gun away
and head for Paris
See that?
- Let's go
What's there to feel shy about?
That's the custom here
Boy meets girl, they fall in love
The boy proposes to her, puts
an engagement ring on her finger...
and then...
What do you think?
The boy proposes, puts an engagement
ring on her finger and then...
All right
Big favor you're doing to me!
Look, I got this just for you
How about it?
No
Why not?
I'm an Indian girl. According
to our customs, all this...
it'll happen after marriage.
- So we must marry soon
Never mind. Till then...
I'm exhausted!
- Already?
We've still got to see the fireworks
and spend the night on the streets
What for?
- People here don't go to sleep
They sing and dance.
Make merry
And what do you intend to do?
- Anything your heart says
My heart? It's yours now
- How about my heart?
I won't tell you
I will! At the top of my voice!
From rooftops!
"My heart belongs to you"
"Your heart belongs to me"
"Ever since we have exchanged hearts,
the world seems to have changed"
"For this moment,
I have waited so much"
"My eyes craved for a loving look"
"For this moment,
I have waited so much"
"My eyes craved for a loving look"
"My eyes craved
for a loving look..."
"My heart belongs to you"
"Your heart belongs to me"
"Ever since we have exchanged hearts,
the world seems to have changed"
"Let our hearts be lost
in a world crazily in love"
"We're mad at heart...
let's get madder"
"Let our hearts be lost
in a world crazily in love"
"We're mad at heart...
let's get madder"
let's get loonier"
"My heart belongs to you"
"Your heart belongs to me"
"Ever since we have exchanged hearts,
the world seems to have changed"
"Let's sing and dance,
everywhere we go"
"Let there be a cloudburst
of joy today"
"Let's sing and dance,
everywhere we go"
"Let there be a cloudburst
of joy today"
"My heart belongs to you"
"Your heart belongs to me"
"Ever since we have exchanged hearts,
the world seems to have changed"
Recognize me?
- With Jack, the other day?
I couldn't talk to you because
Jack was around the other day
And say what?
- About your benefit
What does that mean?
- It involves millions
There are millions we could
lay our hands on
We?
You resemble that girl to the t.
- I've heard that
Jack's going to kidnap her.
- I've heard that too
As soon as that girl disappears,
you will step into her shoes
This, I haven't heard of.
Jack didn't say a word to me
Jack doesn't know anything about it.
It's my plan
I don't have the courage
to go against Jack
Neither have I. But do you like
the idea of being terrified of Jack...
and dancing to his tunes
all our lives?
No. But do we have an option?
Join me. In just a week,
we'll turn millionaires
As soon as we have the money,
we'll no longer be scared of Jack
We'll go somewhere far away.
Someplace he can't ever get us
The danger exists only as long as
we get our hands on the money
Once we have the money, we can
buy our way out of the danger
What will my share be?
- Half the loot
How much is it in cash?
- At least a million dollars
If you need time to decide...
- I've decided
I'm with you
That's Deepa
She looks exactly like me...
there's no difference at all
Take a good look at her
Even her father mustn't be able
to tell the difference
He won't
This is enough, Shekhar. We don't
need to follow them anymore
Have you studied her gait, her
way of talking and mannerisms?
What childishness is this?
What happened?
Let me go!
- But what happened?
As if you don't know. Why were you
so interested in that girl?
And you were offended
at such a little thing?
Little thing?
- I just lit a cigarette for her
By looking deep into her eyes?
So you even get jealous, do you?
Only those in love
will feel jealous
I wasn't jealous when you clung
to Shekhar in Switzerland
Sam, please don't remind me of that.
I want to forget it
And what do you want to remember?
This ring. It gave the true love
I always looked for
For which I traveled here
from India
And your journey is over?
- No. It will now begin
"O companion for the night..."
"where are we going?"
"The dawn of love
is about to arrive"
"With the dazzling light
of beauty ahead..."
"dawn is turning away"
"Those asleep, we must awaken"
"Those awake, we must put to sleep"
"To keep us awake..."
"dawn sings a beautiful lullaby"
"O companion for the night..."
"we're tired, we're headed home"
"The dawn of love
is about to arrive"
"With the dazzling light
of beauty ahead..."
"dawn is turning away"
"Goblets of passion,
the night gave us"
"You and I are drunk
on each other's eyes"
"Our senses haven't
yet been restored..."
"so what else does
the dawn of love offer us?"
"O companion..."
"where are we going?"
"The dawn of love
is about to arrive"
"With the dazzling light
of beauty ahead..."
"dawn is turning away"
"What promises did we make?
What did we swear by?"
"On a new path,
we have now embarked"
"No matter how much
we hide our love..."
"the dawn of love
knows it all"
"O beloved..."
"we're tired. We're going home"
"The dawn of love..."
Tired?
- No
Feeling sleepy?
Paris is a strange place. You never
know when it's day or night
And you also don't know
when you fall in love
Guess what people here do
when they fall in love?
What?
- They have French onion soup
You're with Deepa?
You've conned me to
have her for yourself
I'm angry with you. You are
no longer my Indian friend!
Indian friend?
- A liar and a betrayer!
But he's a Frenchman
- I'm French. He's Indian!
What does that mean?
- He's lying
Am I really? You're the liar!
Look at his passport!
Take a look
Shyam Kumar, Lucknow, India
Shyam Kumar alias Mr. Sam,
alias the fake Frenchman!
Liar, cheat, betrayer!
- How have I deceived you?
You've made a fool out of me!
- Not at all. On the contrary...
I've shown you that Indian boys
are capable of being truly in love
Shut up! I don't even want
to see your face again!
You love me, don't you?
- Let me go!
I'm going to beat you to pulp!
Deepa has been kidnapped.
You are Deepa now
Till her father arrives,
nobody must get suspicious
They won't.
But I'm only afraid of Sam
Sam? He's blinded.
- What?
Blinded by love. You can easily
lead him up the path
Besides, you know what Deepa
and he were up to anyway
Are you okay?
- What's the police for?
I got a call at the office
telling me that...
that someone called Jack
has kidnapped you
He asked for a ransom of a million
dollars for your safe return
Is that all? Only a million?
- This is no time for jokes
The police tell me that Jack is
the most dreaded gangster in Europe
But he hasn't kidnapped me yet.
So why do we need them?
You ought to be careful, dear.
I was very scared
What would I tell your father
if something had happened to you?
Just don't get worried, uncle.
Go on
If you could fool my father...
it's easy to con
Deepa's father
I have no doubt that we'll
soon be millionaires
But there's time.
- Just a few days
It isn't right for me to come here.
I'll be leaving now
I'll give you a call, if need be
Who is it?
- Shyam
Alias Sam. Alias Hukum Pasha.
Alias Deepak Sen.
It's me
For me?
Lovely? You mean, no get out?
- What?
I thought you'd call me names and be
angry and that I'd have to pacify you
What for?
- Aren't you angry with me?
Can I ever be angry with you?
- So what was it yesterday?
Yesterday? Let's forget about it
What happened yesterday
is in the past
Deepa, did you never suspect
that I'm an Indian?
No
Know why I had to pretend
to be a Frenchman?
To prove to you that an Indian
is really capable of loving
I was convinced long ago
Ever since I met you
Are you okay?
- What do you think?
I'm scared! You never got
so close to me!
Sit down
Sam, take me out today
Sure, I will
I'll go and get ready
Who's been here?
No one
Whose cigarette is this?
Oh yes, Uncle was here
This one is still lit.
- Lit?
He was here a little while
before you came in
Why're you stopped here?
I've got to meet Louis.
He has a darkroom in that house there
Oh yes
Strange! Yesterday, you were
angry with me because of him
And now you speak as if
you don't even know him!
I don't like that man
Let's talk about something else.
About you and me
You've changed a lot in a day.
- How come?
There's a world of a difference between
the Deepa of yesterday and today
Yes, there is. And you are
the one who's responsible
I?
I love you more than I
loved you yesterday
Why?
I was angry yesterday.
And instead of taking offense...
you brought so many flowers for me.
- Is that why!
I thought it was the engagement ring...
- Engagement ring?
Where is it?
- I threw it away in a fit of anger
Good thing too. It was Sam who
put the ring on you yesterday
Today, Shyam will do it
Don't lose this one, okay?
Remember what I said yesterday?
- I do
But I'd like to hear it again.
- Just that boy meets girl...
they fall in love, the boy proposes,
makes her wear the ring...
and then...
- Then?
This is where I stopped yesterday.
- Didn't you say...
there's a world of a difference
between yesterday and today?
Let there be no distance today
Let the sky and the earth meet
What happened?
We're Indians. We don't do
these things before marriage
Come, let's go
Damodar...
- Sethji! You?
Hello Damodar.
- Hello
Deepa wasn't at the flat.
So I came here
What brings you here suddenly?
- You sent me a cable...
to come over immediately.
And I came over
I didn't send any cable.
- Didn't you?
So who sent it?
- I did
So you sent the cable?
- Yes, sir. In daddy's name
It was a delicate matter and
I wanted you to be here
What is the matter?
- I want to marry your daughter
What?
We're in love with each other and
Deepa has consented to the wedding
This is impossible!
You can ask your daughter.
- I certainly will
I just can't believe that Deepa
has decided to get married!
What?
- I was fed up of reasoning with her
She just didn't approve of anyone.
And if wants to marry Shekhar...
I'm very happy about it.
- Sethji!
Shekhar is my son, no doubt.
But worthy of Deepa...
I can't find a better match!
Damodar, you have looked after
my business all these years
Shekhar will now look after it.
Go and make a call, son
Check whether Deepa has returned.
We must finalize this immediately
What's the hurry? By tomorrow morning...
- Who knows?
Deepa might change her mind.
You don't know my daughter, Damodar
I'll call Deepa over.
- Go ahead. Hurry up
Suzy?
- Who's this?
When did you return?
- Right now
What's up? Your skin is glowing.
And what's this?
This is an engagement ring
Thank you, Deepaji.
- What for?
You left us in Beirut and
it strengthened our love
Congratulations.
- Thank you
Where's he?
- Over there
My line's now engaged, feller.
How about yours?
Makhan, I've some work with you.
I'll be back, Deepa
Come back soon. We must celebrate
Honey's engagement
I'll be back, Honey
Do you know where the
manager's office is?
Sure, I do.
- Take me there. Quick
What's wrong?
Deepa's telephone appears to be dead.
I'll personally go and bring her
Relax. I'll take it
Damodar Dayal?
This is the last warning
If you still don't agree to pay us
a million dollars...
Deepa will be finished this evening.
- Finish her
He's asking us to finish her
Something is surely wrong
out there
Leave for Paris immediately and
give me a call from there
Shekhar... is your daddy in?
- Yes. What happened?
Can't tell you. Deepa's...
- Makhan Singh. Let's go.
What?
- The girl in your flat is not Deepa
But she looks just like Deepa.
As if she were a twin
Twin?
- Had I not known your daughter well...
I'd have been deceived too
Damodar! Could Roopa still
possibly be alive?
Roopa? Who's that?
Deepa's twin sister.
Twenty years ago, after my wife died...
I came to Europe with
both my daughters
I found an Indian servant
to look after them
But I didn't know that he was
a gambler and a drunkard
One evening...
Jaggu! Where've you been all day?
- I was held up somewhere
Jaggu! You're drunk!
- I've had a little
I've hired you to take care
of my children, Jaggu
It's not for you to go berserk.
- Don't bully me, mister
This is Europe. It isn't India
You could face dangerous consequences
for throwing your weight around
You're threatening me?
Get out!
Settle my accounts, mister.
Right now
Mister, you're going to regret this
That very night, when both
my daughters were asleep...
I couldn't go to sleep
and was reading a book
I suddenly heard a scream
Jaggu! Wait there!
Deepa was saved. But there was
no trace of Roopa and Jaggu
One moment...
I've heard the name Jaggu before
In Switzerland!
When you called Shekhar
Manager, where's your son right now?
- My son? I don't know. Why ask?
He knows a thug called Jaggu.
Jaggu's boss is someone called Jack.
- Jack?
Jack threatened me over the phone
Jaggu and Roopa!
After all these years!
What's happening here?
- I'm baffled too
If the girl I spoke to at
Deepa's place isn't Deepa...
It's Roopa then!
It can't be anybody else!
God has saved her for me!
- Only she knows where Deepa is
Yes!
We must go and
meet her right now
Who's that?
- This is Deepa here
Suzy, take the back door and
come downstairs immediately
Why?
I'll explain later.
Just get out of there. Quick!
But...
Makhan Singh, wait here
Call me later
Do you know him, Deepa?
My father. He wanted to meet you
before we get married
Greetings
I'm Deepa.
- A fake Deepa
Because he's the
real Deepa's father
But you just said...
I had to prove that
you are not Deepa
So who am I?
- My lost daughter. Roopa
Deepa's twin sister
I'm sorry, but you're
making a mistake
Mother, father, brothers and sisters
are words alien to me
I have no one. I'm all alone
in the world
No, you can't be anybody
but my daughter
Why not? I'm Suzy
I'm known at every
night club of Europe
Nightclubs? What do you do there?
I sing and dance
and make money!
No!
- Why not?
It is my profession.
Any more questions?
Yes. Why did you pose as Deepa
and stay here?
Sam, I want to have a
word with you in privacy
Where is Deepa?
- I don't know
Damodar, telephone the
police immediately
You're right. I made a mistake
My daughter could never be
a dancing girl
Hand her over to the police, Shyam!
- Do you want to see Deepa alive?
D'you know where Deepa is?
- Yes, I do
If you want to find out,
just come with me
Don't inform the police
till I return
Why have you brought me here?
Because this is the crossroad
You'll find it easier
to choose your path
What does that mean?
- Mean?
Come, I'll show you
Sam, before I met you, I spent
my life in night-clubs...
displaying my body to lustful
and disgusting men
It was after I met you that I realized
there's another meaning to life
What are you getting at?
I've fallen in love with you, Sam.
- And you know I'm in love with Deepa
And you want her to remain alive?
- Where is she?
That's something only I know
And you want a price to tell me?
- Naturally
How much do you want?
200,000? Half a million?
I want your love. That's all
Please accept me.
I give you my word...
Deepa will return safely
to her father
Aren't you his father?
- That man's a stranger to me!
I've never seen him
or stayed with him!
Have you no sympathies for your sister?
- No!
I've never known her as my sister.
- And now that you know...
you're bargaining with me
for her life?
Only for love
With your love, I want
to start life afresh
I want to belong to you, Sam.
- You're not worth it
Why not? What's the difference
between Deepa and me?
There's one hell of a difference!
In your shoes...
she'd have laid down her life
to save her sister!
The difference between you and Deepa
is what is between real and fake
As much difference as there is
between light and darkness
Between a noble man
and a scoundrel!
Where is Deepa?
Tell me!
If you change your mind,
come to my hotel
Tell me, Suzy!
If you want Deepa to remain alive,
you must pay for it
you'll have to pay a price for it
If you want Deepa to remain alive,
Come to my hotel,
if you change your mind
"Thanks for coming..."
"my love"
"Listen to it, before you leave..."
"the story of my love"
"Thanks for coming..."
"my love"
"Do not ask how I feel"
"This gathering is for you..."
"so please sit down"
"What's the hurry?"
"You have just arrived"
"Enjoy the shade
my tresses give"
"Thanks for coming..."
"you are my love"
"You come for me.
And that is a favor"
"For you, I'd even
lay down my life"
"Cast a loving glance
at me too..."
"that's all I want from life"
"Thanks for coming..."
"you are my love"
"So listen to my love-story
before you leave, my love"
"Thanks for coming..."
"you are my love"
I knew you'd come
Wait here. I'll change
and return in a moment
Sit down, Sam
What have you decided?
I'll marry you
Without any conditions?
- You know
Will you undo the zip, please?
I want you to promise me that Deepa
will return safely
Is that all? You want
nothing else from me?
This is exactly why I love you, Sam.
You want nothing from me
You wanted to marry me.
And I'm willing
That's enough
What I sought from you was love.
Not pity!
I'll be in your arms all my life...
but Deepa will live in your heart
All my life, I'll have the feeling...
that you accepted me
out of helplessness
Maybe I'm rotten and cheap.
But I won't stoop...
to sell my emotions
in the name of marriage
You may go now
I'm sorry, I couldn't
get Suzy to agree
She didn't tell me Deepa's whereabouts.
- I told you to inform the police
That will endanger her life.
- Her life is already in danger
I wonder where my daughter is?
To have her back, I can even
give away all my wealth
I agree to every condition
those gangsters have
I'm willing to pay any price
to have Deepa back!
We only want a million dollars
Who?
Haven't you recognized me, sir?
It's your old faithful servant.
Jaggu
Jaggu! You're still alive?
Sure, I am.
And so is your daughter
I wish she were dead!
The state I saw her in...
Whom did you see?
- Roopa. She calls herself Suzy now
Suzy? Where did you meet her?
- In Deepa's flat!
I see. I get it now.
- Ingrate! Scoundrel!
Where have you kept Deepa?
I'll hand you over to the police!
You've already lost a daughter
D'you want to lose
the other one too?
Jaggu, you know where Deepa is?
- Yes, I do
If Jack doesn't have a million dollars
by tomorrow evening...
Deepa won't be allowed to live.
- No!
Can we raise a million by tomorrow?
- We can
One moment. How can you prove
that Deepa's in your custody?
Proof? Here it is
It's Deepa's handwriting
Where and whom have I
to pay the money?
In a black suitcase, one of you
will carry a million dollars...
and come to the tower at Niagara Falls
at 5:00 p.m. Tomorrow
What happens then?
- You'll get to know once you're there
Now tell me...
where is Deepa?
Speak! Where is Deepa?
Stop it
He has fainted. We had better
hand him over to the police
Damodar, book a seat for me
on the flight to Canada
You won't be able to
handle those thugs
This isn't something for you.
Let me go instead
Let you go? How's that possible?
It has to do with my daughter's life
And your daughter
means the life to me
Look, isn't she your duplicate?
Absolutely
Seems as if I were looking at
my reflection in the mirror
I must leave now.
Jaggu will be calling any moment
Don't cry, Deepa
Who are you?
- Your twin sister
But I didn't have any sisters.
- You don't know
I didn't know it either.
It was your father who told me
Daddy? Where?
- In Paris
It was the first time
I was meeting my father
But he refused to accept me
as his daughter
Why?
Because I'm as rotten
as nice you are
Between you and me...
is the difference that
sets apart darkness and light
Sam was right
Do you know Sam?
I got to know him. Briefly
Never mind all that
Quickly wear my clothes
and get out of here
And you?
- Don't worry about me
Your life is in danger!
Must I endanger my sister's life
to save my own skin?
No, I can never do that
Go away, Deepa. Let's not argue.
- No, I'm not going!
Please, Deepa...
don't waste your love on me
I don't deserve it
I work for these gangsters.
- What?
Henceforth, you must hate me too
But before you go,
please embrace me, Deepa
Maybe I'll never have
the opportunity again
Come
My sister!
When you meet Shyam,
do tell him on my behalf...
one lives in darkness because
there's no one to show him light
Shekhar! You?
I've been sent by Deepa's father.
With a million dollars
You?
- Yes
To take Deepa back
Deepa's father trusts
a fraud like you?
He has agreed to accept me
as his son-in-law
So you've cast a spell
on her father too!
Jack, you always took me
for a fool
You always threatened me
and pushed me around
And now you're a smart man?
- Yes
Okay, smartie.
Set the bag there
Give it to me.
- First call Deepa
I can take it away by force.
- You won't, because this is a deal
You want money.
And I want Deepa
You've indeed smartened up.
I'm beginning to get scared of you
Did you see that?
- Yes, Jack
She's just like me!
- Isn't she!
Shekhar, you've met Suzy?
I'll take a walk outside,
while you chat
Jack, please ask someone
to see me out, will you?
Keep an eye on him.
And just wait there
Who's the other man?
- Other man? Who's that?
He's carrying a black suitcase
and is waiting near the tower
Could be someone.
How'd I know?
Hand it over to me.
- Don't you trust me?
We don't even trust our fathers
in this business
Not yourself either
Hurry up!
Is that man still there?
Send him into the tunnel
immediately
Don't you dare make any noise.
Just come with me
Your old flame. Sam
He has always put
obstacles in my path
Today, I have him where I want him
Sam, go away!
I'm not Deepa! I'm Suzy!
Believe me!
I've helped Deepa escape!
She's waiting for you in Jack's boat.
Go away, Sam! Just escape!
What happened?
- Suzy's hurt, Makhan Singh!
Shekhar shot at her and escaped.
I'm going after him...
and she's lying unconscious there.
- I'll go and get the police
Hurry up!
"From the skies I descend..."
"to give you lessons in love"
"In my heart is my beloved's picture,
I come to show it to you"
"Say you love me"
"Oh yes"
"Say you love me, my love"
"I've said so"