Sir, five female prisoners..
..have been transferred
here from Jabalpur prison.
Tulsi!
Zubeida Bano!
Kalyani!
Jamuna!
Sukhiya!
Sir!
Who's it?
- This is Mahabal Singh!
Greetings!
- What's the matter?
There's some noise in the female ward.
Is it?
- Yes.
Wait, I'll get the key.
We can't live here anymore!
Open the door!
Let us out!
- Quiet!
Why can't you live here?
We're scared of blood!
- Stop!
Stop!
Open the door!
Quiet! The jailor's here!
The jailor's here!
Greetings, sir.
The constable told me
that someone's ill. - Yes.
The old woman Ramdai
vomited blood twice.
That's why the rest of
the women are very scared.
The doctor's here.
I'm sorry for being late.
Who's ill?
- Prisoner no. 8, Ramdai.
Today she vomited
blood while coughing.
Blood?
- Yes.
Come, Devendradra, let's take a look.
- What'll you do in there?
I'll go alone.
- Hurry up.
If I stand here for long,
then even I'll have to be
admitted in your hospital!
Everyone leave.
I won't survive now, doctor.
- Shut up!
Were you ill for a few
nights previously? - Yes.
I'm very thirsty.
Get water.
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
What's wrong with her?
- She's suffering from tuberculosis.
She'll have to be sent
to the hospital ward.
Fine. The female hospital is empty.
But we'll need a nurse too.
Warden.
- Yes.
Just inquire if anyone of
them is ready to serve her.
Who'd like to be with that old woman?
They all are so scared after
seeing her vomiting blood.
Ask them.
- As you say.
Is anyone of you
ready to be with Ramdai?
Why are you quiet?
I'm ready.
But she can't be with her.
- Why?
It's contagious.
And at this age, the tuberculosis
viruses spread very easily.
I don't care, doctor.
Don't worry about me.
Sir, just order me.
I'll be able to serve her very well.
Strange girl! She's come
here just a few days ago,
but she's friendly with everyone.
Here's my ticket. Write the order.
You might forget tomorrow.
Is this the time for
sir to write things?
Doctor, pen please.
Oh, God! Look at her audacity!
She was talking to the jailor as
if she's related to him! - Shut up!
Stop your nonsense! Go to your places!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5..
Why were you so shocked on
seeing that girl's card?
I was shocked to see the
accusation on that girl.
She's a murderer.
She poisoned someone.
And today she wants
to save someone else.
You know, the holy scriptures say..
..that even God can't
predict the character of women..
..and the destiny of men.
Then who are we?
I don't know about
the holy scriptures.
But I feel that if one
commits a crime once..
..that doesn't brand
him a criminal forever.
Why've you brought this bed?
- Doctor has sent it.
We're are slogging here..
..and Kalyani is sleeping
peacefully at the hospital!
Why are you jealous now?
Everyone was quiet
when the warden asked..
..you to look after that old woman!
Why are you feeling offended?
She still has high fever.
We'll have to take her to the
hospital tomorrow, for the X-ray.
You keep her ready.
Doctor, why did you send
another bed for the patient?
For you.
No. I don't need it.
I'll sleep on the floor.
Look, it's the prison rule that..
..everyone gets what they deserve.
Even if they don't want.
I'm an ordinary prisoner.
I'm here to serve the
punishment of my mistake.
I deserve only 3
blankets and a mattress.
Even I've some duties being a doctor.
And I did everything
to fulfill my duty.
Listen.
What happened?
I'm just a C-class prisoner.
Jailors and policemen
don't talk to me politely.
Why are you talking to me so politely?
I'm newly appointed in the prison.
So I couldn't learn its customs.
And I don't believe that one should
talk impolitely with C-class prisoners.
Number 12, Deputy
Mahesh is calling you.
Where..
- Next to the tap.
Why are you standing there? Come here.
How's your patient now?
She has very high fever.
I see.
Yes, after inquiring, I found
out that your case isn't true.
I also consulted a lawyer.
If I could know something else
from you.. - Thank you very much.
The case isn't false.
I wonder why the doctor
appointed you at the hospital.
It's dangerous for you to
serve a tuberculosis patient.
I took up this duty willingly.
Kalyani.
You forgot your ticket
at the ward yesterday.
Here. Keep it with you carefully.
How's that old woman?
I'll take a look.
Both the lungs are infected.
But I'm sure I'll cure her quickly.
I'll start giving her booster
shots from tomorrow.
Doctor.
The good news is that Ramdai
slept peacefully at night.
And she was fine in the morning.
You saved that poor lady.
I won't accept the entire
credit for saving her life.
You looked after her all day.
Nursing is the best
remedy for this ailment.
Ramdai, are you fine now?
- Yes, sir.
Let me check the temperature.
Should I keep resting even now?
No, go for walks.
But beware of the monsoon winds.
Kalyani.
Listen.
Yes.
You look beautiful when
you're engrossed in work.
How long will Ramdai
keep her mouth shut?
Oh.
"O sweet little bird, what're you
chirping in the morning? Tell me."
"What're you chirping?"
"O sweet little bird, what're you
chirping in the morning? Tell me"
"What're you chirping?"
"I'm a mynah who lives in the cage.
My wings are useless."
"There's a big gap between us.
How should I come to you?"
"How should I come to you?"
"O sweet little bird, what're you
chirping in the morning? Tell me.
"What're you chirping?"
"It's the spring. The garden is
blooming. The mango trees are lush."
"I peep through the window.
Spring has arrived."
"Spring has arrived."
"O sweet little bird, what're you
chirping in the morning? Tell me."
"What're you chirping?"
Number 7? I just went to the
kitchen and you started singing!
Madam, I'm in a good
mood today. - I get that.
But the prison rule is to keep
your mouth shut, whatever the mood!
From tomorrow, you'll have
to grind those lentils again!
Sir, give some
medicines to Kalyani too.
She couldn't sleep in
the night, due to headache.
What happened to you?
Nothing. I caught a cold.
You shouldn't be careless about
your health. Let me check your pulse.
What a taste! Romancing a criminal!
You're educated, a doctor,
have a nice job.
Maintaining family's
dignity's also important.
Brother, this is called love!
"Love doesn't
distinguish between religions."
"When you're hungry, you
don't mind even soiled dishes."
"Love doesn't
distinguish between religions."
"When you're hungry, you
don't mind even soiled dishes."
What's the use if one
doesn't become blind in love?
Softly! He's coming!
He looks like Romeo!
This is not a place to romance,
but its prison!
If you want to do this, then go out.
Oh God! Don't you've any other topic?
The deputy jailor has gone to the
jailor to talk about this matter.
Be patient till then.
Kalyani, what are you doing here?
The doctor has sent special
food for you at the hospital!
Rich food!
She's so lucky!
Eggs and butter along
with chapatti! Great!
Oh my, I'm such a fool!
Had I served that old woman,
then even I would've enjoyed now!
And you would've
trapped some young man too!
Doctor.
Why did you send special food for me?
Are all those, who serve
tuberculosis patients in hospitals..
..served special food?
I don't know about others,
but this is the rule here.
But do I need this diet, or
are you doing a favor to me?
No. You do need it.
Can I ask you something Kalyani?
- Yes.
Why did you risk your life,
serving a tuberculosis patient?
Whatever the reason might be..
..but I won't let you
commit suicide here.
Why do you want to save a
downtrodden girl like me?
Do you know why I'm
serving this punishment?
I know.
You still want to save me?
- Yes.
Don't ruin your future,
repenting for your past.
How'll you benefit by this?
- Benefit?
In no way. Is profit and
loss everything in life?
Don't you feel
anything more than this?
The danger signal.
C'mon!
Long live!
- Revolution!
Hail Hanuman! Ocean
of wisdom! Protect us.
The emissary of Ram, very strong!
- What's it?
Those revolutionaries have
created havoc again! Oh god!
What's this danger signal for, Warden?
From the time the freedom
fighters have come to this prison..
..there's no peace!
They do something or the other!
Today Vinay Ghosh
slapped our deputy jailor!
Go back to your places!
19, 20, 21, 22, 23!
All's well!
What's the matter, Kamla?
- Nothing.
I'll grind it. Ramdai is
fine now. I've no work there.
Move aside.
Kamla, if doctor comes to know,
he won't spare you!
What've you to do with that?
Shut up! Don't talk nonsense!
- You're talking nonsense!
No, Kamla.
- No!
It's enough of this daily nonsense!
Wonder what she thinks of herself!
What will you do?
Taunt again and see.
- I will!
Shut up, you dusky!
- What did you say?
I won't spare you!
- Leave me!
Kamla! Kamla!
I'll show you.
Leave. - Stop.
No!
- Kamla!
Murder!
- Quiet!
As soon as I disappeared,
you created havoc here!
I'll complain about each
one of you to the jailor!
I've noticed that you disappear
as soon as the doctor arrives!
Yesterday doctor was
asking me about you.
I'm right near the tap.
Hello sir.
- Hello.
Where's your nurse?
She was right here. Kalyani!
Where is Kalyani? - She's
sitting near to the tap. She sent me.
Shall I call her?
- No, it's ok.
You're fine. I needn't come everyday.
My head was aching yesterday.
I couldn't sleep.
Don't worry. I'll send the medicines.
You'll be fine.
Give this to Kalyani.
Doctor has sent this for you.
'Kalyani, there's no
need to be afraid of me.'
'Now I'll stay away from you.'
What's written?
Can I say something?
What?
- You're making a mistake.
Why are you ignoring such a
great man like the doctor?
You won't understand.
I will. I'm also a woman.
It's no use troubling
someone and being sad yourself.
I don't have any other way.
I'm not just what I seem to be.
Where should I hide my past?
And if you want to attain anything
in life, you've to pay for it.
But I've nothing to give.
Then will you keep
running away all your life?
You'll be released from jail some day.
Where'll you go then? What'll you do?
Kamla, you took leave from work,
saying that you aren't well.
Instead of taking rest,
you're chatting here.
Go.
- Yes.
Kalyani, give me your card.
Why do you want this?
For the board meeting.
- What's that?
Don't you know? There're board
meetings in prisons every year.
Those prisoners who've behaved well..
..they're released before time.
Won't they release me before time?
Definitely!
By lying down and
eating good food here..
..are you doing a
favor on the government?
Warden, listen.
Actually, don't talk
like that. It hurts.
No! I was just joking!
You know, the deputy
jailor didn't propose your name.
But the jailor didn't agree.
He proposed Phool Bano and
your name for the meeting!
The Warden came for
your card, didn't she?
I sent her.
The jailor had cancelled your name,
but I forced them not to do so!
Thank you.
Don't thank me! This was
such an ordinary thing.
Whenever I see you, I feel that..
..the female prisoners shouldn't
be given such a filthy dress.
Such a dirty cloth! And
the stitching is terrible!
I'll definitely write to them..
..that educated and
decent girls like you..
You think I'm decent?
What are you saying?
I mean you.. - Had you spoken
so impolitely to a decent girl..
..then she would've insulted you.
Sir, the entire
prison is discussing this.
I wonder whether you know
it or not. It's disgraceful!
Our doctor and..
That C-class prisoner.. Kalyani!
Examining the
patient is just an excuse!
Both of them sit for
hours together and..
I mean, even if you don't
believe this, these rumors..
Anything else?
Yes.. this is the board meeting file.
There're still some days
left for the board meeting.
Give it to me later.
Yes, sir.
You may leave.
What?
- What did he say?
Nothing, he didn't even bother.
And it never will.
That doctor is the son of
our Jailor's father's friend.
So what? The Jailor isn't everything.
He has a superior too.
If we don't protect hose
female prisoners..
..then who will! - Absolutely!
Ramdai is sitting outside, in
the sun. I'll call her.. - No.
I came here to meet you.
For the last time, I want
to hear from you.. - Doctor!
I want to know your decision today.
First listen to my past.
- Kalyani.
I'm only concerned with your present.
But when your society humiliates you..
..because of me, what then?
I don't care about them.
Why are you quiet? Answer me.
Even today if you can't
understand what my heart wants..
..then I'll wait for you.
- No!
This'll never happen!
Please forgive me!
In line! Doctor! The
superintendent is here!
I'll see if all's well.
Is she the C-class prisoner?
- Yes.
What's she doing here?
- She's nursing the T.B. Patient.
Doctor, how's the patient now?
She's fine from the past few days.
I see.
By the way, send this
patient to Sadar hospital tomorrow.
I'll ask the civil surgeons
to arrange for a bed for her.
And give her some hard work to do.
Wow! Beautiful flowers!
But they shouldn't be in prison.
Attention! Salute!
The princess has
become a pauper again!
I've spent so many years in prison..
but I've never seen such lovers!
What's this? Your resignation?
You want to quit the job?
Yes, brother.
Tell me.
Is your resignation connected to
superintendent's behavior yesterday's?
No.
- Then why are you resigning?
Actually, the prison doesn't suit me.
You know that before coming here..
..I used to work at
the civil hospital.
There I've seen ill patients,
who I can cure.
Here I've seen ill-minded people,
whom I can't cure.
Anyway, send my resignation
to the I.G.'s office today.
I'll take your leave. I've a lot
of work is pending at the hospital.
Look Devendra..
..it's not good to be so
sentimental regarding your job.
What'll mom think if
you quit this job?
You know her.
She wanted me to quit the
job and practice in my city.
Can I ask you something?
- Yes.
Do you really love Kalyani
or is this just an attachment?
No. I really love her.
Knowing the fact that she's punished
for committing a murder? - Yes.
But now all this is useless.
She refused to accept me.
- Why?
She didn't tell me the reason.
Ok, I'll take your leave.
Give my regards to your mother.
All's well!
Sir, when did you arrive?
- Just now.
Devendra?
- Yes, mom.
You returned all of a sudden.
Did you take leave?
No, I quit my job.
- Quit? Why?
I didn't like it.
Good. I'll finish my prayers.
You freshen up. - Ok.
Devendra.
I've been noticing
that you remain sad.
Tell me what the matter is.
- It's nothing.
Look. I'm your mother.
You can't hide anything from me.
What's wrong with you?
There's no point knowing about it.
It'll make you upset instead.
And I can't even
share it with you openly.
Ok, does Mahesh know about it?
Yes, he does.
Forget this tea. It's gone cold.
I'll bring hot tea for you.
"Send brother this time, father."
"Call me during the monsoon."
"When my childhood friends return."
"Send a message to me."
"Send brother this time, father."
"We'll swing again,
under the mango tree."
"It'll rain pitter-patter."
"The bliss of monsoon
will arrive again.."
"..in your courtyard, father."
"My eyes well up. My heart yearns.."
"..when I remember my childhood."
"Send brother this time, father."
"My youth snatched my childhood."
"It stole my dolls."
"Father, you raised
me with such love."
"Then why've I become a stranger?"
"I've neither received any letter.."
"..nor has anyone come to meet me."
"Send brother this time, father."
"Call me during the monsoon."
Sushila said that you wanted
to meet me. What's the matter?
Don't include my name
in the board meeting.
I don't want to be released.
Why?
Where will I go?
There's no refuge
for me outside prison.
But I know that someone
wanted to help you sincerely..
..but you refused.
I'm talking about doctor.
I've known him a long time.
He's a decent man, who
follows sincere principles.
I respect him too.
I couldn't accept his
love for his betterment.
I didn't want..
..to ruin his
unblemished life due to my past.
What's your past that
scares you even today..
..and is ruining your future?
Why are you quiet? Answer me.
Do you want to know?
- Yes.
My father was a post
master in Bahadur Nagar.
We were a small family.
Mom, dad, my brother and I.
Mom expired when I was a child.
My elder brother
gave me motherly love.
Brother deeply influenced my life.
He had a group in the village..
..and their job was to
help the poor and needy.
For this work, very often he
had to stay out many days.
But dad never
stopped or restricted him.
He was proud of him.
Once, 10 miles away from a village..
..a flood occurred at
the river due to rains.
Brother immediately
went there with his group.
And then..
..he never came back!
After a few days, we
came to know that..
..in order to save a
girl of my age, my brother..
I can't say it! I
won't be able to say it!
It's ok.
Write your story
down and give it to me.
I'll ask Sushila to arrange
for a pencil and book for you.
Sushila.
Take her to her ward.
Hail the motherland!
Why is there a commotion in the
male ward? - Hail the motherland!
The revolutionary in our ward
is going to be hanged to death.
The warden was saying
that his widow mother
and sister have come
since evening, at the gate.
Oh, god!
Hail the motherland!
- Quiet!
"Don't cry, mother.
You have many sons."
"I'm fortunate that I was
useful to the motherland."
"Don't cry, mother.
You have many sons."
"Don't cry."
"Send me happily.
My life will be successful."
"Your son took birth crying,
but he's smiling why dying."
"Don't cry, mother.
You have many sons."
"Don't cry."
"Wherever my ashes
mingles with the land's soil."
"A hundred roses will bloom."
"Don't cry, mother.
You have many sons."
"Don't cry."
"I won't be alive, but
whenever there's darkness."
"You'll see a new glowing
star amongst the stars."
"Don't cry, mother.
You have many sons."
"Don't cry."
"I'll take birth again,
when the country is free."
"Mother!"
"I'll take birth again,
when the country is free."
"When the national flag will
is hoisted on the Himalayas."
"Don't cry, mother.
You have many sons."
"Just as one changes clothes.."
"..the soul discards
the old body at death.."
"..and takes on a new body.."
"..to begin a new life."
All's well!
Sir, Kalyani has
sent this book for you.
Ok.
"The other day, I
became very restless.."
"..while talking
about brother's death."
"Brother meant everything to me."
"I can't tell you.."
"..how lonely I became after him."
"I disliked everything in the world."
"I would sit by the river and
stare at that place for hours.."
"..where brother bid us goodbye."
"Father tolerated the shock of
brother's death very calmly."
"He used to try to keep
himself busy in work.."
"..or in devotional poetry."
"He used to stare at
brother's photo with sad eyes."
"Without a drop of tear in his eyes."
Hail God.
The sun never sets
on the British empire.
What are you thinking, father?
I'm thinking about you.
Everyone says that I
should get you married now.
This is what I don't like about you.
Why do you listen to others?
I'll just study.
What if I was your son?
No.
You're good as a daughter.
God gave me a son.
But in vain.
Did he care about his old father?
He ran to help the poor,
leaving his own house.
And sacrificed his life for them.
Whatever it is.
His soul is resting in peace.
Where did you run away again,
leaving your studies?
I'll write to aunt that
you don't study at all!
Sister, if I didn't study..
..then how did I become
the monitor of my class?
Why did you bring all this here?
Had you called me, I would've
come there and had breakfast.
Rubbish! If I called you at 8,
you would've come after 10!
What to do, dear? I
can't work like I used to.
I get tired soon. Keep it.
Oh, God! A bomb blast again!
Where, Mr. Mishra!
A 14 year old boy in Muzzafarpur..
..threw a bomb on a British magistrate,
who was sitting on a carriage.
What's the world come to?
Nowadays children start
making bombs at a very small age!
There was peace in our village.
But from the time that revolutionary
boy has been house arrested here,
I'm afraid bombs will start
exploding in our village too!
Looking at him, I get very scared!
Who're you talking about?
That Vikas Ghosh?
I saw him at inspector
Hussain's house the other day.
He seemed to be very innocent.
Don't praise such a boy,
or else you'll be fired.
You should stay away from them.
"Next to the Jamuna river,
I met Kanhaiya."
Who did you meet?
Not me, Shobha, but
Goddess Radha did! - Really?
Where are you coming from?
- Aunt was not well.
I came to see her. I'm
going home now. - Ok, wait.
Even I've to go there.
Sister Prabha will tutor me.
I'll inform father
and then come with you.
I came so far while talking.
I'm going.
I'll definitely give you my
in-laws' address before leaving.
Do write to me!
Listen! Come here!
The way to the river..
Why did they run
away on seeing that man?
It's obvious. Don't you
know who he is.. - Who?
He's the revolutionary Vikas Ghosh..
..who's under house
arrest in this village.
It's police's strict order
that no one should talk to him.
He has a unique smile.
You find it unique!
I'm scared! I'm leaving.
You better leave too.
Sister Prabha.
- Yes, Kalyani.
I'm done with my studies.
I'll go home now.
How'll you go? It's
raining so heavily.
I doubt it'll stop.
You stay here tonight.
No. If I don't reach home,
dad will get worried.
I'll ask the peon of
the school to inform him.
You'll fall sick if you get drenched.
Come, help me in the kitchen.
What's the news, Tarun?
You've been assigned
an important work.
You know that Vikas from our
group is under house arrest here.
You'll have to deliver a
letter to him by tomorrow.
It's important. He
should get it by tomorrow.
Fine, I will. But why did
you come so late at night?
I came long back..
..but there's tight police surveillance
in this village due to Vikas.
That's why I'm hiding in the jungle.
You're still awake.
You must've heard everything then.
Sister, was it your brother?
Yes. Look, don't
tell anyone about him.
Kalyani, everything is ruined!
I think Tarun is caught!
The police might be here any moment.
You take this letter and run away.
Give this letter to
Vikas at any cost tomorrow.
Me?
- Yes. No one will suspect you.
Go. Hurry up.
Not from here. Go from the backyard,
through the jungle.
Who came here?
- No one.
Someone definitely
came here! We'll search!
As you wish.
- Go! Search the entire place!
Constable!
- What?
Let me pluck some flowers from there!
- No!
Actually, there's a
prayer back at our place.
And I need are these
flowers to worship god..
..or else the
prayers can't be conducted!
I searched everywhere, but
I didn't find such flowers!
Please!
- No one is allowed to go in!
You're very sweet! I'll just take 2
flowers! - Where have you come from?
Don't you know that I'm
the post master's daughter?
Mr. Sadashiv's daughter?
- Yes!
Okay. Pluck them.
Greetings, inspector.
Greetings.
- Welcome, sir! Have a seat!
What's the matter?
You've surrounded my
house with barbwires.
You've appointed two
Constables to guard my house.
Why am I being
honored all of a sudden?
We'll have to. You're a special guest!
Are you completely unaware
of last night's incident?
I heard the sounds of crackers.
And those sounds
have ruined our slumber!
No!
- Give it to me!
You appointed a dumb and deaf servant.
I'm not allowed to
talk to the villagers.
From your new arrangement, it
seems like I can't even go out.
No. After last night's incident, we
had to take precautionary measures.
But I'm facing problems.
I realize your problems,
but I can't do anything.
Yes, I can permit you to talk,
not to the villagers..
..but the government officials.
I won't mind that.
Thank you so much.
- Ok, I'll take your leave.
Come to the police station
for the attendance. - Ok.
It's ok! She's the
post master's daughter!
How long will you stand
holding all this? Keep it.
Let me complete my work
and then have breakfast.
You finish your work. I'm
standing here till then.
Can I come in?
- Who's it?
Come. It's you!
Greetings.
Please sit.
- Yes.
I couldn't find the
courage to meet you.
Now that inspector has permitted me,
so I came to trouble you.
It's no trouble at all. Sit.
I'll order tea.
- Yes, I'll definitely have tea.
Won't I get pudding to eat?
What? Yes. - Sorry! As soon
as I saw this, I'm hungry!
Gopal, ask Kalyani to send tea
and pudding for Mr. Vikas. - Yes.
Don't mind my being informal.
- No.
It's a rule that the host
always force their guests to eat..
..but the guest refuses.
But our society is different.
We hardly get good food to eat.
That's why whenever
I see such a thing..
..I don't feel like leaving it!
Gopal, take. You give him.
No! I'm scared!
- Why? Go!
The inspector was saying that
you've a number of poetries.
If you don't mind, can I come
and listen to them sometimes?
Yes, absolutely! I'll be glad!
Why are you standing there?
Keep the snacks here.
Who's this boy?
- He's the son of my widowed sister.
He lives with me and studies here.
The pudding's very tasty!
Who cooked it?
My daughter, Kalyani.
She was standing here when you came.
I forgot to introduce you.
- Never mind.
Gopla. Call your sister.
- Ok.
Sister!
Uncle is calling you.
Tell him that I'm going for a bath.
- Okay.
Who gave that letter to you?
Sister Prabha.
Is she Prakash's elder sister?
- Yes.
When did Prakash come to
this village? - Mr. Vikas!
The pudding was so tasty that..
..I'll have to come to
your place again for that!
She was the post
master's daughter, wasn't she?
By the riverside! Wow!
- I forgot my way and came here.
But don't forget your
attendance in the evening.
How can I forget in
your presence, inspector?
Sister!
Where are you?
- See!
Oh gosh! I was scared!
I scared you!
- Yes!
Aren't you scared of Mr. Vikas?
Why?
I'm very scared of him!
When he comes this time..
..ask him the technique of making
bombs. - I'll definitely teach you!
Oh gosh!
- Wait! Don't run away!
Is your dad at home?
- Yes. Come.
"O night, today you
decide my fate."
"Let me catch
a glimpse of my beloved."
"And my life
will be successful."
"I feel like I've
the entire world."
Wonderful.
You've heard very little, dear.
Reading this poetry
makes you feel blissful.
Sit, dear.
Your dad recites such
good devotional poetry.
You might know it as well.
She does recite it sometimes.
That's what I wanted to know!
You must sing too.
Not worth singing in front of anyone.
- She's got a sweet voice..
..but she didn't get
a chance to learn.
But this is not any singing
competition. Sing as you can.
I spoke impolitely to her!
So what? She's younger to you.
"Since the time you
came in my life, beloved"
"Since the time you came
in my life, beloved.."
"..my life has become beautiful."
"You read my eyes and
understood what's in my heart."
"I shouldn't have met you."
"Since the time you
came in my life, beloved"
"You fell in love with
this dusky looking girl."
"When I saw you and
peered in your eyes."
peered in your eyes.."
"..my eyes looked
adorned without the kohl."
"Since the time you came
in my life, beloved.."
"..my life has become beautiful."
"I sit at the shore like crazy Radha."
"I return without fetching water."
"It's a strange kind of illness."
"Since the time you came
in my life, beloved.."
"..my life has become beautiful."
"I won't be able to
tolerate this sweet pain."
"I'm a delicate girl."
"I won't be able to bear.
Don't come closer to me."
"Since the time you
came in my life, beloved."
"My life has become beautiful."
"You read my eyes and
understood what's in my heart."
"I shouldn't have met you."
"Since the time you
came my life, beloved."
In the dark night, Radha is
secretly going to meet Krishna.
That's why she has
worn dark colored clothes.
Blue sari, blue bangles,
and kohl in her eyes.
But when her face glows in the dark..
..she's afraid that
someone might see her.
She asks "God to take
away my fair complexion.."
"..and give me a dark complexion."
That's all for today.
Now let's have sweets
prepared by Kalyani.
Can't you taste both together?
No.
We won't come to
know which is sweeter.
These sweets or the poetry.
You're a glutton.
Glutton! That's a compliment!
Girls are valued
because of gluttons like us!
Or else who's bothered about them?
- Why?
Don't we girls have any other work
besides satisfying men's hunger?
It's a difficult job
to satisfy hunger, dear.
You all are the Goddesses of food..
..in front of who even the
gods bow down.. - Absolutely!
Without eating Sujata's porridge..
..Siddhartha would've never
become Buddha.
Sir, someone wants to send a
telegram. Says it's urgent. - Okay.
You sit. I'll finish my work.
Oh, God.
Do you agree with dad?
Regarding?
Girls should always be in the kitchen.
They can't do anything else.
Three years back, I wouldn't
have agreed with your dad.
I would've said that women can equal..
..men in every aspect.
But once, after seeing a woman,
my opinion changed.
Did she belong to your group?
No,
She had no relations with our group.
Three years back..
..while looting ammunition, my
partner was shot by the police.
When I was running
with him on my shoulder..
'I was tired of running,
but I had no time to rest.'
'The sound of the police's
footsteps was coming closer.'
'My injured partner
was striving for water.'
'Finally I saw a safe place
and made him laid him down there'
'..and went to fetch water.'
'When I came back, I
saw that he was dead.'
'The one who wanted to see
the country free, had died.'
'Suddenly, I heard 'Hands up'.'
'The police found us due to the
drops of blood on the ground.'
'I was sleeping in prison.'
'Suddenly someone woke me.'
'That stranger got me out of
prison and brought me near a river.'
'There was a boat over there.
He asked me to wait.'
'He had to return the prison keys.'
'When he came back, giving the
keys to a woman standing in a hut..'
'..I asked "Who that kind
lady was, who got me released".'
'He told me that she was
the inspector's wife.'
'I was shocked.'
'Later when that man told me that..'
'..she has helped a
lot of revolutionaries.'
'I was amazed.'
'After seeing motherly love
in that inspector's wife..'
'..my opinion about women changed.'
'There's no need for
women to be like men.'
'They can help us from home.'
I'll make a move. It's time for me
to register my attendance. - Wait.
I'll light the lamp.
Who named you Kalyani?
I don't know. I think brother did.
It suits you.
Others' names are just for namesake,
but yours reflects your identity.
You're really Kalyani (well-wisher).
It is said that the eyes
reflect what's in your mind.
If this is true, then
I'm not wrong about you.
Why? What did you see in my eyes?
Your gleaming eyes
remind me of dew on flowers.
'Blue sari, blue bangles,
kohl in the eyes.'
"Take away my fair
complexion and give me a dark one."
"I'll hide in the night.
Give me my beloved."
"Take away my fair
complexion and give me a dark one."
"I'll hide in the night.
Give me my beloved."
"My shyness stops me, but my
restlessness takes me ahead."
"I don't know where I'm going,
someone please tell me."
"Take away my fair
complexion and give me a dark one."
"I'll hide in the night.
Give me my beloved."
"The moon peeps
secretly though the clouds."
"I curse you! You're
smiling after troubling me!"
"Take away my fair
complexion and give me a dark one."
"I'll hide in the night.
Give me my beloved."
"There's something that I've lost..
"..there's something
that I've achieved."
"There's something that I've lost..
"..there's something
that I've achieved."
"Where's my mind leading me?"
"Take away my fair
complexion and give me a dark one."
"I'll hide in the night.
Give me my beloved."
"Take away my fair
complexion and give me a dark one."
Do you know why Vikas didn't
come here since a few days?
He's ill. I met
inspector on the way. He told me.
It's difficult for him to find food.
Is there barley at home?
Yes.
Why don't you cook barley and
send it to him through Shambhu?
I'll send it right away.
Hail Lord.
Did you give him the barley?
- Yes.
But he wasn't eating.
When I told him that you
cooked it, he ate it immediately!
He respects you a lot!
Okay, go and give hookah to dad.
- Yes.
Listen!
Is he fine now?
- Oh gosh! I forgot to ask this!
Oh no!
I came because I was
feeling restless today.
So late at night.
Yes. Ok, I'll leave.
What happened?
You've high fever!
Your body is burning!
I was.. ill in the evening.
That's why I fainted.
I'll manage.
No! I won't let you go
in such heavy rains!
Let it stop raining, you
can leave then. Come in.
I'm thirsty.
I'll get water.
I.. Did I fall asleep?
I feel asleep. How are you now?
I'm fine.
Mr. Vikas!
Someone is calling you.
What will we do now?
Mr. Vikas!
Don't worry. I'll see.
What you did was bad!
Anyway, come on.
Where's the post master?
Yes, call him. Explain to him
that decent people live here!
Instead, send her to some brothel..
- Hey! Mind your tongue!
I won't tolerate my
wife's humiliation!
Your wife?
- Yes.
Sir, ask him when and how he
got married.. - Keep quiet!
Excuse me.
Come. Take blessings from your dad.
Don't hesitate.
Come with me.
We want your blessings. Please
bless us that we live happily.
I'm solely responsible for
whatever happened today.
Believe me.
I'm not marrying her just to
save you from getting humiliated.
I really love..
I.. never imagined that..
..I'd have to come to you
for her in such circumstances.
The police are waiting for me.
I need time to think.
Is your dad not well?
Go and serve tea to dad.
Why? You serve him everyday.
Why should I go today?
No. You serve him.
Wonder what's wrong with everyone!
Everyone's upset! Give it!
There's an order from Sadar that
Vikas has to be sent there today.
He wanted to meet you
before going. I allowed him.
What do I do? I can't find
any solution, inspector.
I can understand
your condition, brother.
But I think you should get
Kalyani married to Vikas.
But he's not well settled. - It's
the question of dignity right now.
If you refuse, then the
villagers will start taunting.
Honestly speaking these
revolutionaries keep their word.
I think the restrictions on
him will also be lifted soon.
I suggest don't hesitate
in getting them married.
The rest is your decision.
I'll take your leave.
Don't you want to say anything?
I'd be satisfied if I could hear you
say that I didn't make any mistake.
Here's my address. Write to me.
The police are waiting for me.
I have to go to Sadar.
Did you think about us?
Yes, son.
I've decided to get
Kalyani married to you.
Vikas, I've no one else in
this world, besides Kalyani.
Don't ever hurt her.
Mr. Vikas.
Listen.
Mr. Vikas, hurry up.
How are you, Sadashiv?
Have a seat, doctor.
That school teacher Raghu was
saying that you've slowed down.
Yes. I've been ill since a few days
Poor teacher does my work.
I was busy too. After a long time,
I've managed to come.
Did Mr. Vikas write to you?
Yes, 2 months after he left.
He wrote that the
police have released him..
..but he's down with malaria.
He'll come here as
soon as he gets well.
But 2 months have passed.
Neither did he come,
nor did his letter.
Didn't you write to him?
Four times, but he didn't reply.
That's strange.
It'd be better if
Kalyani got married soon.
The villagers are gossiping.
They're spreading strange rumors.
I think you should get
Kalyani married to some other boy.
It will shut everyone up.
I can't commit a sin in
order to shut everyone's mouth!
Is marriage everything in life?
Vikas has accepted her as his wife..
..and even I agreed.
I believe that Kalyani
and Vikas are married.
Kalyani, there's a letter.
My letter!
It's not for you.
The letter that you sent
to Mr. Vikas has returned.
I hope dad didn't see.
No. I kept it with me.
Kalyani, listen.
Is your marriage date fixed?
I don't know. - You don't
know when your marriage is!
But do invite us!
Invitation for what?
She's already married!
She won't marry again!
Did you call me, sister?
Yes.
Did Vikas reply to your letter?
No. My letter came back.
He doesn't live on that address.
Tarun wrote the same to me.
He sent a bad news too.
How do I tell you?
You'll be very upset.
I'm used to enduring sorrows now.
Tell me.
He has written that Vikas
doesn't live in Lucknow.
He works in Patna. And..
He got married.
Kalyani, women are
born to endure sorrows.
Make yourself strong.
I'm very strong.
We've been listening since
months that he'll write to you!
Don't puzzle us now! - It's a lie!
He neither wrote to them,
nor will he ever write!
He's gone!
What can I do if we
didn't write to us?
Why are you asking us?
Did you ask us
before calling him home..
..and reciting romantic
poetry in front of your daughter?
Please keep quiet!
How many can you stop? The
entire village is saying this!
Bear the consequences of your deeds!
- Fine.
I did what I wanted to. And
now you do what you want to!
This is a government office!
If you people threaten me here..
..I'll complain to the police!
- Yes! Go!
We'll see how you live in this
locality with your daughter!
Won't we?
- Yes!
Kalyani.
I can't find a clean drape.
Didn't the washer-man come?
Answer me!
Gopal!
Yes.
Go and get my washed
drape from the washer man!
Sister sent me to him yesterday..
..but he said that the
villagers have threatened him.
That's why he won't
wash our clothes.
You go.
Kalyani, listen. You
write to Vikas today.
No. I won't.
- Why?
Fine.
I will.
No. You don't write either.
You won't write, neither will
you let me. What do you want to do?
People insult me in my own house
and you want me to keep quiet!
I get so humiliated because of you!
Either you leave this house,
or I'll leave it!
'Dad, I'm leaving this house.'
'But, trust me I'm
not angry with you.'
'I'm going because I don't
have any other alternative.'
'I can't see the
villagers insulting you.'
'Until I'm here,
your sorrows will grow.'
'And I..
..can't see you sad because of me.'
'Had I told you this before,
you wouldn't have allowed me.'
'Perhaps, I wouldn't even feel
like going after seeing you.'
'That's why I'm leaving at night,
without informing you.'
'Dad..
'Don't search for me.'
'Don't worry about me either.'
'Your blessings will
always protect me.'
'Dad..
..please forgive me.'
"Someone is calling
you out every time."
"The one who goes
there never returns."
"Someone tell me what secret is this?"
"O traveller, come back if possible."
"Don't forget this bank, this path."
See who it is.
It's you!
Where's your luggage?
Who have you come with?
- I've come alone.
Ok. Come in.
My dad told me about
you a few days back.
Why did you come all of a sudden,
without informing?
I couldn't live in
the village anymore.
I thought of staying
with you for a few days.
Is there no news about Mr. Vikas?
Why did you leave
the village suddenly?
Everyone started humiliating
my old father because of me.
I couldn't endure that.
Who's she?
- My friend, from our village.
It's ok. Don't touch. You've
come from outside. I've to pray.
Sit, Kalyani.
Daughter-in-law. She's the daughter..
..of the post master of your village?
Your dad was talking
about her, wasn't he?
There was a scandal in
your village because of her..
Mother, come here.
You shouldn't say all
this in front of her.
Look, I don't like to gossip
about anyone behind their back!
We have a family! We'll have to
follow the norms of the society!
If she wants to live here
then refuse her, got it?
Ok, mother. Go in.
Kalyani!
Don't mind mother.
Where will you wander?
You're under my oath. Wait
here until my husband returns.
He'll definitely
arrange something for you.
Come.
We came here with a lot
of expectations, doctor.
What should we do now?
She's in trouble.
Look, Pratap, I would've
definitely done something..
..if it was possible.
There's no work in my nursing
home that I can assign to her.
But our maid is on leave. We
need a replacement for her..
..who could wash the patients'
clothes or clean their rooms.
Will she do all this?
No! She won't!
- I will.
I'll do everything.
I just need shelter right now.
I've heard your story from them.
For now, you can start working here.
I'll make the arrangements to
make you a trained nurse later.
Where will she stay?
Nurse.
Yes, doctor?
Show her the room on the terrace,
next to the storeroom.
She'll stay there.
- Yes, doctor.
This is your room.
You'll back answer me! - Oh gosh!
Will you beat me with this?
Yes! I'll kill you! Why did
you serve me tea in a dirty cup?
What happened?
You ask what happened!
This big hospital of
yours is filled..
..with illiterate
nurses and useless maids!
What did she do?
My husband has
brought new cups for me.
But she served me tea in
this dirty and broken cup!
Why? How would I know that
your husband brought.. - Shut up!
Did you hear? She's
arguing with me in your presence!
You leave. Don't get angry..
Oh, God!
- Sit!
I've never seen such a woman!
She's so hot-tempered!
She hit the cup on my face!
If you don't arrange for
a good maid immediately..
..then I'll break all the
furniture of your hospital!
Calm down. I'll make complete
arrangements for your service, ok?
Listen.
The patient in room no. 3
is suffering from hysteria.
She gets very angry.
None of our maids
are able to handle her.
After observing your work, I think
you know how to control patients.
If you could take
her responsibility..
Don't worry. I'll see.
Good.
What do you want?
- The doctor has sent me.
Are you a nurse?
- No. I'm a maid.
Maid!
What's your name?
- Kalyani.
They've chosen a nice name for you!
Are you married?
- No.
So you're a damsel!
That's why you've
adorned yourself so much!
Wonder what you'd do
if you were beautiful..
What am I supposed to do?
Massage my feet!
Get up, you fool! How
dare you sit on my bed?
I'm sorry.. - Shut up!
Go and wash this bed sheet!
And listen.
I have tea numerous times.
I should get tea on the dot, get it?
Yes. - Now leave.
Kalyani!
Where the hell are you?
See, I've brought
flowers for you today!
You've bedecked yourself in
the morning and come to show-off!
There's no sugar in it!
I've brought sugar. You
can put as much you want.
Are you ordering me? Put sugar in it!
Mix it up!
Enough!
Where are you going?
Go and wash my clothes!
Wait! Open this window!
Shobha! Why did you arrive suddenly?
Why are you quiet?
- Kalyani..
You'll have to come to
Sadar hospital with me.
Hospital! What happened?
Your.. dad..
Dad!
Yes.
He came to my place,
searching for you.
He was coming here, but..
..he met with an accident on the way.
Recently his vision had become weak.
How is he now?
He's.. not fine.
Come on.
Sadashiv, who met with an accident
this morning, in which room is he?
Come.
Kalyani!
Can't you hear? She's calling you.
My throat's paining calling you
out and you didn't even listen!
Wow! Look at her face, as if
she'll drop dead right now!
What do I have to do?
What do you mean? Did you
forget that it's time for my tea?
Where the hell were you?
Go and make two cups of tea.
My husband is coming here.
Wait!
Go and get my talc from there!
Listen.
Don't you dare come decked
up in front of my husband!
Why are you sitting away from me?
Why are you quiet? Answer me.
Don't you love me?
Who is it?
You! What are you doing here?
You were secretly
overhearing our conversation!
Shameless!
- What's the matter, Shivani?
Who're you getting angry on?
- You sit calmly!
She's a shameless maid!
I'll teach her a lesson today!
I'll complain to the
doctor about you!
I'll get you thrown
out of here! Get lost!
Kalyani!
You're still standing here!
The patient in room no.
3 is very furious!
Quickly take tea for her!
Just one cup. Her husband left.
Doctor!
No. 3!
Nurse!
How can you say this,
doctor? She used to be very happy.
When I was with her this evening,
she was absolutely fine.
What happened in this brief while
that caused her to commit suicide?
I think..
- What?
Sorry, but I feel this
isn't a case of suicide.
Someone killed her.
- Impossible.
No one can commit this
crime in my nursing home.
Why did you suspect this?
I can't be sure..
..but when I was
with her this evening..
..she fought with a maid
and scolded her a lot.
Some downtrodden maids do such
things for revenge sometimes.
Call that maid. I'll talk..
- She's right behind you.
Kalyani! You're.. here?
Move!
Doctor, is your
entire staff present here?
Yes.
- And Mrs. Shivani's husband?
Yes, he's Mr. Vikas.
Mr. Vikas, I'm very sorry.
What have you to say about this?
- What?
Inspector, I think she
committed suicide. - No!
No! She didn't!
Murder! I murdered her!
Punish me! I killed her!
I killed her!
When I regained conscious..
..I realized that I had high fever.
In court, Dr. Verma
tried to prove that..
..while committing the crime..
..I was suffering through brain
fever and I wasn't in my senses.
That's why the judge
sentenced me to 8 years in jail.
Mr. Vikas tried to
meet me a few times..
..but I was too
embarrassed to meet him.
My crime was much bigger than his.
Jailor, this is my past.
Now you tell me. How can I
forget this and dream of my future?
How can I ruin a decent
man's unblemished life?
No, Mahesh. This is not possible.
I can't get my Devendra
married to a prisoner.
I told you the circumstances..
..in which that poor
girl committed this crime.
Will she have to suffer all
her life for that one mistake?
If our society doesn't accept
such criminals with an open heart..
..then crime will
increase all the more.
Where will these
unfortunate people go?
Admit her in the ashram that
you've opened for such girls.
I thought the same, but
after knowing her past,
I'm sure that Devendra made no
mistake in choosing that girl.
Devendra is my only son.
I could never imagine..
..that I'd have to
refuse any wish of his.
But this.. - I know that you
shouldn't be stubborn in this matter.
But I request you to read
what's written in this book.
Phool, are you missing your family?
Don't cry.
The board meeting is tomorrow.
The jailor has given your name too.
You'll be released soon.
All those who're present.
We haven't gathered
here to discuss her crime.
We just want to see how
Kalyani behaved in prison.
Has she followed the rules
and regulations of the prison?
Her record clearly shows
that not only in this prison..
..but her behaviour has been good
in every prison that she was in.
She was fabulous in this prison.
She risked her own life and
nursed a tuberculosis patient.
Such a sacrifice by a prisoner is
unparalleled in the history of crime.
I think this case
should be thought about.
Next case.
Wonder whether we'll
ever meet or not!
Don't cry, Phool. If you're
not released in this meeting..
..then you definitely will,
next time.
I'm leaving you people and going.
I've always troubled you.
Sister, please forget it
if possible.
Come, Kalyani. It's getting late.
Come.
I thought of sending you to my
ashram, but mother wrote to me.
Mother!
- Dr. Devendra's mother.
I call her mother too. Here.
'Kalyani dear, may God bless you.'
'I never saw you..
..but it seems as if
your beautiful face..
..is in front of me all the time.'
'When you'll marry my Devendra..
..'I'll become peaceful
and free of my worries.'
'I'm waiting for that
auspicious day.'
'Blessings.'
'Your mother.'
But.. does she know
everything about me?
She does. I told her everything.
She has decided to make
you her daughter-in-law..
..after thinking properly.
Don't cry, dear.
I wished to drop you there myself..
..but I'm not being granted a leave.
That's why I'm
sending you with Sushila.
But you'll have no
difficulty on the way.
I've made all the arrangements.
You're free from here..
..but you'll be imprisoned in
the prison of marriage forever.
Sushila.
Your tickets are with
our head clerk.
You'll have to take a
steamer to Manihari valley.
You'll have to board a train
at 4 in the morning from there.
That isn't a decent place. Beware.
Take Kalyani to my bungalow for now.
I've arranged food over there.
Ma'am, sit here. I'll be back
when it's time to board the steamer.
Come on time.
- Definitely.
Kalyani, you sit here.
I'll make
arrangements for food outside.
But I don't feel like eating.
That means you'll remain
hungry throughout the journey?
I won't be able to
survive without eating!
Let me see if we get
anything over here or not.
Is it fresh?
- Yes, ma'am.
Give me a quarter kilo.
- Ok.
When will the steamer arrive?
It's delayed. It'll
arrive along with the ship.
Medicine!
In the box!
Give me!
What should I say?
Did you suffer an attack again?
Yes! You're late! Where were you?
I went in searchof a stretcher
for you, but I couldn't find it.
I've to die someday, Prakash.
But you want to conduct my
final rituals even before I die!
Never mind! I still
have some strength!
I'll take your support.
- Do you know that man?
Vikas is suffering from
an infectious disease.
He has asked you to wash
your hands with an antiseptic.
How long has be been
in this condition?
Since a long time.
Are you his relative?
No. I know him.
Then you must know a
lot about his life.
I pity him.
He lost everything for the country.
He spent all his life in prison.
After getting released,
he got married..
..but still wasn't happy.
Because he had to marry helplessly.
Why?
Because after getting released,
the party leader ordered
him to marry the daughter of
..a top police officer's relative.
Police officer's relative?
- Yes.
First he refused..
..because he loved someone else..
..and had promised to marry her too.
But there was a deep secret
behind this order of the party.
Knowing the secrets of the
police with the help of that girl.
When brother Vikas learnt this..
..he sacrificed his
love for the country.
But his wife expired.
She was ill and was
admitted in a nursing home.
He says that she committed suicide.
Where are you taking him now?
He insists that he
wants to go to his village.
Although there are no
doctors there to take care of him.
We tried to explain to him..
..but he says that he
doesn't wish to live any longer.
Wash your hands quickly. I've
to book my place in the steamer.
I'll wash my hands. You leave.
Kalyani.
I know you don't want
to listen to me.
You've faced a lot of problems
and humiliation because of me.
I'm.. not defending myself..
..but whatever happened,
happened against my will.
I wrote everything
to you in a letter..
..but it came back to me.
Perhaps, you left the village
It's no use talking
about all this now.
I know, but let me say it.
Perhaps, destiny made us meet
so that I can apologize to you.
Otherwise I never
expected to meet you again.
Kalyani, I was really sorry to
fill your live with problems.
But..
I never asked anything from God.
I didn't even pray.
But until I'm alive..
..I'll always pray for
your happiness.
..your happiness. Your happiness.
"O oarsman!"
"My beloved's on the
other side. I'm here."
"Take me to the other side."
"My beloved's on the
other side. I'm here."
"Take me to the other side."
"My beloved's on the other side."
"Forget all the
memories we had completely."
"I had no good quality in me.
Forget all my bad qualities."
"Forget all the
memories we had completely."
"I had no good quality in me.
Forget all my bad qualities."
"For today's goodbye."
"Even after dying, I
would've waited for this goodbye."
"My beloved's on the
other side. I'm here."
"Take me to the other side."
"My beloved's on the other side."
"Don't play with my heart.
It'll destroy you."
"I belong to my beloved.
I'm his companion."
"It pulls me towards you."
"Every call pulls me towards you."
"My beloved's on the other side."
"O oarsman!"
Kalyani!
Where're you going? -
The one I should go to!
Don't be foolish!
We've to go the other way!
No, warden! I've to go there!
- Kalyani!
Please let me go!
Apologize to jailor on my behalf!
Kalyani, don't go there!
The streamer's departing!
Kalyani!
"I belong to my beloved.
I'm his companion."
"It pulls me towards you."
"Every call pulls me towards you."
"My beloved's on the other side."
"O oarsman!"