Where are you running away?
- No Mr.Khan, I am not running away.
I'II thought I'II go and work
part time somewhere...
and make a few annas so I can
take home dinner for my chiIdren.
When wiII I get my money?
I pIead with you,
give me some more time.
I cannot give you any more time.
Mr.Khan, I swear by my kids,
I wiII settIe your account...
when I get my this month's pay.
CrueI man,
you mentioned your kids again!
You know, the mention of chiIdren
meIts my heart.
How is your daughter?
- She is fine.
The IittIe girI
manages the entire home.
Sis, I'm coming.
- Where are you going?
I'II be back soon.
- But where are you going?
Go Ramu, I'II heIp her.
Aunt, better Ieave. If LaIa
sees you here, he'II be very angry.
Nothing wiII happen.
You go see what he wants.
Where is your father?
He hasn't returned
from the factory yet.
But the factory siren
went off Iong ago
Okay, when he comes,
ask him to do one of the two.
Either pay the rent,
or vacate the house.
I'II teII him.
Both can be done.
I have toId you severaI times...
make him vacate the house,
and take the rent from me.
You can deduct the rent
from my saIary every month.
These chiIdren don't Iet
me sit in peace for a moment!
Neither do they die,
nor Iet others Iive.
You curse other
peopIe's chiIdren aII day.
Perhaps that is why
God didn't bIess us with chiIdren.
He sureIy wiII.
You are so beautifuI...
Leave me. I have so many
chores to do in the kitchen.
Come soon.
Sis, he wants miIk.
- Yes, I know.
I have brought it.
Take, give it to him.
My baby wiII drink miIk.
Aunt, even I am hungry.
Ramu, shut-up!
I have kept rice to boiI for you.
Now I know where
my house Ioot is going.
Just a IittIe miIk
from your house is Iooting?
The baby was crying in hunger.
MiIIions of babies
are crying in hunger.
If I begin to worry
about aII of them...
I wiII have to go hungry.
What they owe us, they are not
giving, and you keep giving them more.
From today, we stop giving,
and start recovering.
UntiI I don't recover
every penny from Raghu...
I'II sit near his door.
- Listen!
Sis, I am hungry.
- I toId you rice is getting cooked.
It's getting cooked since so Iong.
Liar! You say rice is getting cooked.
It's your head getting cooked.
Father!
- You are caIIing your sister a Iiar?
She is not your sister, she is your
mother. She is my mother too.
Take this rice, dear.
What is this, father?
How did you cut your foot?
My work is such.
Why do you do such work
where you cut your feet?
I do it, so that the
soIace I am getting now...
I shouId get it aIways.
When I hug you two,
I forget aII my sorrows.
Okay father, you freshen up,
I'II cook rice.
Fine.
Come, my Munna!
I forgot you, my IittIe one.
Father, get up, the rice is ready.
It's ready?
Get up son, Iet's eat.
LaIaji! I was coming to meet you.
Is it? I know that.
That is why I came to meet you.
LaIaji, I wiII settIe your
account next month.
The house rent, the grocery biII.
One who wants to pay,
does no run Iike that.
Where wiII I run away? You have
aIways heIped me in troubIed times.
When I Iost my wife,
you onIy heIped me.
How can I ever forget that?
- That's what I've come to remind you.
When the job is done,
peopIe often forget the favor.
LaIaji, I pay your instaIIment
every month...
then even if I have to make my
chiIdren go hungry, or burden myseIf.
I have paid the principIe,
onIy the interest remains.
Haven't you heard that a Iender
cares more for the interest than principIe.
I want to recover my interest too.
So I'II take your cycIe.
CycIe?
- Yes cycIe.
But LaIaji, Iisten!
If you take the cycIe...
how wiII I reach the factory on time?
- Leave home a IittIe earIy.
LaIaji...that's the
Iast siren of the factory.
PIease give me my cycIe, LaIaji.
I am aIready Iate.
Come what may,
I won't give you the cycIe today.
I pIead with you, LaIaji.
Give me the cycIe today, I'II myseIf
come and give it to you tomorrow.
I don't beIieve in tomorrow.
Come, BhoIa.
You are in a Iot of hurry, Raghu.
- Let me go, I'm aIready Iate.
That is why the manager has
asked you to go and rest at home.
Someone eIse wiII do the work.
You go and teII the manager
I'II do doubIe the work.
Just Iet me sit on the job,
I'II work hard.
The manager wiII himseIf reIent
on seeing my work. Let me go.
Didn't you hear my orders?
- Manager, don't dismiss me.
Have mercy on me.
My chiIdren wiII die of hunger.
I....no!
Doctor, how is Raghu?
He has Iost his sight.
He's turned bIind.
Aunt!
Father!
Take the chiIdren home.
Don't cry, Ramu.
Sis, father won't be
abIe to see anything now?
No Ramu.
- Not even you?
No.
- Not even me?
Doctor...doctor,
return my vision to me.
How wiII I Iive without my eyes?
How wiII I feed my chiIdren?
Return my vision!
Why are you siIent, doctor?
I am heIpIess,
that's why I am siIent.
Doctor, do something,
do anything!
If you cannot do something,
give me poison.
I can die, but not bear to
see my chiIdren crying with hunger.
Doctor, where are you? Doctor!
The doctor has Ieft.
- He Ieft?
Yes. You take rest.
- Rest?
This is that banyan tree.
Go home and eat. Go!
Where are you running? Wait!
You thieves!
What are you doing!
- You are bent on bIowing up my
weaIth.
The chiIdren were hungry.
I couId not bear it.
Besides, you wiII earn a good deed.
I am worried about this Iife and you
are thinking of doing good deeds.
Instead of donation my weaIth, why
don't you send them to an orphanage?
How can they even go to an
orphanage?
That's aIso true. Those chiIdren
whose father is aIive...
are not considered as orphans.
It wouId be better if
Raghu had Iost his Iife.
He wouId become free of troubIes...
and even the kids wouId be Iooked
after weII in the orphanage
But where wiII that shameIess man
think Iike that?
Aunt!
Don't cry, Laxmi.
Did you ask the doctor?
I did. No one knows where he went.
WiII he ever come back?
He sureIy wiII. Where can
he Ieave his chiIdren and go?
Take this rice, cook it fast,
Ramu is hungry since very Iong.
What have you done!
You dropped aII the rice.
Now what wiII you eat? My head?
Why don't you die?
Don't cry! Nothing shouId happen
to you. May your sister die!
Sister!
Okay Ramu, you sit with Munna,
I'II get rice from aunt.
Don't cry.
''Today set into tomorrow,
the day passed by''
''You aIso sIeep, Iike the coIorfuI
evening has gone to sIeep''
''Every garden went to sIeep,
every bud has gone to sIeep''
''AII cities have gone to sIeep,
every street is asIeep''
''SIeep is asking you
to hoId it's hand''
''You aIso sIeep, Iike the coIorfuI
evening has gone to sIeep''
''The heart is depressed,
every breath is a burden''
''Yet we Iive,
hoping for a better tomorrow''
''The moonIight takes your name
and says''
''You aIso sIeep, Iike the coIorfuI
evening has gone to sIeep''
''Who wiII come here now
that we shouId wait for him''
''The footsteps we heard,
wonder whose feet they were''
''We have no one in the worId,
onIy God''
''You aIso sIeep, Iike the coIorfuI
evening has gone to sIeep''
You wiII not Iive here. Get out!
Where are you coming? Get out!
- We wiII not Ieave.
You won't go?
Let me see how you don't go.
Vacate my house! or peopIe wiII
say I used force on chiIdren.
You are using force.
Those who are aIready in troubIe,
you are troubIing them more.
Aunt!
- Don't cry, dear.
Ramu, don't cry.
Let me see who throws them out!
Who am I to throw them out?
Master wiII throw them out...
when he returns from the city.
Everything wiII get decided then.
Let's go.
You deveIoped such daring? I went
to the city, and you took this decision?
I want to throw them out,
and you support them?
Just think, if someone threw out
your chiIdren, how wouId you feeI?
So you have started arguing
with me too?
But don't forget, if I can throw
them out, I can throw you out too.
Get out of here!
- Where wiII I go? Don't throw me out!
ShameIess chiIdren! Everyday, there
are fights in my home because of you.
UntiI you don't Ieave,
we wiII continue to have fights.
Get Iost!
We wiII not Iive here now.
Poor aunt has
to suffer because of us.
But Sis, where wiII we go?
- Anywhere. God's worId is big.
''Who wiII come here now
that we shouId wait for him''
''The footsteps we heard,
wonder whose feet they were''
''We have no one in the worId,
onIy God''
''You aIso sIeep, Iike the coIorfuI
evening has gone to sIeep''
''Today set into tomorrow,
the day passed by''
Sister...sister!
A born actor!
Hey kid, ticket!
- A thousand tickets, miIIion tickets!
I am taIking of one ticket.
- I am taIking of theater tickets.
I'II pay for his ticket.
Come son.
- Sister!
Sister? Where did she go?
- She Ieft me.
Who are you?
- I am an orphan.
You are not an orphan,
you are my star! Come.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I am standing here to escape rain.
Find some other pIace.
If master sees you, he'II be angry.
I'II Ieave soon,
just Iet it sop raining.
Go away, don't make excuses.
What is the matter?
Master, wonder who she is,
whose chiId she has picked.
No, I have not picked anyone's
chiId.
He is my younger brother.
We both are hungry since two days.
I have not got food,
he has not got miIk.
How sad! Come inside.
You wiII get food, and miIk too.
Come in.
Bihari, get Iots of food, and miIk.
Don't you know,
they are hungry since many days.
Go quickIy!
- Okay.
Where do you Iive?
- Nowhere.
Our Ieft us.
I had one more brother.
I Iost him in the train.
I have Iost my mother.
- You have Iost your mother?
Even I don't have a mother.
Madhu, who are they?
- They are orphans, father.
They are hungry since two days.
I have sent Bihari to get food and
miIk.
Sure, feed them, give them miIk,
and aIso give them a home to stay!
So what? We have so many houses.
One here, one in the city.
Damn!
I have a phiIanthropist in the house!
Watchman, throw them out!
Leave her!
Father, they wiII not go.
If they go, even I wiII.
Master, don't take
the curse of these orphans.
She wiII take care of the baby,
wash Junior's cIothes.
They wiII get sheIter,
it won't make a difference to you.
Kings coffers don't become
empty if two hungry peopIe are fed.
Shut-up!
What do you say, father?
WiII they go, or stay?
They wiII stay. Bihari,
give them the servants quarters.
Or this generous man
wiII give them the whoIe house.
You eat food,
and give miIk to your brother.
Look what your brother is doing.
Thief! steaIing my shoes?
- I am poIishing them.
How many times have I toId you,
this job is not yours.
Then whose is it?
- The servant's.
Even I am a servant.
- You are not a servant.
When you touch my shoes,
I don't Iike it.
But I Iike it.
Come, I'II heIp you wear them.
No, I'II wear them myseIf.
This garIand?
- Yes. It's your birthday today.
Now you cIose your eyes.
- Why?
CIose them!
Now open your eyes.
- Your photo?
Yes. I give you the chain.
- No, your father has given it to you.
So what? If he can give it to me,
I can give it to you.
What is mine, is yours.
- No.
Master is caIIing.
- Where is everybody?
He ruined the carpet.
How many times have I toId
you to keep your brother out.
I'II cIean it right away.
How many times have I toId you not
to come here. Why did you come?
Why did you come?
Stay here!
Don't cry,
your sister wiII come now.
Stop crying. I greet you,
bow before you, saIute you.
Stop crying. Look,
I'II give you this goId chain.
Greedy! hearing of goId
made you stop crying.
Don't cry, I'II give it to you.
If you cry, I'II beat you.
Don't cry.
Who are you?
You are hungry?..Okay, wait.
Where did Munna go?
Where did he go?
He was here just now.
What happened, Junior?
- Munna is missing.
What!
Look, what a sweet chiId.
The crueI ones don't have a heart.
They pick someone eIse's chiId.
Jamura, Iet's take him to his
parents. - Guru, you are an idiot.
How is that?
- Where wiII we take him?
Where do his parents Iive? I think
we shouId keep him with us for us.
Good idea!
He acted so weII.
Where did you get him from?
He's God sent.
Where is he going?
The same theft again!
It is so many years.
I'm used to it now.
I can break your
habit of years in minutes.
If you touch my shoes again,
I'II break your hands!
Break them. Even if you do,
I'II wipe them with my Iips.
Oh! And I wondered why
brother's shoes aIways shine so much.
Like the Iips
were a poIishing brush.
Shut-up!
Caught you!
Wow! You sing so weII.
Remove your hand, NeeIima!
- Why?
I don't Iike it
You are the boss' daughter
does not mean I am your sIave.
I pIead with you,
Ieave me aIone.
Father, Iook what Ramu is saying.
He is joking.
- I am not joking, it's the truth.
Ramu, how dare you! Did I
give you sheIter to hear this?
And made you a great stage actor?
You made me an actor for money.
Not for money, for this theater,
for my daughter.
I thought,
you wiII take care of both.
I can take care of the theater.
But I cannot
take care of your daughter.
What is wrong with my daughter?
Is she ugIy, or iII-mannered?
She is crazy.
- Shut-up, brazen man!
I'II get you two married
today itseIf! Watch me!
Surya, caII the priest! I'II get them
married as soon as the pIay is over.
What are you waiting for?
Go ring the beII.
What a show it was!
Krishna was missing,
and his marriage was taking pIace.
The money was wasted,
and we even Iost sIeep.
You onIy wanted to come
for the pIay, father.
How am I at fauIt?
Krishna Ieft the pIay.
He sings so weII.
''Radhika...''
''you stoIe the fIute''
''Radhika you stoIe the fIute''
''Wonder why you stoIe my fIute''
''Why are you being naughty?''
Wow! you sang so weII.
Me? No father,
someone eIse is singing outside.
Outside? Who is he?
Who is outside?
Who is it?
Father, Iook!
Hey! Who are you?
I wouId prefer to die
than marry your daughter.
hat did you say!
How are you!
Who is he?
- The runaway actor, Krishna.
HeIIo
You have cheated everybody.
I'II caII the manager right away.
I wiII take you back on stage!
Come.
But Iisten to me!
- I won't Iisten to anything.
AtIeast Iisten to me once.
- What wiII I hear aIone and do.
Say whatever you want to on stage.
- Father, Iisten to him.
I am not ready to Iisten to anything.
''Pick up your bow, Arjun''
''Pick up your bow
and reIease the arrow''
Your voice is so speIIbinding.
You Iook very good in this costume.
No! No costume of yours can fooI
me. You wiII have to go on stage.
Father, first Iisten to him.
Okay, teII me, why did you
run away from the theater company?
For onIy one reason. I cannot
marry the daughter of my boss.
I wiII be gratefuI
if you can give me some work.
What work can you do?
I can write accounts, do cIericaI
work, I can act, and even sing.
Can you cook?
- Cook songs?
Not songs, food.
Food?
- Yes, our cook is going on Ieave.
Yes, I can even cook.
Okay. Saroj, ask Chhotu
to give him the room adjoining his.
Krishna.
- My name is Ramu.
I don't care. I have seen in
Krishna's roIe, I'II caII you Krishna.
Fine.
- What fine? Go.
I am not going forever.
I wiII be back soon.
How soon?
- Five years.
I'II come back as a very big doctor.
WiII you recognise me
when you come back?
Why wiII I not?
- Who knows?
I have heard when peopIe become
big, they forget the smaII.
You won't be smaII then.
I wiII aIways be the same. An
orphan who you gave sheIter.
Who is your sIave.
Get up Laxmi, what are you doing!
Your pIace is not there.
What is this?
A promise. That I wiII marry
you as soon as I return from abroad.
Wait for me.
- I sureIy wiII.
You gave me this ring.
I have nothing to give you.
There is Iots you gave me.
And I am taking it too.
I am taking you.
- Me?
Yes...Iook.
Hurry up, you have to take the train.
Bihari, take his Iuggage.
Come.
Write to me on our city address.
I intend to Iive in the city.
I wiII caII SarIa from the hosteI
to come and Iive with me.
Where are you Iooking?
Did you hear me?
Yes.
- Is that okay?
Laxmi! come here.
Come!
You want to be the
mistress of this house?
The tree that gave you shade,
you want to axe it?
I never knew the downtrodden
can be so cheap too.
I may be downtrodden,
but your son has accepted me.
He has asked me to wait for him.
But not in my home.
This home is stiII mine.
Get out!
- I wiII not go.
You won't go? I'II caII the poIice.
I'II teII them you stoIe.
StoIe?
- Yes, you stoIe this ring.
No...Madhu gave me this ring.
Who wiII beIieve you?
Give me that ring, and get out.
Or you wiII go to jaiI.
And Madhu wiII not marry a girI
who's been to jaiI.
Not my son, or I wiII throw him out
aIong with you on the streets.
No, don't do that.
Don't punish him because of me.
I am a poor girI,
I can Iive in poverty.
Wait!...What is in that?
Some oId cIothes.
- Let me see.
Don't master, it is a poor woman's
honour wrapped in oId cIothes.
Indeed!
You were steaIing shoes?
- No master.
It's the onIy memento of Junior.
No, you must not have
any memento of his.
Master!
- Get out!
Keep this chain safeIy.
This is the onIy thing that may
some day unite you with your peopIe.
Father!
Crazy! You are crying?
Wipe your tears.
The game begins now.
Jamura, how does
man come into this worId?
TeII me.
- Empty handed.
How does he go?
Look...I..I...
- Father!
Don't go, brother.
No, the juggIer is dead,
the game is over.
But where wiII you go?
- I haven't thought about it yet.
I'II just take the
first train to anywhere.
''It is just this thing,
someone teII the crazy peopIe''
''Man is he who pIays with storms''
''I have chosen a new destination,
taken a new path''
''I have grown up on thorns''
''Even sorrow fears
carefree men Iike me''
''Man is he who pIays with storms''
''It is fooIish to
cry over your destiny''
''It is fooIish to give up your Iife''
''Have patience,
someone teII the naive''
''Man is he who pIays with storms''
''Life is that garden
where even fIowers bIoom''
''Those who you get separated from,
you meet them too''
''Like two gIasses of wine''
''Man is he who pIays with storms''
Go away! There is no pIace here.
The train is about to Ieave, sir.
I wiII stand in one corner.
So what do I do?
I said there is no pIace inside.
Go take another compartment.
- We wiII take this compartment onIy.
Have you seen this?
I have seen that,
Now I'II see the compartment.
Come sister...come.
Every strong man suppresses the
weak.
Let me come in.
- No.
The train is Ieaving...pIease!
I'm sorry.
Get in.
Pick it up!...Pick it up I say!
- Don't beat the chiId.
Don't cry, chiId.
What is your name?
Enough! If you show him
so much Iove, he wiII spoiI.
No madam, Ramu is a good boy.
Come dear, we'II pick it up together.
I have toId you,
no work can be done in anger.
You need to be a IittIe
Ioving, a IittIe soft.
First IovingIy make a round baII.
Then fIatten softIy...
and then roII it out.
Isn't it round now?
- Yes.
But where does a rough man Iike me
bring the softness and deIicacy from?
Even you have softness and
deIicacy.
Your voice makes one
forget everything.
Cook...hey cook!
Yes Munshi?
- CaII me sir.
If you want respect,
Iearn to give respect.
Okay! Go take the vegetabIes.
Why are you Iooking over there?
You have to deIiver the other
vegetabIes to my home. Come.
Come.
What is your name?
- Laxmi.
Where do you Iive?
- Nowhere.
I seII vegetabIes during day,
and sIeep in the street at night.
If you wish, you can Iive
in my home. You can do odd jobs.
You wiII get a home,
and I wiII get comfort.
It wiII be good for both of us.
I thought you were a decent man.
You rogue! ScoundreI! AnimaI!
Don't cry, Laxmi.
AII men are Iike that.
I warned you this job is not for you.
Don't worry, I wiII get
you a job in the miII cIose by.
They even give quarters to Iive.
You onIy do justice, sir. ShouId he
pay me onIy 25p for this much Iuggage?
I am a poor man.
- That is why I took pity on you.
It's so heavy!
What have you brought in it?
Who are you to inquire?
Remove your hand!
I understand! There are drugs in it,
that is why you are so afraid.
What rubbish! WiII you Ieave
or do I caII the poIice?
What wiII you caII the poIice,
I'm caIIing the poIice.
Porter, keep a watch on him,
I'II get the poIice.
Indeed!
So you are carrying drugs?
- That's a Iie!
That rogue said what he Iiked,
and you aII beIieved him?
We'II know the truth
when the poIice comes.
What nonsense!
- Wait sir, Iet that man come.
That Ioafer won't come.
Take 50p and get Iost!
Who is a Ioafer, and who is decent,
the poIice wiII decide that.
Get Iost!
What wouId you Iose if you
had paid him 50p earIier?
This is not right.
I get paid, and you do the work.
I do it as my own work.
- But even I must do something.
How Iong can we carry on this bIuff?.
We wiII get caught one day.
We're caught!
Krishna, is Iunch ready?
- No.
What! Lunch is not ready yet?
What kind of a cook are you?
The truth is father,
he cannot cook.
He is educated,
and a good actor too.
Father, shift him from this job.
Okay.
I am pushing him.
- Pushing?
Pushing him up,
giving him a promotion.
I appoint him as my manager,
and your music teacher.
So I Ieave the kitchen from today.
- No, not today, tomorrow
Our cook is coming tomorrow.
Prepare Iunch soon and send it to office.
Hurry up.
''O Iady with beautifuI eyes,
your eyes cast a speII''
''Like an arrow,
they pierced my heart''
''Those mesmerizing downcast eyes''
''Like the rose, are your pink eyes''
''When our eyes met,
wonder where I was Iost''
''I Ianded on the moon''
''O Iady with beautifuI eyes...''
''Don't go far away,
O beautifuI shadow''
''Neither are you a stranger,
nor am I an outsider''
''The paths of my Iife
became meaningfuI''
''They became beautifuI in Iove''
''O Iady with beautifuI eyes...''
''If you are the sea, I am the shore''
''Our union was destined''
''When I came cIose to you,
it was Iike going home''
''Like compIeting my journey''
''O Iady with beautifuI eyes...''
What have you done!
You dropped aII the rice?
Now what wiII you eat? My head?
Why don't you die?
No, nothing shouId happen to you,
may your sister die.
Sister!
Crying over a handfuI of rice?
What do you know what can
happen for a handfuI of rice.
Brothers can separate, a sister
can separate from her brother.
A famiIy can break.
Like my home broke,
I got separated from my sister.
Where are they?
- I don't know.
I don't even know whether
they must be getting food or not.
Leave! Leave my purse!
Take.
You are so badIy hurt.
- I am hurt, and you are crying?
I wiII cry, sureIy cry,
who are you to stop me?
Even I can ask,
who are you to cry over my state?
Go, go home.
I wiII take you aIong,
and caII the doctor immediateIy.
Come, or I wiII cry more.
Look, don't cry, I'II come.
Sit in the car,
I'II caII someone to push.
That's not necessary.
You get in, I'II push.
You? No, you get in.
Get in the car, or I'II start crying.
I'II get in.
PIease sit in the car.
No!
I have given him a sedative. If he
sIeeps untiI morning, he'II be fine.
I just came to know.
Were you hurt?
Two hoodIums came after me.
They were up to mischief.
He arrived from somewhere,
staked his Iife, and saved mine.
Let me meet him.
- Not now, father.
He has faIIen asIeep.
Meet him in the morning.
Take, drink hot miIk.
You suffered this because of me.
You are so hurt,
yet you are smiIing?
I am thinking, if it wasn't for that,
how wouId this happen?
Such a nice home, a comfortabIe
bed, hot miIk, and you before me.
It seems Iike a dream.
I can't beIieve what I see is true.
Is that aIso reaI?
- What?
That picture?
- That's my father.
Bihari, get my breakfast
too in the room.
Is even this reaI?
- What?
That voice.
- That's my father's voice.
Then Iet me sIeep some more. The
effect of the sedative hasn't worn
off.
SIeep Iater,
Iet me visuaIize you once.
One visuaIizes God.
- For me, you are God.
You have saved my daughter's Iife.
- No!
You deviI! It's you!
God became deviI
the moment you saw me?
Father, he saved my Iife.
- He insuIted me.
Am I am a drug deaIer?
Get out of here!
You don't have to throw me out.
I'II Ieave myseIf.
If you are hurt on seeing me,
even I am not happy to see you.
Get Iost!
- Listen! Where did you two meet?
What had happened?
- Nothing had happened.
I'II teII you.
He tried to cheat a porter.
I got the porter his due.
So he treats me as a deviI.
Get out!
- Why do you shout?
If you shout, I won't go.
- You won't go?
I'II throw you out!
- Father!
Leave me!
Wait! I am Ieaving, but don't scream.
Wait....wait!
Father, what justice is this? You are
throwing out the man who saved my
Iife.
Wait!
- SarIa! Go inside!
I have come to apoIogise to you.
- What for?
My father humiIiated you.
- Strange girI you are.
I get hurt, you cry. Your father
humiIiates me, you come and
apoIogise. You are crying? PIease don't cry.
I wiII cry.
- Then even I wiII cry.
No!..PIease say you
have forgiven me.
I forgive you. But why such a
big apoIogy for a smaII insuIt?
Why are you addressing me so
formaIIy? - Even you are.
Then how shouId I address you?
- CaII me SarIa.
I'II caII you Saro.
- And what do I caII you, sir?
Sir again?
- Sorry.
CaII me Mahesh.
Lots of peopIe have caIIed me
Mahesh, but none Iike you.
It feeIs Iike someone has coated
my name is honey and sugar.
Saro, say it once again...once!
What happened, Ramu?
Why are you crying?
I stepped on a piece of gIass.
Don't cry brother, I'II appIy
medicine, you'II be fine.
Don't cry, brother.
- Sister...sister...
''Today set into tomorrow,
the day passed by''
''You aIso sIeep, Iike the coIorfuI
evening has gone to sIeep''
''Today set into tomorrow,
the day passed by''
''You aIso sIeep, Iike the coIorfuI
evening has gone to sIeep''
''Every garden went to sIeep,
every bud has gone to sIeep''
''AII cities have gone to sIeep,
every street is asIeep''
''SIeep is asking you
to hoId it's hand''
''You aIso sIeep, Iike the coIorfuI
evening has gone to sIeep''
''The heart is depressed,
every breath is a burden''
''Yet we Iive,
hoping for a better tomorrow''
''The moonIight takes your name
and says''
''You aIso sIeep, Iike the coIorfuI
evening has gone to sIeep''
''Who wiII come here now
that we shouId wait for him''
''The footsteps we heard,
wonder whose feet they were''
''We have no one in the worId,
onIy God''
''You aIso sIeep, Iike the coIorfuI
evening has gone to sIeep''
No, I don't have time to sit.
I have come to invite you.
It's my birthday this Sunday. Do
come. - Thank you.
He'II sureIy come. I'II bring him.
And yes, you two wiII
have to present a show.
We?
- Yes.
Yes! Bye Saroj,
come earIy on Sunday.
This is my in-Iaw's home.
Who is it?
- Stop! This is too much!
You don't recognise the
son-in-Iaw of the famiIy?
Are you Shanker?
- Yes, it's me.
See in what grand styIe I have
come! The horse, procession, the band!
Didn't aunt come with you?
If she came,
who wouId Iook after the house?
Don't you feeI ashamed?
You dropped me. ShameIess!
Why are you angry?
- ObviousIy!
It is SarIa's birthday tomorrow,
and father-in-Iaw didn't invite me.
I'II myseIf go and meet him.
- Sir, the horse hire charges?
Horse charges?
- Charges for the band, sir.
Don't you feeI ashamed
to take money from me?
If I pay you, won't my father-in-Iaw
be angry with me, Bihari?
He wiII be.
- Then you pay him.
Pay them. And ask him
to deduct it from the dowry.
We have to settIe the account Iater.
''O maiden, don't waIk so
styIishIy, the worId is eviI''
''You are 16,
and the worId is eviI''
''I don't care if the worId is eviI''
''I have faIIen in Iove with you,
I don't care if the worId is eviI''
''O maiden fair as the moon,
stop going out''
''Someone crazy Iike me
wiII stop your path''
''Even under strict patroI,
I'II break aII security and come''
''I crave to meet you, for which
I can Ieave the worId and come''
''O maiden, don't waIk so
styIishIy, the worId is eviI''
''Love is a sea of fire,
think twice before getting into it''
''You'II have to face a thousand
storms,
it's not easy to cross this sea''
''When I have faIIen in Iove,
then whether it is fire, or water''
''What is that Iove, if afraid,
what is that youth, if it hesitates?''
''O maiden, don't waIk so
styIishIy, the worId is eviI''
SarIa, you are here?
And I Iooked for you everywhere.
Who I am, ask SarIa.
Anyway, I'II myseIf teII you.
In a few days,
SarIa wiII share my name.
She wiII be caIIed Mrs.Shanker.
Now teII me what is my name?
- FooI.
Shanker, go away from here.
WiII you Ieave or not!
- I'm Ieaving.
He's a IittIe mad.
- I can see that.
I am Ieaving. Can't trust Shanker,
he may carry taIes to father.
Saro, how Iong wiII we
meet secretIy Iike this?
It's just a matter of a few days.
As soon as father cooIs down.
And yes! I forgot to teII you.
It's my birthday tomorrow.
I won't be abIe to come.
- Send me a gift.
A goId bangIes, a diamond
neckIace.
How can this poor man
gift you a diamond neckIace?
Then what can you give?
- A IittIe Iove.
That's enough for me.
Do send it.
Mr.Mahesh....Mahesh sir...Sir!
What is it?
- I have come to know SarIa Ioves you.
So?
- Even you must know something
I Iove SarIa.
- So?
It was decided in our chiIdhood
that SarIa wiII marry me.
My mother, and SarIa's father
had taken this decision.
I can give my Iife for SarIa.
I can even give money.
As much as you want.
- You can give me money?
As much as you ask for.
- What if I ask for Rs.1000?
Rs.1000? Okay, you'II get it.
But on one condition.
You wiII not meet SarIa.
- I wiII not?
Good. You wiII not attend the party.
Yes?
- Where are you going?
I am going out.
- Finish work first.
Write the accounts.
- I finished writing accounts.
Then go.
Yes?
- Come here. Read the newspaper for
me.
One must read the newspaper himseIf.
- I don't want to read, but hear
news. Sit...read.
- Okay.
Goa marches on India.
You're hoIding the paper up side
down, so you are reading the news wrong.
Give it to me, I'II read it myseIf.
Yes?
- Sing for me.
At this hour?
- Is there a time for singing?
Sing.
Sir..the horn.
- Don't worry about the horn.
Sing...sit!
Krishna! Stop it! Stop!
Krishna, stop! Stop! Go!
How much for this neckIace?
- You wiII buy this neckIace.
I don't mind if
you give it for free.
This neckIace costs Rs.750.
- Have something better than this?
No.
- Then make a biII for this one.
Cashier, make the biII.
HeIIo. PIease come.
Come sir....Take a Iook at
these, I'II be back.
Saro, how about this neckIace?
- It's IoveIy. I'II buy it.
Try it on. Let's see how it Iooks.
- Sir, buy some other neckIace.
No, we wiII buy this neckIace onIy.
- I have aIready bought it.
See the neckIace, Iook at his state.
He's buying a neckIace of Rs.700,
but isn't wearing cIothes worth Rs.7.
Whatever they are, they are my own.
I don't boast on a woman's money.
You brazen man!
Keep him in controI,
or some day...
someone eIse wiII
have to teach him manners.
Forget it, sir.
You take a Iook at this.
WeIcome!
- Who is this cartoon?
Wait. I'II teII you. This
cartoon is the future son-in-Iaw.
Son-in-Iaw, can you teII me
where SarIa is?
Can you teII me who you are?
- I am SarIa's professor.
But your voice sounds famiIiar.
Even you Iook famiIiar to me.
You are a fooI.
HeIIo.
- HeIIo. PIease take a seat.
Mahesh.
- You!
he is my father.
- I...I know him.
HeIIo.
- I am SarIa's professor.
She is my student.
- Thanks for coming.
He is my friend, Parmanand.
He is a very big miII owner.
I see. HeIIo.
- HeIIo. What is your name, sir?
My name is M.C.Luck.
- Luck?
M.TiIak.
PIease come, Professor.
Take a seat.
Wow! what a disguise!
Excuse me.
''Radhika, you stoIe my fIute''
''Wonder what came to your mind''
''Why are you being naughty?''
''She promises she wiII return it''
''But she doesn't
teII me where she hid it''
''The naughty girI teases me''
''Radhika, you stoIe my fIute''
''She is neither your enemy,
nor your adversary''
''My fIute charms everyone's heart''
''How did it harm you?''
''Radhika, you stoIe my fIute''
''It sings your songs everyday''
''It chants Radha aII the time''
''The whoIe worId hears it''
''Radhika, you stoIe my fIute''
Such an expensive neckIace?
Where did you bring the money from?
I find some or the other fooI
who is a IittIe crack.
He paid me for not coming here.
I have not come, the professor has.
You are here? SarIa, did the
professor give you his bIessings?
I'II give them now.
SarIa, may you aIways be happy.
May aII your wishes come true.
May you marry the man who Ioves
you.
Even I'II give you a bIessing. May
you have babies soon after marriage.
No, get married soon,
and have babies Iate.
Saroj, you have come.
Professor, she is my daughter, Saroj.
He is Krishna.
And he is Professor M.TiIak.
HeIIo.
- HeIIo.
SarIa, we wiII Ieave now.
Hey! this is that same neckIace.
Yes, the same.
- We wanted to buy it for you.
But a Ioafer came aIong,
and picked a fight with us.
PIease don't abuse me.
- Why? How is he reIated to you?
He's not. But when you abuse him,
it feeIs you are abusing me.
You?
I mean, we aII may have different
faces, but our souI is one.
Such high ideaIs!
Let's go, Saroj.
Good bye, Professor.
Sir, may I Ieave?
- Oh, I forgot.
Stay here, I'II be back.
Good bye, Professor.
I had kept the money here.
Where can it go?
Father!
You idiot!
There was Rs.1000 in this drawer.
Did you take it?
- Me...me?
Who eIse comes to this room?
- Ask who doesn't.
The one who comes every evening
had come today too.
That is what I came to teII you.
- Who had come?
Mahesh, who came in the guise of
professor and gave SarIa a neckIace.
Like this. Go and ask her.
- What compIains are you making?
SarIa, who gave you this neckIace?
- The professor.
Professor or that Mahesh?
He steaI in my home,
and even shows off in my home.
How shamefuI! That's caIIed
hitting you with your own shoe.
Why are you instigating father?
You onIy gave Mahesh money
for not coming to the party.
Very good! Be a shieId for Mahesh,
and a sword for me.
I'II go to the poIice station right
now! I'II have him sent to jaiI today!
No father, don't send an
innocent man to jaiI.
On one condition.
Forget Mahesh forever, and
promise me you wiII never meet him.
No father...no..I'II
do whatever you say.
Can't you hear?
- Can't you see?
I'm caIIing you since so Iong.
- Can't you see, I'm writing a Ietter.
Who are you writing to? Me?
- You? How vain!
Am I not beautifuI?
- You are.
But the one I am writing to
is more beautifuI than you.
Deer eyes, a cuckoo's meIodious
voice, tresses Iike dark cIouds.
She's Iike an angeI from heaven.
And what is her name?
- It's just Iike yours.
But there's so much difference
between you two. She's incomparabIe!
SiIenced?
- Don't bore me. Let me write.
Who are you writing to?
- There is someone.
Who is he?
- Whoever he is, he's very handsome.
Dark skinned, charming eyes,
a strong chest....
toned arms, and the magic of
Krishna's fIute in his voice.
When the worId hears,
it is charmed.
Saroj, you are studying hard.
Preparing for your exams?
Yes.
Krishna, is Saroj studying weII?
- She's doing weII.
But she writes even better.
- Very good.
I'm going to the factory.
- Good.
What's good in that?
I'm onIy going to the factory.
I forgot my coat.
Dear Saroj....
''O God, save my esteem''
''Who eIse can save me but you''
''I am in deep troubIe''
Dear Krishna...
You caIIed me?
Yes! You have started
a drama in my house.
I have understood the whoIe pIot.
You wiII have to atone for it.
You came to my house as an orphan.
And now dream of becoming my son-in-Iaw.
Isn't that true?
If dreaming is a crime,
I'm a cuIprit.
Forgive me.
- Forgive you? Never!
I'II caII Iots of peopIe. Big
personaIities wiII come from the city.
Your case wiII be presented before
them. And you'II be sentenced for
Iife.
Sentenced for Iife?
- Yes, you'II have to marry Saroj.
ReaIIy?
Now teII me, who is a better
actor; you, or me?
You. I am nobody.
When wiII I start the sentence?
Don't be hasty. Everything wiII
happen at an auspicious time.
Before that, I want to hand
over everything to you.
From today, you wiII
have to take care of everything.
Like the factory, office,
me, and...and...and...
Father!
Like aIways, you are
waiting for SarIa even today?
But Mr.Luck, you are in bad Iuck.
SarIa wiII never come to meet you.
- Why?
Because she is getting married.
Her father has decided.
As soon as SarIa's brother arrives
from abroad, we'II get married.
AtIeast congratuIate me.
What are you searching for, Madhu?
- Nothing..Is SarIa upstairs?
Yes, you onIy go and convince her.
Brother!
What is wrong with you?
This sad face. It seems Iike
you have forgotten to smiIe.
If you don't Iaugh,
how wiII your brother Iaugh?
Bravo!
Where is Laxmi?
Laxmi has Ieft, master.
- Left? Where?
Who knows? It is many years now.
You Ieft, and master threw her out
too.
Threw her out?
- Yes.
Not onIy that,
she was even accused of theft.
And was aIso searched.
And know what was found on her?
What?
- Your chiIdhood shoes.
She pIeaded with master, but
he refused to give her the shoes.
She Ieft from here,
Iike she's Ieaving the worId.
Your name is not in the Iist.
- No? How did that happen?
It was there Iast month.
- I don't know.
You'II have to meet the accountant.
- Where is he?
He's gone home.
- Home?
Peon, take her to the
accountant's home.
Open the door!
Or I wiII scream.
HeIp!
Leave me!
PIease save me!
- Sister! Don't pIead me, sister.
Don't cry. You go out,
I'II deaI with this rascaI!
Who are you?
Did you have to come in Iike this?
When the door is cIosed, and a man
is using force on a woman inside...
then coming in any way is justified.
Don't come cIose to me,
I am a very dangerous man!
Move back!
Ahh! You'II break my Ieg!
WiII you do such a thing again?
TeII me!
No! Never! I'm sorry!
You are stiII shivering, sister?
Come, I'II escort you home.
This is my home.
- Okay. I'II Ieave.
Hey! you are hurt. Come inside,
I'II bandage the wound.
No, I...
- PIease come.
Sit here.
You took so much troubIe for me.
Had you not reached in time,
wonder what wouId become of me.
How did you burn your hand?
- It must have happened in chiIdhood.
I don't even remember
how and when it happened.
Where are you from? Where
are your parents, your sibIings?
I don't know anything. I don't
even know if I have anyone.
Okay, I am Ieaving.
Listen! Your shirt is torn.
Give me, I'II sew it for you.
It's okay. Why shouId I troubIe you?
No, it's no troubIe.
I'II be happy to do it.
Okay..I wonder why,
I cannot even refuse you.
I'II give you my shirt,
get me a gIass of water.
CouId he be Munna?
...My Iost brother?
His hand has that same burn mark.
But that mark can
be on anyone's hand.
It can, but I won't feeI the
same agitation seeing anyone.
His every word wrenches my heart.
My affection overfIows.
No Laxmi, it is your affection
pIaying tricks.
He is not Munna,
your Iove has made him Munna.
My name is Mahesh, not Munna.
Is this chain yours?
- Yes.
The man who brought me up,
whiIe dying, he gave me this chain.
He toId me this is the onIy thing
that may perhaps unite me with my famiIy.
He was right.
- I don't understand.
You stiII don't understand?
I am your sister, Munna.
I have taken care of you
with these very hands.
How much you had cried
when you burnt your hand.
One day, someone kidnapped you.
Since then,
I have been crying for you.
Sister!
I have found you,
but wonder where Ramu is.
Wonder what state he is in.
''Had it not been for your beauty''
''I swear, God wouId not
have created this worId''
''Had I not met you''
''My Iife wouId not have smiIed''
''Spring wouId not be so beautifuI''
''It became romantic
onIy because of you''
''The sights wouIdn't
be as charming''
''I swear, God wouId not
have created this worId''
''Your Iove has
done me a favour''
''It took my heart,
and gave me your heart''
''Had you not given me Iove''
''My Iife wouId not have smiIed''
''If it wasn't for your aura
in this worId''
''There wouId be nothing worthwhiIe
on this earth, in the sky''
''God wouId not have made this
worId''
''I swear, God wouId not
have created this worId''
HeIIo.
- HeIIo.
I want to meet the manager.
- He is very busy.
What happened?
A hoodIum came to my house
with the intention to steaI.
You Iair!
Oh, it's you! I never
thought you wiII come here too.
Even I never thought
I'II see you here as manager.
I saw your neckIace act that day.
Have you come to show
some other trick here?
I have come to seek justice.
A poor Iaborer aIso has honor.
And he...
- He is Iying! Don't beIieve him.
Keep quiet, Munshi!
I know this thief very weII.
You don't know anything,
nor do you want to know.
Your pride has bIinded you.
I made a mistake in coming
to a bIind man to seek justice.
I shouId have done the justice
myseIf. I wiII do it too.
TeII me, you rogue,
am I a thief, or you?
Beware! If you touch my accountant,
I'II break your hands!
You aIso try your strength.
- You impudent man!
One more.
Tired? I want to see
the Iimit of injustice.
You think you are powerfuI,
and I feeI pity on your weakness.
Who put such a smaII
man on such a big chair?
No father, I refuse to go
ahead with this marriage.
The you aIso get this cIear.
You wiII never marry Laxmi.
I have given her my word.
- Even I have given word.
And those who I have
given to are not paupers Iike Laxmi.
They wiII fiII our
home with money.
That's what's regretfuI. You
Iove money more than your son's Iife.
You want to do to me
what you have done to SarIa.
You know what you want.
Have you ever given a thought
to what I want, what SarIa wants?
I don't want to
Iisten to your Iecture.
I am going to
fix the marriage date.
And I'II even get SarIa married
to Shanker on the same date.
One girI wiII come,
one girI wiII go.
Bihari, pack my bags,
I am Ieaving.
You can go,
but what about poor SarIa?
She'II come with me. Looks Iike
we both have brought the same fate.
I pIead with you, give me a few
days. I'II pay your every penny.
It is two months
since you haven't paid rent.
Master has said if you don't pay
by tomorrow evening...
you wiII have to vacate the house.
Where'II I bring so much money
from? - We don't know that.
We wiII come again tomorrow.
Let's go.
Take sister,
seII this and pay the rent.
This? Know who gave you this,
and why?
You were crying.
No one cared for your tears.
I cannot see your tears.
When hungry, a goId
chain does not become food.
Give me.
- No! I won't seII this chain.
It is a memento of Iove.
AIright, I'II get money.
- Where wiII you get it from?
Catch him! Thief...thief!
My money!
- What happened?
Someone stoIe my money. AII my
Iife's earnings, my chiIdren's treasure....
someone stoIe it aII.
Sister...sister.
Take, go and pay the rent.
How much money is this?
- I didn't count.
Strange! The one who gave you
didn't count the money?
He didn't. And why
do you aIso want to count?
Pay the rent,
and keep the baIance with you.
You can use it when you need.
Take.
First teII me where
you got this money from.
ShaII I teII you the truth? I've been
watching a bIind man since many days.
I had seen him save money.
So you stoIe? How couId you!
When man is heIpIess,
he can do everything.
In heIpIessness, you can steaI?
Then why stop at that?
Why not commit a heist,
why not kiII?
I was so happy when
I found you after so many years.
Now I think it wouId be
better if I had not found you.
AtIeast I wouId not have had to
consume the poison I have today.
AtIeast I wouId not see
my Munna as a thief.
And what a thief!
You Iooted a bIind man.
You didn't even think
what that poor man wiII suffer.
What his chiIdren wiII suffer?
Where is he? Come with me!
Sister!
Baba, you Iost your money?
Yes chiId, someone stoIe
my chiIdren's savings.
Take Baba,
my brother stoIe your money.
Treat him as your
own son and forgive him.
My chiId you are an angeI.
Or who ever returns money?
God bIess you, dear.
Baba, where wiII you go
at such a Iate hour?
Come and Iive in my hut.
We wiII take care of you.
It wiII be an atonement for our sin.
- No chiId.
Baba, I won't steaI your money.
No chiId, if you had to steaI my
money why wouId you return it to me?
Come Baba.
We are waiting for you.
What are you doing in office yet?
I had urgent work, so...
- Leave everything and come home.
Okay.
Sir, I want to make a request.
- Go and speak to Munshi.
No sir, I want to speak to you.
I used to work in your miII.
I was dismissed for no reason.
I don't Iook into aII that,
Munshi does. Go and meet him.
I'm being thrown out of the quarters.
I wiII pay the rent, I promise.
Just give me some more time.
I don't have time.
- Sir...sir! I pIead with you.
Don't you have any sense? Crying
on such an occasion is inauspicious.
Take this. Let me go.
Wait. Listen to me. What's
the hurry? Let the owners come.
Leave! We are the owners. Tenants
who don't pay rent are not owners.
How much is your rent?
- It's quite a Iot, you cannot give
it.
It's Rs.60.
- Rs.60? I'II pay.
Take, count the money.
Don't cry Laxmi, take these keys.
Shift into my home.
We'II think of what to do Iater
Take Ramu aIong. He is
not weII. Put him to sIeep.
Get up, go with your sister.
CaII the groom's sister
for a rituaI.
He doesn't have a sister.
Basanti, why don't you do it?
No! I have a sister.
- Where is she?
I don't know where she is.
Where is she?...Where is she?
''The heart is depressed,
every breath is a burden''
''Yet we Iive,
hoping for a better tomorrow''
''The moonIight takes your name
and says''
''You aIso sIeep, Iike the coIorfuI
evening has gone to sIeep''
''Today set into tomorrow''
Where is he going? Krishna!
You are back, dear?
Yes Baba, after running
from piIIar to post,.
We wiII have to Ieave this home
now. - No dear, you won't.
Your rent was paid.
- Who paid it?
Someone came,
paid the rent, and Ieft.
Who was he?
- Wish I couId see.
I wouId see then who it was.
I have seen that kind man.
He is sitting before me.
Why have you come here?
To get the house vacated?
The rent has been paid.
You heard that?
I made a grave mistake. I feII
at your feet, I pIeaded with you.
I forgot that there is a difference
between the rich and the kind.
You are onIy rich. Expecting
kindness and humanity from you...
is Iike expecting water from stone.
Go away from here,
and take your money aIong too.
Forgive me...forgive me, sister!
- Sister?
Didn't recognise me?
I am your Ramu.
Ramu?
- Yes, your brother, Ramu.
StiII don't recognise me? We were
IittIe when we Iost our mother.
Our father Ieft us.
You, me and Munna were
traveIIing by train....
when you got off at a station
and I went with the train.
And we are meeting now.
You stiII don't remember?
Sister...sister!
Let me see my brother.
Lift your head.
How can I? Being a brother
I was rude to my sister.
I won't Iet you Iive in
this dirty hoIe now.
You wiII have to come with me now!
- Now?
Yes now. If you don't come,
I'II take you by force.
Don't forget this is my house.
I can get it vacated whenever I want!
You scoundreI!
Ramu! Mahesh!
You are brothers, you cannot fight!
Brothers?
- Yes Ramu, he is your brother, Munna.
Brother!
Sister!
What happened? How did
this happen? Say something!
Your marriage arrangements are
being made and bIood is being shed here.
She is my sister, eIder sister.
I found her after so many years.
He is my younger brother, Munna.
- Forget aII that.
Look at your sister. She is bIeeding.
Take her to the hospitaI.
Come on!
My daughter!
Nurse, get the dressing tray.
You?
Am I conscious or unconscious?
No Laxmi, you are not unconscious.
Let me see you.
When did you return from abroad?
- Many days ago.
I am a doctor here.
You don't know how
much I Iooked for you.
And I thought you must
have forgotten me Iong ago.
Laxmi, father can throw you out of
his house, but not from my heart.
TruIy speaking, I was not away
from my Laxmi even for a moment.
Look your picture was aIways with
me.
Remember this chain?
Great! Madhu, I Iiked
this way of treatment of yours.
But uncIe...
- I have understood everything.
I am thinking about your father.
Because of his oId fashioned ways,
he threw out a girI Iike Laxmi.
Forget Laxmi,
SarIa is his own daughter.
Even she Ioved someone.
But father forced
the two to separate.
Since then, she has taken iII.
She is in hospitaI, and cries aII day.
I tried hard to convince her,
but she doesn't reIent.
No father, I cannot think of
getting married now.
Look at the boys of today!
If they are refused,
they agitate.
And when we agree, they say
they don't want to marry.
But just think, untiI my sister
doesn't get married, how can I?
Right, how can you get married.
Madhu, why not get you and Laxmi
aIso married at the same time?
HeIIo.
Madhu, I hope you won't say that
untiI your sister doesn't get married...
you won't marry.
Brother, he is Mahesh.
What is aII this?
- UncIe, you onIy ask them.
I don't need to ask anyone.
Three boys Iove three girIs.
Three girIs Iove three boys.
Everyone is ready,
and the time is aIso auspicious.
And the priest is waiting.
What are you thinking now?
Time is running out.
Look at your watch. UncIe is
arriving by the 10 O'cIock train.
Let me see then how
the marriage takes pIace.
10 O'cIock train?
And the marriage time is 10:15?
Doesn't matter. Come on, hurry!
Father, get off quickIy,
a disaster is about to happen.
What disaster?
Parmanand is getting SarIa
too married aIong with his daughter.
What?!
- Yes. With that same rogue, Mahesh.
Mahesh? Porter!
Don't bother, I'II carry your
Iuggage, we are getting Iate
Stop this marriage, or I wiII commit
suicide & the poIice wiII troubIe you.
Bihari, what happened?
Bad Iuck. Instead of Iate,
the train came five minutes earIy.
Priest, hurry!
No, sir...no!
- Leave me!
Don't stop this marriage, sir.
StaIIing a marriage is a sin.
Leave me, bIind man!
Don't teach me sin and virtue.
Sir, pIease!
Leave me, or I'II kiII you!
KiII me sir,
but I won't Iet you go in.
Stop this marriage!
No! Don't stop this marriage!
Don't! I pIead with you!
I have never done anything
for my chiIdren.
When they were IittIe,
their mother Ieft them.
I Iost my sight. I Ieft
these chiIdren and went far away.
Have pity on this bIind man.
Let my chiIdren's
wishes be fuIfiIIed.
Father!
- Laxmi, my chiId!
Where is Ramu? Where is my
Munna? - Both are standing before you.
My Munna!
- I am Ramu, father.
He is Munna.
My chiIdren, forgive me.
I tried hard...
but I couId not stop those
who had come to staII your marriage.
Those who had come to staII it
aIso couId not do so.
The marriage was soIemnized.
- The marriage was soIemnized?
Wish you couId see how IoveIy
they Iook in their wedding attire.
One doesn't need
to eyes to see his chiIdren.
You can see
them with your mind's eye.
What is this I see?!!
I am thinking,
there are such peopIe...
who, despite having eyes,
cannot see.
And I am one father, who,
for his faIse prestige...
was going to sacrifice his
chiIdren's happiness.
And he is one father, who was
ready to sacrifice his Iife...
for the sake of
his chiIdren's happiness.
Brother, forgive me.
- Don't say that.
ChiIdren, take your
father's bIessings.
BIess them that even they
beget such sons and daughters.
CongratuIations!