You Tube - Video Running Time 02:30:35
You Tube search name - Do Raaste (1969) (HD) Rajesh Khanna I
Mumtaz I Balraj Sahani I Prem Chopra - Superhit Hindi Movie
Prince College Hostel, London.
Respected brother,
you will be glad to know that..
I have passed the final
year of engineering with 1st rank.
I think this is the result
of the blessings of you all..
More than my own hard work.
I am thousands of miles far from you.
But you all are in front of my eyes.
You must be sitting
on your bed in your room.
Mother must be sitting opposite you.
A young girl must be sitting in her lap..
Whose teeth are cut off by rats.
Hey! How did uncle know that
the rats have cut off my teeth?
And there must be a
monkey sitting beside you..
Trying to read the
letter and whose name is..
Raju!
Directly behind mother
would be standing Geeta..
And whose hands would
be stained with ink.
Wow!
And near you would be standing Bhabhi..
Her hands soiled with flour.
I've been dying to
eat the food cooked by her.
Satyen must be sitting in
his same old place and reading.
Seeing all of Mumbai
from there sometimes..
He must be getting
back to his reading.
I don't worry about Satyen.
There's one more person
who would be standing..
Behind the window and listening
to this letter carefully.
My dear pal, how did Viju know that..
I listen to his letter
from outside the window?
I swear on God, he is a magician!
What do I write about you?
You are not only my brother
but also my father, my god.
You've done a lot for me.
I don't know how would
I repay your favors.
Whatever I am today is because of you.
Silly boy!
Father,
to fulfill the promise I made to you..
I tried to do whatever I could.
And I will do whatever I can in future.
The only thing I regret is..
That you are not
with us to share this joy.
Child, your mother
died when you were young.
After that I could not give
you enough love like other fathers.
Don't say that, father.
You've given me a lot.
Given you what?
A stepmother, two stepbrothers?
And a stepsister?
Father..
I swear that I will
love them all like my own ones.
Always.
God bless you, Narendu.
May everyone have a son like you!
Father..
May God give me the strength
to carry my vow till I die!
Greetings, Bhabhi.
Welcome, brother Khan.
Since the day you've received the news..
That Viju has passed,
you all have stopped doing any work.
You listen to old songs,
and dream new dreams?
Yes, Khan,
this song contains
the dreams of my father.
And it seems that
they'll soon be realized.
Why not, brother Narendu?
You work hard all day,
then also work at night.
- When Viju comes, you will be able to rest.
- Of course.
Mother won't sew clothes.
Bhabhi won't work in the kitchen.
There will be servants for every task.
- And I? I will close my garage and rest.
- Yes!
Greetings, everyone.
Congratulations, Narendu.
Very glad to know about Viju.
Lalaji, we are happy because
our brother is coming back.
But you are happy because..
You will be getting your
loan and interest both back.
I am glad that..
One brother mortgaged
the house and took loan from me..
While other brother
is coming to repay that debt.
Lalaji, you will do good business..
Because the third brother
is also ready to go abroad.
Come, brother Satyen. Take a
chit and decide the fate of your pal.
- What is this?
- You have a bad habit.
- You ask questions on every matter.
- Ok, I won't ask, but what is this?
- Ok, take out a chit first.
- Take one! Take one!
Hurry! Hurry!
Birbal!
- Hey! What happened?
- Get some water?
What happened to him?
It's true.
This had to happen one day.
He is the eighth fool to be sacrificed.
He has seen seven fools
being sacrificed before him.
But what is all this about?
A new problem has come
up in the college, a girl.
Not a girl; a calamity!
Not a calamity, a bomb!
Who is she after all?
Why do you go from this long cut?
Go from there, pal.
Good luck, Birbal. O Allah!
Be careful.
My dear, would you
come for a movie with me?
Strange! A student of the first year,
and so daring?
If you have the guts,
go and break off her boldness.
I will write your name as the 9th fool.
- Kid!
- Yes, pal.
If I don't convince this girl..
In the next 24 hours,
I will change my name.
That boy.. he's taken a challenge.
- Challenge? What challenge?
- To teach you a lesson.
But how do you know that?
His friend is also my friend.
When I tell him,
Rustom, you are so nice..
He speaks out everything.
- I see. What is the name of that mister?
- Satyen Prasad Gupta.
How does he look?
Shaves his face once a week..
And changes clothes
every four days.
Dirty fellow! Where does he live?
From 9:30 to 2:00
in the lecture room.
From 2:00 to 6:00 in the library.
And from 6:00 to 6:30 in
the common room. Then I don't know.
- That means he's a book worm. Loves books.
- Correct.
Ok.. is he fat or slim.
Medium.
- Is he tall or short?
- Medium.
He is not what he looks;
he's very smart.
Be careful;
such men are really dangerous.
Don't you worry! Let the kid come.
Ms. Rina,
no dictionary in this world..
Has enough words
to describe your beauty.
This juicy eyes,
these pink cheeks, this silky hair..
- Keep it up, pal. Keep it up.
- Yes, carry on.
Carry on? These yellow eyes,
these swollen cheeks..
These black lips,
this big, fat tummy.
Seeing this I am forgetting the formula.
- Forget him; tell us the formula.
- Formula is very simple.
Tell us fast, buddy.
- Make friends with the girl.
- Then?
- Praise the girl.
- What then?
- Tell her that you've never seen such pretty eyes.
- And then?
- Then the girl will lower her eyes and feel shy.
- Feel shy!
- Wonderful!
- What then?
Then praise her more. Tell
her that your lips are like roses.
- These lips.. these lips..
- Speak ahead!
- What will the girl do then?
- Then.. Then the girl will fall in love.
- How come?
- Simple.
A pretty girl is always
in love with herself.
When a guy praises her the right way..
She falls in love with him.
Ok, you guys arrange a nice picnic.
Then see what your pal does.
'This silky hair, these pretty eyes.'
'Everyone lives by seeing them.'
'If these eyes lower
down with shyness..'
'The whole matter
would be stopped here.'
'Keep quiet and don't
tell them that..'
'Everyone drinks by seeing them.'
'This silky hair, these pretty eyes.'
'Everyone lives by seeing them.'
'The hair would bring
so much arrogance..'
'It will make my heart
and soul restless.'
'Don't tell them that
they drive us crazy.'
'Everyone lives by seeing them.'
'This silky hair, these pretty eyes.'
Ms. Rina,
can I also live praising your hair?
You.. you've voiced my feelings.
Can I.. how can I say this..
That you're.. you're very nice.
This mere human is your servant.
Ask my heart,
look at yourself with my eyes..
Enough, Rina!
I can't bear it any more.
What happened, Rina?
- I am also surprised.
- Are you?
- When will you meet me?
- Whenever you say.
- Where?
- Wherever you say.
By the way, I go for swimming everyday.
Really? Shall I come there today?
- Yes.. no, come tomorrow.
- Ok.
Excuse me;
can you tell me where is Ms. Rina?
She's in the office.
I mean.. I was..
- Shut up, all of you!
- Get him out right now.
Go in, all of you. Go in.
Hey mister, where are you going again?
Well, actually when I came here..
There was a board reading 'office'.
I am telling the truth;
I am not lying.
So is it me who's lying,
and you're telling the truth?
- Wicked!
- Wicked? Do I look like a wicked person? Do I?
No, dear, you look very decent.
That's why you were looking at the girls.
I say, you can't leave from here.
I will smash you,
make kohl of your bones..
And put it in my eyes.
Gone! Gone!
I say.. I say, leave him.
He will die.
The police will arrest me.
He's come out.
Leave him, girls. I will come in.
Help! Help!
I don't know how to swim.
The police will arrest me.
Help! Help!
Someone come and help, please.
Help...
See? Formula number one is drowned.
Formula number one did not work.
See what formula number
two does tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
Don't you see while you're riding?
That's what I want to ask.
You have such big eyes!
Can't you see while you're walking?
Whose thoughts were you lost in?
Dilip Kumar or Dev Anand?
Get lost!
I will go with you now.
There's a good hotel nearby.
And they also serve beer.
You idiot!
Look, mister, to talk to
girls like this is.. unmannerly!
Sorry, sir.
Sorry, sir. Very sorry. Sorry..
- No, sir.. I made a mistake.. Please, no.
- Speak.
Forgive me, you were bothered..
I swear on God, I had never dreamt that..
A bomb would burst
out by helping someone.
Pal, that is not his fault.
That girl is not a girl;
she is a powerhouse.
If you touch her,
she gives out an electric current.
Girls and boys, let me first tell you..
That theorems and problems
are just like a married couple.
I mean the husband and the wife.
If you can win over the wife,
husband is already conquered.
So if you can master the theorems..
Problems are no more problems.
Problems are already solved.
The first theorem in trigonometry is..
Can anyone of you solve it?
Ms. Rina?
- I'll try, sir.
- Come.
Silence!
My dears, if it is a good joke,
tell us. We will also laugh.
Silence!
You can't help laughing.
Come here.
What happened?
Come; solve this problem.
- First move her aside.
- Why?
Yes, sir, move her.
I am the only child of my parents.
What if I get an electric shock?
Silence! What bluntness is this?
Sir, it's not my fault.
She herself has put such a board.
See it for yourself, sir.
You idiot!
Silence! Silence!
Silence!
- Sir is also laughing.
- Silence!
Sir is also laughing.
This doll is for Guddi.
Now it's Satyen's turn after Guddi.
Here's a cardigan for you.
I got it from Wallstreet, London.
Wow! From the Wallstreet, London?
It will prove handy to
impress the college girls.
Thank you, brother.
Here's your sari, Geeta.
Wear it and show me.
No, brother, I will wear
this sari on your wedding.
Hey dear! Wow! See, brother?
When I left, she was so young.
And now she talks like a mature lady?
You are right, Viju.
I will have to find a guy
for him and a girl for you together.
We will find the girl and the boy later.
Have the meal first. I have
made the Karela especially for you.
- And the Udad Dal?
- Yes, that's also ready.
- Really? C'mon.
- Come, all.
What nice tea!
- Did you like it?
- Very much.
- Viju, I don't get a point.
- Which one?
How come you've got a job abroad?
Bhabhi, the company I work
for has branches all over the world.
Its head office is in London.
I had been after it for a year.
Really?
You were after it for a year?
Sis..
I see. So this is the guy for whom..
My sister left London,
her studies..
And is now also
going to leave the house.
Looks nice.
- How's his nature?
- He's very sweet.
- He hardly speaks anything.
- It's ok then. - Why?
Because even if he wanted to speak..
My dear sister wouldn't
allow him to speak.
Naughty girl! Go away from here.
Father, look at this photo.
Whose photo is it?
My would be brother in law.
Sister met him abroad.
Wow! The guy seems to be really good.
What can one say by a photo?
You also looked very good in a photo.
Why do you blame my face?
Look at your own face, please.
Mine is much better than yours.
It's not as dark as
a snake like yours is.
My complexion was
pink till I got married.
The night I saw your face after wedding..
My color turned so pale,
it hasn't turned normal till date.
I could survive even
after seeing your ugly face..
Because I am a
very courageous woman.
If it had been another woman
in my place, she would have died.
Got it?
Look, dear wife,
I've always listened to you.
Now you listen to me once.
Let me go to the guy's place.
This is the single proposal
we've received in 21 years.
Let at least one of
daughters get married.
I will go there with Rina.
Ok. Rina, go with him.
Stop him if he says something wrong.
You're in trouble!
Who is it.
Open the door, please.
Tell me first who you are.
- Is Mr. Gupta home?
- No one is present in this house.
No one's in? Who are you then?
Me? Consider me not present.
- Please, go from here.
- What a strange family!
- You?
- What are you doing here?
- Silly question! I live here.
- You live here?
- Yes.
Where does Mr. Narendu
Prasad Gupta live?
He also lives here.
He is my elder brother.
Father, please come.
This is the house.
Goodness!
She's brought her father along.
Look, it's a matter between you and me.
What's the need to drag..
I mean to bring your father in it?
- Please come, father.
- You're so stubborn!
Look, a college is a college,
house is house..
- Father is father, mother is mother.
- Back off!
Can't we settle the college
matter in the college?
- Open the door!
- The door? - Yes.
Door! Door.. ok..
You're done for!
Mister, tell Mr. Gupta
that Mr. Alopi prasad has come.
Why don't you disappear from here?
What? What are you thinking?
I've come to talk to your brother.
- You've come to meet my brother?
- Yes.
Brother is not home.
Even if he was,
it wouldn't be of use to meet him.
Look, it's a personal matter of ours.
We will decide on it.
- Yes, it will be decided.
- Yes, decided.
- It's a trifle matter..
- A trifle matter?
It might be a small
matter for you, mister.
But for us it is a big matter.
No, dear! Children make mistakes.
It is children's task to be mischievous..
And the elders'
task to forgive them.
If kids won't make mistakes,
who else will? You, at this age?
- Rina, let's go.
- Yes, please go.
Just a minute, father.
Now that we've come,
let's go after talking to them.
If Mr. Gupta is not home,
his mother must be home.
Mother? Yes, we will meet his mother.
Mother?
Mother! Yes, she is home,
but she's vowed to keep silent.
The priest has said that
she cannot talk to anyone today.
- What nonsense are you talking?
- Yes, whom are you..
Bhabhi, come here.
We have some guests,
but they are leaving.
- No! We have just arrived.
- Yes! Come in! Please, come in.
- Who..
- We had come to meet Mr. Gupta.
But as he's not home..
I thought I might meet his mother.
Can I come in?
- Please, come. Come.
- Come, child.
- Please, be seated.
- Yes, I will.
- Mother!
- What is it, child?
There are some guests.
Greetings. My name is Alopi prasad.
And she is my daughter, Rina.
Greetings. Please, sit.
- Daughter in law, please bring tea.
- Right away, mother.
No, no. No need to bother.
We've come to..
How do I tell you?
My elder daughter,
Nina, has just come from abroad.
I've heard that your son,
Viju, was also there.
I am sorry, but I don't recognize you.
Bhabhi, I had teased this
girl very much in the college.
But she teased me, too.
And today she's come
with her father to complain.
You made a mistake, so pay for it now.
- Satyen!
- God! I'm in trouble.
Bhabhi, please help me for this
one day. I will always serve you.
- Satyen!
- I'm done for!
Mother!
I am telling the truth
that I haven't done anything.
This is wrong, false, false accusation.
What are you saying?
- Yes, mother, whatever he has said is false.
- Wow!
I didn't mean you.
I mean your daughter.
Whatever she said to you is wrong.
I mean right..
I mean it is false; all false.
- Mister, whatever she told me about you seems to be right.
- Yes?
He is my youngest son, Satyen.
Glad to meet you.
Is your elder son, Viju, also like him?
Viju? How can I praise him myself?
My Viju is greater than him.
- Greater than him?
- I'm in trouble!
We will take your leave now.
Please, sit.
Have tea at least. Satyen!
Yes! Please, have tea.
How can you leave without having tea?
- You're so strange!
- It is you who are weird.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
I am a daughter's father;
how can I have tea at your place?
Ok, goodbye. Satyen,
please accompany them till the door.
Yes, yes, please come.
I don't feel like letting you go.
Why do you bother?
We can leave by ourselves.
We are going. Goodbye.
You? Madam,
do you still have to say something?
- Manners.
- Manners? - Yes, manners.
Manners mean good behavior.
You didn't even thank me.
What if I had really
complained about you?
I would have been in real trouble.
Listen!
Why did you act in front of mother..
As if we had met
for the first time?
- Will I have to tell that, too?
- How will I know then?
I heard in the college
that you are very smart.
You're down and out!
The thing you told me about yesterday,
I hope that's all fine now?
What did you assume?
- That we've made up.
- That's it?
- And that our friendship will last long.
- Only friendship?
It's possible this friendship
turns to some other relation.
Which relation? Tell me.
Love.
What else do you want to know now?
Whether I am dreaming all this.
You can dream at least.
I can't see anything.
Why? This beautiful scenery,
these clouds..
They all are with us.
- I don't see any scenery.
- What do you see then?
Two eyes of someone,
and the love in them for me.
Someone's eyes? Are these eyes mine?
I mean, are you unable
to see anything except me?
'All scenery is hidden.
O dear, what has happened?'
'You applied kohl and
the day turned to night.'
'Our eyes met each other's.
O dear, what has happened?'
'A heart called another
heart and they had a meeting.'
'Don't come tomorrow
and nor call me here.'
'The world will taunt us.'
'Don't come tomorrow
and nor call me here.'
'The world will taunt us.'
'Last night you made an excuse.'
'Dear, you said
you can't come today.'
'But you came over.
O dear, what has happened?'
'I've left the world
and am with you.'
'You applied kohl and
the day turned to night.'
'A black cuckoo is singing
on the branch of a mango tree.'
'There must be some reason
behind the arrival of monsoon.'
'There must be a purpose
behind the spreading clouds.'
'The clouds are pouring out.
O dear, what has happened?'
'It is raining because
your drape flew.'
'A heart called another
heart and they had a meeting.'
'I beg of you, don't leave my hand.'
'In this shadow of stars.'
'There was a day when
you didn't even look at me.'
'And now is a day when
you keep awake all night.'
'The pretty girl is restless.
O dear, what has happened?'
'What I feared has happened,
o ruthless man.'
'All scenery is hidden.
O dear, what has happened?'
'A heart called another
heart and they had a meeting.'
Nina, you are going to
marry him against my wish.
But be careful about this point.
Control your husband
right from the first day.
Or your life will be
ruined just as mine was.
Dear me! Listen to her! Her life
is ruined because of marrying me.
Of course. I came as your bride..
But never enjoyed
the life as a young wife.
You are right, dear wife.
You gave birth to our daughters
in your old age, right?
Your brothers, sisters, uncles, aunts..
How many shall I count?
I got 18 people married.
I say, Nina, get a separate house..
For yourself after marriage.
Or you will have to get
married your sister in law..
Brother in law, and both
the kids of elder brother in law.
But how can that be possible, mother?
He loves his family very much.
Shut up, silly! I will tell you how
to do it. It's a simple game for me.
Yes, you've been playing
the same game for 21 years with me.
Enough! Keep quiet!
Don't interfere between us.
That's the only thing left for me to do.
Use it some other day.
One can't talk sense in his presence.
Come with me.
Go, Nina.
You've got your mother's face..
Now also get her way of thinking.
Marriages are not decided this way.
One has to call the priest
and find the auspicious day.
How will the wedding be, mother?
Just like other weddings.
I wish the bride would come
to our house sitting in a Doli.
Mother, the brides don't
come in Dolis these days.
They come by car.
And uncle should come riding a horse.
- Right, uncle? Right, uncle?
- Yes, dear, fool your uncle.
But where shall we make
arrangement for the guests?
Mother, everyone has
reception these days.
We shall also arrange a reception,
at Taj Hotel.
My dear, first ask him what
sort of wedding would he like.
If you ask me,
all these traditions are useless.
Which traditions, child?
This marriage pavilion,
calling the band people..
The Doli, the circles..
All this is worthless.
And because of these useless
things our country is getting ruined.
The cheaper the wedding these days,
the better.
What sort of marriage would you like?
I like civil marriage.
The boy and the girl sign..
In front of two witnesses
and the marriage is solemnized.
A seal worth 2 rupees, and
the marriage is done in 2 minutes.
Nina, you're getting late.
Mother, I'll drop Nina at her home.
Ok, goodbye.
Go, Raju.
This girl is not worth being
the daughter in law of this family.
Why, mother?
To mock marriage like this..
To talk about one's
own wedding like this..
Mother, perhaps she wants
to save our expenditure.
But she does not care about
any traditions or the society.
Mother, she is an educated
girl with modern way of thinking.
She's just returned from abroad.
She'll mix with us when
she comes to this house.
Don't worry about that.
I take that responsibility.
You also sign.
Now you are husband and wife.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations on our wedding.
- Same to you.
Dear Uncle.
Uncle!
What was the need to call the kids here?
How sweet!
It is you who called them in.
Are you out of your senses?
No, I am all right.
I am not mad like you.
Please, think of a way to get them out.
No, you will think over it.
The one who needs it.
Raju, Guddi,
it's time to go to bed. C'mon.
Come, Guddi, let's go to sleep.
Not here, kids.
Mother is calling you down.
We will sleep with you, uncle.
Uncle, we used to sleep with you earlier.
Yes.. but now.. well, the..
Uncle, why do you stammer?
I mean you used to sleep with me,
but.. now.. now.. Nina..
That's fine,
kids, but now auntie is here.
- So what if auntie has come? I will sleep with auntie.
- What?
And I will sleep with you.
- No, uncle. Guddi has made a mistake.
- Very good.
Guddi will sleep with auntie.
And I will sleep with you.
- But you both will sleep here, right?
- Of course.
O God!
- Where shall I put this?
- Put it over there for time being.
I will tell you later.
Be careful.
It's a valuable thing; be careful.
Move. I'll do it.
Madam, where shall we put this chair?
What idiots I have to deal with!
Didn't I tell you to remove
all the old furniture out?
Why do you keep asking me?
Daughter in law..
Perhaps that old chair
looks bad with this new furniture.
But it is your father in law's chair.
Navendu likes it very much.
Nobody except him sits on it.
Very good.
Then let this chair stay in his room.
He won't have to take the
trouble of coming till here.
And then, nobody will
touch this priceless chair too.
Dare you touch that photo. Move away.
Sorry, sister-in-law. This
fool was pulling down father's photo.
I had told him to remove it.
You had said it?
Knowing that it is father's photo..
Your father-in-laws?
Yes. I think that
keeping the photographs..
Of the ancestors in the
drawing room is old fashioned.
What can be said about your thoughts?
Today the photos of the
ancestors are out of fashion.
It is possible that the ancestors..
Are out of fashion tomorrow too.
Behave yourself. I thought
that you studied in the college.
Surely, I do.
But one doesn't learn in college..
To remove the
ancestor's photograph..
And put up some
monkey or horse's photo.
If you understood modern art,
you'd praise these pictures.
Keep such a modern art to yourself.
It doesn't even let one
remember their ancestors.
Satyen..
What is the matter, Satyen?
Brother..
Sister-in-law doesn't like..
- Father's photo in the drawing room.
- It is right.
I think..
Father's photo would look better..
In my room than the drawing room.
- What do you think about it?
- Brother..
You have done right.
You changed the face of the hall.
I liked it.
- Hey..
- Yes?
How do I look?
- Very beautiful.
- And my dress?
- The worst.
- Why?
Oh! Is there a difference between
girls and boy's clothing or not?
And then when you
girls go to the college..
Wearing these clothes, will the..
Boys look at your
dress or at their books?
Therefore the result of the
university is poor year by year.
Okay, sir, please tell me.
Which clothes should I wear?
Girl.. you are a Indian woman..
Wear a proper and simple saree.
Whatever you wish.
Who is it?
What is this?
Here..
When I used to wear a chudidar
kameez you didn't like it.
Now when I wear a saree
even then you don't like it.
I will die on your simplicity.
Is this a simple saree?
Of course.
My mother wears a saree like this.
My grandma wears a saree like this.
And my grandma's grandma too.
Is it is it? They must be wearing it.
Surely they must be wearing it.
But like this?
These flowers and such?
These rhythming anklets..
See..Reena.
Let me teach.
Don't piss me off. Go away, please.
Reena.. what is this?
I am telling you for
the last time go from here.
Go. Vanish..
What are you doing?
This ornament.
Ornament?
Why are you making it shine?
Nothing will shine now, understood?
What is this joke?
"The Bindiya (forehead
dot) will shine.."
"The bangles will rhythm."
"The Bindiya (forehead
dot) will shine.."
"The bangles will rhythm."
"Whether you get sleep or not."
"The garland will have an aroma."
"The flowers will have an aroma."
"Whether you get angry or not."
"The Bindiya (forehead
dot) will shine.."
"The bangles will rhythm."
"I accept you have become crazy."
"There has been something
wrong done to you."
"I accept you have become crazy."
"There has been something
wrong done to you."
"Where do I take my eyelashes?"
"Through the eye of this ornament."
"No matter if the guys turns about."
"The Bindiya (forehead
dot) will shine.."
"The bangles will rhythm."
"If someone's bangle speaks,
there is no pressure on youth."
"Even if the world refuses me a..
Thousand times
my anklets tell me."
"They will rhythm.."
"The maiden will dance."
"Whether the roof falls down or not."
"The Bindiya (forehead
dot) will shine.."
"The bangles will rhythm."
"I have loved you,
not accepted your slavery."
"Whether anyone has a broken heart,
or gets angry with me."
"I will play and I will flirt."
"Whether I gain enemies or not."
"The Bindiya (forehead dot)
will shine.."
"The bangles will rhythm."
"The night that you come to my
house with the marriage procession."
"I won't sit in the palanquin
and tell my father."
"I won't go. I won't go."
"Whether the relation
is broken or not."
"The Bindiya (forehead dot)
will shine.."
"The bangles will rhythm."
- One..
- Ten..
- Two..
- Nine..
Three...
- Eight..
- Four..
- Seven..
- Oh! Stop this.
You have been told not
to touch anything so many times.
What if it conks off or something?
Raju had told us..
C'mon, put on the radio.
Do you know how to play it?
Hey, Raju, why did you tell it?
What did I know that it was so costly?
You talk like a grandpa.
Didn't anyone teach you at home..
That you don't touch other's
things without asking them?
Run away from here.
I am sorry, sister-in-law.
These kids just know that everything..
Comes in this house
is the property of everyone.
They didn't know..
That these things are yours,
just yours.
Very good.
Then why didn't you teach them..
That the radiogram is
as expensive as it is delicate?
A little error can cause it to conk off.
Actually, it was my mistake.
I was so absorbed in preparing the
sketch I didn't remember it at all.
I will teach them to work the radio.
You will teach them?
You don't even know that
the sofa is for sitting, not lying.
You are right.
This sofa is for sitting.
Especially, this sofa.
Which is yours.
I didn't think that Satyen
would act so insolently.
But.. what happened?
The kids were playing with the radio.
I dissuaded them.
Mr. Satyen started shouting at me.
What was the need to shout at me?
Why don't you ask this to Satyen?
He had me hear so many things.
I ask you..
If my father is rich, what is my fault?
Being his daughter,
can't he give me anything?
Why not, he can give you everything..
Then why did Satyen insult me?
Why did he speak wrongly
about my father in my presence?
But.. why does he need to
speak wrongly about your father?
Go and ask this to Satyen.
Okay, come with me.
Satyen.. Satyen..
- Satyen.
- Yes brother.
How did the furniture
of the hall reach our room?
- I have kept it there.
- Why?
It was lying here, if it would
be down.. the kids would ruin it.
And as it is.. modern
furniture is for modern people.
What nonsense?
Then listen to something sensible.
That furniture was sent by your..
Rich wife's rich
father for his daughter.
Is my wife not related to you in anyway?
If she was related she
wouldn't tell me repeatedly..
In the afternoon that
all this furniture is mine..
Don't touch anything
without my permission.
There is a limit for lying too.
When did I say all this?
The girls of a rich
house have a weak memory.
They forget the words
of the afternoon in the night.
Did you see the attitude in his words?
It is your attitude that has to be seen.
Satyen.. I don't like
this insolence at all.
If Neela has told you something,
she is elder to you.
You should apologize to her.
If I am wrong,
I am ready to apologize to her.
What is the matter, Satyen?
The children were playing with the radio.
Neela told them not to do it.
He chucked all the furniture in our room.
Now instead of apologizing to Neela..
He speaking all kinds of gibberish.
What is the matter, Satyen?
Are you shy of apologizing
to sister-in-law?
It isn't the matter
of apologizing, brother.
The woman who thinks that she..
Is better and right than
every other household member..
Satyen.. there is no
need to cross your limits.
I tell you. Apologize to Neela.
She should apologize to me.
She has insulted me.
I don't know who has insulted whom.
All I know is that you
will have to apologize to Neela.
Brother.. You listen to everything
that she says to make her happy.
But the result of pampering
her so much won't be good.
I don't want to learn from
you what I should do and not do.
Brother..
Looking at her selfishness..
And small heart, I think
that she cannot stay in this house.
Uncouth.
Satyen.. why don't you apologize?
You are telling this, sister-in-law?
You know that I am not at fault.
Whether guilty or not, you are younger.
And it is never bad for
the young to apologize to elders.
Go. Go and apologize to Neela.
I apologize, sister-in-law.
Navendu..
I am sorry, mother.
For the first time,
I raised my hand on Satyen.
I don't know what has happened..
To this house ever since
Neela has come in this house.
Whatever be the case, mother.
She is the daughter-in-law
of the house now, isn't it?
But this doesn't mean all
her mistakes should be covered.
I tell you.
If this spark isn't trampled right now..
It will become a fire
and set fire to the whole house.
- What?
- Can't we live separate?
What do you mean?
I mean..
Nowadays..
Everyone lives alone after marriage.
You take a small flat too.
There isn't anyone other than us here.
Even now, there isn't
anyone other than us here.
No, Viju,
one's own house is one's own house.
Look here.
There is no curtain or any privacy.
Even at this time, elders of young.
Anyone can come to our room.
I am scared of changing clothes too.
Oh! Why don't you lock
the door from inside?
Oh no! What will they think?
It doesn't seem right.
Forget these worthless things.
Tonight is not for such things.
No Viju, you always skirt this issue.
- Which issue?
- About the new apartment.
Okay. We will do as you wish, okay?
- Who is it?
- Me..
- Can I come inside?
- Who is it?
Oh! So you don't recognize me now..
Oh.. come,
please come, please have a seat.
What will I do if I don't sit?
I thought that it is many days,
I'd remind you.
Seth.. I remember everything.
So what if you remember?
Even Viju is married off now.
And if God agrees.. there
will be a son in a few days too.
Oh Seth.. I will sweeten your mouth.
Well, you have filled my mouth..
Now, when will you fill my wallet?
See. I don't go to
the court in small matters.
What are you talking about courts?
It is so sad that you say like this.
Tell me. Till when should I wait?
What till when?
Wait for two minutes, I will come.
Viju..
Elder brother.. come brother.
It is the third today, Viju.
You didn't get the salary?
He did get the salary.
But I thought..
It is better if I keep his salary.
Yes.
Yes. It is good. It is very good.
A wife has a right
on a husband's earning.
Like that,
our staying and food expenses..
Work out to be
three hundred rupees.
If you do need money other than that,
just ask me.
Yes. Why not?
I will have to tell you.
Seth..
I am sorry.
- I will not be able to serve you this month.
- What?
But your money will
be arranged next month.
I promise you.
See, I don't need your promise.
I need my money.
If I don't get my
installment the next month..
Then think about it. Yes.
Wait.. wait..
- Is this Neela's house?
- No.
Whose house is this?
The name of the owner of
this house is Navendu Prasad Gupta.
See, do you know where Neela lives?
She lives here.
- Then who are you?
- I am a man.
Even we can see that you are a man.
But what are you doing here?
I am standing here and talking to you.
But who are you?
Think that I am a servant.
Then go and tell Neela
that his guests have arrived.
Come.. please come..
- Hi..
- Hello, hi, Neeta, Hi Sushma.. Hi, Kanta.. oh, have a seat.
Should I bring some tea
or something for your guests?
Of course, and please be quick about it.
Hey, eat it.
I couldn't see the movie.
There were so many guests in my house.
I was all ready. I was so angry.
Here.. Have you
made all these things?
- Why? Didn't you like them?
- No, they are very good.
So, why don't you take some more?
Since when are you cooking?
Since some fifteen to twenty years.
If the tea is ready, just get it.
- Where did you work before this?
- Yes?
Where were you servant before this?
Me?
I am working in this
house since the beginning.
Geeta has come.
- Now can I ask you something?
- You?
- Where did you work before this?
- What?
Why are you staring at me?
- What do you mean?
- I mean what I say. - Satyen!
You have nice friends.
They don't even know how to talk.
Who are you to teach us how to speak?
Madam..
If you become a wax doll,
nothing is achieved in life.
It is necessary to learn
how to speak other's houses too.
- Oh! You shut up!
- You shut up!
- God..
- Out!
Satyen.. don't forget
that they are my friends.
Therefore I am using just my tongue.
And listen..
Your friends too don't have any right..
To think that my
sister-in-law is a cook..
And that my sister is a servant.
Tell them to go away from here.
Wow, Neela.
You abused us well calling us here.
You were so hospitable, oh my god.
If there was something less
in hospitality should I fulfill it?
Satyen.. if they go, even I will go.
By chance.. the door is open.
- Come on, Sushma.
- Come on.
Such insult.
Wait. If I don't
teach them a lesson..
Then do change my name as well.
There is a new problem.
Did you say anything to me?
I am not mad like you.
I challenge just one enemy at one time.
What? I am your enemy?
I was speaking about these chess pieces.
Who is it, Viju?
See, I am Neela's mother.
You come quickly. Yes, right now.
Neela. You won't
get such a chance again.
Take advantage of Satyen's mistake.
And come out of this problem of a family.
It seems that Rahu and Ketu have..
Sat in poor Navendu's
horoscope this year.
Reena's mother..
It is not good to meddle
in Neela's house matters.
You shut your mouth.
How many times have I told you..
Not interfere
in the family affairs.
Where am I talking about my house?
I am talking about Navendu's house.
You just look at your chess pieces.
Neela, I will show you such a way out..
That even you will remember it.
Now let it be, sister.
Why do you think so
much about small matters?
Wow..
On whose money the whole family runs..
She was chucked
out of the house along..
With all her guests, and
you say that it is a small matter.
Even sister must be guilty in this.
She is after them since so long.
You don't advocate their cause.
Neela. I will tell you a
solution to cure them. Come with me?
Tell me too.
How should I make you all right?
Daughter-in-law..
What is Navendu doing?
He is sitting with the accounts,
what else?
Viju.. you people are returning now?
We were waiting for you since so long..
That you come and we eat dinner.
Come sit.
Come on, sit down. We will have food.
What about food?
Even having water in
this house is a sin for me.
No, daughter-in-law,
one doesn't speak like this.
I know that you felt
bad about what Satyen said.
I apologize to you for that.
Neela.. you are responsible
for whatever happened.
You didn't introduce Madhavi
and Geeta to your friends.
Let it be, mother. What is
the need of increasing the matter?
When I don't have any complaints,
why do you worry?
Neela.. please spit out this anger.
Such small matters
do take place in the house.
Don't give me this sympathy.
You set the fire yourself.
And you yourself sprinkle water?
Neela.. think about
what you are saying.
Madhavi is the elder
daughter-in-law of this house.
And as if I am nothing in this house.
No, Neela.
- Even you are a daughter-in-law of this house.
- No!
Only the woman who dances on..
The signals of the mother-in-law..
Can be a daughter-in-law
in this house.
I am educated.
I am the daughter of a rich father.
I have a respect in the society.
Therefore everyone on
the house is jealous of me.
And everyone hates me.
Neela, they don't hate you,
they hate your poisoned words.
Think about it.
Did you ever have Geeta sit with you?
Did you speak nicely to Satyen?
Did you ever embrace the children?
You say that nobody thought you..
A daughter-in-law in this house.
I ask you..
Did you ever give respect
to Madhavi or me..
As a daughter-in-law
which you had to?
The ones who respect others get respect.
Not for them who think
that the other are wretches.
I tell you, be silent, please be silent.
Why should I be silent?
I am not that woman who
tolerates all injustice silently.
I'm the daughter in law
of this house and not the maid.
I have as much right
on this house as Madhavi has.
If you had talents like Madhavi..
Why would we have to see this day?
What kind of talents
does this talented one has?
Let me hear it too.
She just accepts whatever you say.
She serves you all through
the day and presses your legs.
- That's it, isn't it?
- Don't talk, Neela.
If you don't care about youngsters..
At least give some
respect to the elders.
When the elders don't
have pity for the elders..
And they don't have love,
then how can the youngsters..
Have respect and
dignity for the elders?
- Neela..
- The people say that mother-in-law is like a mother.
But I say.. Every mother-in-law
is a enemy of the daughter-in-law.
She is always after her.
Neela, stop this nonsense.
Your words are out of tolerance now.
You have insulted everyone in this house.
You insulted me,
my wife and kids and my brothers.
But I kept silent. But today..
You have insulted mother.
And I will not tolerate
it under any circumstances.
Come forward,
touch mother's legs and apologize.
I didn't say anything
for which I should apologize.
You have said a very big thing.
Such a big thing has
never been said in this house.
- Seek an apology.
- No. Never.
Neela.. only they are humans
who understand their mistake.
And the mistake that you
did has just one repentance.
Fall at her feet and ask
forgiveness from her or else..
- Or else?
- Or else you don't have any place in this house.
- Neela..
- Let it be, the matter will increase.
You don't speak in between.
Viju.. you tell Neela.
Tell her to apologize to mother.
I think that it is not necessary,
brother.
What?
Whatever Neela has said is the truth.
And telling the truth is no crime.
You are advocating Neela's cause?
I am her husband.
All the house hold members
can walk away from here.
But I cannot.
You can do this?
Okay, Viju.
Listen to my decision too.
Either you both apologize to mother.
Or else go away from this house forever.
- You are saying this?
- Yes, I am saying this.
The one who insults mother cannot..
Stay in this house
for even a moment.
So what if he is my own brother?
- Think about it.
- I have thought about it!
If you think that Neela
is greater than mother..
Then even you can go with her,
go away!
Here.. please have some curd.
It is said..
The one who eats curd and goes..
Returns some day or the other.
For my sake?
Farewell.
Forgive me, mother.
I didn't fulfill the
promise I gave to father.
No, son. What did you not do?
The way you have supported them..
People don't even support
their children like that.
Did you call me?
- Yes, please have a seat, Mr. Gupta.
- Thank you.
Here you are.
- What is this?
- Notice. And a month's salary.
Notice?
And you will get your
provident fund later.
But what are you saying, sir.
I have worked for this
company for twenty two years.
I am sorry, Mr. Gupta.
The company is in doldrums.
Other people are being answered too.
I can't do anything.
I am sorry. I am very sorry.
Hey.. what happened?
- Nothing.. I just fainted.
- Are you all right?
I was scared.
What is the matter, son?
You seem very worried?
Nothing mother.
I have a headache.
If you work all through the day,
won't you have a headache?
Please take your coat off.
I will bring some tea.
Ok.
I have told you so many times.
Take care of your health.
Oh! Brother Navendu,
you are at home today?
Why? Should I be outside
home all the time?
- You should be there.
- Where?
- At Viju's house.
- Why?
Mother, don't you know?
Viju has been promoted,
he has become a big man.
Really?
Yes. He has become a general
manager of the company.
- The general manager..
- But who told me?
Viju's driver.. his friend told me.
It is such good news.
I think as if I have been promoted.
Congratulations.
He has become such a big
officer at such a young age..
Nobody. Nobody becomes one.
He has a big buffet in his house today.
Pulao.. Biryani..
Hey.. what are we doing here?
Come on to his house.
Yes. We should surely
go to his house.
- Come on, mother.
- No.
What are you saying, mother?
Did he invite you?
Are household members
needed to be invited?
Think about it.
He has been promoted today newly.
Where will he have sense about anything?
But he should have
thought about the person..
On whose shoulders
he sat and came till here.
Mother is right.
A person doesn't even go
to God's house without being called.
You are strange too, Khan.
You say something and
then something else sometimes.
Think about it. If I don't
reach there to congratulate..
What will Viju think?
What will the world think?
So what if you don't go? I will go.
He is a strange man.
Khan.. you go with him too.
Navendu is sick today too.
Don't worry mother. I will go.
Everything will be all right.
Good evening, madam.
Hey.. where are you going?
I want to meet your sir.
Sir.. you cannot meet the sir today.
I want to meet him for just one minute.
What kind of a person are you? Didn't
I tell you to go away from here?
- What is the matter?
- He wants to meet the sir.
Hey, where has he come from?
Come on from here. Come on.
- See.. Do you work here?
- What is the matter?
- Do you work here?
- Yes. I am sir's special bearer.
- Will you do a small task for me?
- What is the matter?
Tell your sir that Navendu
has come to meet him.
There is a big party in the house.
- You cannot meet sir today.
- Please tell him.
Okay. You sit here. I will go inside.
- When I come back, I will tell sir.
- Okay.
What is it?
You are sitting on the chair now?
Come on. Get out.
You don't know me.
Your sir knows me very well.
Go. All the beggars
know the sir know very well.
Come on, do a good job for me.
Get lost.
- You wretch. What are you saying?
- Who are you?
If I slap you once,
your father won't recognize you.
- How did you come here?
- What could I do?
I stood here and watched
your drama for a long time.
- What kind of a man are you?
You drive a man out of the hours first.
And then you ask his name.
Which country has such a rule?
But who are you?
I am your sir's brother.
And he is your sir's father.
Now go and tell him that
your brother and father have come.
Go!
- Madam.. madam.. one minute.
- What is the matter?
- Just a minute.
- Excuse me.
Two people are standing outside.
They say that they are
sir's father and brother.
What are you saying?
I am telling you the truth..
See, they are standing there.
Go and tell them to come tomorrow.
See.. madam told me to
tell you to come tomorrow.
Tell her that we have
just come to congratulate him.
Oh! Will I work for you or for sir?
You wretch.
You started speaking again.
- Please speak lower. Why do you shout?
- Get lost.
Madam, they say that they
have come just to congratulate.
Okay, tell them they
we got their congratulations.
Okay.
See. Madam said that they
got their congratulations.
Go.
- Khan..
- I cannot tolerate your insult.
I am going and bringing
that donkey to your feet.
What is the need of fighting?
We will come tomorrow.
Come on.
The party is lonely without you.
Please come.
Did you see that?
Such big people are coming to Vijay.
She surely must be some princess.
That is all right. But why didn't
you call out to him when he came out?
He would surely come to me,
he would embrace me.
Then you should have done like that.
But would it be nice to do like that
in the presence of so many people?
Why?
Wouldn't he be embarrassed?
Wouldn't people laugh at him?
You are still..
What soil are you made up of?
Come.
Mother..
It's hot.
- Did you meet your brother?
- Yes, mother.
Sit down, Khan.
What did he say?
What would he say?
He fell at my feet when he saw me.
I had him embrace me.
And he acted so nicely with us,
isn't it, Khan?
Yes.. yes..
I was scared that he
would refuse to recognize you.
How is that possible?
Even when I refused,
he dragged me inside.
He introduced me to everyone.
There were such people there.
Isn't it, Khan?
Yes, such lies..
I mean there were such people there.
What else did he say?
Mother, when he saw me alone,
he was very angry.
He told me that are the household
members needed to invited?
What can I tell you, mother?
I ate so much in happiness..
I ate so much..
Isn't it, Khan?
Yes. We ate so much mother,
we won't be hungry for four days.
And for the kids,
did he not send anything?
For the kids.. why not..
- He sent sweets, cake pastries and..
- And round KACHORIES.
- Kachoris, Samose (snacks) and whatnot.
- Where are all those things?
They are here..
Khan.. I gave you
that basket in the bus?
- In the bus..
- Yes, we came in the moving bus.
- The basket must be left there.
- Yes, so where is it?
Left in bus..
What do you do, Khan?
I had brought those things for the kids.
Okay.. I will bring it.
Go. Go and bring it quickly.
He is a strange man.
Okay, mother.
Madhavi.. something is amiss.
I will see.
You will hide it from me?
What should I tell you, Madhavi?
Maybe you won't be able to listen to it.
For God's sake,
tell me what the matter is.
Madhavi..
I am jobless from today.
That's it? Such a small matter?
I thought what problems
have been created.
The ground has moved and..
Madhavi..
Is being joblessness a small matter?
Think about it. How will it work now?
How did it work for so many years?
Do you know?
When father expired,
you had such a burden.
Satyen..
Viju.. Geeta, all were young.
What is the problem now?
All are grown up now.
That is all right, Madhavi.
But I am not young now.
My hands and legs are tied.
My back is broken.
To tell you the truth..
If Viju didn't leave the house,
would you be defeated like this?
Till the time your hands and legs
worked, wouldn't you have worked?
That is all right.. but.. but..
I know..
You are tired now.
It is right too.
You worked all alone for so many years.
And all of us just kept eating.
Now let me take up this burden.
Madhavi..
There have been many
fire tests in my life.
But you never let it's heat reach me.
And I won't let it reach you even now.
But Madhavi..
Mother shouldn't know about it.
- I am ashamed.
- Why?
I know. Whatever happening
in your house is due to my sister.
I don't know what to do.
Are there so many problems in the
house just because Viju has left it?
No, Reena.
Brother has lost his job.
All problems don't come together.
He will get some other job.
Brother cannot get
any other job at this age.
He has weak eyes.
And then, it is torture
to make him work at this age too.
I feel like leaving this education..
And do some labor
or hard work somewhere.
But.. But I shouldn't
let brother work.
Your education will help brother.
You can help him more
when you are educated.
Where is the time for education, Reena?
Once that Viju has gone,
Kali will ask for the loan.
And on that side..
Mother won't be able
to tolerate Viju's separation.
Everything will be all right.
If you get a proper job..
I won't let you leave the job.
Mother..
I had told Navendu before hand.
Brother.. if you are taking the loan,
think about it.
Yes, brother.
Who knew that the situation
would change like this?
Geeta has grown up.
You were saying something?
I was saying..
See, you don't have anything.
But Viju has everything.
What will happen with that?
What will not happen?
You had taken a loan on this house.
And this house is the wealth
of all you three brothers.
Legally..
I can take the loan back from you,
Satyen or Viju too.
Tell me, or just one.
Is this possible?
Why isn't it possible?
It is happening since years.
Viju has money.
He can repay the loan.
And then, you had taken the loan for him.
Kali babu is right.
Let him take the loan from him.
No mother.
I cannot let him do this at all.
What will you do then?
I will do whatever I can.
If needed, I will sell myself.
See. If you sell yourself,
I won't get my money back.
Navendu.. I have spoken to
you in the tongue of friendship.
I will have to speak
to you in a legal tongue now.
Please don't say like that, brother.
Whatever you say,
this is what will happen.
I give you time for a week more.
If you don't arrange
for my money in that time..
Then this house will be auctioned.
No.. no..
Navendu..
Mother.. mother..
Madhu.. Satyen..
How did you remember me..
You aren't worth to be missed by anyone.
Then why have come to my house?
Even my shoe wouldn't come here.
Aunty has forced me to come here.
To abuse me?
Who will spoil their
mouths by abusing you?
I have just come here to
tell you that mother is not well.
I see..
Okay..
So you can see too?
Much better and sharper than before.
If only your heart was
clear like your sight too.
The ones who have a dirty heart..
They see everything
bad about others.
That is what I wanted to tell you too.
It is good that you said it.
I will leave now.
- Tell brother.
- Listen..
Don't you want money for mother's cure?
What mother wants..
Maybe she won't get it from this house.
What is that?
A son's love and a
daughter-in-law's duty.
"Life has two colors and two ways."
"There are two forms of life to live."
"Think and take your steps,
think about them, crazy man!"
"Make every man understand this."
"One road goes to the temple
and the other to the tavern."
"One shouldn't forget the road."
"The traveler shouldn't be fooled."
"Life has two colors and two ways."
"There are two forms of life to live."
Take this.
What? Your bangles?
They are not dearer than mother's life..
"On one side, there are such people..
Who live for the others,
who live for the others."
"On the other side, there are people..
Who suck other's
blood for themselves.!"
"Someone sows flowers
and some scatter thorns."
"Life has two colors and two ways."
"There are two forms of life to live."
Has your sir come?
No. He has gone to
the club with madam.
He has kept this letter for you.
Letter? What is there in this?
What is there?
He has sent money.
Maybe for mother's cure.
Take this.
And give it back to your sir.
Tell him,
that mother needs a son, not money.
Greeting sir.
Mother..
It is great,
it is a miracle, an absolute miracle.
- What happened?
- Mother..
If a man does good things,
the god himself helps him.
What happened?
A money order worth five
hundred rupees has arrived.
From where has it come?
Who has sent it?
I don't understand
who can send this money.
But whatever be the case, mother.
At this time, the one who
has sent this money is an angel.
An angel.
I understand.
Please call Khan.
What is the need of calling Khan?
Mother has called and Khan has arrived.
Let me see your hand.
I swear to god,
your face is so bright today.
If you talk like this, will I be cured?
What did I do now, mother?
Why did you send this
money order for 500 rupees?
Money order? Which money order?
Why did you send this money?
Money? What money?
Mother, I didn't send any money.
You call me mother and you lie too?
Swear on me.
You didn't send this money?
Don't tell me to swear on you. Don't.
You sent the money.
It is your handiwork.
Mother, I am your neighbor
since ten to twelve years.
I haven't told you my story till today.
I was ten years old, my mother expired.
My father married again.
That mother was very strict.
She used to lock me up and didn't..
Give me any food
for three days and beat me.
At last, I was fed up
and ran away from my country.
I wandered around and came here.
I came here and saw you, mother.
You are Narendu's step mother.
But you love him so much..
I have an ambition.
If God gives me money..
I will go to my country
and serve my mother so much..
That she will embrace me and say..
Gul Khan is my real son,
he is my real son.
All this has happened because of you.
But what did I do?
Why did you send that money?
So what sin did I commit?
If there is a illness in the house..
Money can be needed at any time.
Then why did they send the money back?
Your sister-in-law is so arrogant.
If your money was
used for mother's cure..
Wouldn't she have lost her face?
Therefore, she has sent the money back.
Why don't you understand?
All this is your Navendu
brother's tricks.
His mind is as poisoned
as his words are sweet.
Poison?
What else?
He wants to defame you.
He wants you have you
fall in people's eyes.
How?
By showing the world
that even in the state of..
Joblessness and poverty
he is looking after his..
Step mother sister and brother.
And you..
Once you got money, you left everyone.
You forgot everyone.
Mother..
See who has come.
You?
You got time to meet mother after all.
Mother.. Viju has taken to take you.
Navendu..
You have supported me all your life.
Can you not support
me for a couple more days?
Please don't say like this, mother.
You will be cured nicely at Viju's house.
There will be good medicines
and the best of doctors.
You will be cured very quickly, mother.
No, son.
That death which I get
in your house is better..
Than the life that I
will get living in Viju's house.
I will not go there.
Why do you hate me so much after all?
What wrong have I done?
Just that I live separate?
- And that too because..
- No, Viju..
Not all that.
But whatever you did
with your god like brother..
For that, forget about till I am alive..
I cannot forgive you
for that even after my death.
Mother.. let it be. You are ill.
Let it be, brother.
The fire that had to
be ignited has been already.
What is the use of
sprinkling water on it?
Viju..
The blood which is so poisonous..
Cannot be my blood.
I have given birth..
To you with my womb,
but the truth is..
Today I am ashamed
to call you my son.
Go away from here, out of my sight!
Please don't feel bad
about mother's words, Viju.
Because of her illness,
she has become so weak..
That she cannot tolerate
even a small thing without her wish.
But this doesn't mean that a mother..
Cannot tolerate her own son too.
Viju.. it is just
a matter of a few days.
Let mother get cured.
I will drop her to your house myself.
Keep her at your house
for as many days as you wish.
Mother will stay with me,
and stay in my house.
Will you like this, brother?
What do you mean?
I know who is doing all this.
Who has poisoned mother's
ears against me. You!
Viju..
Who has ignited the sparks
of hatred in mother's heart. You!
Who has instigated
the son against the mother.
- You have..
- Viju..
What are you saying?
Whom are you talking to?
Think about whatever you say.
I have thought about
whatever I am saying.
It is a sin even to think
like this about brother.
The brother who ruined his life for us..
If you cannot give
that brother anything else..
At least don't give
him false accusations.
What kind of accusations?
Whatever I am saying is the truth.
Do I not have a right on mother?
Can I not do anything for my mother?
Look at yourself and see for once.
What have you done for mother till today?
You got a wife and you forgot all of us?
You forgot everything?
Why do you nag me about
my wife every now and then?
I have married.
I didn't commit any sin.
When a man commits a sin,
only he is punished.
But when he marries,
the whole house is affected.
Whether is it good or bad.
If there is a bad effect
on the house due to my marriage..
The reason for this could
be the household members too.
Why are you accusing the household..
Members to hide your weaknesses?
Leave it.
Viju is not in his senses at this time.
Yes, I am not in my senses at this time.
If I were in my senses,
why would I come here?
Viju..
Before I lose my senses,
you go away from here.
I am going away from here.
But you people remember..
You people will have to repent one day.
Oh Allah..
Please help us god, please help us.
- Have you come, Navendu's father?
- Mother..
Have you come to take me?
- I will come right away.
- Mother.. mother..
Brother..
Mother..
Satyen..
It is not Satyen, I am Navendu.
Remember..
Navendu had snatched the morsel..
From his children's
mouth and had fed all of us.
Madhavi..
Daughter-in-law..
When you give children tea
instead of milk my heart is rents.
What? Have Navendu's
glasses not come?
Satyen..
You write to Viju in the foreign country.
He will bring nice glasses for Navendu.
Satyen..
He has lost his job.
My Navendu is very good.
He can keep his children hungry.
But he cannot beg anyone.
Promise me, Satyen. Promise me.
That you will look after his children.
Satyen..
Promise me..
Mother..
Mother.. I promise you.
It will happen like that, I promise you.
Navendu..
You are so unfortunate.
Father didn't give
you anything while leaving.
And even the mother
couldn't give you anything.
Navendu..
Come to me. Don't be afraid.
See. I am your new mother.
I will love you a lot.
Will you love me too?
Navendu.. Navendu.. Navendu..
Oh Guddi and Raju..
Why did you come home
so early from school?
Mother. The teacher
sent us back from school.
Why did she send you?
She insulted us today.
Why?
You didn't pay the fees.
The headmaster called us.
He gave us this letter.
And sent us on a holiday.
It is the fees for four months, mother.
Yes. Therefore they sent us.
Bring it tomorrow.
Or don't come tomorrow.
We will send the money tomorrow.
Go. Go inside.
Don't cry mother.
Otherwise it will be done.
It will be ruined. Come on.
I searched for you in so many places.
I went to your house, you weren't there.
You weren't there in the college too.
What are you doing here all alone?
I was thinking..
What were you thinking about?
Just that you shouldn't meet me.
Why?
Because our roads are different.
I know.
Till the time the
situation doesn't change..
You cannot even
think about marriage.
It is my birthday the day after tomorrow.
You will come and sing
in everyone's presence.
I am yours. I am just yours.
- Happy birthday..
- Happy birthday.
Happy birthday.. happy birthday.
Congratulations. Congratulations.
You are looking so cute.
Congratulations.
"There is no spring due
to the flowers in the breeze."
"I am not fated,
my friend, for your love."
"There is no spring due
to the flowers in the breeze."
"I am not fated,
my friend, for your love."
"I don't know when I
won't keep my word in love."
"When I will become a
tear and fall in my own eyes."
"I swear to you..
I am not to be relied upon."
"I am not fated,
my friend, for your love."
"I set a new sigh in my words everyday."
"I wait for a new sorrow every day."
"My heart doesn't
wait for any happiness."
"I am not fated,
my friend, for your love."
"How can a poor
person love the rich?"
"Many Romeos have been
separated from their Juliet's."
"Nobody knows what
they are fated for."
"I am not fated,
my friend, for your love."
"There is no spring due
to the flowers in the breeze."
"I am not fated,
my friend, for your love."
Did you bring it?
Sister-in-law,
he refuses to give any more loan.
What?
He says.. that you don't repay..
The previous loan
and you come to beg further.
He says.. he says..
Have we thought it
to be our father's shop?
How dare he!
Has he started abusing while managing
the prices of pulses and dough?
- I will teach him a lesson right away.
- No..
The ones who take loans don't get angry.
We are in need, brother.
We take loans, we don't beg for alms.
He gives goods worth ten paise..
And writes twenty
five paise in the accounts.
Life is the name of helplessness.
When the situation is bad,
one has to tolerate everything.
Be calm. See.
Look, if you hide for sometime,
then everything will be all right.
Everything will be all right.
Promise me, Satyen.. Promise me..
Just like how Navendu looked after..
You, Geeta and Viju..
You will look after his
children just like that too.
Hey.. Mr. Satyen..
Will you read all these books today?
I have studied.
I have brought these books to you.
Please sell them.
Wait.. Satyen..
Satyen.. what is all this?
Fruits and vegetables, will you buy them?
Wow.. the elder brother
is general a manager..
And the younger brother
is a vegetable vendor on the street?
What can be done?
The elder brother is God
and the younger brother is a devil.
Driver.. let's go home.
Oh Viju.. come sit down.
How are you?
I am all right till now.
But now whatever has
to happen will happen.
Why? What is the matter?
The matter is a small one.
When a general manager's
brother will sell fruits..
And vegetables on the streets of..
Bombay the matter
will be very small.
I will be defamed, I will be insulted..
Maybe Satyen didn't think..
Satyen thinks a lot.
And before thinking anything,
living is necessary.
And earning is necessary for life.
But.. but this doesn't mean that..
One can do anything
wretched to earn money.
There is respect in
every earning of honesty.
But did you think about my respect too?
When the people working under me..
Find out that my brother
is selling fruits and vegetables..
- What will happen to my respect and dignity?
- Brother..
Even I have become selfish like you.
No, Satyen..
I don't understand.
If you had to do some work,
why didn't you take any job?
One gets money in
a job after thirty days.
But here..
Here there is a need
every morning and evening.
If there was a need,
why didn't you ask me for any money?
If we had to beg,
there is the whole world there.
Why will we beg to a shameless brother?
Satyen..
I have told you earlier too.
I will tell you now too.
I will take Satyen and Geeta to my house.
I will take their responsibility.
- Doubtless. If they want to go.
- Brother.
You decide in between.
Brother, listen to
our decision too. Geeta..
Geeta..
Vijay has come to pick us up.
We will have to stay there.
I have just two brothers.
I am happy with them.
Did you hear that?
I thought that one
is arrogant due to wealth.
But today.. today I can
see that poverty has pride too.
The poor people have only this wealth.
Rich people like you
can never buy it out.
"Everyone is proud of his wife."
"However she is,
she is a maiden for him."
"Everyone is proud of his wife."
"The one who has a black wife.."
"He tells the people around.."
"Even Juliet was black,
this story is very famous."
"Everyone is proud of his wife."
"The one who has a plump wife..
He goes around and tells people.."
"She is from a rich house,
she is away from all sorrows."
"Everyone is proud of his wife."
"The one whose wife is short."
"He tells the people."
"She has come from a big house,
she may be short."
"Everyone is proud of his wife."
"However she is,
she is a maiden for him."
Mummy..
Father.. father.. take this money.
They are a full fifteen rupees.
Money?
Where did you get them from?
We found them on the road.
- Are you lying?
- Yes..
No, father, he is telling the truth.
Both of you are lying.
Tell me the truth,
where did you get this money from?
We thought that we
need money for the fees.
We saw people earn money by singing..
We thought that we will
sing and earn money too.
The people liked the song
and fifteen rupees were collected.
This means that you begged, isn't it?
God knows what has
happened to this house.
One doesn't do like this.
One doesn't beg.
Don't do like this ever. Take it.
Take this money and give it to mother.
She will distribute it amongst the poor.
I want to help you.
But I don't want money.
We already have such a huge loan.
Loan.. who is giving you a loan?
I will give you money with this hand..
And I will take
the money with this hand.
What do you want?
What can I want?
If you wish, our friendship
can turn into a relation.
- Relation?
- Yes.
I have money and you have the girl.
I didn't understand..
I mean.. Geeta..
See, Geeta is of your
grand daughter's age.
Why do you look at my age?
I swear to God.
Look at me.
I am still hale and hearty.
You wretch, rascal.
Get lost from my house.
Yes, I will go. But remember..
You will remember this
insolence all through your life.
- Go.
- I am going.
Kali sir, go to that man
who you had loaned money too.
Tell me.
What kind of darkness is this?
If I go to them,
they kick me out of the house.
If I come to you,
I am told to go to them.
Don't forget.
I have your apartment mortgaged with me.
I can sell it anytime
I want and take my money.
Why don't you have that done?
Have the house auctioned
and take your money back.
Why do you come to me?
Just so that you don't tell me tomorrow..
That they had to leave
their house due to me.
This is what I want too.
They should be rendered homeless.
They should yearn for every paise.
They should beg on the streets.
The brother who separated a mother..
From her son this
should be his final state.
Tell me. There will
be an auction on that house.
"There should be a good bungalow built."
"Where we all stayed together."
Uncle Khan..
Yes, child?
Where are we taking
this furniture off too?
The furniture is old now, isn't it?
New furniture will be made now.
Uncle.. the house has become old too.
The house will be made new too.
So uncle, where will we stay?
With me in my house.
But uncle, your house is very small.
So what if my house is small?
My heart is very big.
My cycle..
Let go of my cycle. Let go!
Hey boy.. go away.
No.. if you take my cycle away,
what will I ride?
Didn't I tell you to go away?
Hey!
If you raise your hand on the boy..
I will make ten pieces
of your every bone. Leave the cycle.
Who are you?
I am the guardian of the house.
Take it away.
This house is to be auctioned.
Everything in this
house is owned by Kali.
This house..
This furniture will be auctioned.
And whatever money comes from that..
Will be used to repay the debt.
Take the cycle and keep it up.
Not at all.
If this cycle goes, then nobody
will go from here, I tell you.
They will call the police.
What about the police,
let them call the army.
- But this cycle will not go for the auction.
- Khan!
Let them do what they want to do.
You cannot fight the law.
But what kind of law is this?
They can take your furniture and things.
Why are they taking this boy's cycle?
If the father is the criminal,
the shadow..
Of the crime falls on the son too.
Take it away.
Take the child's toy too.
Take the vehicle away.
Navendu..
Sister-in-law.. Geeta.. children.
Come on in - What happened, uncle?
Oh, at least come inside.
Sister-in-law..
Come on please..
Come brother.. come..
I committed a mistake.
There is my Allah's name
on the place of worship.
Is it something wrong?
No. Khan.
There can't be anything better than this.
You want to marry me, isn't it?
Marriage?
I am dreaming about this since so long.
This dream can be true.
Oh! I will sweeten your mouth.
Tell me.
Tell me, when should I
take the auspicious date for?
But you will have
to promise me something.
Oh promise!
Ask my life, I will give it to you.
Give his apartment back to elder brother.
- And I will marry you.
- That's it?
Oh.. Geeta..
Come. Come here. It is your house.
You are so beautiful. Geeta, I am..
Dreaming of making
you my wife since so long.
We will marry tomorrow itself now.
You'll marry with me, isn't it!?
Yes.. but.. return the
documents of the house first.
Oh! What about documents..
This apartment,
that apartment, everything is yours.
We will marry tomorrow.
Geeta.. why not today..
- Why not today..
- No.. No.. What are you doing?
Let me go! Let me go!
Save me! Save me!
You wretch!
You want to molest a poor girl?
Tell me, what were you doing?
What were you doing?
You didn't find any other house?
You got our house to do this?
Please let him go, brother.
You remember your devil now.
Because once you go to your devil..
You will never come
back in this world then.
Brother.. Please let him go.
Let him go..let him go.
For my sake.
Get up.
See.
You animal.
The girl whom you wanted to molest,
she is saving your life.
Fall to her feet and pray to her.
This is the question
of our family's dignity.
Please save our house
from being auctioned.
So what if there is nothing else..
Between the walls
of that dilapidated house..
It houses the respect
and dignity of our ancestors.
You are telling this today.
Today, when you have come on the streets.
But why didn't you think
about this when you were at home?
And how would you think about it?
You were the owner of
the house till yesterday.
I was a servant in that house.
And even today,
I am a servant in that house.
The servant of one house can become..
A servant in some other house too.
Don't be so hard hearted.
You have a house too.
God forbid.. if your
house was in such a state too?
Sister-in-law..
Think what you are talking about.
You are standing in my
house and cursing my house?
Please forgive me. Please forgive me.
I don't know what all I said.
I am not in my senses.
Please fulfill my desire,
I will go away from here.
- I fall at your feet.
- Sister-in-law! What are you doing?
Your pure hands are not
to touch these impure feet.
Satyen..
- What are you saying?
- I am right.
The woman doesn't
have love in her heart..
She is useless like a barren land.
Satyen..
Brother..
I am ashamed of your honesty.
Mother was ashamed to
call you her son yesterday.
And today,
I am ashamed to call you my brother.
Please be silent, brother, please..
I have been silent till today.
But I cannot stay silent today.
If they have got some money, they..
Have forgotten that brother who..
Brought them up like their father.
And made them able to
live in this world with pride.
What do you want to say?
You know it very well.
Elder brother starved and thirsted.
His innocent children kept crying.
Sister-in-law shed
tears all her life.
But for your future
and your further studies..
He never thought
or cared about anyone.
He mortgaged his house and took a loan.
But he didn't even buy a
handful of grain from that money.
So that you shouldn't starve.
His whole life..
He spent his whole
life in a tattered dhotie.
So that you should wear expensive suits.
That's enough. That's enough brother.
There is a lot to be said yet,
sister-in-law.
Today when brother doesn't
have that strength..
And his eyes don't
have that brightness..
You have left him today, so that..
He writes on the streets and dies?
- Fie on you.
- Stop your rubbish.
This is not rubbish.
This is the truth.
Satyen..
You are fighting with your
brother for your step brother?
I don't know who is a
step brother or a real brother.
I just know that one can
get a woman like you again.
Satyen..
Silent, Satyen.
But one gets a brother like Rama..
And a sister-in-law
like Sita just once in life.
Satyen..
For my sake, please be silent.
Come on, sister-in-law. Come on.
In a house, where the
man is a slave of the woman..
It is a sin to even
breathe in that house.
You call me a slave to a woman?
Aren't you ashamed?
Come on, sister-in-law.
This way, sister-in-law. Wait here.
I will settle the
account of this damn guy.
You call me a damn guy?
If you were a man,
you wouldn't attack me from behind.
This is something like a man.
Open the door, Satyen.
Aren't you ashamed to raise
your hand on your elder brother?
Open the door, Satyen.
Satyen.. open the door.
Get up.
Enough Satyen, my brother, enough.
Hello? Doctor Verma.
I am Neela. Please come here quickly.
Please go out. Please.
- Nurse.. put him on oxygen.
- Yes, sir.
Doctor..
My brother will live, isn't it?
See. He is in a critical state.
Maybe, he will have to be operated upon.
It will be decided when
the senior doctor comes.
He must be arriving right away.
Hello. Bandra police station.
I am Dr. Mathur, from Nanavati hospital.
I want to report a case.
Concussion of the skull.
Yes. It is very serious.
The people who brought him here are here.
Yes. Yes. Okay. Thank you.
Please listen. Come here.
The matter has worsened.
I think that before the police arrives..
- We should call our lawyer.
- Yes.
Doctor.. has the operation completed?
Yes.
I want to take his statement.
You cannot take his
statement at this time.
In what state is Satyen in?
He has been taken
to the operation theatre.
This means that the case is serious.
What should we do now?
We will have to wait and see,
Mrs. Gupta.
But sir, what is the legal implication?
You are responsible for that.
If Satyen survives and
says that you have hit him..
Then you will held
guilty under the IPC 325.
And you will be in prison
for five to six months.
And if..
What about if?
If Satyen is killed, you
will be held guilty under IPC 307.
And under that, you will be
imprisoned for five or seven years.
This means that our
life is in Satyen's hands.
Then it is impossible for us to survive.
Satyen won't rest unless
he sends us to jail.
Please, save us.
I am sorry, inspector. My
client won't give any statement here.
Whatever statements have to be given,
I will give them.
But not here, in the court.
- As you wish.
- Thank you.
How is Satyen?
He is unconscious as yet.
He may have to be operated.
God knows what will happen now?
When we are ill fated, what can we do?
But tell me. How did this
happen when you were here?
What could I do?
Satyen locked me in a room.
And they were fighting outside,
the both of them.
I knocked a lot.
But nobody listened to me.
There was such fighting..
Such fighting..
Satyen is temperamental.
But even an enemy doesn't hit like this.
I had so many dreams for Viju.
What all did I not do for Viju?
He should study and become successful.
He should have nice concepts
and be respected and famous.
He put my years of penance
into dust in a moment.
I tried so much that the respect
of the house should be there.
But this brother of mine defeated me.
Sister-in-law..
Satyen.. how is Satyen?
Everything is in the hands of the Lord.
Daughter.. we are ill fated.
We just have to see how lucky we are.
Sister-in-law..
Brother..
Oh Viju.. you fool.
What problem did you put yourself in?
Brother..
You are still thinking about me?
What can I do?
How can I forget what
I have done all my life?
Brother..
I am not worthy of your love.
I'm not naīve. I did everything
whatever I didn't have to do.
And yet, you aren't angry with me?
Brother..
Why don't you beat me and insult me?
Why don't you break my face?
Viju..
If the teeth bite the tongue,
one doesn't break his teeth.
See, Vijay has come back.
This police.. for you?
- Did you give any statement?
- No.
Excuse me, have you come in this matter?
But who are you?
I am Navendu Prasad Gupta.
The boy who has been hurt..
Is my brother.. younger brother.
Actually, he is my step brother.
We have an ancestral house.
He used to ask his share in it.
I didn't like it.
One day, we argued and had a scuffle.
I took something and hit
him on the head by mistake.
No.. no..
This is wrong. This is lies.
Are you all right?
What do you mean?
When the elder brother
is taking our crime on his head..
What are you thinking?
You mean, that he should go
to prison and we should be silent?
This is the best chance.
The everyday fights will be done with.
One is ready to die and
the other is ready for prison.
Take advantage of their stupidity.
The cane will break
and the snake will die too.
Shameless. Low woman.
Viju..
What insolence is this?
Don't meddle, brother.
She is not a woman, she is a snake.
Silent, whatever Neela is,
she is your wife.
My eyes have opened today.
The curtains on my mind have been undone.
She is not a woman, she is a witch.
She separated me from my blood.
Viju..
The one who repeats the
things of the past is immature.
Brother.. what all you didn't
do for me. I can't tell you.
I just know..
That if I make shoes out of my
skin and make these feet wear them..
- Even then I cannot repay your gratitude.
- Silent..
But now.. not any longer, brother.
Not any longer.
- Inspector..
- Viju. -I have hit Satyen..
No.. for my sake..
Congratulations to all of you.
Congratulations.
Mr. Satyen didn't
have any internal wounds.
And doctor.. the operation..
That wasn't needed
and won't be needed too.
- Where is he? - He is inside.
- Can we see him? - Of course.
Just a minute.
Forgive me. Doctor.. till
the time I don't take his statement..
Nobody from them can meet him.
Oh! I see.
Please come out for a minute,
if you don't mind. Come with me.
Oh God!
What if Satyen says
anything wrong in anger?
Don't worry. Satyen is temperamental.
But he is our brother after all.
I am sorry for the trouble.
But can I ask you how you got this wound?
Yes?
I want to know who hit you.
You have some misconception, inspector.
Nobody hit me.
Then this wound..
That..
I was getting down from the stairs,
I slipped and fell down.
Are you telling the truth?
I am saying the truth.
Okay.
Didn't I tell you?
Satyen is temperamental.
But he is our brother.
Brother.. brother..
Please forgive me.
I haven't walked on the road of good.
I have just walked on
the road of my own needs.
Now, I will walk on your road.
Please give me place in your feet.
No, daughter-in-law. Get up..
"A beautiful bungalow
should be made.."
"All my family members
should live in it."
"A beautiful bungalow
should be made.."
"The bungalow of gold,
a settlement of silver.."
"It demands for a whole bed."
"A beautiful and good bungalow."
"A beautiful bungalow
should be made.."
Father..
If only you could see
it with your own eyes.
There is no one who is step today.
"The Bindiya (forehead dot) will shine,
the garland will be aromatic.."
"Whether you don't
get sleep or you get it."
"The collyrium will radiate and
the flowers will exude a fragrance."
"No matter if he
gets annoyed with me."
"The Bindiya (forehead dot) will shine,
the garland will be aromatic.."