With a girl in the house
atmosphere was very pleasant
But what to do?
Rosy child do you know train
leaves at 7.30
Have you packed your
things?
What's this, your clothes are still
hanging here?
You know very well mother that
Rosy will not go anywhere
Be sensible Raju
She should go back
to her house
She has no house, no support, she
has to stay here only
If she stays here then I'll
have to go from here
So long as I am alive my house
belongs to my sister
I'll not allow you to go
First go & push her in
the train
Then only your mother will
stay here
Do you think she will stay with a dancer
- I'm talking to my mother
Will you keep quiet
Whom are you talking to
you idiot
Are you throwing her out of the
house or not?
No
Alright, sister pack your things
bus leaves at 5
Mother you are going!
Shameless girl, she
won't move at all, Oh God...
Please don't go mother, I fall
at your feet
Mother! I am a short while you'll
call me uncle
Your mother need not go
from here
If I like I can turn you
out from here
Your father wasn't
a fool
Half of the property he has given
to my sister
Mother if you go then...
I warn you won't see my face for
the whole life
Mother, I am hungry
give me food
I cried and dissuaded
her from going
Mother has gone?
She couldn't defy uncle
You allowed her to go
No Rosy, I got angry not with you
but with me
I swear by you Raju I caught
mother's feet
But uncle pulled my hair and
pushed me away
I wasn't able to stop it
And after that I behaved with you
so shabbily
This you should have done
earlier Raju
I seperated a son from his
mother, I should kill myself
Mad girl, mother has gone only
to uncle's place...
She'll cool down in a few days
& come back
Raju you throw that woman out
of your house
For that woman entire town has
turned hostile towards you
She has no honour & respect
The one who has left her husband
how can she be faithful...
One more word & it'll be the
end of friendship
Let the friendship
go to hell
Which creates a rift between friends
for a bad woman
Get up... Get up...
Why don't you throw me out
Raju, it'll be the end of miseries
Who all will you fight with
for my sake?
Who else is there for me
except you?
I had already decided about this...
I'm a social worker, wedded to
the old culture-
I want the old traditions
to blossom again
And its your responsibility
because you are the teachers...
Because the future generation is
dependent on you
You've to mould their
character
Should they go for Pop & Jazz
or classical music
You've to decide about it
I came to remind you that the
annual function is to be held
And fortunately the famous classical
dancer Ms. Nalini is in town
Ms. Nalini?
Please keep on sitting
Ms. Nalini they're my friends
A variety show is going to be
held in their school
And they want to know whether you...
Fancy dress, dancing, singing, skit...
And I've to dance in that?
No No! It means that...
All these items will be over by
interval & after that your...
Yes yes yes...
These gentleman want to know
what item you will give...
You want me to dance now
- No no you're mistaken
Your item will be excellent, but
the programme has to be printed
And something has to be mentioned
- yes yes
But no audience, no music
If all of you insist then...
Why all this trouble?
One minute Raju
The one who has charmed this
worshipper of art by her dance
Where does that Mr. Nalini live?
He is an ordinary Guide Raju
who serves people
People who want to learn while
going on excursion
The objects that they see I decribe
them in an enchanting way
I may be mixing lies with the
truth but it can't be helped
Because this world is
fully adulterated
And the more a man is adulterated
the more he is appreciated
I want to show my talent
Ms. Nalini if she'll come with me
I am sorry Ms. Nalini is tired &
she is taking rest
You come some other day
Who are you?
I am Rosy, attendent of Ms. Nalini
But you wanted her only
isn't it?
What did you say?
These are the days of
adultration
Nalini is adulterated with Rosy
Rosy will be fine with me
Fine!
I show the people the world
through my eyes
Create history in ruins
I draw a picture with my words
show all the past
I show the future also
sometimes
See what there is infront
You might say its an old
lonely uninhabited house
Will it be a lie?
Ms. Rosy see further
Not beyond the landscape but
beyond the time
8 Months have passed Nalini is
written on the name plate
A blooming garden
is there
And the shining car belongs
to Ms. Nalini
You want to know what is
that crowd
Those mad people are waiting since
morning to have a glimpse of Ms. Nalini
And that man, didn't you
recognise him?
He is her Manager, all
in all Raju
See how impressively he walks
How reverendly people greet him
What he professed he has proved
he made Rosy & Ms. Nalini
People thought he boasts but
now they worship him
Raju, is it true?
- 100%
Can I know, who is interested
to know?
Every mirror has a picture
There is one mirror in
my heart also
Which hides this charming face
all the time
Really?
- Yes
Go ahead
Will you marry me?
You've got the divorce
from Marco
Atleast some one has found me
worthy of him
I can give my life for you
Shall I take It as acceptance
- yes yes
To become your wife, I will leave
my dance & job
Gladly
Our joint efforts are there
in your work!
The situation to quit this
will never come!
If we have children then?
There isn't any guarantee that we'll
have children after marriage
Is it a necessity that our
marriage take place now itself!
...But putting off long is
also not tolerable for me
There, what you see in Lake palace
Jag Temple... City palace
And that yellow Bungalow
on the hillock!
Belongs to the famous
dancer Ms. Nalini
10 shows in Delhi 10 shows
in Bombay,10 in Calcutta
30 days,10 days for travelling, etc
...totally 40 days! But...
Rosy tell me truthfully
why are you not happy?
You've become what you
had dreamed!
You're doing what you've
always wanted to do!
I never thought...
What?
I fear that my life will
become like yoked ox!
Blind folded, I'll be going round
round... round at the same place!
Tell me if you get tired, I'll not
accept new programmes!
Rosy, today you were wonderful
Feeling very happy to see you
Is Rosy here?
What are you doing here?
Last time when you met me
you talked to me respectfully
Last time when we met, you
considered dancing as
...A proffession of a woman
of a Harlem
...You!
Yes Raju!
I want to meet Rosy!
Rosy doesn't want to meet you!
Did you ask her?
Not necessary
Look Raju, I want to
meet her once!
I am behaving respectfully
with you!
So, leave this place
with respect!
If you try to enter
inside forcibly
Then, I too will be forced
to throw you out forcibly!
Do you know how much money
I made in this tour?
Rs 40,000!!!
Do I have a share in it?
Are we two separate?
Why don't you feel happy
seeing the cheque?
I can get happiness even
in a flower!
If not, even if I get the entire
world, I'll not be happy
Raju, I was never avaricious for money
even at Marco's house!
How did you get to
remember Marco today?
He's Mr Khanna!
He's Dinanath propritor
of Rajasthan Textile Mills!
He's Dhawan our chief of police!
Mr. Rudra, Lender of City Bank
...Mr. Sinha, who's going to contest
the next election!
...And Mr. Khanna is the
Editor of Truth of Voice!
Sir, Your article on Nalini
was very good!
But the photograph wasn't
very good!
May be he didn't photograph it!
Hey Mr. Raju where is Nalini?
...Please, you must definitely
hear Mr. Varma's new poetry
It's very noisy here...
please you come this side
You come this side!
Come on Mr. Varma
Yes please! It's a request!
She's going away...
...she's gone!
Till which time these people are
going to stick around you!
Why?
From morning they're stuck here
do you know its 12'o' clock!
I've called friends for lunch!
And you've not yet taken
bath and dressed
Raju, they're your friends
you be with them!
Let me be with my associates
Are you calling them as
your Associates?
Half-naked, half-hungry
road side Romeos!
They all look like beggars!
You only see their cloths!
They're not like your friends who can't
talk without a sip of liquor
They're exceptional artistes!
And who giggle loudly
on useless talks!
I hate in make belief!
My stake's 50!
Mine also a 50!
100! 100?!
No... I am dropping out!
My stake is Rs 200!
Mine also Rs 200!
And mine... is Rs 500!
Another Rs 500 from my side!
Okay! I quit!
It's show in Rs 1000!
Come on show! I'll give it!
Look Raju, we'll lose the
excitement of the game!
Okay! Lend me a 1000! I'll get
it from upstairs
No credit for gambling, please!
By the way you can take even
a lakh out side!
Come on, get it from the locker
what's so urgency in it?
Every second day you come to
get the cheques signed
Why don't you keep money in
your account also?
Fearing creditors!
Rs 2000?!
Only day before yesterday you
had drawn Rs 2000?
Rosy, big people's expenses are
also very big!
To maintain you prestige
it'll lost dearly!
Let it be... my prestige?
Take this... return back
Rs 1000 and show!
It's run!
Please take it!
What are you doing in
my room at this time?
Are you still awake?
No... I am talking
in my sleep!
Now a days you do remember only
when you're drunk, isn't it?
I drink remembering you and I
remember you when I am drunk
Okay, now you go to your
room and sleep!
You're always telling to go
away now a days!
Have you forgotten to say
come?
Move away!
Lay like that only
No, Raju now I don't like
all this!
Don't you like me anymore?
I don't like anything!
Because I consume liquor!
No!
I gamble...
- no!
Then, why Rosy?
- Enough!
There'll be a matter!
Then it's all over!
You mean, Love?!?
What's the meaning of Love?
Expectation, is thy name of Love?
When there's love with expectation
there won't be any meaning of Love!
There's always adulteration
in Love!
Just as you had an intention
about while seeking Love!
Now, do you love me with
any other intention?
If I tell something rash, you'll
tell that I am drunk!
Tell it, making drunkenness
as a reason!
I am thinking that Marco
might have been correct!
Marco was right!
He was right when he said that man shouldn't
live on a woman's earnings
Then, you've mistaken that
I am living of your earnings!
And you've forgotten that, it's me as
ladder, you has reached the top!
Have you forgotten that every pie
you earn is result of my hard work
Can you deny it?
Even before
I was rich all by myself!
We'll work after the show!
Yes Raju! When did I refuse it?
Sir, A parcel in the name
of Mrs. Rosy Marco!
I am greatful for Udaipur's Guide Raju
for helping & taking me to the caves
But, do you know Raju why no one
had ever reached upto this place!
Because, lt was in my fate
to do this job!
I was here searching it!
I was here only to know
the price of it!
I was here to get this place
a fame which it deserves!
But Raju, don't worry
your name will be definitely
mentioned in the book!
Because, it was you who had
brought me upto this place!
The matter is that...
This was sent to us from our
Bank's Delhi Head Branch
There in a joint account
of Mr & Mrs Marco!
...Some Rs 20-25 thousand worth
jewellary is there in the locker!
Because Mr. Marco wants to
close the Bank account!
...lt's obvious that you've
to take away the jewellary too!
And for this, they both have
to sign this application!
After being signed by
Mrs. Marco
...This will be sent to Mr. Marco for
his signature!
Yes... yes!
So Mr. Marco wants to steal
Ms. Nalini's jewels!
Mr. Marco wishes the jewellary
be given to Ms. Nalini
Then, he wants to show off
how large hearted he is?
Look sir, Ms. Nalini absolutely doesn't
want Mr. Marco's jewellary?
She will not even spit on it?
You can tell this with Mr. Marco!
Neither, you allow we to meet Mrs. Marco
not try to understand my words!
What do we have to do with
the fighting of a wife & husband?
The Bank wants the jewellary
be taken out!
After that throw it into drain
how does it concern us?
Get out Raju, otherwise
I've to walk out!
Then, please tell, will you
get this signed or...
Shall I send it by
registered post?
Get your balance Raju!
Get your balance
Marco is doing this cleverly
First, he sent book...
now... jewellary!
May be he's planning to win
back Rosy's heart!
It's better, if this matter
never reaches Rosy!
Hey look at this photos!
Yuch, they may be of some
priest!
Do you know what's
the time now?
What?
It's 11.30 PM
Oh! My God! I should've gone
home by 11 PM
...I am going off!
...Okay go and take rest!
Now a days you don't have any
time left for me!
I want to ask you something
...Let's talk tomorrow!
Thought that, why not ask now, what I
wanted to ask tomorrow
Where have you kept the
Marco's book?
This Fella Mani, will definitely
lose his job!
But, sir... l...
If you utter even a word more
I'll kick you out!
Are you my employee
or some one else?
Behind me, you go to
complain against me!
And... moreover try to
explain it!
...Don't do it like this
in future
Can't this distance between
us be closed?
Try it!
I've come to try, don't you
want to help me?
Raju, I don't have any
complaint against you!
My complaint is that you don't
have any complaint against me!
I wish that, you cry, shout
and abuse me!
...And even slap me also!
But do something by which I can
know that you've concern on me!
You had shown this much
of mercy, even on Marco!
A sort of a fort has formed on
all the 4 sides of the heart!
No gesture is able to reach
there now!
Neither happy... nor sad!
Raju, you're absoultely free
from my side!
Infact I am happy...
That you've learnt the
technic of acquiring happiness!
Don't throw me away Rosy
don't throw me away
Please Raju, I am very tired!
Sleep in my arms, resting
your head on my shoulder!
There was once a time, when you
used to get rejuvenated by that!
What are you doing?
Leave me!
This isn't anything new, me
holding your hands like this!
Suddenly, why is this
alieness?
Rosy, why is this hatred?
Where has the love gone
away for me?
What was my crime?
If you say, I'll quit drinking
gambling, all my friends!
...Even this world but for once
you become my old Rosy!
Please, for once tell me that
you love me, you love only me!
After that, I'll never be
a trouble to you!
...And I'll never come to you!
Oh! Mani! Come... come!
You said, we'll work
after the show!
Bring a glass from there
for yourself
No sir, after doing this
work I'll go!
Hey! Man! Get it!
Don't you also want to sit
with me & have a small talk?
You're making me feel shy!
Sir, What's the matter, today
you're drinking alone?
I was longing to talk so, I
thought I'll have a few pegs
...And say few words
to myself!
...I have become little
irritated!
If I say something bad in anger
don't take it seriously!
Do I've that capacity sir?
Life is also like a
intoxication! Friend!
When it gets you, don't
ask what'll be the condition?
...But when it gets down...
What's this fun?
It may have been good
if it was for fun?
Neither the castles would've
been built, nor destroyed!
Neither our paths could've
joined nor get split!
The funny thing about this is
this isn't fun!
Is all this drama neccessary?
One who has himself become drama
what drama will he play?
Come madam, I'll see you
up to the Car!
Alright, now you go and
change your dress!
...l'll be waiting for you!
I've waited for someone
very long!
On a path, which was never
in your journey!
What happened to all
of a sudden?
Look! It's show time!
The time is over!
The show is over!
I've seen it!
I think today you don't have the
intention of coming with me
My intention was right, but the
companion couldn't keep up with me
Raju, I've understood what
you want to tell me!
But, before hurting me
ask your heart
...Whether the whole
crime was mine?
Let God forbid anyone
hurting your heart
...Take madam to the theatre!
Has Boss come?
No madam, not yet!
For whom are you waiting here?
Everyone has left!
Any whereabouts of him?
No, not yet!
Mother! Your Raju has
come back!
Without you, this home isn't
like a home!
All the night I am lying
but I don't get sleep!
Neither there's anyone to feed me nor
to tell story and put me to sleep!
Tell uncle to forgive me!
Anyhow, the blood is of our
clan isn't it?
Didn't I tell you that one day
he'll change & come back!
...Come on sister, pack your bags
we will go to the city!
You sit there!
I thought that not only from
Nalini's house
...you might've run away
from the city itself!
What made you come here
my friend?
Not friendship! But today my
duty has brought me here!
Come... please come in!
You didn't do it rightly, Raju!
You could've done this to anyone
but you shouldn't have cheated Rosy
When, she had willingly given you
lakhs of her earnings to you!
Why did you do this for a
paltry Rs 30,000 worth jewellary?
For which, out of greed, you had
forged the signature!
Who told you this?
Who told me this?
...The whole city knows it
...This is your warrant!
...The sad job of arresting was
given to me
...For the crime of forgery...
What is the evidence that this
signature is mine not Nalini!
Do you think even after this
Nalini will lie for you?
When she came to know about it
she started crying
...She said that she never expected
something like this from Raju!
Where do I've to come?
For now to the lock-up!
...Till the judgement is
passed on the case!
Right now!
Won't you give me a chance
to meet Rosy?
Why not? When our friendship is
going to come to the help?
But, Raju as far as
I know
...She'll hate to see
even your face!
But still...
...l'll see her!
As you wish!
Ms. Nalini it's time!
I am coming
Madam, the curtains are up!
Where did you got lost
in thoughts?
Come on! Atleast now the
show is also over!
Have you talked to Rosy?
Talked?
Raju, why did you
do like that?
If you were in need of money
you could've told me!
...I would've sold my jewellary
I would've sold my property!
But, why did you do
like that?
I thought, if not anyone
atleast you'll understand me
Look, how ignorant my
thoughts were also
Raju, the truth is that
Neither you understood me
nor I understood you!
Offender Raju...
Under Indian Penal Code
Section 417...
...You're being Sentenced with
2 years prison!
Raju, when you left me
Only now I able to know
what you were to me?
...What you are?
I am abusing myself always
for not lying to save you!
Rosy! The crime was
definitely mine!
It would've been better if I
had made you as my wife!
But, I don't know, what was my compulsion
before I could make you my wife!
...I felt like making you
Queen of this world!
You achieved fame and
I become proud
...When I regained my senses
I found myself in Jail!
2 Years will fly away! We'll
start a new life again!
Yes! I've to start
newly again
...Life!
...Only I know it!
I had only this hope that someday
Raju will be able to forgive me!
Today, I don't have even
that hope also!
I don't know whose fault
was it!
...And I don't want to
know also!
But, one thing's definite
I've lost my son!
I don't know where he may be
in what condition?
The Govt has accepted
your petition
Next month a post office
will be opened here!
First school! Then Hospital...
and now post office!
My Lord, you've come and this village
has become a heaven!
Uncle, you said it right?
Go... school's over!
Okay... Okay... children
first stop the noise!
And tell me which story
do you want to hear?
Today, I'll narrate a story...
...Which my mother had narrated
many times in my childhood!
Once there was a
severe famine!
The Earth cracked up!
...There was not a drop of Rain!
...Even humans started dying in
utter starvation
...Even God's got afraid!
Is the God trying to eliminate
the mankind?
This is the story of
that great Sage
...Who had fasted continously
for 12 days
...And forced the God
to shower rain!
Lord! 12 days?
Didn't ate anything?
Neither did he ate nor drank!
Did it rain?
It poured!
It's a miracle of God!
Lord! Can this happen?
Lmagine that your house got
fired & this boy is inside
Won't you jump into the fire
to save the child?
You're just his mother!
They say that God for
his devotees!
Is mother, father, relative
and also friend
Yeah! I was talking
about famine...
Everything is over!
He's lying!
He has piled up stocks
in his godown!
Greetings Lord! Your food!
Hey! How are you here?
Where is Bhola?
Brother is on bed!
Bed?!
...Brother-hurt!
Hurt?!
Beat on head by stick...
lot of blood!
Is it? Where? How?
Brother! Stop... Riots
knifes, daggers & spears!
How do you talk without
any connection?
Sit here and regain your breath
and tell in detail!
Did the villagers fight?
Yes!
Did they loot the shop?
They looted!
A lot of people got hurt, isn't it?
Yes! They have... many more will
Tonight!
In this bad time, without helping
each other, why this bad blood?
Do humans live here
or Demons?
Go and tell the villagers that...
...Even If one life is lost, I'll
secrifice my life
Sacrifice you life?
If they don't stop rioting, then
I'll stop eating & drinking
Stop eating & drinking?!
Take back this food!
...And send those people
to me!
One side there's no rain
& other side these riots!
No rain, I'll fast
sacrifice my life!
I'll fast... sacrifice my life
I'll fast... sacrifice my life!
Hey! What's your problem?
Saint?
- Yes!
Saint will fast?
Yes! -why?
One there's no rain here... on that
...l'll fast sacrifice my life
Did saint say this with you?
- Yes, he told this with me!
Did he say that he'll fast
because there's no rain!
Will the saint fast for
bringing rain?
Fast?
Don't you remember, that saint
used to narrate a story!
Yes... yes!
We have done gross injustice
towards a saintly man!
There he's ready to sacrifice
his life for us!
...And here we are after
each other's life!
It's matter of great shame!
Saint... saint...
saint has arrived!
Saint! As soon as they heard
about you, the riots stopped
What did you tell them?
What you had told me?
What did I say?
...That you'll sacrifice your life!
And...
...And you'll fast!
How many days?
For 12 days!
Did I say it?
It wasn't you or me, they
had thought like that!
...That saint will fast and
there'll be rain!
This story is of that great saint
...Who had fasted continously
for 12 days!
...And forced God to rain!
Bhola, come with me!
Bhola, what's all this
you've all mistaken!
I've never claimed that
I am a saint or messiah!
Even If I am will it rain
if I fast? -why not?
Those are just tales! That
too children's tales!
You make these villagers understand
that I've just threatned to fast!
...Just to stop the riots!
Now that it has been achieved
everyone go back to your house
My condition is very bad
with hunger... go!
Why are you staring at me?
Saint... saint...
show mercy on us!
I accept... I accept that I've
committed a sin!
But, you know how greed
makes us to do all bad things
For the past 2 days there's no
food in my house!
The children are crying for
food in hunger!
My wife is having high fever
...And night... even my cow
also died!
Saint! Every home is in the
same condition!
Now, only your mercy can
save us!
You've gone crazy
what can I do?
Saint... saint...
Our cries, shrieks may never
reach him
...But God can never refuse
your prayers!
If you fast...
...l'll guarantee that the whole
village will join you!
It has already been decided that
some will fast for 2,some for 4 days
...And few will skip
one meal every day!
Show mercy, Saint show mercy on us
otherwise we'll die
Not only for 12 days, I'll fast till
death, if it brings good for you
...But I am not the one whom
you're thinking me to be!
I am an ordinary Guide!
...And I've been even to Jail also
for a girl!
Yes Jail!
If you hear my story!
You'll find that there's no
big difference between us!
I too have weaknesses!
I too have troubled people
told lies! Cheated people
I've been cursed by my own
as well other people!
They're taking a lot of time!
Come... let's see! Come!
Hiding my face & wandering for
a year, I took shelter in this temple
You people thought I was
a saint
It's true that I had
compassion for you!
...But that's all nothing
more than that!
May be now, you consider me as
a cheater & start hating me
But telling you the truth
was a neccessity for me!
Saint! The path of knowledge
is very crooked!
...Valmiki became a sage
after being a dacoit!
Goswami Tulasidas cut through a desire
of a woman to became a sage!
My confidence in you has
become even stronger!
After getting purified by
12 days of penance
...The cry which comes
out of your soul!
...That will tear open the skies!
...And Gods will be forced to cry & wet the
earth to quench the thirst!
Come on saint, where are
you going?
Today is just 2nd day
of your fast!
Go... go... and search for
your benefactor!
Priest
- yes!
...Come little aside!
Priest! Priest!
Danger! -then...
Slip away...
Slowly... slowly...
We too were going there only!
...But came to know that a great saint has
appered about 100 miles from here
And for bringing rain he's
fasting!
...Thought that we'll go for
his glimpse!
You too come with us!
Move on move on
A lot of people are waiting!
Move on! Move on!
Sister don't disturb saint
bow from here only!
Bhola, it will be greatful if
you ask the saint once...
Look, why are you disturbing
saint for trivial matters!
For the past 6 days he's been
fasting for us!
Didn't touch even a
drop of water!
...Be patient!
Don't do it like that!
Bhola, how many times I had told you
that no one should touch my feet!
Oh! They don't heed even
after I warn them!
Mother!
Sister, I've already told
you once that...
Hey Raju, My son... Raju!
Where every head bows in reverance
there even a stone becomes God
The place which makes you
remember the God!
...That place is called "Aura"
On a glimpse of man, if it rakes
up devotion of God in you!
...He's called as Saint!
...Because of you, this old temple
has become a Pilgrim centre!
...And thousands of eyes
are raising up!
...Towards light!
Then, why are you worried?
Bow your head, sit peacefully!
Think that someone else is
there to do the job
...And you're just a medium!
Work is done by him!
But the name is yours!
Chant his name! And continue
doing the entrusted work!
Just like me!
Just like a stone
Mother, I must be serving you
Go and sleep
Saint! This lady has come
from America so meet you
...She has been sent here by a
big television company!
She wants to ask you
a few questions!
Permission granted?
Saint, do you believe
in fasting?
If 40 Crores fast for one time
40 Crore can eat one meal
Saint, do you believe that
it'll rain?
These people have
confidence in me...
Now, I've begun to be confident about
these people's confidence
This lady is asking whether
you had ever loved anyone?
Water!
Rosy has come back!
And mother too!
What if it doesn't rain?
The life from which I got vexed
and ran away!
...ls now chasing me!
...lt's calling me back!
...Promising happiness!
Thousands of people's wishes
will go down the drain!
...Their confidences will
be shattered!
What will they think of me?
Cheater?!
Fraud?!
Are you sure that its
going to rain?
You too have started believing these
Supersitions like these illiterates!
Raju, is it you?
Haven't you also started
believing that...
...There'll be a relationship
between a man's fast and clouds!
I don't know it, Raju! I am
getting more & more confused
I've started thinking those things
which I've never thought necessary
...But thinking about which is more
important than life & death
The question now, is not
if it rains or not!
The question's not whether
I'll live or die!
The question is whether the Creator
and Protector of this World
...ls someone like that
is there or not!
If he isn't there then no problem
whether its life or death
There's no excitement in living like
a blind man in a blind world
And if he's there...
Then, I want to see whether he'll listen
to his desperate people or not!
Are you asleep?
I was sleeping
...But now I've just started
awakening little
Didn't I tell you that you
can't come inside?
But sir, listen me, you may
have mistaken me!
This photograph resembles my
bosom friend! Look at it
For God sake, all I want to know that
one whom you call as Raju swami...
Whether he's my bosom
friend Raju, that's all
But you belong to other religion
you can't enter a temple!
My friend, I know it definitely
that it'll be you only!
But Raju in what condition?
Yes sir
What is my religion?
Saint!
Love is my religion
Friendship is my devotion
Mother, did you hear that
Raju's life is in danger!
Please do something
Saint!
...My son!
Saint! Saint!
God! These people consider
me as your son!
And you're so far
away from me
If not mine, atleast heed
these people's prayers!
...Take my life...
Take away their sorrows God
Take away their sorrows
God, don't
Oh God!
My child! Don't be afraid
of sorrows
Sorrow is that nectar with which
sins are washed away!
I am not very far away
from you...
I am inside you & outside of you!
I am omnipresent
Only I am there... only me!
God!
Today how free I
am feeling!
Like the body has forgotten
to make demands!
And that the heart has stopped
beating and creating sensation
As if the life is in my fist!
And death is like a game!
Now, I'll fall dead
then watch it
I feel that, today all my wishes
have been fulfilled!
And the fun is that, today
I don't have any wish!
Atleast don't allow the wish
to live go away
The life has melted away and
become a enlightenment
...And truth is my real form!
If tomorrow comes or not!
...l'll be there!
Raju, save me
...My breath...
Throw me into fire
I'll not burn
Attack me with a sword, I'll not
get cut into pieces
You're proudness
You must die!
I am soul! I am eternal!
Death is like a thought!
Just how life is a thought
There's no happiness, sorrow
distressed or the World
Neither there's man...
nor the God!
Only I am there... only me
...me...
Only me
Far away its raining
on the mountains
My body got drenched!
Come on, change it
Raju, your fast has
become fruitful!
It's raining heavily!
Look how happily people
are dancing?
Raju... Raju... Get up! Raju
Mother, Raju is no more!
No, my child! Raju is no
more in this body!
There's no happiness, sorrow
distressed or the World
Neither there's man...
nor the God
It's only me... lts only me
...only me!