Who was he?
The same
Follow him
Daddy I'll be with his girl friend,
Ican get to know a lot about him
Alright, take care of yourself, go
Hallo who is it?
Early morning somebody is in a
mood jokes-
He says himself
to be Amar
Look, look, look.
He is one scowndrel who is
following me
Ask him where is he speaking from?
Talk a little sweet
Hallo, who, Amar darling, where
are you speaking from?
All this I'll
tell later-
First tell me, that last
night who was in your room?
In my room, no one
Look ourling, last night I
couldn't meet you-
And now I am again leaving to pune,
I am speaking from V. T station
In another 20 minutes
my train will leave
I called up to inform you
only this-
That last night there was
someone in your room-
I am scared, if the police
is chasing us
Just take care
of yourself-
The moment I reach pune,
I'll contact you
Now where will
you escape?
Brother, I... I... I
I am Vinay
Where are you going?
To catch Amar, that wicked,
the son of there's
Even you
Even you, how do you
know that he is in Pune.
In Pune
Yes,
But, first tell me that how did
you come to know of this?
Look at that rascals gut's, he again
wrote a letter to Shalu-
Telling her to come in this train
and meet me in Pune station-
And Shalu also
got ready-
I come to know
of it
I locked her in
the house-
And told her, dare
you go?
I'll go and
punish him-
Brother, we'll not have to go
till Pune-
Amar, is in this
train only
In this train
He is in this train and
going to Pune
But...
How did I get to know,
it's a long story
First let's catch him, later I'll tell you
It's good that all the compartments
of this train are joined-
The entire train can be
searched off
This is really
very good-
Do one thing, you go that side,
I'll go this side
And look if you get him, inform me,
after that I'll take him to task.
Even you do the
same thing
Yes, yes, yes.
You didn't get him,
isn't it
Somebody has lied you, he is
not in
Not lied, but may be
he has changed his mind.
I am sure he will definitely come
to Pune station, to meet Shalu
Even I think the
same
Your estimation was
rightly-
Instead of Shaly, his brother
has come
It's good that you came
Otherwise, he'll start the
fight again unneccessarily
And we should leave
from here immediately
Yesterday you were
wearing the same coat?
Yes... Yes... absolutely the same
Oh... Come...
Prince! Sweet drink!
Prince! What you had written
in the letter has come true
And Mr. Radha has reached Calcutta-
And he wants to see
the jewellery worth 80 lakhs
Prince!
As instructed by you. We have
printed your visiting cards
He is from france,
representing a famous jewaller-
And he is here to buy diamonds
and jewellery from India
From all the corners of the world
buyers have reached Calcutta
But this word has been
put into Mr. Rana's ears-
That if you like
the jewellery,
You are carrying 80 lakhs
cheque in your pocket
Your new dresses are stitched
with latest French fashion
As written by you
Mr. Rana is a flirt
Wonderful Prince! You have
again hit the bull's eye!
In two meetings he has
been charmed by Julie!
First, he was going on
interviewing, modern girls!
Now, he says...
If anyone is going to wear
my jewellery. It will be julie!
So, Prince...
Are we going to kidnap Julie
by our selves from the hall
I will think...
You all may leave now,
and let Prince take some rest
Darling, I suspect that
I am pregnant
This is happy news!
Then, when are you
going to marry me?
As soon as I get a chance...
Poor Mr. Rana, how restlessly,
he must be waiting?
What happened?
I am ruined, I am ruined!
Why will I
do like this?
Oh! Jagga!
Girl with 80 lakhs
jewellery... kidnapped...
For the first time jewel theif
see for first time jewel theif
Yes, yes, he is the same.
Look here brother he is indentical
with this Yes... yes... he is the same
He is the same thief
he is absolutly the same thief...
Why don't you show
your face and then go.
Vinay... stop... Vinay
Elder brother, is it you?
What did you do?
Why are they chasing you?
What are you doing sir?
I thought they
would have killed you.
I don't know what has
happened to all of them?
What has happened? Didn't you
see today's newspaper?
Every newspaper has printed
Amar's photograph!
Yesterday night he has
committed a big robbery
Look at this...
How identical his face
is with yours!
Brother! It's me!
You!
They think thatl am Amar, and
made me to commit the robbery
You are talking of which time?
Yesterday night!
What has happened to you? You
were with me the whole night
Aey, me...
Are you drunk?
We had seen the 9:30 show
together last night
After that, we went
to hotel and slept.
About whom are you talking?
After Poona's train, I am
meeting you for the first time
Vinay, What's wrong
with you
We have come to-gether
from Poona to Calcutta.
Booked a double room
in the hotel, -
We were not seperated
even for a moment.
In the morning, upto
what time I was with you?
You were sleeping
when I left, Why?
Drive immediately.
Arey I should also Know
what's the problem?
Because, the person with whom
you spent 2 days, he is Amar
Amar! Amar!!
Driver quickly.
Drive immediatly,
he has once again deceived me-
You, cheat!
Amar! He is not here
How will I know
his where abouts. Look there.
What is this?
Looks like, it will be
in the letter!
This is the paper from his pad
Read what is written?
You think, you are very clever?
But you are a fool Amar.
How dare?
You think, you are very clever
I am a fool, I will wring
the neck of that rascal
Come, we will ask the
manager; he might know
I think it's him only
Julie!
Beware, don't come forward
, I will shoot you
Suddenly, what's
happened to you?
I have been deceived once-
That doesnt mean,
I will always be deceived
Deceived?
How were you deceived?
You are not our Prince Amar-
Your name is Vinay.
Vinay! Who told you that?
Don't try to act smart.
Now I, know every thing.
You made a fool of me,
you made a fool of my friends.
The theft that Amar was to
have committed, you did it.
Tell me where are those 80 lakhs
worth of jewels.
Otherwise you won't be spared.
Tell me, who told you all this?
I won't tell.
Tell me, who is that?
Leave me, I will tell you.
Tell me quickly.
I saw it with my own eyes.
What did you see?
Both of them
Amar and Vinay.
Where did you see Amar?
He was also with me.
And he told me that you are
impersonating him.
And he also told me, -
That I should catch you.
Where is he now?
He has gone
Where has he gone?
Gangtok, Sikkim.
Did you see?
You were always cursing him.
To-day that son
has stood in good stead
Now you understood?
Why I wanted him
to join the police force.
He has my blood in his veins
Darling!
Where is this Gangtok?
In Sikkim.
The thief is very clever.
He knows that our police
can't do anything there.
But how I will pressurize
that govt. Through our govt,
That they should help us.
Anyway
There the swimming pool
is very beautiful-
I will take you there.
That is north hill hotel and
it is the best hotel of Gangtok.
It's a very beautiful city.
I will write to shalu and ask
her to come with daddy.
Yes, as it is she will be
coming in a few days.
Is in't daddy's jeep.
How are you son?
He is my son Vinay.
You look at him
and understand-
As to what type of a person
are we looking for?
Brother has shown me all the
places, which he used to visit.
Had I not seen your feet
even I would have been deveived.
Has anybody told you before
that how beautiful you are.
Has anybody told you before that
you are more handsome than him.
With Amer!
His hair has started greying here.
And wrinkles have
appeared here.
What's your name?
If any body sees then,
You will be in trouble yourself,
and put me in trouble too.
Then let's go some where else.
If he comes to know then...
You are so scared of him?
Till I am in his clutches
I have to be scared.
But once I extricate myself,
I will be free for ever
What is your relationship
with him?
He is an expert in
making false promises
But once he can grab a girl,
Then he makes her dance to his tunes.
Really?
Every girl thinks
that he will marry her.
But I have become wiser
At the first opportunity
I will disappear.
Where will you go?
Delhi, Bombay
wherever I wish...
Will you come with me?
Really?
Go away. You want me to do
something under false pretexts.
Yes, there is some work
if you wish to do it.
Once, I want to meet him.
Why do you want to put
your life in danger?
Think it over, you do
my work, I will do your work.
Okay listen! He comes to
my house in the night.
Where is your house?
Oh God! He is Amar's man,
he is looking for me.
Shalu.
You probably thought I am Amar,
that's why you were running away.
I want you to go away
don't follow me like this.
Why are you scared?
If brother comes to know
he will be very angry.
If someone sees then.
Your brother was saying-
That you were going to come
after 3-4 days.
I have come just now,
I haven't met him.
He wasn't at home
He doesn't even know.
I will go.
You are a strange girl.
I have come to your city-
You don't have the courtesy of
offering me a cup of tea
Why don't you understand?
It's not proper for us
to be seen to-gather
Go away Vinay.
They are all excuses
there is something behind it.
There is nothing.
Tell me
I tell you there is nothing
I don't belive it.
You leave me.
You'll have to tell me
I won't tell.
If there is something
only I can tell you.
You are unnecessarily
troubling me.
Then, why did you run away
after seeing me?
If you ask me unnecessary
questions, I won't answer.
Brother has forbidden
you to meet me?
I won't answer.
Will you meet me again?
I don't know.
You don't like to meet me?
I will not answer.
Okay go.
We might not meet again.
You know, what a dangerous man
I am chasing.
Good Bye.
You won't hate me, is'nt it.
I thought I will love you...
No. Don't say like that
don't think like that.
Shalu come with me
for a little while.
I promise you that I shall
not ask any such questions.
Which you may not wish to answer.
Make one more promise.
That you will not
mention this to brother.
Done.
Where do you wish to go?
Wherever you want to take me.
Actually brother it's all my fault
Shalu, said that she didn't
meet you till now.
I dragged her forcibily
Oh!
Why are you getting scared
like this Shalu.
I haven't prevented to you
from anything till to-day.
If I had known that
whom are you going with-
And when are you going to return,
I wouldn't worry.
Actually Vinay, Shalu is
my only sister.
And you know, this poor thing
has been deceived once
Have faith in me,
I am not one of them.
Who break the betrothal,
If you give the blessings, I am prepared to
make her mine for ever.
Really! Wonderful.
If Shalu has the same intention,
then I would be very happy.
You also come inside.
Vinay, Vinay. Not there
here, here.
I couldn't come to-day understood...
Hey stop.
Take me away from here.
He will kill me.
Who?
He came to know, all that
I had talked to you yesterday.
Who came to know?
Amar who else?
Come on Vinay I will tell you
everything on the way.
Amar!
Come Vinay please come.
You can drive the jeep, is'nt it?
Whose is this jeep?
It is his. What are you thinking
Vinay come soon there is no time
Come on.
We will go home for a minute,
you pick up your bag from there.
After that...
Go ahead and then right.
You wait in the jeep,
I will come just now.
Amar what are you doing? Leave my hand.
; getting worried, that I have come to the enemy's
But here I found my own friends.,
There are more, come.
Gentleman, our guest has come.
Come, Come sir.
Mr. Rana.
You made us wait for a long time friend.
At least he has come.
Come on Sir! Will you have a drink?
Taste this.
Taste it from my glass because
he has special affection for me.
He doesn't know me, but I know him very well-
That's why I will embrace him.
He has ordered that he (Vinay)
Should'nt have any problem.
He'll have no problem.
If you feel hungry, these are
the things to eat.
If you feel thirsty,
this is here to drink.
That means, I am a first class prisoner
Prisoner
no no. Don't utter
such a bad word.
You are our special guest.
If you need anything,
we are at your service
For that purpose. This man will
be at your service for 24 hours.
Finished? I will drink more.
Any body here? Any body here?
What is it?
Bottle is empty
I will drink more-
I am your special guest, serve.
It's enough go and sleep.
I will drink more,
I will drink more.
Pick him up.
He has drank a lot. Take him.
Keep it that side, It may go off.
He has drank too much.
He is not bothered about...
Come on friend... Come on...
Amar it is useless to hide now.
I know you are inside.
Come out.
Open the door otherwise...
You had promised that the day
Vinay reaches here.
The same day you will
return my brother to me.
Sister! Where were you? -
They were not allowing me
to play or to go out
And you also left me.
No., no Shishu, I will not go, I will
never leave you and go.
Listen whoever has troubled you,
I will punish him severely-
You don't worry.
Sister let's go home.
Yes we'll go home,
I have come to take you.
Really!
What's all this?
Why are you closing the door?
I am telling you
to open the door.
Open the door-
open the door...
Don't you know.
Brother, gave the
permission to go.
Open the door otherwise
I will beat you to pulp...
Don't worry,
I will open the next door.
Vinay!
Vinay are you listening
Who is it?
I am Shalu.
Shalu.
Where are you
speaking from?
From under your room
there is a tunnel.
How did you reach here?
If you remove the carpet of your bath room
You will find
the way to get down
Make fast!
Make fast I am waiting for you.
Shall we go!
Vinay, Vinay will you forgive me?
If you will ask for
forgiveness like this-
Then it will be difficult to refuse.
But I have not understood
so many things till how.
We will get lot of time to
understand and explain.
But if we are caught, now the
life of 3 of us will be in danger.
Who is third one?
Come there.
Sister! Come to me.
My brother, Shishu.
Once I had told
you is'nt it.
I am living for him.
And that brother of yours.
He had kidnapped
this poor thing.
By threatning to kill him-
He forced me do, whatever he wished.
You know from the begining
itself that I am not Amar.
You haven't come to know till now.
That there is no person by the name of Amar.
Is there is no person by the name of Amar?
There is no other person looking like me?
There is no other person looking like you.
You have been deceived.
I, Helen, Julie and the rest of
them who work with that thief.
All of them combimned to-gather
and tried to prove.
That there is another person who looks like you.
And whose name is Amar.
But there is no such person.
The business man, who sells
all the stolen goods,
He is also in our group.
And the theft that
was commited there?
There was no theft commited,
it was all a lie, a deception.
It was just a drama,
It took 6 months to enact it.
Each and every one moved by the word of mouth.
But, don't worry come!
There is a hole
in the carpet.
It seems someone has
cut it with scissors.
Where can he go?
Samson.
Yes Please.
How long will it take?
Prince! A person cannot be given
more then 1 electric shock a day
There are some people who
with a single shock itself.
Loose their memory
There are others, who have to be
given even six shocks.
That means you are convincing me
that in six days-
Vinay will forget all about his life.
What are you talking?
He won't remember even his name.
So you are the jewel thief.
I was... but now you are
what's your name?
Vinay, Amar.
Police commissioner of Bombay has sworn,
By 26th Jan, he will definately
arrest the Jewel thief.
I am very much hurt by this.
It's a pity that the punishment
for the sins of the father,
Is being borne by the son.
Do your work.
Forget... forget...
Forget that you are Vinay
You are not Vinay.
You are Amar. You are Amar.
You are Vinay's enemy, Amar
Police commissioner's enemy, Amar!
Julie's husband, Amar!
Prince Amar!
Enemy of the police, Amar
Enemy of the police, Delhi Amar.
Daughter, I was helpless.
I am also helpless daddy.
I thought that at least
four shocks have to be given.
What did you say?
I thought at least
four shocks have to be given.
But in two shocks only
His condition became compatible
to your requirement.
How are you feeling Prince?
Who are you?
Doctor,
My ten year old associate
does not even recongnize me-
Please do something.
You be assured that he will
remember everything soon
Which place is this?
Prince Amar. This is your head quarters.
To escape from the police
Your entire group hides here.
Amar.
Dr. He doesn't even remember his name.
Police...
Police is looking for you from
every corner of the India.
You are blamed for thousands of thefts-
There is a reward of
lakh's of rupees for your arrest.
Just try to remember prince
we are all your accomplices.
How did I get
into this condition?
Bombay's police commissioner
shot you!
You had a severe head injury!
Doctor saved your life by operating.
This doctor!
Doctor! Why my legs
are also paining?
Prince Amar!
Don't you remember that you had
six toes on your right leg.
You always wished to get
The sixth toe removed.
Long with that operation doctor
has removed your toe also.
Amar-Amar you have become alright.
You don't know how happy I am.
What nonsense they are talking.
I Don't belive it
They say that
you don't remember anything.
You can forget everything
even your wife-
But you can
never forget your Neena.
3 most enchanting years
of my life I have spent with you
I have brought some thing
for you, come.
See how beautiful
these flowers are!
Let God punish that
police commisioner, who shot you.
It seems he has reached
Sikkim in search of you.
I am very much amused!
When he comes face to face with you
I fear he will meet his end.
Oh! Amar, I could never forget you.
You are again here!
Oh! Mrs. Amar. I was just...
You shameless!
How many times I have warned you
to stay away from my husband.
Julie Madam... I came here, just to
enquire about his health.
I know you very well.
Under false pretences,
you meet him to entice him.
You want to take
advantage of his situation.
You are mistaking me!
Get away from here.
Get out!
Does she know? Doctor said your room
should be peaceful.
But couldn't control my self
after seeing that wretched
Look here!
Till we weren't married all the
girls had equal rights on you!
But, even after having a child
they are still desiring!
A child!
Okay, leave it!
How do you feel now? My, love!
Only one point should be
brought in when Vinay is there-
That, he is Prince Amar
known as "Jewel Thief'
Until he is fully convinced-
Our work is half finished.
An excellent theft was committed
in Amritsar!
The police were outwitted
in broad day light!
Prince cleaned all the
bank lockers in no time.
And that Mysore, robbery!
Was it any inferior?
How tightly secured
Maharaja's museum was
Even then, nobody got the wind of it, -
Nobody ever knew where that costly
antique jewellery vanished.
I consider the robbery of seth
bishambar Das's shop as the best.
Prince was cutting diamonds right infront of him!
And that fool thought that
he was his employee Vinay.
What brothers? Is it true that...
This Vinay's face resembled
with our Prince.
Except this, that his right foot
had 5 toes and Prince had 6.
There was not even a bit of
difference between the two.
Can any one tell me? Whether
this Vinay is alive or dead.
If our Prince targets can anyone escape.
That's why his father,
Bombay's police commissioner-
Is after the life.
First he said that he would
catch him alive-
Now, he says that he will
drag the corpse upto Delhi.
Is it a joke!?
Let our Prince get better...
This police commissioner will
forget all his lofty ideals
He will run for his life.
What do you all think!
Will Prince be alright
before 26th January.
Why?
Don't you people remember?
On 26th January, the near-by
hill estate Maharaja-
Was to hand over his throne
to his Prince.
Yes, Yes...
Prince planned to steal his
crown on that day.
10 lakhs worth of jewels are
engraved in that crown.
Prince, Prince you have
become alright-
Long live Prince!
Long live Prince.
Yes, he was staying
in this hotel, -
But he is missing
for so many days now.
Neither he has taken his luggage,
nor has he paid the bill.
Hey! Where have you
lost in thoughts?
Julie, come near me.
Tell me the truth darling.
I am in such a position
that I can't tell anyone-
I can't trust anyone
All this wealth and treasure
belongs to me.
Amar, my Prince,
what has happened to you? -
This is your earnings of
12 years of your blood and sweat
Be brave,
gather your wits even now.
By putting your life in
thousands of dangers-
You have stolen
every single jewel
And for this 1 crore worth
of wealth, you are asking-
Whether it belongs to you
Think hard and
try to remember,
This wealth is all yours.
This palace is yours
And they. -
They are your servants who live
on the morsels thrown by you
Doctor, had said that slowly
I will remember everything.
What do you mean by slowly you
after you loose every thing by then.
I tell you, our people
have revolted
When they have no faith
in your strength-
How will they respect you?
If you don't remember,
it doesn't matter.
At least you act
in front of them
That you are the same jewel thief;
the same Prince Amar-
Who was a terror to the police.
Who has revolted?
Tell me his name
I will beat him into a pulp
Who is that brown fellows?
Who can confrent me?
Nobody should think that
I am sick
I am not an ordinary man
I am jewel thief,
I am jewel thief
"The Jewel Thief'
Arey what's this?
Did I impres?
Plenty,
Now watch.
26th January.
Do you people remember that we
have to do something on 26th Jan.
We do remember, Prince;
How can you remember?
Whole day you are drinking
and playing cards
You tell me, what was our plan?
We were to raid
the court of shaito, Prince.
And the crown that was
to be put on Prince's head-
I have been entrusted the task
of drawing the map of the court.
As per your order
I went in disguise-
And went through every
nook and corner of the court.
If you permit me,
Then on 26th Jan, what type of
function is going to be held
Shall I say something about it
You are permitted.
Prince big personlaties
are coming there.
Foreign ambassadors will also be there
So, the security will be very tight.
Can succed in entering only
in disguise of dancers.
Without invitation, a bird also
can't enter there
There is only one way
to go inside.
There is a
dance programme there.
You and your associates. -
You already know
that once the king...
Has requested our Shalini
To perform a dance
in his court.
Do you remember Shalini?
Yes I remember very well
Then, tell Prince Amar.
King has specially
asked
That... at that time... I...
No. No, I will not let this game be successful
Vinay. Vinay they are
all your enemies... enemies
You are not Amar
these people have made you mad-
So that you should think, yourself
to be the jewel thief-
Whatever you are listening,
thinking and understanding-
Is all false.
Except me, nobody is yours
here, Don't beleive anyone
Recognize me? Recognize me
I am Shalini, Shalu
You are not Amar,
you are Vinay,
Son of Bombay's
Commissioner of police, Vinay.
What nonsence
this girl is talking-
The person who is
my deadliest enemy, -
She is calling him my father.
Who has entisted this
mad girl in my gang.
This is not your gang
Ask her to keep quiet
Otherwise gag her mouth
and take her out
No you are not Amar,
no you are not Amar.
Where is this
police commissioner these days?
And see this. And this photo is...
No not this, that one
You are the commissioner?
If you love your life then
get away from my path.
Otherwise the way
I have sent your son to hell... -
What!
The same way I will
send you there too.
I have come to
tell you this only
That if you don't disappear
from here by to-morrow
Then you take it
that your death
Will be caused by the
bullet of Prince Amar
Take away their pistols.
Come on, come on
You!
You are the daughter of
Bishambhar Das.
Yes Sir.
And I have to
tell you something.
It is 26th January.
Police commissioner
has been informed
That a theft will be
commited in the court today
He will leave nothing
to chance, but Prince
I still think,
That it is risky to give a
loaded pistol to a mad person.
The Pistol will be loaded
but with empty cartridges
Police will try to catch
jewel thief alive. Get my point
But we want the corpse of the
jewel thief to go out of the court
How is it possible?
Police will start firing only
When the first attack
will be from the jewel thief
And our jewel thief has threatened
the police commissioner
That if he comes forward
he will be shot dead
In spite of this if police tries
to catch Vinay alive. Then...
Under no circumstances Vinay
can be left alive
If the police misses
Then anyone of you, who gets
a chance, has to do this job
What are you thinking Shalini?
I have told you before
and I repeat it again.
I will not dance, I will not dance
You can kill Vinay
you can kill me
But by using me
you can never kill Vinay
I am fed up with
your attitude Shalu
If you refuse once again, -
Then in front of you
your brother will be shot dead
You will dance
You will not only dance, but you
will keep your mouth shut also
Hey brother look here,
how am I looking
No one will
move out from here!
Prince, we have entertained you
won't you give us our presents.
What do you want?
I have no temptation
for money and wealth... but...
A shining diamond or emerald
is always more tempting!
Yes, you'll be put
to inconvenience!
For which I am
extremely sorry?
But, the crown that is
on your head...
Please, remove it
and place it on my head.
If you behave like this
in a loving and affectinate way...
Our relationship will be very cordial.
A small inconveniance once again! -
Take this prisoner and show him the door
One of your guards
may make a mistake-
And I may be
forced to shoot
Come on... Come on...
Amar, your game is over now.
Drop the pistol! Drop it!!
Come on...
Second one also!
Hands up!
Place the crown, once again
on prince's head.
Turn this side, see and then
recognize the person-
...Who has vowed to catch you
before 26 January
When bad times come
man looses his senses
I had told you
once before also
...That, if you love your life
you should leave this place.
It seems that
you don't love your life!
Now, I will see, who is going
to catch whom
Amar, you have
been arrested.
Now, you cannot
escape from here.
If you fire
one bullet on me...
...Serveral bullets will be
rained on you
Look up
Look!!
I don't have the slightest
intentian of shooting...
But, if it starts
from your side...
...Don't blame me for it
world knows that. I don't have any connection with
You have blocked,
my every move...
And you have tried to
spoil all my plans
I will settle that account
some other day...
But now...
You, Please take the trouble
of escorting me outside safely
I have never considered my life
more precious than my duty.
If you shoot me...
Our people will take
your corpse to Delhi.
I will feel
very sorry about it.
Because, I always wanted
to take you alive.
Give it. Hand over the pistol.
It seems you are
a dull headed person-
...And you prefer not to
take those 4 steps with me.
Okay! I will go alone.
Good bye!
If you want the
safety of Mr. Commissioner-
Then withdraw your guns
Don't bother about me,
spray the bullets on him.
Beware,
Start firing.
Beware
After to-day, the police force
in India will sleep peacefully.
Because the jewel thief is killed
And we will sleep peacefully, -
Because the police
will sleep peacefully.
It was not possible to do
this job. Without your help
The job that all
of you have done,
Can't be rewarded by money.
Even then, infront of each of you
50 thousand rupees
Consider this as a small
parting gift from my side.
Good bye
I also can't belive it
but it is the fact
I am alive
But I saw you dying
with my own eyes.
Can empty cartriges be loaded
only in your pistols
And not in the guns
of the police?
Empty cartriges!
But, how did your father
come to know?
Sir on the paper
from you pad only,
Written by your pen only.
In front of
four of your own people.
Your servant handed over
the letter tohis father
That means you were not effected
by the electri at all.
Why not?
But I understood that you will
definitely make me mad
Irrespective of
the number of shocks
That had to be given.
But, I thought
it would be better-
That I should start acting as mad
after getting shocks
And after being associated
with such good actors,
One leasns a
bit of acting
What's the plan now?
My father has plans.
Today's date
is related to 26th January
Will you take these jewels
with you or leave them here
Without the jewels,
the jewel thief won't be complete
You are 20 and we are 50,
Even then you want to fight
we are ready for that
But it will be
better for you to
Drop your weapons and
come out with your hands up
Where did you go?
I thought I would
arrest him myself
But he, escaped
We have surrounded
the place and laid a strong seige
Even then he slipped away
Sir look, up there, up there.
No Don't shoot him
We have to catch him alive
Daddy, you leave this
job to me
Keep the plane ready
Start the plane
I am coming
Vinay now
you can't harm me
Don't try to enter unnecessarily
Fate has saved your life
a number of times, Protect it.
If people like us are
worried about our lives-
Then people like you
would have ruled the world.
It's you who has to
save himself, not me.
I coming in
Don't come Vinay
my plan has failed-
I will get nothing
by killing you now
If I had wanted to kill you
I would have killed you long back
But I have vowed
to catch you alive
Then you fulfill your vow
Bobby get ready to take off
Before you shoot,
Just think,
Till now you have not
been accused of murder.
Today, To-morrow or the day after
you will definitely be arrested.
Why do you want
to be hanged after killing me
You are a kid Vinay
As you watch
I will be from the Indian Border
Hundreds of miles far away.
Where even the angels
of Police won't reach.
You have been useful person
that's why I won't kill you-
But you will
always remain my prisoner
You have already made me
your prisoner once
With the result
you are running away-
Like a coward
to save your life
Shut up. I am
not running away
I am going away
like a Prince
This is my plane,
this is my wealth
I am the master
of my own life
And you... you are
at my mercy
When empty bullets
didn't work-
You started giving
empty threats.
Just check. May be
the gun is also empty.
You think by your talk...
Bobby, how is this empty?
Now we are ready to fly
You please sit on
your seat and tie the belt
Anju, what are your doing here?
Who is there with you!?
Where are you going?
Bobby can't meet you now
Thank you. Timing was good
You please come here,
people are waiting for you
Could you hand over this to me
Move on
Every body has
already assembled here
Yes. They are all here, but now
it will be more interesting
Instead of
becoming interesting-
It has become indifferent
Prince you sit here.
No, No, Prince, not there. Here
In between these three goddesses,
Prince should not
have any trouble
The game is over here
go to your seat,
Myself?
Yes, yes come
Come Sishu we will sit there
Why are you all so sad like this?
Winning and loosing is
apart of life
Come on, sing a song.,
You sing.
What happened?
Sing a song.
Alright, if not a song
narate a story.
Listen the story from me.
There was a "JEWEL THIEF"...