Anwar Hussain is bound to win
tonight's poetry competition.
I'm willing to bet anything
from Rs.1 to RsJOO.
You're on for a bet.
You're my witnesses.
Lala Rastogi will win the
gold medal this year.
Are you embarrassed to
call me Ghayal ?
I'm a poet, you know.
No ordinary one.
If I don't win,
GhayaPs not my name.
But I won't win.
Because Anwar's my friend.
Did that penetrate your brain ?
- You penetrated our group.
I'm sorry. I'm off now.
All the girls are talking
about you.
Everyone says that you will win the
Urdu poetry competition his year.
Pal, if you want to win
recite your poem to me.
And get Binda Din GhayaPs
expert opinion.
Ghayal, tonight's poetry
competition ?
I don't have a single poem
to recite.
Not a single poem ?
Why ever not ?
My heart and my brain just
haven't been obeying me.
I was awake all night.
I see. As usual you must have
eaten too much.
And now you must have a
stomach ache.
You idiot. Not a stomach ache.
A heart ache.
You knowl haven't found
the girl in purdah yet.
The college will close for
the holidays today.
Everyone will go home.
So will she.
My friend. Think of something
so I can find her.
Listen.
Everyone knows...
You'll will be reciting a
poem at the contest tonight.
If she loves you
She's bound to come to
see you tonight.
Recite a poem. In which you
address your beloved
And reveal your heart to her.
Tell her you weep for her.
You're dying for her.
Present yourself at the
poetry contest.
The contest will end.
You wish will be fulfilled.
But where's the time to
compose a poem ?
There are 2 hours yet.
Where there's a will
there's a way.
Get your act together.
This is my first poem!
We now present the young poet
from Aligarh.
"My beloved"
"I swear upon my love"
"Let your beautiful eyes
assure me of your love"
"Return my lost joy to me"
"You are the vision
of my dreams"
"Your image haunts me
away and night"
"My every heartbeat
calls out to you"
"Assure me your tomorrows
will be mine"
I cannot forget
your beauty"
"We met in a chance encounter"
"Athousand poems lay
scattered at our feet"
I dedicated them
all to your voice.
"How can I forget that
first time?"
Your eyes intoxicated me.
"Lightning thrilled
my very being"
"When I touched your
velvet hands"
"Assure me those hands
will be mine"
"I caught but a glimpse of
you once"
"I long to meet you again"
"Your shadow is a beautiful
Taj Mahal to me"
"Let me woo you on a
starlit night"
"Let your fragrant curls
assure me of your love"
"I seek you everywhere"
"My hopes near exhaustion"
"I dare to hope but one
more day"
"Who knows where we'll be
tomorrow?"
"Gift me the assurance of
your gaze!"
"Appear before me,
unveil your face"
"You alone can cure my
loneliness"
"This separation pains me"
"Let these memories sustain
my heart"
Anwar, that was terrific.
My heart tells me
Your beloved
Must have been moved
by your song.
She must be searching for you.
Look over there.
What are you staring at ?
It's her. Go on.
Go ahead.
Anwar, what a poem that was.
We went out of our minds.
Good day.
She's gone.
Damn these people.
They just don't let 2 lovers
come together.
Never mind if you couldn't
see her face.
You must have got her name
and address ?
You didn't ?
Oh, no !
You had better forget all
about her then.
You won't find her in
this lifetime.
Because you are going
to Lucknow.
Well, that's the end of that.
Let's go.
Porter, wait.
Husna!
Keep this ticket with you.
I'm in the next compartment.
I hope I'm not troubling you.
Not at all.
Move, will you ?
Good day, Nawab.
I'm sorry.
I didn't recognize you.
You don't know me.
You know my father very well.
Seth Kanhaiyalal Rastogi.
- Oh, You're Mr. RastogFs son.
Yes. Binda Din Ghayal.
This is my friend
Anwar Hussain Anwar.
He's also a very good poet.
This is Nawab Buland Akhtar.
Good day.
Please sit down.
Do sit down.
I'm so glad we met.
It'll be a pleasant journey.
Yes... We two crazy people
will have a great time.
But there are three of us.
- How could I call you crazy ?
Well, Anwar, here's Lucknow.
Don't forget your promise.
Meet me in Lucknow.
Very well.
Ghayal, why don't you
come with me?
I'll drop you on the way.
Daddy must have sent
the old rattle trap.
Gulabbo
How many times have I told you
not to yell ?
I'm not deaf, you know.
- Move back.
Useless woman!
What are you staring at?
Go and tell the Begum
A Mr. Anwar has come
from Aligarh.
Do sit down.
- Thank you.
Madam, a Mr. Anwar from
Aligarh is here. - Anwar!
My brother!
- Sister!
Bless you.
Have a sweetmeat, son.
Try this one , son.
I've had enough of this stuff.
I've a yen for something
else now.
Tell me. What would you like?
I'll send for it immediately.
What I want...
isn't to be found in shops.
If you want to get it for me...
Then order some sorrow quickly.
Sorrow ?
Yes. Put sorrow on my plate,
father.
Give me tears, Mother.
To sharpen my wits.
If not for ever, at least for a
short term loan. I want that.
Very good.
Did you hear that?
Do you see the interest
our son has...
in improving the family
business?
This reminds me of my youth.
My father used to charge
a very small interest.
Still he doubled the business.
And I doubled it again.
Now my brilliant son will
increase it ten fold.
People'll say Kanhaiyalal RastogFs
son Binda din Rastogi is very -
No. Not Binda din Rastogi.
Binda din Ghayal.
- Ghayal ?
son, who's made you "Ghayal",
Where is your wound ?
This isn't a wound that
can be seen.
It can only be heard.
Can't be seen ?
Can be heard ?
Why can't it be shown ?
It's in a delicate place.
In my heart.
I'm Ghayal from head to toe.
From head to toe?
Have you got lots of wounds?
Did the hooligans of Aligarh
beat you up ?
Who dare beat me ?
I'm the one who beats
everyone in poetry.
I'm the best in poetry
reading sessions.
I'm the king of poets.
Ghayal is my pen name.
Oh, so Ghayal is your
pen name?
Our son has become a poet.
He must be given
some sort of reward.
Do it with a generous heart.
I bow before you. Friend, give me
whatever comes to mind.
Did you hear that?
He calls his father his pal?
What are you doing ?
In order to bring me up and
educate me...
you were forced to become
a dancer.
You joined the theatre.
But by the grace of God,
our problems are over now.
I have completed my education.
I'm back now.
Now I'll look after you
And you can stay at home
God bless you.
How fine boy you are!
How much you care for me!
- You have done so much for me.
Only a mother would do that
much for her child.
A child's heaven is at his
mother's feet.
But my heaven is at
my sister's feet.
May every brother be
like you!
Anwar, I shall be madly happy-
...when you return from abroad
as great a doctor
...as your late father was.
I've never disobeyed you.
From childhood till now.
You sent me away from you.
I stayed away.
You didn't let me call you
my sister.
I've been longing to do that.
But I never called you sister
before anyone.
But now I won't let you work
in the theatre.
And I will call you sister.
Will you acknowledge me as
your sister ?
You'll lose your prestige
in society.
Society won't respect you.
I don't care about society.
Until yesterday,
I was a weakling.
I didn't have the strength
to fight the world.
But now I won't let you work.
No, no.
My hopes will be destroyed.
My dreams will be
frittered away.
Anwar, my brother, for God's
sake, bring that day to mind.
Our father died.
Our relatives thought us
as good as dead.
They started torturing us.
Mercilessly.
They took away everything.
I took you and ran away.
Else they wouldn't have
left us alive.
We became homeless.
I held on to you.
I wandered from place
to place.
Dr. Yawar Hussain's daughter!
Suraiya became Najma
the dancer.
I want to see you reach
the highest level.
You're on the first rung of
that ladder now.
I swear by my mother.
I want to see you reach
such heights.
So high you can reach
for the sky.
May happiness rain upon you.
May wealth and prosperity
surround you.
May our family rise again.
My dear sister !
Come in.
Sir, this house has been
closed for 5 years.
Many people have tried
to get it.
But I had decided.
I would give it only to
people with character.
You judged us very well.
I have experience.
lam a man of the world.
Have a look around.
Don't think too long.
Rent it quickly.
By God, it's a lucky house.
My God ! What a view to the west.
I'm shaken from head to foot.
Come. Tell me if it's a girl
or a vision.
Oh no. The door's closed now.
Ghayal, you're crazy!
You can't stare at people
in your neighbourhood.
The neighbours will finish
you if they notice.
Idea !
- Get inside.
We like the people in
the neighbourhood.
Here's the advance.
The house is mine now.
Advance from me too. When he
leaves the house, I'll take it
We'll close the western
window and open the eastern.
Thank you.
Now don't ponder too much.
Everything you need to
write poetry is here.
Forget your beloved.
Write a restless and intense
love poem.
Ghayal ?
Go on.
Do you - I know what you're
about to say.
What ?
That I have great ideas.
Not at all.
Then ?
You're a very handsome idiot!
One idiot recognizes another!
Let's shake hands at that!
Ouch! what's this ?
You -_>
MY dear !
Husna, when I look at you...
...I'm angry with God.
- Why ?
Why didn't he make me a boy ?
I'd have surrendered to
your beauty.
And do you know what I'd do?
- What ?
Get lost!
You're utterly shameless.
Tell me, what happenned about
that admirer of yours?
The one you bumped into. The one
you wrote to me about.
He walked past me so
many times.
I wanted to talk to him.
But I just couldn't.
I was too shy.
Shyness, and that too
with an admirer!
You could have dropped your
hankerchief. Or bumped into him.
You could have let him
see your face.
That happened one day.
He was close.
Great !
He kept gazing at me.
Good for him !
I kept gazing at him.
- Good for you too !
We were lost in each other.
- That's great !
Then we heard someone
approaching.
I got scared and ran away.
- Oh no.
He didn't ask my address.
Nor did I ask his.
Then this love story ends
before it begins.
My dear, you'll know when you
fall in love.
You call it the end.
But's it's only the beginning
of the love story.
"You are somewhere near"
"But oh so far"
"The pain of separation
weakens me"
"This is the state of my heart"
"For I'm in love with you"
"God alone knows howl feel"
"I think of you all day"
"And cannot sleep at night"
"This sweet pain permeates
my being"
"I wonder what awaits me"
"You are my life"
"I hope to meet and talk
to my heart's content"
"Mend this broken heart
of mine"
"I am restless with longing"
"I yearn for you"
I am sorry.
Blind idiot, loafer, hooligan.
Thank you.
You've awarded me several
titles in one breath.
Actually, I have a very
short name.
Ghayal (wounded).
Wounded by a lovely gaze.
Wounded by good breeding
and honour.
Wounded by beautiful eyes.
- Oh! You shut up.
You speak English very well.
Aticket! I say!
Listen.
Aren't you ashamed
of yourself ?
Actually, I'm a very
shy person.
But I'm forced to set
my shyness aside.
Are you going to the theatre?
- What is it to you ?
I have the ticket here.
You keep one.
I'll keep one.
We'll watch the show together.
- You really are shameless.
What's your problem ?
You yell because of me.
I'm very sorry.
I hope you didn't get hurt.
Don't offer sympathy from
a distance. Come closer.
Then I can tell you.
What a hand !
One slap!
And I'm seeing stars.
Anwar, I won the battle.
V for victory.
Answer me where ever you are.
I for- - ?
Loafer, lout,
lightweight, louse.
Not loafer. Not lout.
Not lightweight. Not louse.
I for love. Tenderness. Passion
Worship.
O, so you've been smitten too.
You've decided to
fall in love?
Don't talk rubbish. You don't
decide to fall in love. It happens.
I bumped into a girl today.
Exactly what happened to you.
We bumped into each other.
She fell down.
And said - Oh God !
Just as your girl in purdah
had said. Oh Allah!
What an interesting story.
What happened next, pal?
Next ? I went closer.
She was coy.
I extended my hand.
The velvet like hands held
on to it.
My heart beat faster. Bells
started ringing in my head.
Lies. All lies.
You bumped into her.
I accept that.
She fell down.
I believe it.
She said " Oh God "
I can trust you on that too.
You gazed into her eyes?
- Yes.
You held her hand to help her up.
- Correct.
She tried to release her hand.
Absolutely correct.
And then"
With great feeling...
With great force...
She gave you a slap!
- How did you find out ?
Rastogi, your face still
carries the mark !
Your cheek is red.
- Never mind.
I've had one slap so far.
I'm fifty percent in love
with her.
With the next one it will be
hundred per cent.
Come with me.
- Where to?
Just come.
- Let me wear my coat at least.
"Love has been brought to
such a state today"
"it has become a matter of
prestige rather than emotion"
"God save me from
such young men"
"Brash young men without
any depth"
"The rogues gaze into our eyes
and sigh"
"They use any means to
entice us"
"They roam the streets,
singing of their love"
"They barter their hearts
at every turn"
"Their love is false, as is
their passion"
"Better keep away
from such men"
"God save me from such
young men!"
"They wangle their way
into our hearts"
"But before you know it,
they're gone!"
"They build up a relationship
when the whim takes them"
"And break it up
when boredom strikes"
"I've had quite enough of
such men!"
Wow, what a performance!
- She can certainly dance!
"No one recognizes
the flame of love"
"They want to experience
the fire of love"
"But they know not what
love is"
"The woman is heart-broken,
dishonoured, disgraced"
"Save me from such
two-faced lovers!"
What's wrong ?
You look upset.
No. It's nothing.
You knew this would happen.
You would see me on stage.
And you wouldn't be able
to stand it.
You shouldn't have come.
I know.
You must have visualised
our ruin.
Seen you sister destroyed by it.
Your pride must have been hurt.
Your blood must have boiled.
I saw the tatters of your
reputation.
I heard your voice.
It was a plaintive call.
But for others -
It was just a show.
You're not in your right
senses, Anwar.
Go, go home.
I won't.
Until you make a promise.
Leave the stage forever.
Bless you. You're the finest
brother ever.
I promise.
The day my hopes are
fulfilled...
when you become a doctor,
I will leave the stage.
I don't want to be a doctor.
I'm neither hungry for money
nor fame.
I don't want the world to bow
before me.
Nor do I want to reach
the skies.
I only want to love and respect
my sister.
I beg of you.
Only give me the rest of
your hopes.
I want to realise them
for you.
Don't be childish.
So you won't leave the theatre.
Don't.
I wish you the very best.
I am going.
You have given meour
decision. Now hear mine.
You'll never see me
after today.
I'll kill myself.
Good bye.
Anwar, take back those words,
Don't ever say those words.
I'll leave the stage.
Forever.
What's wrong, Husna?
Ever since you've come back
from Aligarh, you are very quiet.
What else I can do in this
huge house?
What do you mean ?
If only I had a sister-in-law.
There would be children.
It would be lively.
I would be happy too.
You're aware of my
problem, Husna.
The woman I love...
can't be made mistress of
this house.
But you always said...
that she comes from a good family.
Why can't she become mistress
of this house ?
No one cares for her
excellent past.
They only know what
Najma is today.
I'm dying
What happened?
- Pain. In half my face.
I can't sleep at night.
I can't stay awake during
the day.
You're responsible for the pain.
Find me the medicine too!
I'll cure you right now.
- Thank you.
Since you slapped me,
I've been in love with you.
I am further in love with you.
My God, are you a poet?
Yes. Here's a new one.
Whenever we meet,
you slap me.
My love, let's meet elsewhere.
What do you think ?
Buy this handkerchief.
It's useful to drop.
How much is it ?
25 paise for the scarf,
75 paise for the idea.
That's brilliant.
Anwar, I scored an
equaliser.
She gave me another slap.
As she was walking away,
I recited a poem to her.
She stopped and smiled.
She dropped her handkerchief
and left.
I'm crazy about love too now.
Just as you are.
Your love says "Oh Allah".
Mine says "Oh Ram".
He's got up and gone.
He takes no interest in
my romance.
Love isn't the only problem
in life.
Majnu only had one problem -
Laila.
But what is your
other problem ?
Tell me.
I want to find a job, Ghayal.
A job ?
Are you abandoning your studies ?
Yes. I need it.
A job is available.
But I need a good recommendation.
I know the wealthiest man
in town.
Who's that ?
- My father.
His recommendation won't do.
I need someone respected in
government circles.
That's true. My father is
a money lender.
It's a good idea. Read on.
My love does not make me proud.
Love is a natural state.
Husna. You've got the word wrong.
Why don't you consult
a good poet.
You'll correct your mistakes
and improve your style.
Sir, someone is here to meet you.
Invite him in.
You? Come in.
How do you do, sir ?
- Bless you, Anwar.
Namaste, sir.
How are you, Ghayal ?
- Still wounded, Ghayal.
I'm so glad to see you.
But I do have a complaint.
You've taken a long time
coming to see me.
What could I do ?
Since coming to Lucknow,
we've had problems.
I hope all is well.
Tell me about it.
The thing is
What is it, Ghayal?
The Azad Press publishes
a newspaper,"Youth".
They need an editor.
He is hoping to get
the appointment.
Mr Murlidharan, the owner of
the press, is a good friend.
I'll phone him right now.
Azad Press? Can I speak to
Mr. Murlidharan ?
Murli, is that you?
I believe -
- Yes, I'm fine.
I believe you need an editor
for your paper.
My close friend has put in
an application.
Mirza Anwar Hussain.
I think he should get the job.
I'd be very grateful.
Thank you so much.
There you are.
It's done.
Do sit down.
I'm obliged to you.
Not at all.
It was my duty.
Say what you will.
But Anwar is very grateful.
Look, he's bowed his head too!
If he stands up, he'll start
bowing to you.
Actually, there is something
you could do for me.
It'll be my pleasure, sir.
My sister is very fond of poetry.
If you don't mind, comment
on her work sometimes.
He doesn't deserve the honour.
But he'll do it.
You're very witty, Mr. Ghayal.
- So are my poems.
One who's depressed
and thinking of suicide
should love someone
who's been bitten by a mad dog.
You were slow with your laughter.
It was a difficult poem.
You left the theatre
because I asked you to.
I'm so glad.
If you can, do one
more thing for me.
I swear it'll be my last request.
Let him make requests
who cannot command.
You can ask for my
very life.
I don't want to take life away.
But to gift it.
You gave me life...
...the day you gazed into
my eyes.
That wasn't a gift of love.
It was love.
Let me finish.
Your love is my life.
No, Najma. My love is death
for you, not life.
Only the fortunate
receive such death.
Don't try to reassure me, Najma.
My love is a trap that
has ensnared you.
But I won't let you be ruined.
I'll sacrifice my life for you.
Your wit has taken
a new turn today.
This is no witticism.
It's reality I'm talking about.
Even if I want to
marry you, I can not.
I come from an old and
respected family.
No one has ever done anything...
...to taint the family's
reputation.
It has always been said...
...the sun and moon may be
blemished...
...but this family's reputation
is spotless.
Tell me, Najma.
How can I marry a girl...
...seen to have a tainted
character?
I swear before you
I have never even dreamed
of becoming your wife.
Don't use my
welfare as an excuse.
Don't turn away from me.
If you abandon me...
...the light will disappear
from my life.
No, Najma.
Believe me.
There is hope in
your tomorrows.
Everyone is not as helpless
as I am.
Najma, marry someone.
Love doesn't consider
marriage necessary.
Najma, why don't you
understand?
Leave me to my devices.
Arrange your life.
Settle down.
Your family needs an heir.
An heir to bring glory
to the family.
The spotless reputation of
the family will remain.
I only wish for darkness
to envelop us...
to overtake ancient
families like ours.
We are guilty of destruction.
Please sit down.
- Thank you.
Please do sit down.
I hope you're not upset.
No, I know you're my
brother's friend.
I present a few of my poems
for your opinion.
Here they are.
Excuse me.
Before I comment on these
I'd like to hear you recite
work by other poets.
I'd like to guage your taste.
Only a few days ago
I was lucky enough to hear
...a beautiful song.
It has found a place in my heart.
Excellent.
Recite it.
It's called "My Beloved".
"My beloved, I swear
upon your love"
Where did you hear this song?
Tell me quickly.
It carries the secret
of somebody's love.
Whose secret?
The secret of my friend's love.
Do you know your friend?
Would I call him my friend
if I didn't?
But why are you asking
about him?
I'm Not for myself.
I ask for my friend.
The truth is, this song
is important to her.
It's a memory of her love.
This song was written
for my friend.
Does she study at Aligarh?
- Yes.
Then she's the one.
- Who?
She's the one for whom my
friend weeps.
His tears are at the heart
of this poem.
Separated from her,
he is so restless.
So is my friend.
She cannot sleep.
Nor can she rest.
She keeps repeating
this prayer.
Dear God.
If meeting him is not
in my fate...
...then grant me death.
Don't say that.
May your friend live long.
Now, tell me.
Would you like to help
these lovers ..to meet again?
They're restless without each other.
Why not?
It's a question of my
friend's life.
Tell me what I can do.
As soon as you can
Give her my friend's regards.
I'll go to her today
as fast as I can.
Please give my regards -
I mean, my friend's regards
to your friend.
Bless you.
Ghayau
Are you in your senses?
- You bet I am!
Then talk sensibly.
Ghayal, I saw the sun rise
in the west today.
I saw rain rising from the earth.
There was a harvest
in the sky.
That's done it.
You've gone crazy.
I'll tear your shirt
The urchins on the street
will stone you for sure
Do you know what my
beloved will say?
Don't throw stones
at my lover
You mean you met her?
What do you think I'm
talking about?
Then say Oh Allah!
- Oh Allah!
Oh Ram!
Listen, will you?
What is this?
Have you gone mad?
Yes.
What? Have you found him?
- Yes.
May he father a dozen children.
Shameless hussy!
I'm talking about
my poetry tutor.
He's a friend of his.
Naseem, what a lucky
day this is!
I feel like singing, dancing,
painting Lucknow red.
So, she's a friend of
the Nawab's sister.
That's right.
You know how I yearn for her?
She's in the same state over me.
"My beloved..."
"I swear upon your love"
We've been looking everywhere
for this girl
And she's right here,
our neighbour!
I have to hand it to you.
You're a lucky man.
Did you send my regards on?
Your regards?
I mean, my friend's regards.
Yes.
She sent her regards too.
Is that all? Didn't she
say anything else?
Plenty. But let's hear
yours first.
I passed on your friend's message.
His face lit up,
his eyes brightened.
Oh Allah! And then?
Finally anxiety was
replaced by calm.
When I went to deliver
the message...
...she was depressed,
despairing over her love.
I told her not to cry.
That I would brighten up
her life...
"with the message I brought.
Then what happened?
Finally anxiety was
replaced by calm.
What is your friend's name?
What? My friend?
Naseemara.
Naseemara? What a lovely name.
The Nawab is here.
Good day.
- How are you, Anwar?
I hope you are well.
Is your pen name Anwar?
Oh, I quite forgot to
tell you his name.
His name is
Anwar Hussain Anwar.
What's so surprising?
It seems familiar somehow.
It should be.
You study at Aligarh
and so does Anwar.
Besides, he's well known as a
poet at the university.
Does she study at Aligarh?
- She does.
And your friend Naseemara?
Naseemara? No, she doesn't
study at Aligarh. Why?
She told me she'd heard my
song from her.
It didn't take her long
to fool you!
She's full of mischief!
She heard it herself at Aligarh.
She hums it day and night.
And she told you she got it
from her friend!
Oh Allah! Many thanks to you.
You brought my beloved to me.
Accompaniment is available.
You have a good voice.
And I have a request.
It's my pleasure, Nawab.
Sing one of your new
songs for me.
"Wake up, my beauty,
Let love awaken you"
"You could change my destiny
Once you are roused"
"I come full of hope"
"To sings my songs of
love to you"
"Don't let disappointment
come my way"
"Inspire a melody in my heart"
"Come, sing with me"
"I come to you, full of hope"
"You are the flame
I surrender to"
"I long to be consumed
in your fire"
That was marvellous, Anwar.
You don't realise how badly
The world needs the
balm of poetry,
lnspite of the U N O,
the world is full of war
and violence.
I have started this
Poet's Club...
"because I'm sure this
club of ours...
...will surely replace
the U N one day.
Ask me how.
- How ?
Breakfast is on its way.
The poet's thoughts are sensitive.
His temperament is sensitive.
His heart is sensitive.
So if we popularise poetry
all over the world...
sensitivity will be the
order of the day.
Where the sensitive reign,
can there be violence ?
Tell me.
Think of your breakfast.
- Never.
To popularize poetry...
my father's wealth is
available.
As soon as we can
please my father...
the fate of poetry
will improve.
And then every poet will
receive a new shirt
A new pair of pyjamas
And as much betel nut
as they want.
Eat betel nut in peace
And recite your poetry.
Ask why.
- Why ?
Because I love poetry.
Poetry is my life.
What an excellent proposal
this is!
You won't get a better
proposal for your son.
How's the girl?
She's about 16 or 17
16-17 lakhs of rupees or
16-17 crores of rupees ?
No. The girl's age
is 16-17 years.
However, the girl's father has
some 40-50 lakhs of rupees.
How many brothers and sisters
does she have?
She's the only child.
- The only child ?
In that case, find an
auspicious date.
That can come later.
Tell me.
I hope the girl doesn't have
any faults ?
No particular fault.
She's a fine girl.
She's a healthy girl.
The only thing is
She lost an eye as a child.
One-eyed ?
- Never mind.
We'll have a glass eye fixed.
Turqoise blue.
Look for a date.
I refuse to sell my Binda
for money.
Why not? His father did the same.
If your father hadn't
shelled out Rs. 100,000...
I wouldn't have looked
I'd have married a beauty.
Look at yourself.
You dare to speak like that!
Your father came begging to us.
Don't lie!
Your father begged for our consent.
This wedding will take place.
Should I proceed with the matter?
Absolutely.
With all speed.
Tell them we're interested.
Don't cry. I'm alive yet.
Where are you taking all
these snacks and tea?
Your son has started
a Poets' Club.
Lots of poets have gathered.
All this is meant for them
A Poets' Club?
You mean I have poets
in the house?
My hard earned money is
feeding poets?
I won't let them eat this.
I'll starve each one of them.
Where's my stick?
Let go.
What will you do to my son?
- I'll beat him black and blue.
I'll give him the beating
of his life.
No, no!
That was great!
All right.
Any other poem?
Do listen to one of mine.
Balancing a pot on
her head, Heer slipped
straight into Ranjhefs heart.
You have tried a little wordplay.
But in the legend
of Heer and Ranjha...
...this is how you
could phrase it.
Ranjhefs heart slipped
out of his shirt...
and was enmeshed in
Heer's tresses.
I managed to slip out
with my stick.
Your mother didn't care for
my trick.
The spitting image of a poet!
The look of penury.
Tattered clothes.
Let's carry him in procession.
We'll go through the neighbourhood.
My beloved!
"My beloved...
I swear upon my love"
"Let your beautiful eyes
assure me of your love"
"And return my lost joy to me"
Let me go.
If anyone sees us, it'll
be embarrassing.
Let me go!
Husna!
"The nightmare of separation
is over"
" I've found you"
"The pilgrimage is over"
"I reveal my feelings to you"
"I hardly know how
it all happened!"
"I lose myself in your beauty"
"I unveil my secret to you"
"This is the best thing that
has ever happened to me!"
"Cupid's arrow has pierced
my heart,"
"You are responsible
for the wound"
"I think of a lifetime
with you"
"How charming,
how impish you are"
"Lucky is the man who
wins you!"
"He's the one"
Wait.
Where are you going?
Come here.
You coward! Why are you
trembling ?
Do you know this girl ?
- No. Never seen her.
Who is she ?
- This is my daughter
In that case she's as good
as my daughter too.
Take me to your father.
- To my father
He died a long time ago.
You love her.
And you keep lying.
Take me to your father.
I want to meet him and
arrange your wedding.
Wedding? Very good.
In that case, he's alive.
Father-in-law, bless me.
Grant that I'll make your
daughter happy.
After being much humbled,
I still dare to come to you.
What rubbish are you talking ?
You need intelligence
to understand me.
What are you looking for ?
Just checking.
Your shoes aren't, are they
Good.
- Why?
If you don't have your shoes
near, you won't throw them.
The gentleman here to see you...
...has a somewhat delicate
constitution.
I hope it isn't a poet
you've grabbed.
I have no taste for grabbing.
I've brought someone,
He isn't a poet.
If he isn't a poet, why would
he be with you ?
Binda, is he here to talk
money with me ?
It has to do with trade.
Nothing small.
this is big time business.
Really, Binda ?
Business for a life time.
A lifetime's business.
Well done, son.
You've finally begun taking
interest in business.
And how!
Even I haven't trapped
such a customer yet.
What did you say?
Do you think you are going
to trap me ?
No, no, nothing of the sort.
Father was talking of
someone in Assam.
Assam? We' re Punjabi.
Punjabis are great.
Come in. Sit down.
We consider Punjabis as one of us.
- Really ?
This is my daughter
What
He says she is his daughter.
Oh, in that case she's my
daughter too.
Ah, that's the response I like.
Come on let me embrace you.
Stand up.
It's fixed then.
Shall we negotiate too?
Your methods have left
my bones weak.
We will fix it.
But first tell me.
How much interest will you pay?
What kind of customs
do you have ?
He wants interest along with
his daughter-in-law.
Are you talking of marriage?
What else ?
Tell me what you want ?
How much dowry do you want?
Rs. 20000 ? Rs. 25000?
I'll give it to you.
You'll give that?
Come. Come this way.
You too, child.
Go on.
What is this?
The door.
You came in this way,
didn't you ?
You can go out the same way.
- What ?
With the girl. Fast.
How dare you ?
If you weren't this
nice boy's father
I'd have made chutney of you.
Come, child.
Thinking of marriage, eh ?
Come in, Ghayal.
Why do you knock ?
Excuse me. I think you've come
to the wrong home.
No, I've come to see you.
I mean, I've been sent.
Who has sent you?
The lady next door ..
the one you always see.
I'm her maid.
Your windows haven't been opend
Naseemara is very worried.
She worries all day,
in case you are unwell.
May Allah keep you healthy.
May all you troubles come to me.
Listen.
Is Naseem at home?
She's in here.
Where had you gone out
disguised as a servant?
To meet my beloved.
The one at the window?
What's he like ?
Fair or dark ?
Fair.
Tall or short?
How does he look?
As if God had made him
with His own hands.
Get lost.
Only my beloved was made
by God with His own hands.
I met him today.
Really?
Tell me quickly.
When did you meet him?
How? Where?
You know the young man who
guides me with my poetry?
It turned out to be him!
He's a deep one!
What's he like?
Don't ask.
He's an Adonis,
He dazzles me!
Like a spark in the distance
That I had only dreamed of.
I get the picture.
My beloved has sensitivity.
Maybe.
My beloved has sweetness.
My beloved has love.
His gaze isn't as brilliant
as lightning.
His face doesn't dazzle
like the sun.
But a vision in himself.
"What doesn't my beloved have?"
"He's one in a million!"
"He's handsome and young"
"He's an angel from heaven"
" In human form"
"What doesn't my beloved have?"
"Shall I call him a star?
Or a heavenly stream?"
"He has such an effect on me -
I lose my senses"
"As God is my witness!"
"My beloved is as handsome
as can be!"
"My beloved is a young man,
As special as special can be!"
"He has such grace in his gait"
"As swaying branches of
flowers have"
"His voice has a ring to it"
"As only the truest
crystal has"
"His manner wins my heart!"
"What doesn't my beloved have?"
"Your story, my dear,"
"ls so much like mine"
"We are two lovers in
similar situations"
"He's one in a million!"
"We've placed our beloveds
on pedestals"
But how do we decide
which is better ?
What's so difficult. I'll
show you my beloved.
You show me yours.
You are right. But ..
...It's a dull answer.
But if we lay bets,
it'll be fun.
You're on.
I'll bet anything.
When will you show me
your beloved ?
Not me. Show me yours first.
- Ok. I agree.
All right. I'll be off.
But when can I see him ?
Tomorrow night. At my place.
God protect me from your
dazzling eyes...
Even an angel would have
fallen in love with her.
How can I resist her?
Ve ry p retty .
Listen to me. Don't say a word.
Hold your feelings in check.
But she stuns me.
Naseema, who is this girl?
- My friend.
I can't praise her enough.
I swear I've never seen such
a beautiful girl before.
Careful, Munne Raja,
you'll lose your senses.
I've left my senses
behind already.
I'm at your mercy.
Get me married to her somehow.
Else, I'll be in Majnu's
state of despair.
Come down to earth.
She's the nawab Buland
Akhtar's sister.
That' s sad.
You seem to be lost in thought.
I must get Husna married quickly.
She's grown up now.
Are there any proposals ?
The families that
have shown interest...
only have money but no culture,
no education, no character.
Set them aside.
Find a young man likely to succeed.
I have a boy in mind.
He's handsome, educated,
I know nothing of his family.
But his face shows character
And good breeding too.
The thing is, he's poor.
He's only just got a job.
So what if he's poor?
He has the wealth of
education with him.
Let him share Husna's destiny.
He's bound to make something
of himself.
I'm glad I talked to you.
I feel better now.
I've brought you here to meet him.
But how can I do it ?
When I see him, I go to pieces.
My heart will pound and
I'll forget to speak.
If you don't believe me,
check my pulse.
It's fairly leaping.
Let me see.
Oh yes, It's running like a
freight train.
Here I am dying of nerves.
And you're cracking jokes.
All right.
You go and hide.
I'll meet him.
Let's see how much I like him.
Enough to flirt a bit?
He's here.
Where are you running off?
Aren't you going to stay and flirt?
Get lost.
My coy maiden, raise your
eyes to me.
I yearn to see my love's
reflection in your eyes.
Husna, look at me.
This lucky moment comes after
years of misfortune.
As soon as our eyes meet,
I lose my senses.
If this is how it is now,
I wonder how it'll end.
Why are you so quiet?
You asked me to come.
Talk to me.
I didn't call you.
- You didn't?
But not for myself.
For my friend.
We had a bet.
She said her beloved was better.
I said mine was.
Husna ?
My friend is watching.
She's hiding over there.
Do come here.
Come and have a look at me.
I'm sure you won't be disappointed.
Your beloved must be
infinitely better than me.
Are you afraid that
I might see you ?
Don't be afraid.
I'll close my eyes.
You can come and compare me
with your beloved.
Look, I've closed my eyes.
Well, what do you think of me ?
What can I say ?
Better than anyone else in
the world.
You're only consoling me.
- No, I speak the truth.
In comparison with you...
my beloved is only a
fraction of your reality.
Don't mock me.
I've seen myself in the mirror.
You may have.
But not through my eyes.
You -_>
Why are you surprised to see
my friend ?
That's what I was wondering about.
Tell me, Anwar, where
were you lost?
I just thought...
That you'd seen me before?
The thing is, he's stunned
by your beauty.
You' re right, Husna.
God preserve your beauty.
Your friend is truly beautiful.
Thank you for the compliment.
All right, Husna.
I accept defeat.
Good bye.
- Good bye.
Ma'am, Anwar is here.
Who?
The man at the window.
Tell him I'm not at home.
Allow me to say something.
I won't forget this favour.
Neither will I.
What is it?
If I have hurt your feelings
I am truly sorry.
God is my witness.
Whatever happened was accidental.
I hadn't met Husna.
I heard my song being sung.
I saw you.
I thought you were Husna.
I bear no grudge.
If I have any complaint
..it is against my fate.
It has played a trick on me.
Anwar, I have a request.
Don't tell Husna my
ill-fated story.
Good bye.
I am the Begum of
Raunaq Mahal.
Naseemara is my brother's daughter.
I've brought her up
as my own child.
I've given her every joy.
At any price.
I don't understand.
Today I want to buy her your love.
Name your price.
Begum, love is worship.
Love is felt, not sold.
I understand...
You are leaving Naseemara for Husna...
you think that Nawab Akhtar has more
wealth than we do...
all of it is show! He is completly in debt!
- I request your abscence.
Husna's beauty is being discussed
in every house in Lucknow.
Everyone hopes to win
her as a bride.
Let's see where Husna's
fate takes her.
If God wills it, she'll
marry into a prosperous family.
I see no suitable family
in Lucknow.
Why not? I've been
thinking of her.
I've found you a very
good proposal.
Nawab Munne Raja of
Lal Haveli.
I don't like this
proposal at all.
Husna may be known for
her beauty.
But Munne Raja is known for
his bad character.
Don't be childish.
He's a rich man.
He lives that life.
He has a penchant for music
and nautch girls.
This adds to his reputation.
It doesn't detract from it.
Milk fairly flows in the
Lal Haveli.
If you don't believe it,
go and check it out.
Gold and silver abounds there.
Gold, silver, marble.
I don't want a mausoleum
for my sister.
I'll get her married to a man
...who has love and character
to offer her.
Do what you will.
I brought a suggestion.
Husna could be a queen.
And Munne Raja would take
care of all your debts.
Don't forget. You're in
debt up to your ears.
If you lose the mansion,
your reputation will be lost.
Brother, if you'd only
listened to me.
You strayed. And
mortgaged the property.
Now the family's reputation
is at stake.
Your death became your escape.
How long can I hold up
these crumbling walls?
Someone to meet you.
May I come in, Nawab?
Excuse me.
I don't recognise you.
I dare say. How could you?
When I went on the ha],
you were this small.
Son, Lucknow was glorious
when your father was alive.
Lucknow has lost its dazzle now.
He was my childhood friend.
What are those days those were!
What nights!
What conversation!
What meetings! What follies!
I suffer from the cough.
It's particularly bad today.
Yes. weather's bad.
What can I do for you?
I'm here to serve this family.
For the last time.
I'm a professional matchmaker.
I had arranged your father's
wedding too.
I have come to arrange
your sister's marriage.
I've brought Husna up
with great love.
I'd like her to marry someone...
...with looks, character,
breeding and education.
Money is immaterial.
I agree. You're right.
Money comes and goes.
Absolutely. But whose proposal
have you brought?
The boy's name is Mirza
Anwar Hussain.
He's a great poet.
His pen name is Anwar.
He's a good friend.
I know him well.
Then what do you say?
If he's your friend, you
shouldn't hesitate.
You took the words
out of my mouth.
I've been thinking of
this for some time.
Is it certain then?
- Absolutely.
Anwar and Husna's marriage
is fixed.
Congratulations!
Bless the couple.
I take your leave.
Mr. Ghayal?
- Yes?
Your stick.
Excuse me.
Nawab, you recognised me, did you?
You're an old friend
of my father's.
Nawab, sir.
I beg your pardon.
The thing is, Anwar has
no one except me.
I was afraid to broach
the subject of marriage.
How could I?
I put on the beard for a
touch of dignity.
I made a mistake.
Not at all, Ghayal.
Embrace me in the joy
of your friend's wedding.
You're great.
I'll have a sweetmeat.
I've arranged your wedding
with Anwar.
You'll leave me in only
a few days now.
A daughter is but a guest
in her father's house.
Parents do all they can
for a child.
When the responsibility
came to me, I did my best.
I am but a man.
I can make mistakes.
Forgive me for any shortcomings.
Gone mad, Ghayal?
I too saw the sun rise in the west.
Rain rising from the earth.
And a harvest in the sky.
Good. This lover has
lost his senses.
I'll tear your shirt and
throw you out.
Urchins will throw stones
at you. Dogs will bark.
When I'm stoned, d'you know
what your beloved will say?
"Don't throw stones at my
brother-in-law"
Have you brought a message
from Husna?
First offer me a sweetmeat.
We don't even have sugar
in the house.
OK. How about a sweet kiss?
This one's sour.
Then take the sweet one.
Now tell me.
Come here.
Tell me.
I've been walking. I'm tired.
Press my feet.
All right.
Praising you has given me a
headache too. Massage my head.
Here.
Ghayal, your throat must be
aching after all that talk.
Speak up!
All right. I will.
I've arranged your marriage
with Husna.
Fixed my marriage?
But how did the Nawab agree?
I praised you to the skies.
The Nawab was carried away.
He asked me to fix Husna's
marriage with you.
I was obstinate.
He went down on his knees.
Then I melted.
The wedding was arranged.
He gave me one but took two.
Aunt, the Nawab called my
mansion a mausoleum, did he?
I'll take revenge on him,
brick by brick.
I'll turn his estate
into a graveyard.
Go and buy the Nawab's
debts at any price.
Very well, sir.
I'll demean him in the eyes
of Lucknow society.
Anwar, how do you come
to be here?
Are you here to meet me?
- I came to meet a friend nearby.
What's he called?
Mr. Kewal Kashyap.
Does he stay near here?
Excuse me. I'm in a hurry.
I'll take your leave.
Najma, what do you think
of this boy?
He's a boy of character
who'll go far.
This is the boy I've chosen
for Husna.
I don't think Anwar is
suitable for Husna.
Do you know Anwar?
Yes. He's a good poet.
I've seen his work in
the papers. His photos too.
You've pampered Husna so much.
How will she get that
comfort in a poet's house?
Poets are poor.
I'm amazed. Till yesterday
you praised the poor.
Today you scorn them.
I've given my word.
In that case,
congratulations.
May they be happy.
So be it.
I'll go now.
Bless you.
Sister.
I know what you're here for.
Don't doubt the Nawab.
He's innocent.
I swear our love is pure.
Selfless.
I'm obliged to him.
If it weren't for him, I'd
have lost my reputation.
I'd have been on the streets.
He isn't a man but an angel.
He deserves the
greatest respect.
I misjudged the Nawab.
I'm ashamed.
Forgive me.
The Nawab gave you respect.
And looked after you.
I bow to him.
Bless you.
May God protect you.
The Nawab said he was getting
his sister married to you.
Yes. That's what I came
to tell you.
Can't you find an excuse
and refuse?
But why?
Husna isn't like you.
She's rich.
If she doesn't get the
comfort she's used to...
...you' ll be uneasy.
With your blessings, I'll
give Husna every happiness.
Make preparations.
The groom's party will leave
from your house.
If you don't join in the
celebrations...
...I'll never forgive you.
Don't worry.
After your engagement,
you'll come as a groom.
I'll be very haPPV-
Do something for me.
I want to acknowledge you
as my sister publicly.
Be brave.
You will have to join many
celebrations...
...without your unlucky sister.
This plant that I have
planted ..will bear flowers.
And bear fruit.
I thank God.
Ghayal, I request you
to tie this.
Nawab, you are my friend
and an elder.
I would like you to tie it.
Congratulations.
"My dear, spare me a glance"
"Cast your eyes this way"
"This is a day of happiness"
"May the first moonbeam
kiss your feet"
"Even if you don't think
of me as your own..."
"Raise your eyes"
"Look upon me as you will.
Cast your eyes this way"
"Whatever your preference is,
I am happy to accept it"
"I wish you every happiness"
"And many days of love.
Another may be consumed"
"Let happiness be yours!
I swear upon this lovely face"
"My feet are unsteady"
"It occurs to me
to steal your joy"
"With your inimitable grace,
accept my gift"
"Look into my heart and see
what I have given up for you"
Bless you.
You look like a prince.
You must have dazzled everyone.
They must have talked
to each other.
They'd never seen a more
handsome groom.
It's very late.
Sleep here tonight.
All right.
Anyone at home?
Husna!
What happened?
Call a doctor.
I'm not feeling well.
I don't know what's wrong
with my brother. Come quickly.
Your blood pressure is normal.
Forget about heart attacks.
Why did he suffer so much
last night?
I told you last night.
The reason is some
mental anguish.
Nothing of the sort.
In that case, you're
absolutely well.
There are no restrictions.
You can sit up.
You can walk around.
You can eat anything you like.
But cut down on this.
Anwar wants to meet you.
Shall I call him in here?
Didn't you hear what
the doctor said?
I'm absolutely well.
Good day.
Sit down, Anwar.
How are you?
I was worried by your
sudden illness.
That's natural.
You're my friend.
And relation too.
You must be surprised
to see me alive.
With such a severe blow
I'm still alive.
May your enemies die.
May you live long.
Anwar, why award me
a poison-filled life?
I'd prefer the peace of life.
My heart isn't totally
broken yet.
I still seek the support
of my friends.
Excuse me.
You can hug and kiss Husna.
Najma can hug me too.
Anwar, Husna is my sister.
She is like my daughter.
Najma is my sister.
And a mother to me.
You're lying.
No, it's the truth.
Yes, Nawab.
Naima, you?
Anwar is my brother.
Why didn't you tell me this...
...the day I introduced
him to you?
I told you clearly that he
was the groom I'd chosen.
As God is my witness,
I tried to dissuade you.
Later, I tried to persuade
Anwar to refuse.
But when I found out
they were in love...
I don't want to hear
any more.
All I know is this:
I saved you from ruin.
I gave you protection.
I gave you a chaste love.
I protected your honour.
But in return you deceived me.
You deliberately
hid it from me...
...that Anwar is your brother.
You thought that once
Anwar enters this family...
...l would have to
accept you as my wife.
I swear I never thought that.
My life has blossomed
in your shadow.
Take your accusation back.
I would rather die in
your shadow.
Take Anwar to your heart.
Let this be your last
favour to me.
I swear I'll never darken
your door again.
Nor Anwar's.
My sister!
Quiet, Anwar.
Nawab, for God's sake, don't
take Anwar's love from him.
I bow before you.
I honour you.
I won't let you bow
before anyone.
I don't want that love.
If you have to beg for it.
We too are children of
a noble family.
Time destroyed our
family's glory.
But the blood that flows
in our veins...
is no less noble than yours.
Anwar, it would be best
for you to leave.
Before I leave, allow me
to thank you.
This brother and sister's
relationship...
...which had been drowned
in darkness...
...will see the light
of day now.
I won't forget this.
I can now proudly and
publicly state this.
Najma is my sister.
She's my mother.
Today I'm the luckiest
man on earth.
I feel I'm touching the sky.
Let's go.
Rumours have spread
all over Lucknow.
After getting engaged,
Anwar refused to marry Husna.
Whatever they may say,
I feel for you.
How dare they say anything
about Husna or this family!
No one dare say that.
We know why we broke
the engagement.
We don't want any interference
in our family matters.
Tell me why you are here.
You mistake me.
I come at this delicate
time to help you.
I wish you wouldn't think of
my Lal Haveli as a mausoleum.
But as Husna's home.
I told your aunt very clearly.
I don't care for this proposal.
Now your family honour
is in my hands.
I have purchased all your
debts -at double the price.
Paying off your debts
...is beyond your power now.
But it's very easy for me
to auction this place.
This house isn't sold yet.
It still belongs to me.
It is my kindness that
allows you to stand here.
You are my senior.
I give you one more chance
to think it over.
If this mansion is sold,
your glory ends.
You'll find it difficult
to get Husna married.
Whether our glory
lives or dies...
even if this mansion is sold
...and we move into a hovel.
I may lose my title.
But my sister will never
marry a degenerate like you.
Anyone here?
Throw this man out.
I see darkness everywhere.
I don't know what to do.
Believe me.
I won't be able to live even
a moment... without you.
Husna, family honour is more
important than love.
Tell me.
If you were in your
brother's place -
If you had made sacrifices
to bring up your sister -
Would you have got her
married to me?
Answer me, Husna.
I swear I never blamed
my brother for this.
I know he's right.
I know duty is more
important than love.
But what can I do?
I'm just so much in love
with you.
I've lost my peace of mind.
I can't sleep.
Husna, I honour you and
your love.
I ask something of you today.
Forget me.
Cast my love out of your heart.
Forget our dreams of
a life together.
We were going to travel
the road of life together.
Forget all that.
Forget it all.
I fold my hands
before you, Husna.
Whenever you see a
smouldering fire...
think of me.
And when you see a moth
burn in a flame
Think of me.
Anwar. My friend.
Forgive me.
"I lie sleepless,
thinking of you"
"I toss and turn all night"
"At every moment..."
"A flame burns in my heart
for you"
"Since you have turned
away from me"
"I am lonely, the night
is dark"
"Even the moon has hidden
itself..."
"The stars hardly come
out at all"
"Lost is that joy,
that celebration"
"Lost is the happy goal
of love"
"In the lonely lanes of life"
"only your memory stays
with me"
"I was so happy when I won you"
"But then I lost you"
"Our garden of joy lies crushed"
"How can I account for
our separation?"
"I know only how helpless I am"
"The sorrows of the heart"
"Stream out in tears"
"I lie sleepless,
thinking of you"
"I toss and turn all night"
By the order of the government!
This announcement is
made for everyone.
On the 18th of September,
on Sunday,"
...at 1O in the morning,
Nawab Buland Akhtar
Changezi's mansion...
and all its valuable contents
...will be auctioned.
Anyone can make a bid.
Come, make your bid.
Take advantage of this
golden opportunity.
Participate in the auction.
Buy the ancestral home of
the Changezi family.
Enhance your prestige.
By the order of the government!
Stop.
Everyone, leave.
Come in.
It's a wonder you have
come to my house.
I'm amazed to see you in
this mausoleum.
So, Nawab Akhtar, how
do you come to be here?
My ancestral pride is
being auctioned.
I will write over my mansion,
my property to you.
Stop the auction.
I'll be beholden to you for life.
Very good.
You're finally seeing sense.
But you've come alone.
You want to save your
ancestral pride.
I thought you'd bring
your sister along.
Anyone here?
Throw the Nawab out.
You useless creatures.
Get out.
This mansion is being auctioned.
Anyone can make a bid
and buy it.
Rs. 1000/-.
The court has fixed the minimum
price at Rs. 300,000!-
No lower bid will be entertained.
Make any offer over
Rs. 300,000.
Speak LIP-
Rs. 3O 1000/-
Rs. 305000]-
Rs. 306000]-
Rs. 315000/-
Rs. 320000]-
Rs. 321000]-
Rs. 324000]-
Rs. 325000]-
Rs. 650000]-
Dear Allah!
You protected us till today.
You saved us from disgrace
till now.
Why have You turned
away from our family?
Allah, if You rejoice
in our ruin...
Grant me a favour.
Grant me death.
I cannot bear to watch...
with my own eyes...
...my family's and my
brother's dishonour.
I beg of You.
Grant me death.
Rs. 825000]-
What are you staring at?
Such a grand mansion!
You won't find one
like it again.
To save my family's honour
Time and time again I have
paid a great price.
I took on my brother's debts.
Along with my own hopes...
I sacrificed Husna's young
life to this mansion.
But today -
The other day you sought to
buy love for your daughter.
Today I offer myself for sale.
You'll get the proper price.
Tell me. What price had
you in mind?
Don't be embarrassed.
We're trading in love.
Think it over and name your
price openly.
You're lucky to find a
buyer like me.
I need a million rupees.
Is that all?
A million rupees?
Looks like you don't know
your own value.
Increase your price.
No, I only need
a million rupees.
But before I pay it,
I need an assurance.
You needn't worry.
I'll be back very soon.
Then I'll be your slave for life.
Son, what are you saying?
You'll come to this Raunaq
Mahal as a groom.
And live here as the master.
May Allah grant you both
long lives.
Allah, I cannot bear such
disgrace to my ancestors.
I cannot watch this with
my own eyes.
Therefore I am ending my life.
God, I see this suicide
as a sacrifice.
Don't condemn it as a sin.
My brother.
You'll drink poison and
escape this misery.
What will happen to me
after you're gone?
In this merciless world..
...full of greedy wolfish
creatures...
how would I preserve my
honour or the family's?
If, after you're gone -
I also have to dance on
stage like Najma -
...then the world will
look upon me...
...with the same contempt
as you see Najma today.
I' m your sister.
I also have a sensitive heart.
I can't watch this tragedy
take place either.
I would rather die.
Come, my brother.
Let us both take poison.
And wipe out this
entire family.
This is crazy!
This cannot be.
Forgive me, Husna.
I'd become blind.
I thought only of myself.
Not of you.
If only you were already married
to a decent boy like Anwar.
If you had left this
mansion as a bride
I would never have let my
ancestral home be sold.
I'd have destroyed it
myself first.
Nawab, a man loses his honour...
...when he loses truth
and integrity.
A man loses his honour when
he sells his soul.
And humanity. And decency.
Selling inanimate houses
doesn't rob him of his honour.
But if you still think honour
belongs to those...
...who live in mansions...
...then here are the title
deeds to your house.
Your entire debt has
been cleared.
The mansion won't be
auctioned, Nawab.
While life goes on...
a man won't let his friend's
honour be auctioned.
Don't misunderstand me.
Whatever I did was done in
the name of friendship.
Anwar, my friend,
let the house go.
I care nothing for this
grandeur now.
I regret my actions.
I have been very unfair
to you and Husna.
In the name of our friendship
Don't blame me too much,
Accept Husna's hand. Anwar.
I'm afraid that day will
never come.
No, Anwar. Don't say that.
Don't take revenge on me.
I beg of you.
I'm helpless.
But why?
I've promised Naseemara
I'll marry her.
Husna, I'm to blame.
Forgive me.
I've wronged you.
I'm leaving Lucknow for ever.
Join me in my
journey through life.
Accept my hand, Najma.
I'm not worthy of you.
Leave me to my devices.
I'm very ashamed of what
I have done.
Forgive me if you can.
Najma, I have so much
to say to you.
Can I come in, Aunt?
Come, come. You've
come at a good time.
I've ordered some jewellery
for Naseemarefs wedding.
What do you think of it?
Beautiful.
You saved my honour by giving
Anwar that money.
I've come to thank you.
What's there to thank me for?
I did it for Naseemarefs happiness.
May God bless Naseemara
and Anwar.
Here you are, Naseemara.
Your wedding present.
I've transferred the
mansion to you.
I'm leaving Lucknow for ever.
There comes a time in
one's life...
...when one loses something
but gains a lot.
I won't let you go before
my wedding.
Who else do I have to call my own?
No elder person.
Won't you tie the sehra
for your sister?
Won't you be at my side?
If you think of me as
your sister
...you must fulfill your
duty to me.
After what you have
done for me
I'm willing to fulfill
your every wish.
Thank you very much.
Aunt, offer him a sweetmeat.
Come with me.
Mulla, you can start
the rites.
We are starting the
wedding rites.
To marry you to Mirza
Anwar Hussain...
...a bride price of Rs.5000OI-,
has been paid.
Are you willing?
Say "yes", child.
We start the wedding rites...
...to marry you to Mirza Asghar
Hussain's daughter Husna.
Are you willing?
See how surprised Anwar is to
see I'm not the bride.
He thought he's sold his love.
And I had bought it.
Who'll explain to him?
Love is worship.
Love is to be felt.
Not bought. Not sold.
Are you willing?
The groom is a little bewildered.
Will my word do?
Shut up.
Sorry, father-in-law.
Are you willing?
"I caught but a glimpse
of you once"
"I long to meet you again"
"Your shadow is
a Taj Mahal to me"
"Let me woo you on
a starlit night"
"Let your fragrant curls