Who came into my room?
- Your room was Iocked, sir
Do you see what state it is in?
- Like someone has combed this pIace
I'II caII the manager.
- Wait
Have you seen anyone prowIing around?
- No sir
Oh yes, a whiIe ago, I saw someone
smoking a cigar outside your room
Go on
Looks Iike the poIice has got wind
about Rupa's suicide because of me
Accepted that the poIice know,
and they searched your room for cIues
Even if the poIice have the evidence,
what can they do to you?
I know, the poIice can't make a case
against me. But what do I teII Sunita?
For some reason, she's convinced that
her sister committed suicide because...
Rocky defIowered her and ditched her.
She hates the very name, Rocky!
If she couId, she wouId kiII him!
Someone was eavesdropping.
I'II see you tomorrow
Is your dance over.
- Not yet
What are you doing here?
- Just trying to figure out...
how high the third storey is.
- I didn't get it
You can't
Have mercy on her IittIe sister
I hope she doesn't have to...
jump off the third fIoor, into
the waiting arms of mother earth!
PIease Iisten to me.
- You're going to Iisten to us!
Brother!
- My foot!
Sister! Make your brother see reason!
- Sister? Maybe she's yours!
Go now
I want to see your Daddy.
- Why?
To taIk about the wedding and aII that.
- I've toId him
What?
- Everything
Everything?
- AIso the fact that...
you're Prince Mahender Singh's nephew.
He asked me to invite...
you and your uncIe to dinner tonight.
You'II bring him aIong, won't you?
UncIe...?
- Yes. He has to discuss everything
Bridegrooms don't do the taIking.
- But I...
Don't refuse. I've promised Daddy
Someone is coming. Go now. Bring your
uncIe aIong. I'II expect you tonight
I see
I can understand
So what do you want?
- PIease teII Sunita and her father...
the truth about me.
- That you aren't my nephew
That you're Rocky, the drummer?
- Not onIy that. AIso...
the whoIe story about Rupa and me.
- Rupa? Who's Rupa?
You remember the girI who
committed suicide Iast year?
Yes
She was Sunita's eIder sister
But how are you concerned about Rupa?
- Sunita thinks that her sister...
committed suicide because
Rocky seduced her
And what is the truth?
- The truth?
I cIearIy remember the night.
I think the stars were against me
Rupa was casting a shadow on my Iife.
It was just an excuse to meet me
Like any other day,
I was pIaying the drums
And she was dancing with someone eIse.
Right in front of me
I've never seen a drummer Iike you
My name is Rupa
WiII you dance with me?
- You see...
You Iike it here?
- Yes, very much
But where's everyone eIse?
I mean, your famiIy...
the ones you wanted me to meet.
- Oh, them?
You are so naive!
Naive?
- Of course
Eat a biscuit
Are you married?
- What? No!
You get the drift?
Why I caIIed you here?
Yes! Understand!
I have to go to a rehearsaI!
- What's the hurry? Sit!
I have Iots to do!
- Okay, wiII you see me this evening?
Sure!
Hi Ramesh! Weren't you supposed to go
to CaIcutta? How come you're here?
So whatever I heard was true!
- What do you mean?
You're a wanton woman!
- You're getting this wrong. ActuaIIy...
MeddIe, and I'II break your teeth!
Shut up! I know what you are!
You're affianced to me!
And you're in someone eIse's arms,
in pubIic! Not a matter of shame?
You don't know me! I'm not man enough
if I don't strangIe you!
Go, woo him.
- No need!
Upto you. But there's nothing
for you here
Who is it?
Who is this?
- Rupa. I regret what happened tonight
It won't be repeated. I've caIIed off
my engagement to Ramesh
I toId you, I wiII have nothing
to do with you
Don't taIk Iike this, Rocky.
Try to understand me, for once
I'm coming over to see you. Now.
- Not at this time of the night
If you come, I won't open the door.
- I'm madIy in Iove with you, Rocky
I have to see you! Right now!
BeIieve me, if you don't Iet me in...
I'II throw myseIf to my death
from the third fIoor!
Do what you wish!
I won't see you!
Rocky! Open up!
I never imagined she'd kiII herseIf
for reaI! But...
Forget it. You aren't at fauIt
for whatever happened
And you must state this cIearIy.
- No! I can't do it!
BeIieve me, if Sunita gets to know that
I'm Rocky, she's going to be shocked!
So many things in Iife seem impossibIe.
But if man picks up courage...
if he is true, he wins. Don't worry.
Everything wiII turn out fine
This evening I'II come to the hoteI.
Let's go together
Prince Mahender Singh!
- And his nephew, Mr AniI Kumar
God bIess you son
WeIcome
Come son
Be seated.
- Sit down, son
PIease be seated too.
- Sure
Daddy, do you know the Prince?
- Who doesn't know him?
His is one of the Iast gIorious
Iineages from DeIhi
Thanks very much for the euIogies,
Mr Shankar DayaI
So, is he your eIder brother
Prince Bhupender Singh's son?
Yes
The Iooks are simiIar. Same height,
same coIour, same profiIe
Ditto.
- Excuse me...
The matter we have to discuss...
What is there to discuss, son?
I am honoured to host the Prince
No dearth of suitors for Sunita.
But a Iineage as prestigious...
That's for the fortunate onIy.
- You are too kind
Do I consider this aIIiance finaI?
- CertainIy!
And it isn't onIy my choice.
It's Sunita's choice too
Do we take a waIk and taIk things
over? Let them decide the rest
Maybe Iater?
I have something to teII you.
- Go on
You see...
What is it? TeII me
- Not tonight. See me at the hoteI
Tomorrow. The Independence Day party
is going to be a big bash. Come aIone
I'II teII you everything.
- What is the matter?
Something about me.
- I don't want to know anything!
Promise me, you'II come. PIease!
- AII right, I'II come
Let go of my hand.
I have to serve dinner
Mr AniI Kumar, Ms Ruby is refusing
to dance unIess you pIay the drums
It's the primary cIause
in her contract
Do you reaIise what a big programme
we have tonight?
Without you on the drums tonight,
this hoteI's reputation...
wiII take a beating. You can imagine.
After this, if I drag you to court...
you shouIdn't compIain
What a crisis. What is to happen now?
- What eIse? Rocky wiII be exposed
But you've invited Sunita over.
- Yes. Tonight I was supposed to...
teII her everything about myseIf.
But I can't wait tiII then
Therefore?
- I'II write a Ietter...
expIaining everything.
''That's aII there is to the secret''
''This is what I wanted to teII you.
But I thought I'd write about it''
''I shaII await you eagerIy
this evening. If you come...''
''my truthfuIness, my Iove
wiII be rewarded''
''If you don't come,
tonight wiII be my Iast''
''Yours, onIy yours,
AniI''
You know the address, don't you?
- Yes
No one but Sunita must Iay
her hands on this Ietter
''I shaII await you eagerIy
this evening. If you come...''
''my truthfuIness, my Iove
wiII be rewarded''
''If you don't come,
tonight wiII be my Iast''
''Yours, onIy yours,
AniI''
Keep this
There's a bigger reward
in store for you!
Tonight!
Mr AniI Kumar had asked me to deIiver
this Ietter to your residence
It sIipped my mind compIeteIy.
- Never mind
''I shaII await you eagerIy
this evening. If you come...''
''my truthfuIness, my Iove
wiII be rewarded''
''If you don't come...''
Tonight, on Independence Day,
we present the artiste of your choice
Friends, you have aIways cheered me
whenever I have sung here
But tonight, the appIause means more
to me, because for the first time...
I poured my heart out.
And for a moment, I feIt...
as if the earth and the skies
stopped moving...
and a beautifuI fairy stepped down
Iike a ray of Iight...
into my dark, empty, desoIate Iife.
My friends...
this is the pretty angeI whom
I'm getting engaged to
You heId my hand
and you Ied me into Iight
Cheat! ScoundreI! You raped my sister!
You kiIIed her! You're a murderer!
I hate you!
What's going on?
Manager, where's your car?
- Right here. Bring the car over
I'II have the car sent back
FoIIow him
PIease Iet me see Sunita!
If you ever come here, I'II kiII you!
The heat of the moment makes it worse.
Forget it!
Come with me
I'm a poIice detective
I have to taIk to you.
PIease come
Recognise her?
- Yes
Is this why you've been taiIing me aII
these days? You even searched my room
But how am I to bIame if a girI
is insane enough to kiII herseIf...
because she's in Iove with me?
- KiIIed herseIf?
Maybe you don't know. Rupa didn't jump
off the 3rd fIoor. She was thrown down
She didn't commit suicide.
She was kiIIed
KiIIed? But who wouId
kiII her? And why?
You think I kiIIed her? Here's the
entire story about Rupa and myseIf
This feIIow has ruined
the reputation of my hoteI
Mr Manager, why is the poIice here?
- What can I say?
You don't beIieve me?
- At what time did Rupa teIephone you?
EIeven o'cIock.
- She feII down at tweIve
Yes. I have aIways wondered why
she took so Iong to reach the hoteI
On the way, her car ran out of gas
She waIked to the gas station,
bought a can and went back
And then?
- She came to you
And according to you, onIy two peopIe
knew that Rupa wouId come here
One you, and the other Ruby.
She eavesdropped
Yes
Is Ruby in Iove with you?
- Yes
And you?
- OnIy professionaI reIationship
So much for today. See me at
the poIice station. Ten tomorrow
I have something more to ask you
The poIiceman says, Rupa was kiIIed!
- How can that be?
It's true! That night,
I had my doubts
Even afterwards, I saw and I heard
in bits, in pieces and snatches
But I never paid attention. Maybe I
know something that the poIice doesn't
Why didn't you teII the poIice?
- I'II teII them
If not tonight, then tomorrow. Tonight
is a night of decision! Tomorrow...
Even waIIs have ears. Your naivete has
aIready Ianded you in troubIe
You shouId consider every step
you take. It's Iate. Go to sIeep
If you have any probIems, caII me
Take rest, AniI
Boss! When did you arrive?
Where are you putting up?
I'm a guest in someone's house
Do you have whisky?
- Whisky? I even have scotch. Come
It shouId be done tonight.
- WiII be done
How did aII this happen?
What came over Sunita?
You think you're too smart?
You thought you couId go on
doing things on the sIy?
You thought your frauds couId be swept
under the carpet forever?
You thought you couId impIicate me,
and you'd get off as innocent?
There's bIood on your hands.
Not so easy Ruby, not so easy!
Your fraud has been exposed!
Don't you know where you are?
On the 3rd fIoor!
The 3rd fIoor from where
you pushed Rupa to her death!
Death Iurks for you around the corner!
Rocky! Stop! You're insane!
- I am in my senses, Ruby!
That's why I'm hoIding a knife!
Tonight you wiII confess your crime
EIse, this dagger is sharp
and you are soft!
Is death the price to pay for being
heId in your hands?
I've paid my price!
Rocky, I'm not the criminaI
My onIy crime is,
I have Ioved you
What are you staring at?
CaII the poIice
Ruby has been murdered!
You know very weII that it was
someone eIse who kiIIed Ruby
And you aIso accept that the murderer
escaped from the third fIoor...
using the drainpipe.
You aIso have his footprints
Why are you hoIding this poor feIIow?
- You have baiIed him out
He's being reIeased today, now.
But before that, I have to taIk to him
PIease be seated.
- No, I shouId be Ieaving
I have urgent business in DeIhi.
AniI, I see you in a coupIe of days
Everything wiII be aII right.
- Thank you very much, Prince
Had the Prince not baiIed you out,
I wouId've kept you in custody...
tiII the verdict.
- Because you suspect me?
No. Because your Iife
is in danger
Your enemies are waiting
for you. Out there
If you go out, he'II attack you again.
This time, he might not miss his mark
Remember. He didn't come to kiII Ruby.
He wants to siIence you forever
Because, he is the man who kiIIed Rupa.
And he's afraid that you suspect him
But I suspected Ruby!
It was a man who committed both
the murders. Not a woman
I'II show you a cIue in Rupa's murder.
You speak of this to no one...
if you vaIue your Iife
Rupa had this button in her hand,
ripped out of the kiIIer's jacket
This singIe button is worth
some 2000 or 2500
The jacket must have five
such pieces
OnIy a very rich man
couId use such a jacket
An on that night, he wore this jacket.
His button's were aIso worthIess.
The man who threatened to kiII Rupa!
Who eIse wouId want me dead?
Whom are you taIking about?
He was Rupa's fiance.
Now he wants to marry her sister!
At the time of the kiIIing Iast year,
he was in staying in the hoteI!
want to kiII Rupa? She was innocent!
- But she didn't commit suicide
She was kiIIed
At this time Iast year, where were
you? I mean, around the time...
when Ms Rupa was kiIIed.
- I was in CaIcutta
You're forgetting. You were in
Mussoorie, at the same hoteI...
where Ms Rupa was murdered.
- This is wrong! I wasn't here!
Even if he was here, what's your
contention? My son kiIIed Rupa?
Did I say that?
I'm onIy investigating
Why have I been brought here?
- Do you know this man?
HeIIo!
I know him very weII. Last year,
he stayed at my hoteI. Remember?
I don't remember.
- You don't remember?
We never ever had such a heavy tipper
at our hoteI! StrangeIy...
the biII for his stay of two days
was onIy 200 Rupees
He paid a thousand! I never received
such a huge tip!
When did he check out?
- I remember cIearIy
The morning of the same day on which
the unfortunate Rupa committed suicide
Yes! I was here! No sin for me.
Rupa was my fiancee
I Ieft home on the pretext of going
to CaIcutta. I came here to see her
What I saw here was quite different!
- You saw Rupa dancing with Rocky
You had an aItercation with Rupa,
and you threatened to strangIe her
A man says so many things when he Ioses
his head. But that doesn't mean...
that I reaIIy kiIIed her!
- Maybe you're right
WeII?
Who are you? What do you want?
- Tonight, when you have gone to bed...
the revoIver wiII be aimed at
you again. You wiII be shot
In the morning, you wiII be
discovered dead
You want to nab the man
who kiIIed Rupa and Ruby?
How?
- Come here
That's my car. Here are the keys.
Drive heII for Ieather
Get to the Lucky Restaurant
at the foothiII
You'II find two peopIe
in cabin number three
They are pIotting your murder.
They wiII be there tiII 1 1 o'cIock
OnIy 15 minutes Ieft. Hurry!
What are you doing?
- Come aIong
AniI here. I'm coming over. You must
come with me to the Lucky Restaurant
I'II teII you when I see you.
In five minutes
I'm taking your car. TiII I get back,
here is where you stay
If whatever you said turns
out to be faIse...
I'II turn you over to the poIice.
Then it's between you and the poIice
I think it's the his enemy at work.
I think the brakes were tampered with
Even if he's aIive, there's no news.
We haven't found AniI's corpse either
The search is on.
But I have IittIe hope
But I am hopefuI. He's aIive!
God forbid, if he's dead...
his body wouId've been found
with the wreck
That part of the forest is infested
with wiId animaIs. As you know...
animaIs carry their prey miIes away
So you're certain that
AniI can't be aIive?
Had he been aIive, wouId he have gone
into hiding? He isn't a criminaI
You're right. But my heart teIIs me...
- How I wish AniI was aIive
How I wish I couId nab
the man who murdered him
But circumstances say that AniI
is dead. I have no hopes
Ms Sunita was here
to inquire about AniI
She heard my part of the conversation.
She just broke down
She was very much in Iove with AniI.
God give her courage
''I am sure my death wiII come
as a shock to you''
''But now that AniI is gone,
Iife is such a burden for me''
''I can't bear this burden anymore.
Forgive me if you can''
''Your unfortunate daughter, Sunita''
AniI, I had given up hope for you!
But God heard my prayers!
You're aIive! I'm so Iucky!
Forgive me, this once!
Where's Ramesh?
- He isn't at home
He goes to Park HoteI every evening.
He returns drunk, past midnight
CeIebrating my death! In her company!
- Who's this?
The one who gave me the car sans brakes.
- Ramesh done?
Find out Ramesh's room number,
and get back here, fast!
Thank God, you're aIive!
I was so worried!
Where have you been?
- Who Iives in that cottage?
My estate manager.
He's a drunkard
Anyone eIse Iives there?
- No, no one eIse
Take a Iook. Two shadows
on the window
The girI just came here.
- GirI? Who?
The one who set up the car sans brakes.
I foIIowed her from the hoteI!
Did she go into my house?
- I didn't quite make out in the dark
The car came in through these gates,
and went out through that gate
I think she has found out
that you're taiIing her
She took a Ioop through my compound
to throw you off her taiI
We shouId get back to the hoteI!
- Naivete has Ianded you in this soup
Your enemies must've got wind that
you're aIive. Who know when...
the next attempt wiII be made
on your Iife! and here you are...
But I must do something!
- Not a word! I'm not Ietting you go...
anywhere in the middIe of the night!
- But Prince...
Come with me!
Come in
This room has been Iocked up for years.
Spend the night here
I'II have the pIace cIeaned up tomorrow.
You stay with me tiII...
this whoIe thing has bIown over.
- But we must find her!
It has to be done tonight!
- Everything wiII be done tonight
Don't you worry a bit.
Leave it to me
But...
- No buts. Just change and go to sIeep
I wiII give you my nightsuit.
Use a nightsuit that fits you.
- Where are you going?
To the poIice station.
- I'm coming with you
Not at aII. Don't argue.
Just change and go to bed
I'II see you tomorrow morning
Don't you try to get out.
I'm Iocking the door from outside
What happened?
- Escaped! Out of the window
Escaped?
- Yes. Either he's out Iooking for you
Or eIse, he suspects me. In any case,
he has gone to the poIice
But he must be waIking; he won't
get there before an hour
I'II get him on the way!
Wait here. I'II be back
No, I'II go back to the hoteI.
- Are you trying to escape?
No! If I'm caught here,
everything wiII be exposed
And you'II hang. With me
But you don't want to die with me.
-I'm a heIpIess widow with two chiIdren
What wiII happen to them?
- Now you remember your chiIdren?
You didn't remember them when you were
squandering my money? For 3 years!
Who compeIIed me to do this? You!
For whom are my hands tainted? You!
You can't get away so easiIy, Sabina!
You're my equaI partner in crime!
And I'm not going to the gaIIows
aIone, you're coming with me!
Stop! Or, I'II stab you!
Stop!
- Shut up!
You're so fragiIe, and this knife
is so sharp! One stroke...
and your head couId
roII off your shouIders!
Wait!
- I swear by Rupa and Ruby!
I'II carve you up in IittIe pieces!
- But...
You have onIy one way to Iive on.
The Prince wiII be back soon
Before he gets here, you'II teII me
aII about everything!
I'II teII you everything!
Don't kiII me!
I'm caIIed from the Prince's mansion.
Yes, I'm aIive
As of now, the assassin's accompIice
is with me. Listen to the story...
of how Rupa and Ruby were kiIIed
Speak!
I haven't kiIIed anyone!
I was forced to become an accessory
to murder to save my Iife!
My misfortunes began three years ago.
I was widowed with two chiIdren...
when I met the Prince in DeIhi.
The affair went too far
I came to Mussoorie on his say-so,
and I put up at Park HoteI
What happened Iast year,
was what I feared the most!
The Prince's wife caught us. She was
carrying a gun. She wanted to kiII me
In the scuffIe with the Prince...
the gun went off
His wife was dead! He decided
to bury the body in the forest
He wore his estate manager's cIothes
and we set out in his jeep
Rocky! Open up!
His wife's death was an accident.
To hide the incident...
he had to siIence Rupa.
But the matter didn't end there
He suspected that Mr AniI Kumar
wouId uncover the truth
So he tried to shoot AniI Kumar.
But accidentaIIy...
AniI, you can't escape!
You might have come to know my secret.
But the price for this is death
I'm not going to spare you.
If I couId kiII the woman I Ioved...
I'II kiII you too
A singIe buIIet in the head
is better than bIeeding to death
If I were to have died at your hands,
you wouId've been successfuI by now
I can tear you to pieces!
But I don't want revenge
You better surrender to the poIice
I can be very crueI.
And you're heIpIess
We'II see who's heIpIess!
You were right, AniI. You aren't
destined to die at my hands
Take my hand, and cIimb up.
Surrender to the poIice
The Iaw might spare your Iife.
- And Iive on? For whose sake?
I have no one. Let me go
Death is my onIy way out
Forgive me, if you can.
Now Iet me go. I have to go